<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2025-05-16T11:11:59.285Z</id>
    <title>AngJianming RSS Feed</title>
    <updated>2025-05-16T11:11:59.285Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[90% of institutions ‘taking action’ on stablecoins: Fireblocks survey]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/traditional-banks-stablecoins-cross-border-fireblocks</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/traditional-banks-stablecoins-cross-border-fireblocks?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-16T11:05:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new report from enterprise-grade digital assets platform Fireblocks shows that 90% of institutional players are either using or exploring the use of stablecoins in their operations.
The report, published May 15, surveyed 295 executives across traditional banks, financial institutions, fintech companies and payment gateways. Nearly half of respondents (49%) said they already use stablecoins in payments, while 23% are conducting pilot tests, and another 18% are in the planning phase.’
Only 10% of institutions surveyed said they are undecided about stablecoin adoption.  
“The stablecoin race has become a matter of avoiding obsolescence as customer demand accelerates and use cases mature,” Fireblocks wrote in the report. 
Current stablecoin adoption among institutional respondents. Source: F…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Ezra Reguerra</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[👋 Just Passing By...]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/onedev/just-passing-by-2nl1</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/onedev/just-passing-by-2nl1"/>
        <updated>2025-05-16T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[👋 Just Passing By...
👉 Check it out here
Thanks for the support — and see you there! 🎥💻]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>OneDev</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Strings, Arrays & Hash Tables — Let’s Talk About the One You’re Probably Not Using Enough]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/onedev/strings-arrays-hash-tables-lets-talk-about-the-one-youre-probably-not-using-enough-2ebn</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/onedev/strings-arrays-hash-tables-lets-talk-about-the-one-youre-probably-not-using-enough-2ebn"/>
        <updated>2025-05-16T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you’ve been coding for a bit, chances are you're already comfortable working with strings and arrays.
So let’s skip the warm-up and jump straight into the one structure that quietly powers a ton of efficient solutions but often doesn’t get the spotlight it deserves:
Hash Tables are data structures that store key-value pairs, and they give you constant-time lookups on average — O(1) time complexity for accessing, inserting, and deleting items.
Hash Tables are your go-to when you need to:
Count things (like frequencies of characters or items)
Track what you’ve seen (e.g., duplicates)
Map one thing to another (like IDs to objects)
They're elegant, fast, and can simplify problems that otherwise require nested loops.
Imagine a real-world dictionary:
You want to look up the word “banana”
You …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>OneDev</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gemini 2.5 vs OpenAI o3: Which is Better]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/_37bbf0c253c0b3edec531e/gemini-25-vs-openai-o3-which-is-better-8fg</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/_37bbf0c253c0b3edec531e/gemini-25-vs-openai-o3-which-is-better-8fg"/>
        <updated>2025-05-16T10:59:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google’s Gemini 2.5 and OpenAI’s o3 represent the cutting edge of generative AI, each pushing the boundaries of reasoning, multimodal understanding, and developer tooling. Gemini 2.5, introduced in early May 2025, debuts state‑of‑the‑art reasoning, an expanded context window of up to 1 million tokens, and native support for text, images, audio, video, and code — all wrapped in Google’s AI Studio and Vertex AI platforms. OpenAI’s o3, released April 16, 2025, builds on its “o‑series” by internally chaining thought steps to tackle complex STEM tasks, scoring top marks on benchmarks such as GPQA and SWE‑Bench, while adding web browsing, image reasoning, and full tool access (e.g., code execution, file interpretation) for ChatGPT Plus and Pro users. Both platforms offer robust APIs and integrat…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>安萨</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Midjourney: Turn Your Sketches into Amazing Images]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/_37bbf0c253c0b3edec531e/midjourney-turn-your-sketches-into-amazing-images-24od</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/_37bbf0c253c0b3edec531e/midjourney-turn-your-sketches-into-amazing-images-24od"/>
        <updated>2025-05-16T10:57:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Here’s a comprehensive guide on how to elevate your rough sketches into polished artworks using Midjourney’s cutting‑edge AI tools. We’ll cover everything from the platform’s latest capabilities to best practices for preparing your input sketches, refining prompts, leveraging new editing features, and iterating towards gallery‑ready outputs. Along the way, you’ll discover practical tips—backed by the freshest updates from Midjourney’s V7 release and community insights—to help you transform simple lines into stunning masterpieces.
Midjourney is an independent research lab and AI art platform founded to explore novel modes of human creativity through generative models ([midjourney.com][1]). Launched in open beta on July 12, 2022, it operates predominantly via Discord, allowing artists to iss…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>安萨</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[✨ Bringing Children's Stories to Life with the Amazon Nova Family of Models]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/damogallagher/bringing-childrens-stories-to-life-with-the-amazon-nova-family-of-models-597m</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/damogallagher/bringing-childrens-stories-to-life-with-the-amazon-nova-family-of-models-597m"/>
        <updated>2025-05-16T10:56:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[🎉 A Nova for Every Need – My AI Engineering Month Submission



To test the launch of the Amazon Nova model family, I created a magical storytelling application that generates fully immersive kids’ stories—powered entirely by using Nova models and Amazon Bedrock.
As a parent of young children, I wanted to build something both fun and meaningful. An interactive story creator that could bring joy to kids while showcasing the capabilities of Amazon’s latest AI models. Nova models were the perfect choice as they contained everything I needed. For images, video, text - this could all be handled by Nova.
Imagine a child saying: “Tell me a story about a rainbow dinosaur and a flying cookie.”

The app responds with:

✅ A custom-written story

✅ Colorful images

✅ Narrated audio based on the story…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Damien Gallagher</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How does OpenAI Detect AI-generated images?]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/_37bbf0c253c0b3edec531e/how-does-openai-detect-ai-generated-images-4kab</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/_37bbf0c253c0b3edec531e/how-does-openai-detect-ai-generated-images-4kab"/>
        <updated>2025-05-16T10:56:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Artificial intelligence–generated images are reshaping creative industries, journalism, and digital communication. As these tools become more accessible, ensuring the authenticity of visual content has emerged as a paramount concern. OpenAI, a leader in AI research and deployment, has pioneered multiple strategies to detect and label images produced by its generative models. This article examines the mechanisms OpenAI employs to identify AI-generated images, drawing on the latest developments in watermarking, metadata standards, content provenance, and emerging detection research.
The proliferation of AI image generators poses risks ranging from the spread of misinformation and deepfakes to unauthorized mimicry of artists’ work. Detecting AI-generated imagery helps news organizations verif…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>安萨</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Klein Vision’s AirCar Prepares For Takeoff In 2026]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=351946</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/351946/klein-visions-aircar-prepares-for-takeoff-in-2026/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-16T10:49:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A flying car is a dream for many people, and it seems like Slovakian-based Klein Vision, is making that dream come true with the world’s first certified flying car: the AirCar. The four-wheel vehicle with wings is expected to go on sale early next year, with a starting price of US$800,000 (~RM3,419,200). Last week, the final […]
The post Klein Vision’s AirCar Prepares For Takeoff In 2026 appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Keran</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Asynchronous builders in Flutter: Analyzing FutureBuilder and StreamBuilder]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/vlopess/asynchronous-builders-in-flutter-analyzing-futurebuilder-and-streambuilder-2hko</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/vlopess/asynchronous-builders-in-flutter-analyzing-futurebuilder-and-streambuilder-2hko"/>
        <updated>2025-05-16T10:49:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I just published an article on how to use FutureBuilder and StreamBuilder in Flutter to simplify asynchronous operations. These builders eliminate repetitive code and make your UI more responsive, without complications.
If you're tired of managing setState manually or dealing with nested callbacks, it's worth checking out.
🔗 Read here: https://medium.com/@Victorldev/asynchronous-builders-in-flutter-analyzing-futurebuilder-and-streambuilder-d3f8af3af88a]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Victor Lopes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing BlazeJob: A TypeScript Task Scheduler for Node.js 🚀]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/novathemachine/introducing-blazejob-a-typescript-task-scheduler-for-nodejs-3ok8</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/novathemachine/introducing-blazejob-a-typescript-task-scheduler-for-nodejs-3ok8"/>
        <updated>2025-05-16T10:48:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I’m excited to announce the release of BlazeJob, a lightweight and flexible task scheduler for Node.js and TypeScript!
Key features:
Schedule custom async JS/TS functions
HTTP connector (GET/POST)
Cosmos blockchain connector (send tokens, query balances)
CLI for automation
SQLite persistence
BlazeJob is open source and ready for your automation workflows.

Check it out, give it a ⭐, and share your feedback!
👉 Npm]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gérald Quenum</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Beginner-Friendly HTML Courses You Can Take for Free in 2025]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/srdan_borovi_584c6b1d773/beginner-friendly-html-courses-you-can-take-for-free-in-2025-1i10</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/srdan_borovi_584c6b1d773/beginner-friendly-html-courses-you-can-take-for-free-in-2025-1i10"/>
        <updated>2025-05-16T10:44:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HTML serves as the backbone of the web, providing structure to every website you visit. For aspiring web developers, it's the perfect entry point into the coding world - straightforward to learn, yet powerful enough to build the foundation for incredible web experiences.
The good news? You don't need to spend a fortune to learn HTML in 2025. Plenty of high-quality, free resources exist that can take you from complete novice to competent HTML coder. This guide explores the best free HTML courses available this year, highlighting interactive learning experiences that will have you creating web pages in no time.
Before diving into the courses, let's quickly address why HTML remains worth learning:
Foundational web skill. Every web developer needs to understand HTML
Quick to learn. Basic HTML …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Srdan Borović</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[No-Code Game Development: Using AI to Build Your First Game]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/srdan_borovi_584c6b1d773/no-code-game-development-using-ai-to-build-your-first-game-1k17</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/srdan_borovi_584c6b1d773/no-code-game-development-using-ai-to-build-your-first-game-1k17"/>
        <updated>2025-05-16T10:44:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Remember when making video games required years of programming experience and technical know-how? Those days are fading fast. The game development landscape has transformed dramatically with AI-powered no-code tools that put creative power in everyone's hands.
Whether you're a teacher looking to engage students, an entrepreneur with a game idea, or simply curious about game creation, AI-assisted no-code platforms offer a pathway that wasn't possible even a few years ago.
Game development traditionally stood as a fortress guarded by coding languages and technical barriers. Breaking in required either specialized education or thousands of hours of self-teaching. This limited who could participate in creating games.
Today's AI-powered no-code tools have changed the equation entirely. They're …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Srdan Borović</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Best No-Code Android App Builders to Launch Your Mobile App in 2025]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/srdan_borovi_584c6b1d773/the-best-no-code-android-app-builders-to-launch-your-mobile-app-in-2025-42hl</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/srdan_borovi_584c6b1d773/the-best-no-code-android-app-builders-to-launch-your-mobile-app-in-2025-42hl"/>
        <updated>2025-05-16T10:44:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The mobile app market continues to explode, with billions of downloads yearly and no signs of slowing down. Yet many entrepreneurs, small business owners, and creators with brilliant app ideas lack the technical skills to bring their visions to life. Enter no-code Android app builders, platforms that democratize app development by removing coding barriers.
These powerful tools have revolutionized how we create mobile apps, making it possible for anyone to launch a professional Android application without writing a single line of code. Let's explore the top no-code Android app builders in 2025 that can help you transform your idea into a market-ready mobile app.
The surge in no-code platforms stems from a simple reality: traditional app development is expensive, time-consuming, and technica…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Srdan Borović</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use AI to Build Your Own Web App]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/srdan_borovi_584c6b1d773/how-to-use-ai-to-build-your-own-web-app-6ak</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/srdan_borovi_584c6b1d773/how-to-use-ai-to-build-your-own-web-app-6ak"/>
        <updated>2025-05-16T10:43:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Remember when building a web app required months of coding, a team of developers, and a hefty budget? Those days are quickly becoming ancient history. Thanks to AI-powered tools, anyone can now create functional, professional web applications without writing a single line of code. Whether you're an entrepreneur with a brilliant idea, a marketer needing a custom landing page, or a small business owner wanting to digitize your operations, AI web app builders have transformed what's possible.
In this guide, we'll explore how you can leverage artificial intelligence to bring your web app idea to life, even if you've never coded before.
The landscape of web development has dramatically shifted in recent years. Advanced AI now powers tools that can understand your intentions, generate code, and …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Srdan Borović</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[After months of coding with LLMs, I'm going back to using my brain]]></title>
        <id>https://albertofortin.com/writing/coding-with-ai</id>
        <link href="https://albertofortin.com/writing/coding-with-ai"/>
        <updated>2025-05-16T10:29:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Central banks testing smart contract toolkit under BIS Project Pine]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/central-banks-smart-contract-tokenization-pilot-bis</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/central-banks-smart-contract-tokenization-pilot-bis?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-16T10:15:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Central banks are experimenting with smart contracts to implement monetary policy in tokenized environments, signaling a growing interest in integrating blockchain technology into traditional finance (TradFi).
According to a joint research study by the Federal Reserve Bank of New York’s Innovation Center and the Bank for International Settlements (BIS) Innovation Hub Swiss Centre, smart contracts could offer central banks flexible, rapid-response tools in a tokenized financial system.
The study, dubbed Project Pine, tested a prototype “generic customizable monetary policy tokenized toolkit” for further research by central banks, according to a BIS report published May 15.
“The smart contract toolkit was fast and flexible,” the BIS wrote. “In hypothetical scenarios, the central bank was abl…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Zoltan Vardai</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Apple Blocks Fortnite's Return to iOS App Store, Epic Claims]]></title>
        <id>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/16/apple-blocks-fortnite-return-to-ios-app-store/</id>
        <link href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/16/apple-blocks-fortnite-return-to-ios-app-store/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-16T10:08:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Stellar Blade Gets PC Port On 11 June; Comes With Denuvo DRM]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=351909</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/351909/stellar-blade-pc-port-11-june-denuvo-drm/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-16T10:00:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Slightly over a year after its initial PS5 release, Stellar Blade will be making its way to PC. Shift Up announced, via the official PlayStation Blog, that there will also be additional content for the game when the PC version of th game launches, which those on PS5 will also be getting as an update. […]
The post Stellar Blade Gets PC Port On 11 June; Comes With Denuvo DRM appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ian Chee</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Leeks and Leaks – Daniel.haxx.se]]></title>
        <id>https://daniel.haxx.se/blog/2025/05/16/leeks-and-leaks/</id>
        <link href="https://daniel.haxx.se/blog/2025/05/16/leeks-and-leaks/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-16T09:42:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The first year of free-threaded Python]]></title>
        <id>https://labs.quansight.org/blog/free-threaded-one-year-recap</id>
        <link href="https://labs.quansight.org/blog/free-threaded-one-year-recap"/>
        <updated>2025-05-16T09:42:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Beyond Text: On-Demand UI Generation for Better Conversational Experiences]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.fka.dev/blog/2025-05-16-beyond-text-only-ai-on-demand-ui-generation-for-better-conversational-experiences/</id>
        <link href="https://blog.fka.dev/blog/2025-05-16-beyond-text-only-ai-on-demand-ui-generation-for-better-conversational-experiences/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-16T09:23:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Here is why Bitcoin price is stuck below $105K]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/here-is-why-bitcoin-price-is-stuck-below-105-k</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/here-is-why-bitcoin-price-is-stuck-below-105-k?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-16T09:09:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Key takeaways:

Bitcoin price consolidates as resistance at $105,000 prevents a rally to new all-time highs.

Traders are slightly bearish, but historical data suggests a sudden bullish move should not be ruled out.


Bitcoin (BTC) price has been consolidating within a roughly $3,500 range over the past seven days as the $105,000 level remains the overhead resistance to break.
BTC/USD weekly chart. Cointelegraph/TradingView
Bitcoin unable to crack $105,000
Data from Cointelegraph Markets Pro and Bitstamp shows that BTC’s price has been oscillating between its resistance level at $105,000 and $101,500, where it has found support.
“$BTC is stuck in a narrowing $101.5K–$104K range,” said Swissblock in a May 16 post on X. 
The onchain data provider said that Bitcoin began consolidating after t…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Nancy Lubale</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Access to experimental medical treatments is expanding across the US]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1116526</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/05/16/1116526/access-to-experimental-medical-treatments-expanding-us/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-16T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A couple of weeks ago I was in Washington, DC, for a gathering of scientists, policymakers, and longevity enthusiasts. They had come together to discuss ways to speed along the development of drugs and other treatments that might extend the human lifespan. One approach that came up was to simply make experimental drugs more easily…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jessica Hamzelou</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Prasarana Aims To Expand Electric Bus Fleet To Improve Public Transport Services]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=351953</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/351953/prasarana-aims-to-expand-electric-bus-fleet-to-improve-public-transport-services/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-16T08:50:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Prasarana Malaysia Bhd is set to significantly expand its fleet of electric buses as part of a broader effort to improve public transportation services and increase its share of daily commuters, according to president and group chief executive Mohd Azharuddin Mat Sah. The announcement comes in response to recent remarks by Deputy Prime Minister Datuk […]
The post Prasarana Aims To Expand Electric Bus Fleet To Improve Public Transport Services appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Heirul Kamel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Animoca’s Yat Siu says student loans can supercharge DeFi growth]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/defi-student-loans-onchain-education-wave</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/defi-student-loans-onchain-education-wave?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-16T08:42:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bringing student loans onchain would increase the total value locked (TVL) in decentralized finance (DeFi) by more than four times, supercharging the industry, according to Yat Siu, chairman of Animoca Brands.
Speaking at Consensus 2025 in Toronto, Siu pointed to the $3 trillion global student loan market as an untapped opportunity for the crypto industry. He said moving even 10% of that market onchain could significantly boost DeFi’s growth.
“You basically more than quadruple TVL in all of DeFi,” he said, underscoring how the industry is still in its early stages. 
Consensus chairman Michael Lau (left) with Animoca Brands chairman Yat Siu (right) at the Consensus mainstage in Toronto, Canada. Source: Cointelegraph
Web3-based education tools to drive crypto adoption
Siu said that Web3-base…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Ezra Reguerra</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Is XRP price going to crash again?]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/is-xrp-price-going-to-crash-again</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/is-xrp-price-going-to-crash-again?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-16T08:41:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Key takeaways:

XRP is retesting a falling wedge breakout, which could lead to a rally toward $3.60.

Whale wallets are in the red, and history shows this isn’t bullish for XRP price.

A breakdown below $1.11 could trigger an inverse cup-and-handle pattern, targeting a sharp drop to $0.50.

XRP (XRP) has rebounded by more than 50% in the last five weeks to reach $2.42 on May 16. But the price remains 30% below its January 2025 peak of $3.40, raising concerns of a bull trap.
Will XRP’s price sustain the recovery or drop further in the coming days? Let’s examine.
Falling wedge retest hints at sharp XRP rally 
XRP is completing a textbook retest of its falling wedge breakout, according to chartist CW. 
Often, after the breakout, the price comes back down to “retest” the wedge’s upper trendlin…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Yashu Gola</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Samsung Opens Up Preorders For Its 2025 Samsung AI TVs]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=351930</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/351930/samsung-opens-up-preorders-for-its-2025-samsung-ai-tvs/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-16T08:25:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Samsung has opened up the preorder list for its latest 2025 AI TV lineup. Announced last week, the new TVs are powered by the brand’s Vision AI technology. The preorder period started in 13 May and will continue until 1 June this year. In order to entice customer and as an extra added bonus, Samsung […]
The post Samsung Opens Up Preorders For Its 2025 Samsung AI TVs appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John Law</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin hitting $220K ‘reasonable’ in 2025, says gold-based forecast]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-hitting-220k-reasonable-in-2025-gold-based-forecast</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-hitting-220k-reasonable-in-2025-gold-based-forecast?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-16T07:56:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Key points: 

New Bitcoin price targets leverage interplay with gold to deliver $200,000 and higher this year.

Bitcoin price cycles remain in focus as part of the BTC price “power curve” model.

Eating gold’s market cap could propel BTC/USD to nearly $1 million by the decade’s end.

 
Bitcoin (BTC) has a “decent chance” of hitting $250,000 or more in 2025 as attention turns to gold copycat moves.
In his latest analysis, X analytics account Apsk32 argued that the four-year BTC price cycle should provide unprecedented highs this year.
Bitcoin “power curve” delivers $200,000+ target
Bitcoin following gold to new all-time highs is a popular theory among bulls. Historically, BTC/USD follows XAU/USD higher with a delay of several months.
For Apsk32, the implications are considerable this time a…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by William Suberg</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Bulls Face $120M Challenge in Extending 'Stair-Step' Uptrend]]></title>
        <id>875777fd-5f50-4689-b99e-51d6d344ff14</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/16/bitcoin-bulls-face-usd120m-challenge-in-extending-stair-step-uptrend"/>
        <updated>2025-05-16T07:48:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BTC has chalked out a controlled stair-step price rally from $75,000 to $104,000.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Omkar Godbole</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tether AI: What it is and why it matters for crypto and AI]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/explained/tether-ai-what-it-is-and-why-it-matters-for-crypto-and-ai</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/explained/tether-ai-what-it-is-and-why-it-matters-for-crypto-and-ai?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-16T07:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What is Tether AI?            
            
                
Tether AI is an open-source, decentralized artificial intelligence (AI) platform launched by Tether, the company behind the Tether USDt (USDT) stablecoin. Unlike traditional AI services that depend on centralized servers and require application programming interface (API) keys, Tether AI runs on a distributed peer-to-peer (P2P) network, offering enhanced privacy, autonomy and resilience. 
Designed to be modular and composable, Tether AI can operate on any hardware, whether mobile, desktop or edge devices, without centralized control or a single point of failure. 
A core innovation of Tether AI is its integration with cryptocurrency infrastructure. It natively supports Bitcoin (BTC) and USDt payments using Tether’s Wallet Developm…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Dilip Kumar Patairya</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Xpeng Reveals Second-Gen P7 Sedan Coupe EV]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=351924</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/351924/xpeng-reveals-second-gen-p7-sedan-coupe-ev/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-16T07:19:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Xpeng has recently revealed its next-generation P7. This sedan coupé EV is set to replace the company’s current flagship, the P7i. The official images were released by the model’s lead exterior designer, Rafik Ferrag, on his social media platforms. At first glance, people might notice some shades of design from the Polestar 5, especially with […]
The post Xpeng Reveals Second-Gen P7 Sedan Coupe EV appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Keran</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DOJ Charges 12 With $263M Crypto Theft Linked to Genesis Creditor]]></title>
        <id>24429206-3446-4811-9613-026699836e05</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2025/05/16/doj-charges-12-with-263m-crypto-theft-linked-to-genesis-creditor"/>
        <updated>2025-05-16T07:02:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Most of the individuals were arrested this week in California.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Parikshit Mishra</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Wasmer (YC S19) Is Hiring a Rust Compiler Engineer]]></title>
        <id>https://www.workatastartup.com/jobs/15822</id>
        <link href="https://www.workatastartup.com/jobs/15822"/>
        <updated>2025-05-16T07:00:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[iQOO Neo 10 To Debut In Malaysia Soon]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=351911</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/351911/iqoo-neo-10-debut-malaysia-soon/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-16T06:30:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Back in November, iQOO launched the iQOO Neo 10 series, a lineup of mid-range smartphones. At the time, the phones were only released in China, but now the company has confirmed that it is releasing the Neo 10 to the Malaysian market. The model we are getting differs slightly from the Neo 10 released in […]
The post iQOO Neo 10 To Debut In Malaysia Soon appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nurul Kamil</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BuyMeACoffee silently dropped support for many countries (2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://zverok.space/blog/2024-08-08-bmac-snafu.html</id>
        <link href="https://zverok.space/blog/2024-08-08-bmac-snafu.html"/>
        <updated>2025-05-16T06:23:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FTX to Pay Over $5B to Creditors as Bankrupt Estate Gears Up for Distribution]]></title>
        <id>3eeaa32e-6f08-49d7-8633-3ec951f9deab</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/16/ftx-to-pay-over-usd5b-to-creditors-as-bankrupt-exchange-gears-up-for-distribution"/>
        <updated>2025-05-16T06:20:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Payouts of up to 120% begin May 30 for thousands of creditors, just as U.S. regulators warm to crypto and the industry stages a comeback.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shaurya Malwa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Xiaomi To Launch Its Own Smartphone Chip Called The XRING 01]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=351873</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/351873/xiaomi-launch-own-smartphone-chip-xring-01/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-16T06:14:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Xiaomi has announced that it is making its own smartphone chip, called the XRING 01. The chip has apparently been in the works for more than ten years, and is set to launch later this month, although no specific date was given. The company’s co-founder and CEO Lei Jun personally made the announcement on his […]
The post Xiaomi To Launch Its Own Smartphone Chip Called The XRING 01 appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nurul Kamil</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto gaming interest drops in April, overall ecosystem healthier: DappRadar]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/blockchain-gaming-interest-dropped-april-overall-ecosystem-healthier</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/blockchain-gaming-interest-dropped-april-overall-ecosystem-healthier?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-16T05:59:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Blockchain gaming user activity dipped and funding slowed in April, but the overall ecosystem is healthier and maturing, according to blockchain analytics platform DappRadar.
User activity dropped 10% over April, with blockchain gaming reaching a 2025 low of 4.8 million daily Unique Active Wallets, DappRadar analyst Sara Gherghelas said in the platform’s April Games Report.
Gaming dominance over the decentralized app industry also fell and is now tied with decentralized finance at 21%. 
Gherghelas said it’s clear user attention is shifting away from gaming, but under the surface, new infrastructure went live, major publishers doubled down, and high-quality games edged closer to launch.
Source: DappRadar
“The blockchain gaming industry isn’t dead — it’s evolving. It’s moving from noise to s…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Stephen Katte</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Starknet hits ‘Stage 1’ decentralization, tops ZK-rollups for value locked]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/starknet-stage-1-decentralization-top-zk-rollup-tvl</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/starknet-stage-1-decentralization-top-zk-rollup-tvl?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-16T05:53:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum layer-2 scaling platform Starknet has reached a decentralization milestone laid out by Ethereum co-founder Vitalik Buterin and is now the largest zero-knowledge rollup-based network by total value locked.
Starknet said in a press release shared with Cointelegraph that it has hit “Stage 1” decentralization, according to a framework Buterin laid out in 2022, which means the network operates with limited oversight or “training wheels.”
Starknet added that the framework was the “gold standard onchain tool for analyzing Ethereum scaling solutions,” and said it achieved the milestone through changes such as creating a security council and censorship-avoidance mechanisms. 
While the system still allows intervention from a security council, it has implemented a fully functional validity p…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Martin Young</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Doom The Dark Ages Review: Going Medieval On Demon Butt]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=350771</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/350771/doom-the-dark-ages-review/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-16T05:40:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Five years after Doom Eternal, id Software and Bethesda have finally launched Doom The Dark Ages. Instead of a sequel (for reasons that are explored in the Ancient Gods DLC for Eternal), the entry serves as a prequel, exploring the history of the Slayer on the world of Argent D’Nur, his engagement with The Night […]
The post Doom The Dark Ages Review: Going Medieval On Demon Butt appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John Law</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Stablecoin bill passes in Northern Marianas as House overrides veto]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/northern-marianas-house-overrides-veto-passes-stablecoin-bill</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/northern-marianas-house-overrides-veto-passes-stablecoin-bill?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-16T05:18:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Pacific US territory of the Northern Mariana Islands has passed a bill allowing its small constituent island of Tinian to launch a stablecoin, overriding an earlier veto by the territory’s governor.
The 20-member Northern Mariana Islands House voted 14-2 to undo Governor Arnold Palacios’ April 11 veto of the bill, which allows the Tinian local government to issue licenses to internet casinos and includes a provision for the Tinian treasurer to issue, manage and redeem a “Tinian Stable Token.” 
The territory’s nine-member Senate had revived the bill on May 9, voting 7-1 in a two-thirds majority to override the veto, which then needed a two-thirds majority in the House to pass.
Representative Marissa Flores (top left) had urged for “thoughtful deliberation” on the internet gaming and sta…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Jesse Coghlan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[realme 14T Lands In Malaysia At RM999]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=351889</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/351889/realme-14t-price/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-16T05:05:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[realme has finally announced the arrival of the 14T in Malaysia, which it states is the final addition to the 14 series.  The fourth member of the 14 family, it is technically the second cheapest model, but it is actually the most affordable option when compared to the 14x with the same 8GB+256GB configuration. The […]
The post realme 14T Lands In Malaysia At RM999 appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ikmal Rozlan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Apple CarPlay Ultra Starts Rollout; Starting With Aston Martin Only]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=351869</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/351869/apple-carplay-ultra-rollout-starting-aston-martin-only/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-16T05:00:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CarPlay is normally the bridge between a modern vehicle and an iPhone, and Apple has rolled out what it calls the “latest next-generation infotainment system”. It’s simply called CarPlay Ultra which has begun its gradual rollout, with the US and Canada being the first countries to get it. Limiting access even further though is that, […]
The post Apple CarPlay Ultra Starts Rollout; Starting With Aston Martin Only appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ian Chee</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[XRP Slides 4% as Bitcoin Traders Cautious of $105K Price Resistance]]></title>
        <id>febf0f3f-b820-4e03-8fe8-fce323fd17ce</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/16/xrp-slides-4-as-bitcoin-traders-cautious-of-105k-price-resistance"/>
        <updated>2025-05-16T04:47:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Market sentiment remains positive, but signs of exhaustion appear as BTC nears key technical and psychological levels.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shaurya Malwa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto’s lack of ‘frothy use case’ a good sign: WisdomTree exec]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/crypto-lacks-frothy-use-case-good-sign-wisdomtree</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/crypto-lacks-frothy-use-case-good-sign-wisdomtree?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-16T04:47:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jason Guthrie, head of product at asset manager WisdomTree, says he’s optimistic despite a noticeable lack of hype that typically comes along with a crypto bull run. 
There hasn't been a “really frothy use case that has typically driven these market cycles previously,” such as initial coin offerings (ICOs), non-fungible tokens (NFTs), or DeFi lending, Guthrie told Cointelegraph at Consensus. 
“This time, we’ve continued to see the asset class gathering value, we’ve continued to see the companies that are built on this technology, growing revenue, growing client bases, continuing to innovate without really hanging their hat on one of these frankly less than useful use cases,” he said.
WisdomTree founder Jonathan Steinberg (left), Jason Guthrie, head of product (middle) and head of digital a…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Stephen Katte</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DOJ charges 12 more gamer-turned $263M Bitcoin robbers]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/12-more-charged-263-million-crypto-theft-ring</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/12-more-charged-263-million-crypto-theft-ring?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-16T04:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Another 12 people have been charged for their involvement in a $263 million crypto crime spree that stole 4,100 Bitcoin from a Genesis creditor last August, along with a string of break-ins and money laundering. 
The 12 new names, included in a superseding indictment, add to charges originally brought against the main defendant in the case, Malone Lam, on Sept. 19, 2024, the Department of Justice noted in a May 15 statement.
Jeandiel Serrano was named a defendant in the initial indictment but was not included in the superseding one. 
The DOJ said several defendants have been arrested, while two others are believed to be living in Dubai.
Many of the suspects, with aliases like “Goth Ferrrari” and “The Accountant,” come from California, mostly aged between 18 and 22. 
The group allegedly beg…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Brayden Lindrea</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Grok &#039;white genocide&#039; rant due to unauthorized prompt change: xAI]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/grok-white-genocide-rant-caused-by-unauthorized-prompt-changes-says-xai</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/grok-white-genocide-rant-caused-by-unauthorized-prompt-changes-says-xai?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-16T04:25:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Elon Musk’s artificial intelligence firm xAI has blamed an “unauthorized modification” to the Grok chatbot’s response, causing it to generate responses mentioning political and racial tensions in South Africa. 
On May 16, xAI provided an update on the Grok AI chatbot’s inflammatory responses, stating that on May 14, “an unauthorized modification was made to the Grok response bot’s prompt on X.”
“This change, which directed Grok to provide a specific response on a political topic, violated xAI’s internal policies and core values,” it added.
The firm stated that it had conducted a thorough investigation and is implementing measures to enhance the AI chatbot’s transparency and reliability.
Grok generated responses on May 14, mentioning a “white genocide” conspiracy theory in South Africa when…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Martin Young</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase drops 7% on customer breach, SEC probe into user numbers]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/coinbase-drops-7-on-staff-breach-sec-probe-into-user-numbers</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/coinbase-drops-7-on-staff-breach-sec-probe-into-user-numbers?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-16T04:12:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase stock dipped after news broke of a cyberattack that exposed customer data and an ongoing Securities and Exchange Commission investigation over misstated user numbers in 2021.
The double whammy of bad news rattled investors as company stock (COIN) slid 7% in a fall to $244 in after-hours trading on May 15, according to Google Finance.  
Coinbase stock 24 hours. Source: Google Finance 
Coinbase has since confirmed the report from The New York Times, which stated the SEC has been investigating whether Coinbase misstated its user numbers in past disclosures, an inquiry that began during the Biden administration and has continued under the Trump administration.
“This is a hold-over investigation from the prior administration about a metric we stopped reporting two and a half years ago,…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Martin Young</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Awful German Language (1880)]]></title>
        <id>https://faculty.georgetown.edu/jod/texts/twain.german.html</id>
        <link href="https://faculty.georgetown.edu/jod/texts/twain.german.html"/>
        <updated>2025-05-16T04:09:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elon Musk’s xAI tries to explain Grok’s South African race relations freakout the other day]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3007876</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/elon-musks-xai-tries-to-explain-groks-south-african-race-relations-freakout-the-other-day/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-16T02:47:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With its prompts now public and a team of human babysitters on call, Grok is supposedly back on script. But the incident underscores...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carl Franzen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cracked - method chaining/CSS-style selector web audio library]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/billorcutt/i_dropped_my_phone_the_screen_cracked</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/billorcutt/i_dropped_my_phone_the_screen_cracked"/>
        <updated>2025-05-16T02:46:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brazil fintech gets approval to become a Bitcoin treasury company]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/meliuz-becomes-brazils-first-bitcoin-treasury-company-after-shareholder-approval</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/meliuz-becomes-brazils-first-bitcoin-treasury-company-after-shareholder-approval?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-16T02:22:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Méliuz’s executive chairman says his fintech firm has become Brazil’s first publicly-traded Bitcoin treasury company following shareholder approval, with the firm also announcing it bought $28.4 million worth of Bitcoin to add to its existing stack.
“Historic day! Our shareholders have approved, by a wide majority, the transformation of Méliuz into the first Bitcoin Treasury Company listed in Brazil,” Israel Salmen posted to X on May 15.
Salmen said the firm snapped up 274.52 Bitcoin (BTC) for an average purchase price of $103,604, achieving a BTC yield of 600%. 
Méliuz now holds 320.3 Bitcoin, worth a little over $33 million, with the latest purchase adding to the Brazilian fintech firm’s first purchase of 45.73 Bitcoin on March 6.
Details of Méliuz’s latest Bitcoin purchase. Source: Isra…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Brayden Lindrea</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AI scammers are now impersonating US government bigwigs, says FBI]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/us-officials-targeted-deepfake-phishing-attacks-fbi</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/us-officials-targeted-deepfake-phishing-attacks-fbi?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-16T02:03:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Deepfake-assisted hackers are now targeting US federal and state officials by masquerading as senior US officials in the latest brazen phishing campaign to steal sensitive data. 
The bad actors have been operating since April, using deepfake voice messages and text messages to masquerade as senior government officials and establish rapport with victims, the FBI said in a May 15 warning. 
“If you receive a message claiming to be from a senior US official, do not assume it is authentic,” the agency said.  
If US officials’ accounts are compromised, the scam could become far worse because hackers can then “target other government officials, or their associates and contacts, by using the trusted contact information they obtain,” the FBI said. 
As part of these scams, the FBI says the hackers a…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Stephen Katte</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ollama's new engine for multimodal models]]></title>
        <id>https://ollama.com/blog/multimodal-models</id>
        <link href="https://ollama.com/blog/multimodal-models"/>
        <updated>2025-05-16T01:43:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tornado Cash dev Roman Storm trial goes ahead with slight trim]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/tornado-cash-roman-storm-trial-goes-ahead-drop-one-count</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/tornado-cash-roman-storm-trial-goes-ahead-drop-one-count?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-16T01:15:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[US federal prosecutors are pressing ahead with their case against Tornado Cash founder Roman Storm, but will drop a small part of their indictment after the Department of Justice rolled back its crypto enforcement last month.
Jay Clayton, the acting US Attorney for Manhattan, told federal court judge Katherine Polk Failla in a May 15 letter that the charges against Storm still stand, bar one part of a conspiracy to operate an unlicensed money transmitting business charge.
“After review of this case, this Office and the Office of the Deputy Attorney General have determined that this prosecution is consistent with the letter and spirit of the April 7, 2025 Memorandum from the Deputy Attorney General,” Clayton wrote.
Deputy Attorney General Todd Blanche’s April memo said the Justice Departmen…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Jesse Coghlan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Teal – A statically-typed dialect of Lua]]></title>
        <id>https://teal-language.org/</id>
        <link href="https://teal-language.org/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-16T00:40:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Software engineering-native AI models have arrived: What Windsurf’s SWE-1 means for technical decision-makers]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3007851</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/software-engineering-native-ai-models-have-arrived-what-windsurfs-swe-1-means-for-technical-decision-makers/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-16T00:30:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Windsurf's new SWE-1 AI models tackle the complete software engineering workflow, potentially reducing development cycles and technical debt.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sean Michael Kerner</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NASA keeps ancient Voyager 1 spacecraft alive with Hail Mary thruster fix]]></title>
        <id>https://www.theregister.com/2025/05/15/voyager_1_survives_with_thruster_fix/</id>
        <link href="https://www.theregister.com/2025/05/15/voyager_1_survives_with_thruster_fix/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-16T00:29:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Wisconsin Investment Board sold off its Bitcoin ETF stash]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/wisconsin-investment-board-sold-entire-blackrock-bitcoin-etf-stash</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/wisconsin-investment-board-sold-entire-blackrock-bitcoin-etf-stash?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-15T23:58:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The State of Wisconsin Investment Board (SWIB), which oversees the state’s retirement funds, unloaded its shares in BlackRock’s iShares Bitcoin Trust ETF (IBIT) during the first quarter, filings show.
The Wisconsin Investment Board reported no spot Bitcoin ETF positions in its 13F filing to the US Securities and Exchange Commission on May 15, liquidating all 6,060,351 IBIT shares it reported holding from the previous quarter. 
The more than 6 million IBIT shares are worth around $355.6 million at current prices.
SWIB was one of the first state investment funds to provide Bitcoin exposure to US retirees when it bought $164 million worth of Bitcoin ETFs in Q1 2024 — the same quarter the Bitcoin products launched.
Source: Julian Fahrer
The mass sell-off comes only a quarter after SWIB reporte…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Brayden Lindrea</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DOJ Will Still Pursue Roman Storm Case Despite Blanche Memo, Prosecutors Say]]></title>
        <id>dded795a-fe9d-4b63-abfc-ead803ed4276</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2025/05/15/doj-will-still-pursue-roman-storm-case-despite-blanche-memo-prosecutors-say"/>
        <updated>2025-05-15T23:52:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Department of Justice said it had reviewed the memo by Todd Blanche with his office.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nikhilesh De</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is Sui: A Comprehensive Guide to Web3 Scalability]]></title>
        <id>6823533984101f00013a5ca4</id>
        <link href="https://blog.quicknode.com/what-is-sui-a-comprehensive-guide-to-web3-scalability/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-15T23:34:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Explore how Sui Network achieves 300,000 TPS through parallel processing, and its applications in gaming, DeFi, and supply chain management.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>QuickNode</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AI Meets Blockchain: Transforming Technology for the Next Era]]></title>
        <id>682354c584101f00013a5cb9</id>
        <link href="https://blog.quicknode.com/ai-and-blockchain-transforming-technology-together/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-15T23:34:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discover how AI and blockchain integration enhances security, efficiency, and innovation in healthcare, supply chains, and financial services.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>QuickNode</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Reduce model integration costs while scaling AI: LangChain’s open ecosystem delivers where closed vendors can’t]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3007838</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/reduce-model-integration-costs-while-scaling-ai-langchains-open-ecosystem-delivers-where-closed-vendors-cant/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-15T23:16:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Through the LangGraph Platform, organizations can deploy agents with one-click deployment, horizontal scaling to handle “bursty, long-running traffic."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Emilia David</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The $1 Billion database bet: What Databricks’ Neon acquisition means for your AI strategy]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3007813</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/data-infrastructure/the-1-billion-database-bet-what-databricks-neon-acquisition-means-for-your-ai-strategy/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-15T22:54:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Databricks' $1 billion acquisition of Neon highlights how serverless PostgreSQL has become essential for agentic AI development.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sean Michael Kerner</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Legacy forex, payments platforms ‘hate’ stablecoin adoption — Kevin O’Leary]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/legacy-forex-payments-platforms-hate-stablecoin-adoption-kevin-o-leary</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/legacy-forex-payments-platforms-hate-stablecoin-adoption-kevin-o-leary?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-15T22:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Global foreign exchange and payments platforms are lobbying hard against stablecoins, which stand to significantly disrupt their business models, investor Kevin O’Leary said during a keynote address at Consensus 2025. 
Legacy forex and payments platforms often extract large fees for servicing cross-border cash transfers and stand to lose out on revenue if regulated stablecoins become accepted as a cheaper, faster alternative, O’Leary said at the Toronto conference. 
“Currency trading is a multi-trillion dollar market — and it’s old and ugly and inefficient,” O’Leary said, adding that “[ t]he biggest threat to that monopoly or oligopoly is a regulated stablecoin.” 
“Once that’s approved, the multi-trillion dollar FX market becomes efficient, transparent, and inexpensive,” he said. 
Kevin O’…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Alex O’Donnell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trump’s crypto ties ‘add a certain level of challenge’ to passing bills — Coinbase exec]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/donald-trump-crypto-challenge-passing-legislation-paul-grewal</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/donald-trump-crypto-challenge-passing-legislation-paul-grewal?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-15T22:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase chief legal officer Paul Grewal addressed some of the concerns raised by US lawmakers and industry leaders around President Donald Trump’s crypto ventures, and how they may affect related legislation.
Speaking at the Consensus conference in Toronto on May 15, Grewal said there had been “hiccups” in Congress since the Senate Banking Committee voted to advance the Guiding and Establishing National Innovation for US Stablecoins, or GENIUS Act, in March. 
Though Grewal said there were disputes over “substantial issues that need to be addressed” in the bill, he hinted that Trump’s involvement in the industry was a “complicating factor.” 
“The discussion around the president's support for a certain memecoin or two and other efforts does add a certain level of challenge to the effort to …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Turner Wright</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Here’s what happened in crypto today]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/what-happened-in-crypto-today</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/what-happened-in-crypto-today?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-15T21:58:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today in crypto, the US Department of Justice added another 12 people to their list of defendants suspected of being involved in a major US crypto racketeering ring. Coinbase reportedly refused to pay a $20 million ransom after insiders leaked user data in a phishing scheme, and the company has since fired the group of contracted customer support agents allegedly involved in the attacks. 
DOJ charges 12 more gamer-turned $263M Bitcoin robbers
Another 12 people have been charged for their involvement in a $263 million crypto crime spree that stole 4,100 Bitcoin from a Genesis creditor last August, along with a string of break-ins and money laundering. 
The 12 new names, included in a superseding indictment, add to charges originally brought against the main defendant in the case, Malone Lam…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Cointelegraph</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A leap year check in three instructions]]></title>
        <id>https://hueffner.de/falk/blog/a-leap-year-check-in-three-instructions.html</id>
        <link href="https://hueffner.de/falk/blog/a-leap-year-check-in-three-instructions.html"/>
        <updated>2025-05-15T21:57:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[From OAuth bottleneck to AI acceleration: How CIAM solutions are removing the top integration barrier in enterprise AI agent deployment]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3007718</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/from-oauth-bottleneck-to-ai-acceleration-how-ciam-solutions-are-removing-the-top-integration-barrier-in-enterprise-ai-agent-deployment/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-15T21:43:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New CIAM platforms are addressing a significant barrier to enterprise AI adoption: identity management for autonomous agents.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Chen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dave Portnoy Says Meme Coins Are 'Gambling' and Not Built to Last]]></title>
        <id>063d56e3-b643-410a-964d-ca73e9a5a6de</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/consensus-toronto-2025-coverage/2025/05/15/dave-portnoy-says-meme-coins-are-gambling-and-not-built-to-last"/>
        <updated>2025-05-15T21:39:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Barstool founder opened up about the risks and rush of meme coins at a fireside chat with Bullish CEO Tom Farley.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Helene Braun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘The world is trying to hoard Bitcoin right now’ — Eric Trump]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/everybody-in-the-world-is-trying-to-hoard-bitcoin-right-now-eric-trump</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/everybody-in-the-world-is-trying-to-hoard-bitcoin-right-now-eric-trump?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-15T21:30:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There is an ongoing race across the world for Bitcoin accumulation, according to Eric Trump, the second-eldest son of US President Donald Trump. Speaking at a crypto conference in Toronto on May 15, Trump said that from families to government funds, “everybody in the world is trying to hoard Bitcoin right now.” 
The remarks came during a panel at Consensus 2025. Sharing the stage with Asher Genoot, the CEO of Bitcoin (BTC) mining company Hut 8, Trump said Bitcoin adoption has been incredible.
“I'm traveling. I'm on a plane. Everybody in the world is trying to hoard Bitcoin right now. Everybody. I hear it from sovereign wealth funds. I hear it from the wealthiest families. I hear from the biggest companies.”
Asher Genoot and Eric Trump at Consensus 2025. Source: Cointelegraph
Trump describe…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Christopher Tepedino</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Initialization in C++ is bonkers (2017)]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.tartanllama.xyz/initialization-is-bonkers/</id>
        <link href="https://blog.tartanllama.xyz/initialization-is-bonkers/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-15T21:27:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Holds Above $100K, Altcoins Slide as Analyst Sees Crypto Rally Into Summer]]></title>
        <id>4bb241b3-26c5-4efe-a9b0-d0c26fe1c244</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/15/bitcoin-holds-above-usd100k-altcoins-slide-as-analyst-sees-crypto-rally-into-summer"/>
        <updated>2025-05-15T21:13:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After testing the $100,000 level early Thursday, bitcoin reversed to above $103,000.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Krisztian Sandor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin traders’ evolving view of BTC’s role in every portfolio bolsters $100K support]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-traders-evolving-view-of-btc-s-role-in-every-portfolio-bolsters-100-k-support</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-traders-evolving-view-of-btc-s-role-in-every-portfolio-bolsters-100-k-support?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-15T21:02:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Key takeaway:

Bitcoin’s struggles to overtake the $105,000 level as US macroeconomic headwinds remain a challenge.  

Steady inflows from institutional investors and the strength of the $100,000 support point to growing confidence in Bitcoin.

Bitcoin (BTC) has struggled to break above $105,000 since May 10, leading traders to question whether the bullish momentum has faded. Although BTC managed to reclaim the $104,000 level, demand for leveraged long positions has dropped sharply, as indicated by the decline in the Bitcoin futures premium.
 
Bitcoin 2-month futures annualized premium. Source: laevitas.ch
On May 14, the annualized Bitcoin futures premium peaked at 7%, but then fell to 5%, which is near the neutral-to-bearish threshold and matches the level seen four weeks ago when BTC tra…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Marcel Pechman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Asset tokenization expected to speed capital flows, says Chainlink&#039;s Nazarov]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/chainlink-jp-morgan-kinexys-ondo-partner-rwa-payment-rails</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/chainlink-jp-morgan-kinexys-ondo-partner-rwa-payment-rails?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-15T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Asset tokenization is set to accelerate the movement of capital across traditional markets, according to Chainlink co-founder Sergey Nazarov. Speaking with Cointelegraph at Consensus 2025 in Toronto, Nazarov said the shift will boost capital velocity in asset classes such as treasuries, equities, private credit, commercial debt, and real estate.
"I think that there are two sides to this equation. One is the asset, and the other one is the payment. So, you need more high-quality assets onchain, but you also need more frictionless payments that existing institutions can use easily," Nazarov said on May 14. 
The remarks came on the same day Chainlink announced a partnership with Kinexys, a blockchain network for institutional-grade tokenized assets by JP Morgan, and digital asset firm Ondo Fi…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Vince Quill</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitdeer Q1 revenue falls more than 40% year-over-year]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitdeer-q1-revenue-down-40-year-over-year</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitdeer-q1-revenue-down-40-year-over-year?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-15T20:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitdeer Technologies Group reported a 41% year-over-year drop in revenue to $70.1 million for the first quarter of 2025, the Bitcoin miner said on May 15. 
The Singaporean company clocked an operating loss of $3.2 million for the quarter, down from a $34.1 million profit during the same period last year, its earnings release said. 
However, Bitdeer reported a Q1 net income of more than $400 million, largely driven by gains on convertible notes and warrants issued to stablecoin issuer Tether in 2024.
Bitdeer’s revenue declines come as miners increasingly expand beyond Bitcoin (BTC) mining and pivot toward supplying high-performance computing (HPC) for artificial intelligence applications. 
“As we scale self-mining and execute on our ASIC [mining hardware] roadmap, we are also advancing plan…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Alex O’Donnell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FTX estate to start distributing more than $5B on May 30]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/ftx-second-distribution-starting</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/ftx-second-distribution-starting?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-15T20:24:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[More than two-and-a-half years after filing for bankruptcy, cryptocurrency exchange FTX is moving forward with repaying users who have not had access to their funds.
In a May 15 notice, the FTX Recovery Trust announced that it would begin disbursing funds to the second group of parties eligible under the exchange’s reorganization plan. Starting on May 30, FTX will send more than $5 billion to creditors “within 1 to 3 business days” through crypto firms BitGo and Kraken. 
In accordance with the reorganization plan, FTX said five groups of “convenience classes” would receive between 54% and 120% distribution of assets. The repayment schedule for the next class of creditors will be “announced in due course,” and the debtors were expected to pay up to $16 billion if all claims were filed.
Brea…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Turner Wright</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Stablecoin regulation next ‘catalyst’ for crypto industry — Aptos head]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/stablecoin-regulation-next-catalyst-for-crypto-industry-aptos-head</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/stablecoin-regulation-next-catalyst-for-crypto-industry-aptos-head?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-15T20:05:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Stablecoin regulation is “the next catalyst” for the crypto industry and could lead to unprecedented “appetite from institutional investors,” according to Ash Pampati, head of ecosystem at the Aptos Foundation.
In an interview with Cointelegraph at Consensus 2025 in Toronto, Pampati said that “the whole world outside of the United States […] has already jumped onto this [stablecoins],” adding that “the US is [...] at the doorstep.” 
“I really think about new use cases that can emerge because of the borderless nature of stablecoins, because of the efficiency of the dollar onchain,” he said. “If you're trying to send money to your friend in Nigeria, why do you have to go through a bunch of hoops?”
Stablecoins are often used to transfer money across borders, as they are easier and cheaper to …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Christopher Tepedino</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tek – A music making program for 24-bit Unicode terminals]]></title>
        <id>https://codeberg.org/unspeaker/tek</id>
        <link href="https://codeberg.org/unspeaker/tek"/>
        <updated>2025-05-15T19:56:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PayPal Crypto Head Says Banks Are Needed to Unlock Full Stablecoin Potential]]></title>
        <id>66c80209-dfa1-4c99-9e3a-f8da6e90fdf4</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/consensus-toronto-2025-coverage/2025/05/15/paypal-crypto-head-says-banks-are-needed-to-unlock-full-stablecoin-potential"/>
        <updated>2025-05-15T19:38:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At Consensus 2025, leaders from PayPal and MoneyGram pointed to regulation, real-world utility and trust as keys to stablecoin growth.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Krisztian Sandor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘Really Great Example’: Coinbase Praised for Hack Response Amid $400M Crisis]]></title>
        <id>24c43608-f1fd-4939-9bf6-5d1d88eaf162</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/consensus-toronto-2025-coverage/2025/05/15/really-great-example-coinbase-praised-for-hack-response-amid-usd400m-crisis"/>
        <updated>2025-05-15T19:37:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At a panel at Consensus 2025, TRM Labs' Ari Redbord discussed Coinbase’s response to their recent hack]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Margaux Nijkerk</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The unreasonable effectiveness of an LLM agent loop with tool use]]></title>
        <id>https://sketch.dev/blog/agent-loop</id>
        <link href="https://sketch.dev/blog/agent-loop"/>
        <updated>2025-05-15T19:33:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Solana network activity surge and ‘megaphone’ chart pattern set $210 SOL price target]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/solana-network-activity-surge-and-megaphone-chart-pattern-set-210-sol-price-target</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/solana-network-activity-surge-and-megaphone-chart-pattern-set-210-sol-price-target?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-15T19:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Key Takeaways:

Solana formed a megaphone chart pattern with a potential $210 price target. 

Solana’s ecosystem growth highlights renewed investor interest with a $4 billion realized cap increase and 731 million transactions.

Solana (SOL) price tested its key resistance at $180 earlier this week, but the altcoin failed to establish a position above the level. Over the past few days, SOL has consolidated above the $170 mark, but prices have dropped 5.65% since May 14.
Including the recent minor dip, Solana has formed a megaphone pattern on the 4-hour chart, a classic technical setup indicating increasing volatility. 
Solana 4-hour chart. Source: Cointelegraph/TradingView
The chart illustrates that the megaphone’s upper resistance trendline sits near $185, aligning with immediate resistanc…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Biraajmaan Tamuly</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The current state of TLA⁺ development]]></title>
        <id>https://ahelwer.ca/post/2025-05-15-tla-dev-status/</id>
        <link href="https://ahelwer.ca/post/2025-05-15-tla-dev-status/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-15T18:53:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Senate's New Stablecoin Draft Doesn't Target Trump's Crypto, Tweaks Big-Tech Approach]]></title>
        <id>42c7cc9c-ee6f-4958-a5e5-414c0997d683</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2025/05/15/senate-s-new-stablecoin-draft-doesn-t-target-trump-s-crypto-tweaks-big-tech-approach"/>
        <updated>2025-05-15T18:52:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A legislative draft obtained by CoinDesk shows a marginally revised version despite Democrats citing "major victories" in the Senate negotiation.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jesse Hamilton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Windsurf SWE-1: Our First Frontier Models]]></title>
        <id>https://windsurf.com/blog/windsurf-wave-9-swe-1</id>
        <link href="https://windsurf.com/blog/windsurf-wave-9-swe-1"/>
        <updated>2025-05-15T18:47:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Is Bitcoin price going to crash again?]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/is-bitcoin-price-going-to-crash-again</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/is-bitcoin-price-going-to-crash-again?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-15T18:13:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Key takeaways:

Bitcoin's 36% rebound from $74,500 runs into resistance at $106,000.

Bid-side liquidity is staking up on the downside near $93,000.

Bitcoin (BTC) price has rebounded by 36% from its April 9, five-month low at $74,500. However, its failure to decisively break above $106,000 has sparked concerns about whether a sharp correction is possible in the coming days.
BTC/USD daily price chart. Source: Cointelegraph/TradingView
Over 97% of Bitcoin’s holders are now in profit
Bitcoin’s recent break above $105,000 saw its price rise above the short-term holder realized price as this cohort of traders flipped some of their unrealized losses into profit. 
Data from CryptoQuant reveals that less than 2.8% of Bitcoin investors were still in a position of loss when the price hovered around…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Nancy Lubale</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SEC Is Probing Coinbase Over User Number Misstatement Concern]]></title>
        <id>6c08c502-08f1-4e28-946d-3dbb700237e5</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2025/05/15/sec-is-probing-coinbase-over-user-number-misstatement-concern"/>
        <updated>2025-05-15T18:09:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The investigation began under former SEC Chair Gary Gensler and has continued under the current administration, according to the NYT, which first reported the story.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cheyenne Ligon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Baby is healed with first personalized gene-editing treatment]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nytimes.com/2025/05/15/health/gene-editing-personalized-rare-disorders.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.nytimes.com/2025/05/15/health/gene-editing-personalized-rare-disorders.html"/>
        <updated>2025-05-15T18:06:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Eric Trump Says He Got Into Crypto Amid Political Attack, Calls Bitcoin 'Digital Gold']]></title>
        <id>0a65e816-9215-470e-ad40-f651113483af</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/consensus-toronto-2025-coverage/2025/05/15/eric-trump-says-he-got-into-crypto-amid-political-attack-calls-bitcoin-digital-gold"/>
        <updated>2025-05-15T17:44:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[He became interested in cryptocurrency when politics connected the Trump family with the crypto community.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nikhilesh De</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Litecoin’s ETF Hopes Rise Even as Price Retreats From $101 Peak]]></title>
        <id>d32567ac-8f51-40b7-a8b1-b242a9f5f4fb</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/15/litecoin-slides-6-from-highs-amid-etf-uncertainty-and-global-headwinds"/>
        <updated>2025-05-15T17:26:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Heightened volatility sends LTC tumbling from recent highs as traders eye key support levels]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>AI Boost</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum Meant To Be Alternative, Not Rival to Bitcoin: ETH Co-Founder Anthony Di Iorio]]></title>
        <id>2002ab0c-b47f-459e-b771-10d7f8828f39</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/consensus-toronto-2025-coverage/2025/05/15/ethereum-meant-to-be-alternative-not-rival-to-bitcoin-eth-co-founder-anthony-di-iorio"/>
        <updated>2025-05-15T17:17:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At Consensus 2025, Ethereum co-founder Anthony Di Iorio reflects on the blockchain’s early days.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Margaux Nijkerk</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This baby boy was treated with the first personalized gene-editing drug]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1116524</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/05/15/1116524/this-baby-boy-was-treated-with-the-first-personalized-gene-editing-drug/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-15T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Doctors say they constructed a bespoke gene-editing treatment in less than seven months and used it to treat a baby with a deadly metabolic condition. The rapid-fire attempt to rewrite the child’s DNA marks the first time gene editing has been tailored to treat a single individual, according to a report published in the New…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Antonio Regalado</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Canada lags with stablecoin approach, but there’s room to catch up]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/canada-lags-stablecoin-approach-room-to-catch-up</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/canada-lags-stablecoin-approach-room-to-catch-up?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-15T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The slow adoption of stablecoins in Canada has some local crypto industry observers concerned that the country is falling behind.
The Canadian Securities Administrators (CSA) classified stablecoins as “securities and/or derivatives” in December 2022 after the FTX debacle that shook markets and turned many lawmakers against the crypto industry.
Regulating stablecoins as a security has seen few local stablecoin issuers arise, but in the United States and the European Union, softening regulations have seen significant growth in the stablecoin market. This makes Canada, observers say, less competitive with other jurisdictions. 
Of particular concern is the perceived gap in peer-to-peer (P2P) payments in Canada, which stablecoins are uniquely qualified to fill. 
Stablecoins globally have grown …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Aaron Wood</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kevin O’Leary: 'I Want More Regulation, And I Want It Now']]></title>
        <id>656ad052-c60f-40f9-8d75-da534c2e93f7</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/consensus-toronto-2025-coverage/2025/05/15/kevin-oleary-i-want-more-regulation-and-i-want-it-now"/>
        <updated>2025-05-15T16:34:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[O’Leary predicted that a market structure bill will open the floodgates for institutional investors into crypto: “ ... a trillion dollars will come in ...”]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cheyenne Ligon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Launch HN: Tinfoil (YC X25): Verifiable Privacy for Cloud AI]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=43996555</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=43996555"/>
        <updated>2025-05-15T16:19:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Arm is rebranding its system-on-a-chip product designs to showcase power savings for AI workloads, targeting a surprising sector]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3007796</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/arm-is-rebranding-its-system-on-a-chip-product-designs-to-showcase-power-savings-for-ai-workloads-targeting-a-surprising-sector/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-15T16:17:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For engineers orchestrating AI pipelines across environments, the modularity and performance tiering within Arm’s new architecture...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carl Franzen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Exchange CEO's Daughter, Grandson Targeted in Paris Kidnap Attempt]]></title>
        <id>6504e8b4-bed7-45b6-adcc-4c22b8f1c723</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2025/05/15/crypto-exchange-ceos-daughter-grandson-targeted-in-paris-kidnap-attempt"/>
        <updated>2025-05-15T16:10:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[French Interior Minister Bruno Retailleau said he will meet with French crypto entrepreneurs to discuss how to protect them.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Camomile Shumba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Uniswap (UNI) Falls 6% as Institutions Offload $82M, Still Up 20% in a Month]]></title>
        <id>5b573efd-3300-4706-a05e-f55ed65f178d</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/15/uniswap-uni-falls-6-as-institutions-offload-usd82m-still-up-20-in-a-month"/>
        <updated>2025-05-15T16:00:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Massive exchange deposits signal bearish sentiment as Uniswap's native token breaks critical support levels amid heightened market volatility.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>AI Boost</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[U.S. Senate's Stablecoin Push Still Alive as Bill May Return to Floor: Sources]]></title>
        <id>aefc37fb-d682-4c8a-8627-0b100128b7f7</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2025/05/15/u-s-senate-s-stablecoin-push-still-alive-as-bill-may-return-to-floor-sources"/>
        <updated>2025-05-15T15:41:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The legislation to regulate stablecoin issuers hit a big bump a week ago, but negotiations continued and the latest version may move again.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nikhilesh De</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Smokey The Bera to Make Berachain More Resilient to Crypto Volatility]]></title>
        <id>201f509e-1323-47a6-a723-a0d2a2d5f67b</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/consensus-toronto-2025-coverage/2025/05/15/smokey-the-bera-to-make-berachain-more-resilient-to-crypto-volatility"/>
        <updated>2025-05-15T15:36:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Market reflexivity is a big problem in DeFi.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tim Craig</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[0x Acquires Competitor Flood in Push to Boost Share of $2.3B DEX Aggregator Market]]></title>
        <id>6448bb1f-b222-4336-8806-d1fed49411d0</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2025/05/15/0x-acquires-competitor-flood-in-push-to-boost-share-of-usd2-3b-defi-aggregator-market"/>
        <updated>2025-05-15T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The acquisition is 0x’s first since the firm’s founding in 2017.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tim Craig</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto for Advisors: Stablecoins Explained]]></title>
        <id>f9ee2937-887a-4708-addf-8f3c05dc053d</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/coindesk-indices/2025/05/14/crypto-for-advisors-stablecoins-explained"/>
        <updated>2025-05-15T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Stablecoins — a tokenized representation of money on-chain that’s taking over traditional financial rails and underpinning crypto trades.  Read about where they started and where they are going.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Harvey Li</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Shiba Inu (SHIB) Price Drops 7% in 24 Hours but Remains Up 25% Over the Past Month]]></title>
        <id>04dfd4dc-ae42-4986-9523-5e8926328eec</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/15/shiba-inu-shib-price-drops-7-in-24-hours-but-remains-up-25-over-the-last-month"/>
        <updated>2025-05-15T14:58:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Meme token faces significant downward pressure amid shifting economic conditions despite positive developments in US-China trade relations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>AI Boost</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase Canada CEO Urges Mark Carney Government to Move Fast on National Crypto Strategy]]></title>
        <id>a43749d8-6d18-4af0-83b7-da75b142dd0d</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/consensus-toronto-2025-coverage/2025/05/15/coinbase-canada-ceo-urges-mark-carney-s-government-to-move-fast-on-national-crypto-strategy"/>
        <updated>2025-05-15T14:27:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Lucas Matheson said Canada risks falling behind as other nations actively shape crypto policies.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Aoyon Ashraf</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Movement Labs Secretly Promised Advisers Millions in Tokens, Leaked Documents Show]]></title>
        <id>b672f2bf-904b-4556-9768-7f24241822f8</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/tech/2025/05/15/movement-labs-secretly-promised-advisers-millions-in-tokens-leaked-documents-show"/>
        <updated>2025-05-15T14:24:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Signed memos reveal that Movement Labs, a Trump-backed crypto startup, offered up to 10% of its token supply to shadow advisers through undisclosed agreements.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sam Kessler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin, Strategy Confirm Concurrent Bull Cross, Strengthening Uptrend Signal: Technical Analysis]]></title>
        <id>26d76f3a-ec5d-4d48-b033-ec2f2b0870fe</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/15/bitcoin-strategy-confirm-concurrent-bull-cross-strengthening-uptrend-signal-technical-analysis"/>
        <updated>2025-05-15T14:17:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin and MSTR both flashed a bullish signal, indicating a potential major uptrend.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Omkar Godbole</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Tiny Boltzmann Machine]]></title>
        <id>https://eoinmurray.info/boltzmann-machine</id>
        <link href="https://eoinmurray.info/boltzmann-machine"/>
        <updated>2025-05-15T13:41:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[You.com’s ARI Enterprise crushes OpenAI in head-to-head tests, aims at deep research market]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3007729</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/you-coms-ari-enterprise-crushes-openai-in-head-to-head-tests-aims-at-deep-research-market/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-15T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You.com launches ARI Enterprise, an AI research platform that outperforms OpenAI in 76% of head-to-head tests and integrates with enterprise data sources to transform business intelligence with 400+ source analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Nuñez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Show HN: A free AI risk assessment tool for LLM applications]]></title>
        <id>https://www.gettavo.com/app</id>
        <link href="https://www.gettavo.com/app"/>
        <updated>2025-05-15T12:50:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Download: Montana’s experimental treatments, and Google DeepMind’s new AI agent]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1116516</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/05/15/1116516/the-download-montanas-experimental-treatments-and-google-deepminds-new-ai-agent/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-15T12:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is today’s edition of The Download, our weekday newsletter that provides a daily dose of what’s going on in the world of technology. The first US hub for experimental medical treatments is coming The news: A bill that allows clinics to sell unproven treatments has been passed in Montana. Under the legislation, doctors can apply for…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rhiannon Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Adventure Layer: AI Native Onchain Games, Unleashed]]></title>
        <id>6824c55abf73460001094973</id>
        <link href="https://blog.quicknode.com/adventure-layer-launches-on-quicknode-raas/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-15T12:04:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Adventure Layer launches layer-2 chain leveraging QuickNode's Rollup-as-a-Service (RaaS) product.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>QuickNode</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How US research cuts are threatening crucial climate data]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1116485</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/05/15/1116485/climate-data/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-15T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Over the last few months, and especially the last few weeks, there’s been an explosion of news about proposed budget cuts to science in the US. One trend I’ve noticed: Researchers and civil servants are sounding the alarm that those cuts mean we might lose key data that helps us understand our world and how…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Casey Crownhart</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OpenAI brings GPT-4.1 and 4.1 mini to ChatGPT — what enterprises should know]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3007689</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/openai-brings-gpt-4-1-and-4-1-mini-to-chatgpt-what-enterprises-should-know/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-14T23:46:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As OpenAI continues to evolve its model offerings, GPT-4.1 represents a step forward in democratizing advanced AI for enterprise environments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carl Franzen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Beyond sycophancy: DarkBench exposes six hidden ‘dark patterns’ lurking in today’s top LLMs]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3007681</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/darkness-rising-the-hidden-dangers-of-ai-sycophancy-and-dark-patterns/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-14T23:14:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Without a strong push from AI companies to combat sycophancy and other dark patterns, the default trajectory is more engagement optimization, more manipulation and fewer checks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Leon Yen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How DNS Works: A Guide to Understanding the Internet's Address Book]]></title>
        <id>6824f1ac04a60b4a58654ddc</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-dns-works-the-internets-address-book/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-14T19:40:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Domain Name System (DNS) translates domain names (like example.com) into IP addresses (like 192.0.2.1) so we can easily access websites. In this guide, you’ll learn how DNS resolution starts, its step-by-step process, how caching works, and the r...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dhruv Prajapati</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Load Balancing with Azure Application Gateway and Azure Load Balancer – When to Use Each One]]></title>
        <id>6824f10a7d203c180e5ea4b2</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/load-balancing-with-azure-application-gateway-and-azure-load-balancer/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-14T19:37:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You’ve probably heard someone mention load balancing when talking about cloud apps. Maybe even names like Azure Load Balancer, Azure Application Gateway, or something about Virtual Machines and Scale Sets. 😵‍💫 It all sounds important...but also a l...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Prince Onukwili</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elon Musk’s Grok AI is spamming X users about South African race relations now, for some reason]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3007646</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/elon-musks-grok-ai-is-spamming-x-users-about-south-african-race-relations-now-for-some-reason/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-14T19:08:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Grok was caught earlier this year censoring results critical of President Trump and Musk himself, sowing more doubt of its factual integrity.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carl Franzen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build Slim and Fast Docker Images with Multi-Stage Builds]]></title>
        <id>6824b1638a2b26e9d2d0fe86</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-slim-fast-docker-images-with-multi-stage-builds/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-14T15:06:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Apps don’t stay simple forever. More features mean more dependencies, slower builds, and heavier Docker images. That’s where things start to hurt. Docker helps, but without the right setup, your builds can quickly get bloated. Multi-stage builds make...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniel Adeboye</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google DeepMind’s new AI agent cracks real-world problems better than humans can]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1116438</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/05/14/1116438/google-deepminds-new-ai-uses-large-language-models-to-crack-real-world-problems/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-14T15:00:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google DeepMind has once again used large language models to discover new solutions to long-standing problems in math and computer science. This time the firm has shown that its approach can not only tackle unsolved theoretical puzzles, but improve a range of important real-world processes as well. Google DeepMind’s new tool, called AlphaEvolve, uses the…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Will Douglas Heaven</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meet AlphaEvolve, the Google AI that writes its own code—and just saved millions in computing costs]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3007538</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/meet-alphaevolve-the-google-ai-that-writes-its-own-code-and-just-saved-millions-in-computing-costs/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-14T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google DeepMind's AlphaEvolve AI system breaks a 56-year-old mathematical record by discovering a more efficient matrix multiplication algorithm that had eluded human mathematicians since Strassen's 1969 breakthrough.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Nuñez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn Vite for a Better Web Development Workflow]]></title>
        <id>6824ae178a2b26e9d2d0fe4c</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-vite-for-a-better-web-development-workflow/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-14T14:52:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Speed and simplicity are at the heart of modern web development. As applications grow more complex and the demand for rapid iteration increases, developers are constantly searching for tools that minimize friction and maximize productivity. Tradition...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Web Services Work – The Unseen Engines of the Connected World]]></title>
        <id>6824ad336ea9fe84cfb4d0c4</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-web-services-work-with-examples/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-14T14:48:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Have you ever wondered how your weather app instantly knows the forecast, how you can book flights from multiple airlines on one travel site, or how logging into one service can magically log you into another? The answer often lies in a powerful, yet...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kumar Anand</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Master Kotlin & Android 60-Hour Course]]></title>
        <id>6824aba7be2c002301d59188</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/master-kotlin-and-android-60-hour-course/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-14T14:41:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Do you want to create the next groundbreaking mobile app? Kotlin, a modern and powerful language officially backed by Google, not only makes Android development more efficient and enjoyable but also opens doors to diverse programming opportunities be...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[QuickLee V2: An Improved Transparent Look into RPC Provider Latency]]></title>
        <id>680fc8e1f8ae810001969b47</id>
        <link href="https://blog.quicknode.com/quicklee-v2/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-14T13:57:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[View public and real-time dashboards to better understand latency and speed when evaluating RPC providers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>QuickNode</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Patronus AI debuts Percival to help enterprises monitor failing AI agents at scale]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3007592</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/patronus-ai-debuts-percival-to-help-enterprises-monitor-failing-ai-agents-at-scale/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-14T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Patronus AI introduces Percival, a real-time monitoring platform that helps enterprises detect, debug, and prevent failures in autonomous AI agents to improve reliability, safety, and scalability.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Nuñez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The first US hub for experimental medical treatments is coming]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1116428</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/05/14/1116428/first-us-hub-for-experimental-medical-treatments/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-14T12:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A bill that allows medical clinics to sell unproven treatments has been passed in Montana.  Under the legislation, doctors can apply for a license to open an experimental treatment clinic and recommend and sell therapies not approved by the Food and Drug Administration (FDA) to their patients. Once it’s signed by the governor, the law…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jessica Hamzelou</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The VentureBeat AI survey is back: Are you ready for the agentic AI future?]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3007483</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/the-venturebeat-ai-survey-is-back-are-you-ready-for-the-agentic-ai-future/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-14T12:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AI is a critical competitive advantage — and it’s time to find out how your company stacks up. The annual VentureBeat AI survey is back. The survey is brought to you by ActiveFence, a leader in expert-driven gen AI safety and security solutions, and returns alongside Transform 2025 in SF this June 24 and 25. […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>VB Staff</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Download: taking the temperature of snow, and the future of privacy]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1116426</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/05/14/1116426/the-download-taking-the-temperature-of-snow-and-the-future-of-privacy/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-14T12:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is today’s edition of The Download, our weekday newsletter that provides a daily dose of what’s going on in the world of technology. Why climate researchers are taking the temperature of mountain snow The Sierra’s frozen reservoir provides about a third of California’s water and most of what comes out of the faucets, shower heads, and…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rhiannon Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why climate researchers are taking the temperature of mountain snow]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1116395</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/05/14/1116395/why-climate-researchers-are-taking-the-temperature-of-mountain-snow/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-14T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On a crisp morning in early April, Dan McEvoy and Bjoern Bingham cut clean lines down a wide run at the Heavenly Ski Resort in South Lake Tahoe, then ducked under a rope line cordoning off a patch of untouched snow.  They side-stepped up a small incline, poled past a row of Jeffrey pines, then…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>James Temple</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Notion bets big on integrated LLMs, adds GPT-4.1 and Claude 3.7 to platform]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3007515</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/notion-bets-big-on-integrated-llms-adds-gpt-4-1-and-claude-3-7-to-platform/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-13T22:18:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Notion used OpenAI's GPT-4.1 and Anthropic's Claude 3.7 for its new AI features for enterprises, moving away from reasoning models.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Emilia David</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What your tools miss at 2:13 AM: How gen AI attack chains exploit telemetry lag – Part 2]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3005726</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/what-your-tools-miss-at-213-am-how-gen-ai-attack-chains-exploit-telemetry-lag-part-2/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-13T22:05:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Explore a strategic 2025 roadmap for cybersecurity leaders to tackle GenAI, insider risks, and team burnout with actionable guidance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Louis Columbus</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AI power rankings upended: OpenAI, Google rise as Anthropic falls, Poe report finds]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3007490</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/ai-power-rankings-upended-openai-google-rise-as-anthropic-falls-poe-report-finds/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-13T19:13:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New Poe data reveals major shifts in AI market share as OpenAI and Google gain ground while specialized reasoning models surge to 10% of usage in 2025.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Nuñez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SimilarWeb’s new AI usage report reveals 5 surprising findings, including explosive growth in coding tools]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3007475</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/similarwebs-new-ai-usage-report-reveals-5-surprising-findings-including-explosive-growth-in-coding-tools/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-13T17:22:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The signs point to early-stage AI disruption beginning to erode the utility of some legacy platforms. It also offers a hint to enterprises...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carl Franzen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Material 3 Expressive]]></title>
        <id>https://design.google/library/expressive-material-design-google-research</id>
        <link href="https://design.google/library/expressive-material-design-google-research"/>
        <updated>2025-05-13T17:20:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lock-Free Rust: How to Build a Rollercoaster While It's on Fire]]></title>
        <id>https://yeet.cx/blog/lock-free-rust/</id>
        <link href="https://yeet.cx/blog/lock-free-rust/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-13T16:43:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Thermoelectric generator based on a robust carbon nanotube/BiSbTe foam]]></title>
        <id>https://onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/10.1002/cey2.650</id>
        <link href="https://onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/10.1002/cey2.650"/>
        <updated>2025-05-13T16:20:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Náhuatl and Mayan Language Renaissance Occurring in Mexico]]></title>
        <id>https://yucatanmagazine.com/mayan-language-renaissance/</id>
        <link href="https://yucatanmagazine.com/mayan-language-renaissance/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-13T16:08:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Zinc Microcapacitors Are the Best of Both Worlds]]></title>
        <id>https://spectrum.ieee.org/zinc-microcapacitor</id>
        <link href="https://spectrum.ieee.org/zinc-microcapacitor"/>
        <updated>2025-05-13T14:57:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Top Ways Hackers Exploit Web Applications (and How to Prevent Them)]]></title>
        <id>682354c58b3805ff1d2335d0</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-hackers-exploit-web-applications-and-how-to-prevent-them/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-13T14:18:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Every website that takes user input is a potential target for an attacker. You might think your app is too small or too new to get noticed, but attackers use tools to scan the web for common security mistakes. If your site is online and has a login f...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Manish Shivanandhan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The interoperability breakthrough: How MCP is becoming enterprise AI’s universal language]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3007355</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/the-interoperability-breakthrough-how-mcp-is-becoming-enterprise-ais-universal-language/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-13T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Just a few months after it's release, MCP adoption is growing. VentureBeat spoke to some enterprises asking why MCP is winning the standards race.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Emilia David</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Guardian agents: New approach could reduce AI hallucinations to below 1%]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3007370</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/beyond-detection-why-automatically-correcting-hallucinations-could-transform-enterprise-ai-adoption/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-13T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There are lots of ways to detect AI hallucination, new guardian agent model promises to correct them.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sean Michael Kerner</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Archisuits (2005–2006)]]></title>
        <id>https://insecurespaces.net/archisuits-2005-2006/</id>
        <link href="https://insecurespaces.net/archisuits-2005-2006/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-13T12:20:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Download: CRISPR in court, and the police’s ban-skirting AI]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1116357</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/05/13/1116357/the-download-crispr-in-court-and-the-polices-ban-skirting-ai/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-13T12:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is today’s edition of The Download, our weekday newsletter that provides a daily dose of what’s going on in the world of technology. A US court just put ownership of CRISPR back in play The CRISPR patents are back in play. Yesterday, the US Court of Appeals for the Federal Circuit said scientists Jennifer Doudna and…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rhiannon Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Police tech can sidestep facial recognition bans now]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1116321</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/05/13/1116321/police-tech-can-sidestep-facial-recognition-bans-now/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-13T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Six months ago I attended the largest gathering of chiefs of police in the US to see how they’re using AI. I found some big developments, like officers getting AI to write their police reports. Today, I published a new story that shows just how far AI for police has developed since then.  It’s about…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>James O'Donnell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GTK Krell Monitors]]></title>
        <id>https://gkrellm.srcbox.net/</id>
        <link href="https://gkrellm.srcbox.net/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-13T06:19:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Comma 3X: Initial Impressions]]></title>
        <id>https://beesbuzz.biz/blog/14719-Comma-3X-Initial-impressions</id>
        <link href="https://beesbuzz.biz/blog/14719-Comma-3X-Initial-impressions"/>
        <updated>2025-05-13T00:26:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sakana introduces new AI architecture, ‘Continuous Thought Machines’ to make models reason with less guidance — like human brains]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3007376</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/sakana-introduces-new-ai-architecture-continuous-thought-machines-to-make-models-reason-with-less-guidance-like-human-brains/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-12T23:08:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While the CTM shows strong promise, it is still primarily a research architecture and is not yet production-ready out of the box.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carl Franzen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OpenAI just fixed ChatGPT’s most annoying business problem: meet the PDF export that changes everything]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3007361</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/openai-just-fixed-chatgpts-most-annoying-business-problem-meet-the-pdf-export-that-changes-everything/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-12T20:43:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[OpenAI has added a powerful PDF export feature to its Deep Research tool, signaling a major push into enterprise AI and transforming how businesses generate and share insights.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Nuñez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New fully open source vision encoder OpenVision arrives to improve on OpenAI’s Clip, Google’s SigLIP]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3007349</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/new-fully-open-source-vision-encoder-openvision-arrives-to-improve-on-openais-clip-googles-siglip/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-12T18:19:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A vision encoder is a necessary component for allowing many leading LLMs to be able to work with images uploaded by users.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carl Franzen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Automate Compliance and Fraud Detection in Finance with MLOps]]></title>
        <id>68222009a8daed5c1fbf1692</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/automate-compliance-and-fraud-detection-in-finance-with-mlops/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-12T16:21:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[These days, businesses are under increasing pressure to comply with stringent regulations while also combating fraudulent activities. The high volume of data and the intricate requirements of real-time fraud detection and compliance reporting are fre...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Balajee Asish Brahmandam</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn Object-Oriented Programming in TypeScript]]></title>
        <id>682201c8ba77730da04e15a8</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-object-oriented-programming-in-typescript/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-12T14:12:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Object-Oriented Programming (OOP) is one of the most widely used programming paradigms in software development. But is also one of the most misunderstood. This article will help you gain a solid grasp of OOP in TypeScript by walking you through the l...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lucas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Become an Analytical Programmer – Solve the "Rock, Paper, Scissors" Game 5 Ways Using JavaScript & Mermaid.js]]></title>
        <id>6822006162f6347293451e07</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-become-an-analytical-programmer-compare-five-projects/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-12T14:06:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Over the past year, I’ve explored tools and practices that help developers build an analytical mindset. One recurring theme is how experienced programmers often describe understanding code as forming a mental picture – a conceptual map of the program...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>evaristo.c</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Glass Imaging raises $20M to use AI to improve digital image quality]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3007251</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/games/glass-imaging-raises-20m-to-use-ai-to-improve-digital-image-quality/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-12T13:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Glass Imaging, a company harnessing the power of artificial intelligence to revolutionize digital image quality, raised $20 million in funding. Global software investor insight Partners led the round. With the funding, Glass Imaging will continue to refine and implement their proprietary GlassAI technologies across a wide range of camera platforms – from smartphones to drones to wearables and […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dean Takahashi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Aarki launches Encore as privacy-first mobile growth platform]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3007252</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/games/aarki-launches-encore-as-privacy-first-mobile-growth-platform/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-12T12:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Aarki has launched Encore, a next-generation machine learning platform built to deliver full-funnel growth for mobile marketers in a privacy-first landscape. Designed for smarter user acquisition and stronger retention, Encore combines dynamic targeting, continuous model evolution, and SKAN 4-ready optimization.  Encore is the industry’s only unified platform with a privacy-first framework that supports both User […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dean Takahashi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[From silicon to sentience: The legacy guiding AI’s next frontier and human cognitive migration]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3007219</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/from-silicon-to-sentience-the-legacy-guiding-ais-next-frontier-and-human-cognitive-migration/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-11T17:05:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As AI systems master tasks once uniquely human, we find ourselves on an accelerated journey to discover what truly lies beyond automation.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gary Grossman, Edelman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MCP and the innovation paradox: Why open standards will save AI from itself]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3007210</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/mcp-and-the-innovation-paradox-why-open-standards-will-save-ai-from-itself/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-10T19:05:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Much like HTTP and REST standardized how web applications connect to services, MCP standardizes how AI models connect to tools.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Noah Schwartz, Postman API Network</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fine-tuning vs. in-context learning: New research guides better LLM customization for real-world tasks]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3007197</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/fine-tuning-vs-in-context-learning-new-research-guides-better-llm-customization-for-real-world-tasks/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-10T00:23:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By combining fine-tuning and in-context learning, you get LLMs that can learn tasks that would be too difficult or expensive for either method]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ben Dickson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What your tools miss at 2:13 AM: How gen AI attack chains exploit telemetry lag – Part 1]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3005673</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/security/what-your-tools-miss-at-213-am-how-gen-ai-attack-chains-exploit-telemetry-lag-part-1/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-09T20:56:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Explore a strategic 2025 roadmap for cybersecurity leaders to tackle gen AI, insider risks, and team burnout with actionable guidance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Louis Columbus</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OpenAI’s $3B Windsurf move: the real reason behind its enterprise AI code push]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3007170</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/openais-3b-windsurf-move-the-real-reason-behind-its-enterprise-ai-agent-code-push/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-09T17:00:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[OpenAI’s $3B Windsurf buy puts it on defense as Google & Anthropic surge in AI-powered coding—discover the stakes for agentic development and enterprise teams.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matt Marshall</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Zencoder launches Zen Agents, ushering in a new era of team-based AI for software development]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3007152</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/zencoder-launches-zen-agents-ushering-in-a-new-era-of-team-based-ai-for-software-development/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-09T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Zencoder launches Zen Agents, the first AI platform enabling teams to create, share, and leverage custom development assistants organization-wide, plus an open-source marketplace for enterprise-grade AI tools.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Nuñez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Breathe lands $21M Series B to predict battery performance]]></title>
        <id>https://techcrunch.com/?p=3003769</id>
        <link href="https://techcrunch.com/2025/05/07/breathe-lands-21m-series-b-to-predict-battery-performance/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-07T12:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Breathe has developed a suite of tools that it says helps automakers and others get the most out of their batteries.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tim De Chant</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Join the 2025 Web3j Mentorships: Build the Future of Ethereum on the JVM]]></title>
        <id>6819c8dc41eeeb000183d37b</id>
        <link href="https://blog.web3labs.com/join-the-2025-web3j-mentorships-build-the-future-of-ethereum-on-the-jvm/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T08:32:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Linux Foundation’s Decentralized Trust (LFDT) mentorship program is back in 2025 with two exciting opportunities for developers passionate about Ethereum, Android, and the Java Virtual Machine (JVM). Whether you’re a seasoned blockchain developer or an Android enthusiast eager to dive into Web3, these mentorships offer]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>George Tebrean</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>