<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2025-04-30T03:34:20.767Z</id>
    <title>AngJianming RSS Feed</title>
    <updated>2025-04-30T03:34:20.767Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[Boost] Agentica, Every TypeScript Developer is an AI Developer (AI function calling framework)]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/samchon/-2djp</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/samchon/-2djp"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T03:19:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[[Agentica] Every TypeScript Developer is an AI Developer
Jeongho Nam ・ Mar 26
#programming
        #typescript
        #opensource
        #ai]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeongho Nam</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build an NSFW AI Image Generator Using Next.js and React]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/ficav/how-to-build-an-nsfw-ai-image-generator-using-nextjs-and-react-4ak1</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/ficav/how-to-build-an-nsfw-ai-image-generator-using-nextjs-and-react-4ak1"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T03:17:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build an NSFW AI Image Generator Using Next.js and React


In the rapidly evolving field of artificial intelligence, image generation has become a fascinating area for developers. Building an NSFW AI image generator can be both an exciting and educational project, especially when leveraging modern web technologies like Next.js, React, and Tailwind CSS. In this tutorial, we'll walk through the steps to create your own NSFW AI image generator web application.
Prerequisites
Setting Up the Next.js Project
Integrating Tailwind CSS
Building the Image Generation Component
Handling NSFW Content Responsibly
Testing the Application
Conclusion
Resources
Before we start, make sure you have the following installed:
Node.js (v12 or later)
npm or Yarn

Basic knowledge of React and Next.js
Familiar…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ficav</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nothing Rolls Out 4K Telephoto Recording For Phone (3a) Series]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=350102</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/350102/nothing-4k-phone-3a/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T03:04:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nothing has announced the rollout of its Nothing X 3.0 software update for the Phone (3a) series. The update is packed with numerous UI and performance improvements, with the highlight being the addition of 4K recording when using the telephoto lenses. With the new update, both the Phone (3a) and (3a) Pro now support 4K […]
The post Nothing Rolls Out 4K Telephoto Recording For Phone (3a) Series appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ikmal Rozlan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Understanding Scope in Software Design from Architecture to Idioms]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/dimasbagussusilo/understanding-scope-in-software-design-from-architecture-to-idioms-497h</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/dimasbagussusilo/understanding-scope-in-software-design-from-architecture-to-idioms-497h"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T03:04:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Software development is filled with terminology that can sometimes feel overlapping or confusing. We talk about "architecture," "design patterns," and "best practices," but what do these terms really mean, and how do they relate to each other? Understanding the different scopes or levels at which we make design decisions is crucial for building robust, maintainable, and scalable software, and for communicating effectively within development teams.
Think of software design not as a single activity, but as a series of decisions made at different levels of abstraction, ranging from the highest-level system structure down to the specifics of individual lines of code. Let's break down these common layers.
Scope & Purpose: Operating at the broadest scope, Architectural Styles and Patterns define…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dimas Bagus Susilo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Driving Innovation: Blockchain Funding and Token Incentives]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/kallileiser/driving-innovation-blockchain-funding-and-token-incentives-2k4g</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/kallileiser/driving-innovation-blockchain-funding-and-token-incentives-2k4g"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T03:00:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Abstract:

This post takes an in‐depth look at the evolving landscape of blockchain funding mechanisms and token incentives. We explore key concepts such as ICOs, STOs, DAOs, and IDOs as methods of raising capital for blockchain projects while examining the role of various tokens – from utility and governance tokens to staking and security tokens – in fueling blockchain ecosystems. The article also reviews regulatory challenges, user adoption issues, and offers a future outlook on streamlining funding and compliance in a decentralized world. Drawing on insights from original resources like Driving Innovation: Blockchain Funding and Token Incentives, as well as expert commentary from Dev.to and License Token’s ecosystem, we offer a holistic overview enriched with tables, bullet lists, and c…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>kallileiser</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[hey Everyone!]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/vishal_choudhary_836/hey-everyone-3ino</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/vishal_choudhary_836/hey-everyone-3ino"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T02:58:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mera naam Vishal Chaudhary hai, aur main ek BCA student hoon IGNOU se. Jab maine programming ke baare me pehli baar suna, toh bas curiosity thi — yeh code kaise kaam karta hai? Lekin aaj, main coding ko ek skill hi nahi, apna passion maan chuka hoon.
Ye blog maine isliye start kiya hai taaki apna programming journey share kar sakun, aur un sab logon ki help kar sakun jo naye hain coding me ya BCA jaise course pursue kar rahe hain. Agar aap bhi beginner hain, toh aap sahi jagah par ho — hum milke seekhenge, galtiyan karenge, aur grow karenge!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Vishal Choudhary</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Technology Behind YouTube’s Auto-Captioning System]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/activejack/the-technology-behind-youtubes-auto-captioning-system-1o45</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/activejack/the-technology-behind-youtubes-auto-captioning-system-1o45"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T02:57:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[YouTube’s auto-captioning system has become an essential feature for millions of viewers and creators worldwide. Whether you’re watching a video in a noisy environment, learning a new language, or relying on captions for accessibility, auto-captions make content more inclusive and user-friendly. But have you ever wondered what technology powers this impressive system? Let’s take a closer look at how YouTube’s auto-captioning works behind the scenes.
At the heart of YouTube’s auto-captioning is advanced speech recognition technology. When a video is uploaded, YouTube’s algorithms analyze the audio track and convert spoken words into written text. This process, known as Automatic Speech Recognition (ASR), relies on deep learning models trained on vast datasets of human speech. These models a…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jack</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[C++ Tips and Tricks for Advanced Developers]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/media_geneous_bb80d6b5563/c-tips-and-tricks-for-advanced-developers-33ko</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/media_geneous_bb80d6b5563/c-tips-and-tricks-for-advanced-developers-33ko"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T02:57:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[C++ Tips and Tricks for Advanced Developers
C++ remains one of the most powerful and widely used programming languages, especially in performance-critical applications like game development, embedded systems, and high-frequency trading. Even experienced developers can benefit from advanced tips and optimizations to write cleaner, faster, and more maintainable code.
In this article, we’ll explore some lesser-known C++ techniques, best practices, and optimizations that can elevate your programming skills. And if you're looking to grow your YouTube channel while sharing your C++ expertise, consider checking out MediaGeneous for powerful content growth tools.
1. Move Semantics and Perfect Forwarding


Move semantics, introduced in C++11, allow for efficient resource transfer, reducing unnecess…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>MediaGeneous</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The thing about AI...]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/mwlang/the-thing-about-ai-1bok</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/mwlang/the-thing-about-ai-1bok"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T02:57:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Software Engineers Worldwide are on notice:  "Your job will be replaced by AI generating your code base in the next five years."
The thing is, this is just pure hype and does not represent reality. 
I grew up through a large swath of the computerization and digitization of civilization.  What's going on now is indeed revolutionary.  But no more so than the advancement of computers from punchcard driven monstrosities taking up entire floors to handheld smartphones that bring you live captioning with amazingly accurate and robust speech to text capabilities.
We've seen the programming languages advance from machine language to Assembler to C and Pascal to Smalltalk to Tcl/Perl to PHP, Ruby, and beyond.  
We've seen how we write code go from punchcards to VI to IDEs to snippets to code comple…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Lang</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Coimbatore Is Becoming a Hotspot for Artificial Intelligence Learning]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/kannan_palanisamy_c10fdfb/why-coimbatore-is-becoming-a-hotspot-for-artificial-intelligence-learning-kk4</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/kannan_palanisamy_c10fdfb/why-coimbatore-is-becoming-a-hotspot-for-artificial-intelligence-learning-kk4"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T02:55:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence (AI) has become one of the most transformative technologies of our time. From automating repetitive tasks to powering advanced robotics and data analysis, AI is reshaping how we live and work. For anyone looking to break into this exciting field, the city of Coimbatore has emerged as a powerful hub for high-quality, industry-focused learning.
Located in Tamil Nadu, Coimbatore has long been recognized as a center for engineering and technical education. Over the past few years, it has rapidly evolved into a thriving destination for tech innovation. Now, it offers some of the best AI courses in Coimbatore, combining theoretical foundations with practical experience.
The city is home to several reputed institutes and training academies that focus on Artificial Intellig…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kannan Palanisamy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Personal Picks: Data Product News (April 30, 2025)]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/sagara/personal-picks-data-product-news-april-30-2025-44m4</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/sagara/personal-picks-data-product-news-april-30-2025-44m4"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T02:52:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Modern Data Stack Updates: April 2025


※This article is an English translation of my original Japanese post.
As a consultant specializing in the Modern Data Stack, I've noticed that there's a constant stream of new information being released in this field. In this article, I'll summarize some of the most interesting Modern Data Stack updates from the past two weeks.
Note: This article doesn't cover all the latest updates for the mentioned products. It only includes information that I personally found interesting.
Cognition Labs, the company behind Devin, has announced "DeepWiki," a service that generates a wiki for a GitHub repository simply by changing the domain part of the repository URL to deepwiki.
https://x.com/cognition_labs/status/1915816544480989288
As shared by @satoshihirose on…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sagara</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Manual Data Entry and Inaccurate Asset Records: Challenges in Asset Valuation and Planning]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/assettracker01/manual-data-entry-and-inaccurate-asset-records-challenges-in-asset-valuation-and-planning-5606</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/assettracker01/manual-data-entry-and-inaccurate-asset-records-challenges-in-asset-valuation-and-planning-5606"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T02:51:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Accurate asset records are critical for organizations to determine their financial standing, plan for future investments, and ensure operational efficiency. However, many companies still rely on manual data entry for asset management, which often results in inaccuracies, inconsistencies, and inefficiencies. These inaccuracies, in turn, lead to incorrect asset valuation and flawed planning decisions.
The Problem with Manual Data Entry
Manual data entry involves human operators recording asset information into spreadsheets or outdated databases. This process is prone to errors due to fatigue, misinterpretation of data, and inconsistent formatting. Even minor inaccuracies, such as typographical errors, missing serial numbers, or incorrect purchase dates, can cause significant discrepancies in…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Asset Tracker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[From Zero to Cloud Hero: My First AWS EC2 & S3 Web Project]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/casualweightlifter54/from-zero-to-cloud-hero-my-first-aws-ec2-s3-web-project-26jh</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/casualweightlifter54/from-zero-to-cloud-hero-my-first-aws-ec2-s3-web-project-26jh"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T02:49:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As someone pivoting into cloud security, I wanted to get hands-on with AWS. This blog documents how I built a basic web server on EC2, hosted an image on S3, and embedded that image in a live Apache-hosted web page — all secured and scalable. If you're starting your cloud journey, this is the post I wish I had.
The goal:
Launch an EC2 instance (Ubuntu)
Host a simple webpage using Apache
Embed an image stored in an S3 bucket
Apply basic security best practices
Power it all from scratch with my own hands
This post is a walkthrough — not just of what I did, but what I learned.
The first step was to launch a virtual server (EC2 instance) on AWS. Here's how I did it:
1. Choose the AMI (Amazon Machine Image)

2. Select Instance Type

3. Create a Key Pair

Make sure to store the .pem file securel…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Javier Seng</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Malaysia attracts US$3.7 billion in digital investments, solidifying]]></title>
        <id>b95e1bfb983c9cc102bc4266d362a8c2</id>
        <link href="https://www.digitalnewsasia.com/digital-economy/malaysia-attracts-us37-billion-digital-investments-solidifying-position-aseans-tech"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T02:31:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Malaysia’s digital economy continues to go from strength to strength, emerging as a strategic engine of growth that creates jobs, opens new opportunities, and fosters local innovation for businesses]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>@DigitalNewsAsia</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Australia’s finance watchdog to crack down on dormant crypto exchanges]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/australia-finance-agency-austrac-dormant-crypto-exchange-blitz</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/australia-finance-agency-austrac-dormant-crypto-exchange-blitz?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T02:24:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Australia’s financial intelligence agency has told inactive registered crypto exchanges to withdraw their registrations or risk having them canceled over fears that the dormant firms could be used for scams.
There are currently 427 crypto exchanges registered with the Australian Transaction Reports and Analysis Centre (AUSTRAC), but the agency said on April 29 that it suspects a significant number are inactive and possibly vulnerable to being bought and co-opted by criminals.
The agency is contacting any so-called digital currency exchanges (DCEs) that appear to no longer be trading, and AUSTRAC CEO Brendan Thomas said they’ll be told to “use it or lose it.”
“Businesses registered with AUSTRAC are required to keep their details up to date; this includes details about services that are no l…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Stephen Katte</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MDV powers Malaysia's tech innovation with over RM13bil financing]]></title>
        <id>d3f5fdc4ea236d719dc3a9d352d4620c</id>
        <link href="https://www.nst.com.my/business/corporate/2025/04/1209375/mdv-powers-malaysias-tech-innovation-over-rm13bil-financing"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T01:56:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[KUALA LUMPUR: Malaysia Debt Ventures Bhd (MDV) has emerged as a key enabler of the nation’s innovation and digital transformation agenda, with more than RM13 billion channelled into over 1,000 high-impact, technology-driven projects.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bernama</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[One UI 7 Update Rolls Out To Older Samsung Galaxy Flagships]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=350094</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/350094/one-ui-7-update-rolls-out-to-older-samsung-galaxy-flagships/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T01:50:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Samsung has begun rolling out its latest Android-based interface, the One UI 7, to older flagship devices. The good news is that the update is now live in Malaysia, as confirmed by multiple Galaxy S23 users. We’ve also received the update on our own units, including the Galaxy Z Fold5 (shown above). It appears that […]
The post One UI 7 Update Rolls Out To Older Samsung Galaxy Flagships appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Heirul Kamel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ledger scammers are sending letters to steal seed phrases]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/ledger-scammers-send-letters-steal-recovery-seed-phrases</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/ledger-scammers-send-letters-steal-recovery-seed-phrases?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T01:50:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Scammers are mailing physical letters to the owners of Ledger crypto hardware wallets asking them to validate their private seed phrases in a bid to access the wallets to clean them out.
In an April 29 X post, tech commentator Jacob Canfield shared a scam letter sent to his home via post that appeared to be from Ledger claiming he needed to immediately perform a “critical security update” on his device. 
The letter, which uses Ledger’s logo, business address, and a reference number to feign legitimacy, asks to scan a QR code and enter the wallet’s private recovery phrase under the guise of validating the device.
The letter threatens that “failure to complete this mandatory validation process may result in restricted access to your wallet and funds.”
Source: Jacob Canfield
A seed phrase, or…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Brayden Lindrea</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Redmagic 10 Air Launches In Malaysia; Starts From RM3,199]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=350053</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/350053/redmagic-10-air-launches-in-malaysia-starts-from-rm3199/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T01:13:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nubia has released its newest mid-range gaming smartphone, the Redmagic 10 Air, in Malaysia. The device is designed to be sleek and lightweight while offering high performance and a long battery life at an affordable price. The Redmagic 10 Air features a 6.8-inch AMOLED full-screen display with a refresh rate of 120Hz and a peak […]
The post Redmagic 10 Air Launches In Malaysia; Starts From RM3,199 appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nurul Kamil</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MyEG, MIMOS Launches Malaysia Blockchain Infrastructure]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=350089</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/350089/myeg-mimos-launches-malaysia-blockchain-infrastructure/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T00:53:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[MyEG Services Bhd and MIMOS Technology Solutions Sdn Bhd launched the Malaysia Blockchain Infrastructure (MBI) yesterday on 29 April 2025, a national platform aimed at accelerating blockchain adoption across public and private sectors. The initiative is expected to strengthen Malaysia’s position in the regional digital economy. Described as a “neutral and trusted platform,” MBI is […]
The post MyEG, MIMOS Launches Malaysia Blockchain Infrastructure appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Heirul Kamel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trump Media considers crypto token and wallet for streaming arm]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/trump-media-exploring-crypto-token-digital-wallet</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/trump-media-exploring-crypto-token-digital-wallet?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T23:56:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Trump Media and Technology Group, the social media conglomerate backed by US President Donald Trump, is considering integrating a crypto token and wallet into its video streaming site, Truth+.
"We're exploring the introduction of a utility token within a Truth digital wallet that can initially be used to pay for Truth+ subscription costs, and later be applied to other products and services in the Truth ecosphere," Trump Media CEO Devin Nunes wrote in an April 29 letter to shareholders.
He added that the crypto token and wallet would be part of a rewards program that Trump Media is exploring across its services, which include the social media platform Truth Social and the financial services platform Truth.Fi.
Trump Media first signaled plans for a potential crypto payments venture last Nove…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Brayden Lindrea</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Labor pain, crypto gain — How weak JOLTS data sets path for Bitcoin price to rally]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/labor-pain-crypto-gain-how-weak-jolts-data-sets-path-for-bitcoin-price-to-rally</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/labor-pain-crypto-gain-how-weak-jolts-data-sets-path-for-bitcoin-price-to-rally?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T23:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Key points:

Weak labor and consumer data often precede Bitcoin rallies, leading some analysts to anticipate future economic stimulus programs.

Job openings fell to 7.2 million in March versus the 7.5 million forecast and consumer confidence hit its lowest level since January 2021.

If past patterns hold, Bitcoin could rally by mid-July and possibly reach $140,000 by October 2025.

Macroeconomic conditions have long been seen as a major influence on cryptocurrency prices. Generally, Bitcoin (BTC) and altcoins perform poorly when investors fear that employment and consumer data are weakening. 
According to a US Labor Department JOLTS report released on April 29, job openings in March approached their lowest levels in four years. US employers posted 7.2 million vacancies in March, below the…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Marcel Pechman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Waymo and Toyota outline partnership to advance autonomous driving deployment]]></title>
        <id>https://waymo.com/blog/2025/04/waymo-and-toyota-outline-strategic-partnership</id>
        <link href="https://waymo.com/blog/2025/04/waymo-and-toyota-outline-strategic-partnership"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T23:06:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Betting markets’ Q1 US GDP forecast flips negative amid tariff turmoil]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/betting-markets-q1-us-gdp-forecast-flips-negative-amid-tariff-turmoil</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/betting-markets-q1-us-gdp-forecast-flips-negative-amid-tariff-turmoil?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T22:58:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bettors on prediction platforms Polymarket and Kalshi are flipping bearish on the US economy. As of April 29, both platforms are predicting that the US will log an economic contraction during the first quarter of 2025 in an upcoming economic data release. 
The US has logged positive growth figures every quarter since 2022, and a reversal in that trend could mark the start of a recession.
The pessimistic outlook marks a stark sentiment shift for prediction markets, which had recently anticipated a positive US growth report. On April 29, consensus Q1 US growth estimates on Kalshi, a US derivatives exchange, plunged from around 0.5% to -0.4% in less than 24 hours. 
Meanwhile, Polymarket bettors are setting the odds of a US economic contraction in Q1 at around 70%. On April 28, they still had …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Alex O’Donnell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Author of Crypto Bills Now Being Rehashed Predicts 'Wicked Hot Summer' in Congress]]></title>
        <id>efd65f86-4255-4797-861a-23f03284b564</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2025/04/29/author-of-crypto-bills-now-being-rehashed-predicts-wicked-hot-summer-in-congress"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T22:49:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Patrick McHenry, the ex-lawmaker who championed last year's crypto legislation, also said he expects a role to be found for Tether in the U.S. stablecoin field.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jesse Hamilton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Path Isn't Real on Linux]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.danielh.cc/blog/path</id>
        <link href="https://blog.danielh.cc/blog/path"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T22:35:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[US Senate majority leader expects stablecoin vote before May 26 — Report]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/senate-majority-leader-john-thune-stablecoin-bills</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/senate-majority-leader-john-thune-stablecoin-bills?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T22:32:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[US Senate Majority Leader John Thune reportedly told Republican lawmakers that the chamber would address a bill on stablecoin regulation before the May 26 Memorial Day holiday.
According to an April 29 Politico report, Thune made the comments in a closed-door meeting with Republican senators, who hold a slim majority in the chamber. The Guiding and Establishing National Innovation for US Stablecoins, or GENIUS Act, was introduced by Senator Bill Hagerty in February and passed the Senate Banking Committee in March.
Thune did not mention any crypto or blockchain-related bills in his public comments on US President Donald Trump’s first 100 days in office. Since his Jan. 20 inauguration, Trump has signed several executive orders with the potential to affect US crypto policy, including one affe…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Turner Wright</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[No more window switching: Mastercard’s Agent Pay transforms how enterprises use AI search]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3005997</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/no-more-window-switching-mastercards-agent-pay-transforms-how-enterprises-use-ai-search/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T22:24:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mastercard is working with AI companies and banks to allow AI platforms and agents to facilitate transactions.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Emilia David</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin price still in bargain zone as US jobs report sparks rate cut hopes]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-price-still-in-bargain-zone-as-us-jobs-report-sparks-rate-cut-hopes</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-price-still-in-bargain-zone-as-us-jobs-report-sparks-rate-cut-hopes?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T22:22:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Key Takeaways:

Fidelity Digital Assets says Bitcoin is undervalued and the firm holds an optimistic mid-term outlook.

The JOLTS report shows a sharp drop in open US jobs, raising investors’ hope for Fed interest rate cuts. 

According to Fidelity Digital Assets, Bitcoin’s (BTC) mid-term outlook dropped to an “optimism” zone, as the investment firm noted that BTC is trending toward “undervaluation.” 
As proof,  the firm cited the ‘Bitcoin Yardstick’ metric, which measures BTC’s market cap divided by its hashrate. A lower ratio suggests that Bitcoin is “cheaper” relative to the energy security of its network. 
In Q1 2025, the metric stayed between -1 and 3 standard deviations, cooling from its Q4 2024 overheated levels. The number of days above 2-standard deviations dropped from 22 to 15, …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Biraajmaan Tamuly</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Growth of crypto poses risks to investors, financial stability — Bank of Italy]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/crypto-risks-investors-financial-stability-bank-of-italy</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/crypto-risks-investors-financial-stability-bank-of-italy?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T21:50:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Bank of Italy identified Bitcoin and other digital assets as emerging risk factors in a recent report, citing concerns for both investors and the financial system.
In its April 2025 Financial Stability Report, the Bank of Italy flags crypto volatility and rising integration with the broader economy, singling out stablecoins and non-financial firms’ crypto exposure as key concerns.
"The strong growth of Bitcoin and of other crypto-assets with high price volatility means risks not only for investors but also potentially for financial stability, given the growing interconnections between the digital asset ecosystem, the traditional financial sector and the real economy,” the report notes. 
Excerpt from the Bank of Italy’s Financial Stability Report. Source: Bank of Italy
The Bank of Italy…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Christopher Tepedino</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trump's Truth Social Mulls Launching Token for Subscriptions in Latest Crypto Push]]></title>
        <id>38806852-3f69-4584-a468-6c835ffce78f</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2025/04/29/trump-s-truth-social-mulls-launching-token-for-subscriptions-in-further-crypto-push"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T21:39:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The company also plans to forge ahead with its ETFs, which will include cryptocurrencies.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tom Carreras</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Indian high court orders steps to block Proton Mail]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/indian-high-court-blocks-proton-mail</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/indian-high-court-blocks-proton-mail?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T21:13:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A court in India has ordered the encrypted email service Proton Mail blocked in the country for refusing to share information with authorities.
In an April 29 hearing of the High Court of Karnataka, Justice M Nagaprasanna ordered the government to “block forthwith” domain names associated with Proton Mail, citing authority under the country’s Information Technology Act of 2008. The order stemmed from a complaint filed in January by a New Delhi-based design firm, alleging that some of its employees received offensive emails through the service.  
It’s unclear whether the ban will take effect or face other possible challenges in court. The Proton team reported in March 2024 that Indian authorities had similarly proposed ordering the service blocked in response to alleged “hoax bomb threats,”…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Turner Wright</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Modern Realty (YC S24) Is Hiring]]></title>
        <id>https://www.workatastartup.com/jobs/66546</id>
        <link href="https://www.workatastartup.com/jobs/66546"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T21:00:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Only Teslas exempt from new auto tariffs thanks to 85% domestic content rule]]></title>
        <id>https://fuelarc.com/cars/only-tesla-exempt-from-new-auto-tariffs-thanks-to-85-domestic-content-rule/</id>
        <link href="https://fuelarc.com/cars/only-tesla-exempt-from-new-auto-tariffs-thanks-to-85-domestic-content-rule/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T20:59:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SEC punts decisions on XRP, DOGE ETFs]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/sec-punts-decision-on-bitwise-xrp-doge-etfs</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/sec-punts-decision-on-bitwise-xrp-doge-etfs?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T20:51:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) has postponed deciding on whether to greenlight two proposed cryptocurrency exchange-traded funds (ETFs) holding Dogecoin and XRP, filings show. 
The US regulator has delayed its deadline for ruling on the proposed ETF listings until June, according to two filings reviewed by Cointelegraph. 
The filings were responses to March requests from US exchanges NYSE Arca and Cboe BZX Exchange to list Bitwise’s Dogecoin (DOGE) ETF and Franklin Templeton’s XRP (XRP) ETF, respectively. 
They came on the same day that Nasdaq, another US exchange, asked for permission to list a 21Shares Dogecoin ETF. 
Dogecoin is the world’s most heavily traded memecoin, with a market capitalization of around $26 billion as of April 29, according to data from CoinGecko. X…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Alex O’Donnell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Edges Above $95K, U.S. Stocks Remain Strong as Analyst Warns of 'Blind' Market]]></title>
        <id>0b77b062-fd9e-4a51-9e8c-b2f07d34ab15</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/04/29/bitcoin-edges-up-to-usd95k-u-s-stocks-remain-strong-as-analyst-warns-of-blind-market"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T20:11:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Secretary of Commerce Howard Lutnick announced that the White House was finalizing a trade deal with an unnamed country.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tom Carreras</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meta unleashes Llama API running 18x faster than OpenAI: Cerebras partnership delivers 2,600 tokens per second]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3005976</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/meta-unleashes-llama-api-running-18x-faster-than-openai-cerebras-partnership-delivers-2600-tokens-per-second/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T20:02:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Meta partners with Cerebras to launch its new Llama API, offering developers AI inference speeds up to 18 times faster than traditional GPU solutions, challenging OpenAI and Google in the fast-growing AI services market.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Nuñez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitget, Avalanche form crypto partnership in India]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitget-avalanche-form-partnership-to-boost-crypto-in-india</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitget-avalanche-form-partnership-to-boost-crypto-in-india?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T19:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitget, a cryptocurrency exchange with 100 million users, has announced a partnership with Avalanche to support community initiatives across India, one of the fastest-growing areas for crypto and Web3 developers.
The partnership will see at least $10 million doled out in mini-grants, scholarships, hackathons, and workshops to the Web3 community in the country. The initial focus will be in Delhi and Bangalore. Delhi is the most populous city in India, and Bangalore is known as the local “Silicon Valley.”
Cryptocurrency activity in India has surged over the past two years. According to CoinSwitch, a local exchange, crypto investment across the country accelerated in 2024, with the highest concentrations in Delhi (20.1%), Bengaluru (9.6%), and Mumbai (6.5%). Youth 18- to 35-years-old now acco…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Christopher Tepedino</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin price always rallies at least 50% after these two patterns emerge]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-price-always-rallies-at-least-50-after-these-two-patterns-emerge</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-price-always-rallies-at-least-50-after-these-two-patterns-emerge?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T19:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Key takeaways:

Bitcoin tends to rally significantly when low leverage meets stronger-than-expected retail sales and hawkish Federal Reserve signals.

In three separate 7-week periods, Bitcoin rose 50% to 84%.

Upcoming speeches from Fed Chair Jerome Powell could benefit Bitcoin price.

Bitcoin (BTC) price rallies are frequently linked to investors’ inflation concerns or data that surpasses expectations for economic growth, yet clear signals of an impending rally are rare. However, a combination of three independent events has historically coincided with BTC price surges of 50% or more.
Bitcoin/USD, log scale. Source: TradingView / Cointelegraph
Significant Bitcoin rallies occur when US Federal Reserve policy expectations ease, crypto market leverage is low, and strong retail data supports…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Marcel Pechman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SoFi Plans Major Push Into Crypto Amid New Regulatory Environment]]></title>
        <id>2f3ada3b-e97d-4f16-8191-76362479c063</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2025/04/29/sofi-will-allow-clients-to-invest-in-crypto-again-after-suspending-service-in-2023-plans-major-push"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T19:11:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There's been a “fundamental shift” in the crypto landscape in the U.S., CEO Anthony Noto said on Wednesday.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Helene Braun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bunq, Europe’s second-largest neobank, expands into crypto]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/bunq-europe-second-largest-neobank-expands-crypto</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/bunq-europe-second-largest-neobank-expands-crypto?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T19:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Update (April 29 at 8:54 pm UTC): This article has been updated to include comments from Bunq's CEO to Cointelegraph. 
Europe’s second-largest neobank, Bunq, is expanding into cryptocurrency, citing growing retail investor demand for digital assets worldwide.
The Amsterdam-based neobank announced the launch of Bunq Crypto on April 29, a new offering enabling its users to invest in over 300 cryptocurrencies, including Bitcoin (BTC), Ether (ETH) and Solana (SOL).
Starting April 29, Bunq users in the Netherlands, France, Spain, Ireland, Italy and Belgium will be able to access cryptocurrencies directly through the Bunq app, according to an announcement.
Bunq CEO Ali Niknam told Cointelegraph that the move was driven by growing client demand for digital assets. "We believe that now many, many …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Zoltan Vardai</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tornado Cash Can’t Be Sanctioned Again, Texas Judge Rules]]></title>
        <id>fc5b1370-af53-43a5-b5da-ec4d7b6197e9</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2025/04/29/tornado-cash-can-t-be-sanctioned-again-texas-judge-rules"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T18:43:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In December, a U.S. appeals court ruled that the U.S. Treasury’s Office of Foreign Asset Control (OFAC) exceeded its statutory authority in sanctioning Tornado Cash.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cheyenne Ligon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meta’s first dedicated AI app is here with Llama 4 — but it’s more consumer than productivity or business oriented]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3005961</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/metas-first-dedicated-ai-app-is-here-with-llama-4-but-its-more-consumer-than-productivity-or-business-oriented/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T18:19:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This mainstream exposure will likely accelerate a shift in what people expect not just from consumer apps, but from workplaces...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carl Franzen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum’s ‘capitulation’ suggests ETH price is undervalued: Fidelity report]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/ethereum-s-capitulation-suggests-eth-price-is-undervalued-fidelity-report</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/ethereum-s-capitulation-suggests-eth-price-is-undervalued-fidelity-report?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T18:17:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Key Takeaways: 

Fidelity Digital Assets’ report said that multiple Ethereum onchain metrics suggest ETH trades at a discount.

The BTC/ETH market cap ratio is at mid-2020 levels. 

Ethereum's layer-2 active addresses hit new highs at 13.6 million. 

Fresh data from Fidelity Digital Assets hints at a cautiously optimistic outlook for Ethereum, suggesting its dismal Q1 performance could be an opportunity. According to their latest Signals Report, Ether (ETH) dipped 45% during Q1, wiping out it post-US election gains after peaking at $3,579 in January.
The altcoin posted a death cross in March, with the 50-day simple moving average (SMA) dipping 21% below the 200-day SMA, reflecting bearish momentum. Yet, Fidelity noted that the short-term pain may swing in the altcoin’s favor. 
The investme…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Biraajmaan Tamuly</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nasdaq files to list 21Shares Dogecoin ETF]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/nasdaq-files-list-21-shares-dogecoin-etf</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/nasdaq-files-list-21-shares-dogecoin-etf?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T17:57:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The United States exchange Nasdaq has asked regulators for permission to list a 21Shares exchange-traded fund (ETF) holding the popular memcoin Dogecoin, regulatory filings show. 
The move follows 21Shares’ April 10 filing of its initial proposal to launch its Dogecoin ETF, shortly after similar applications from rivals Bitwise and Grayscale. The asset manager has also sought regulators’ permission to list ETFs holding other cryptocurrencies, including Solana (SOL), XRP (XRP), and Polkadot (DOT). 
Nasdaq must gain approval from the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) before it can list and trade the fund. The request amounts to a regulatory review process that could determine whether Dogecoin becomes accessible to a broader range of investors through an ETF structure.
Crypto ETFs sche…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Alex O’Donnell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Show HN: Beatsync – perfect audio sync across multiple devices]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/freeman-jiang/beatsync</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/freeman-jiang/beatsync"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T17:32:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bamba: An open-source LLM that crosses a transformer with an SSM]]></title>
        <id>https://research.ibm.com/blog/bamba-ssm-transformer-model</id>
        <link href="https://research.ibm.com/blog/bamba-ssm-transformer-model"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T17:24:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chain of Recursive Thoughts: Make AI think harder by making it argue with itself]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/PhialsBasement/Chain-of-Recursive-Thoughts</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/PhialsBasement/Chain-of-Recursive-Thoughts"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T17:19:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Everything we announced at our first LlamaCon]]></title>
        <id>https://ai.meta.com/blog/llamacon-llama-news/?_fb_noscript=1</id>
        <link href="https://ai.meta.com/blog/llamacon-llama-news/?_fb_noscript=1"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T17:17:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[O3 beats a master-level GeoGuessr player, even with fake EXIF data]]></title>
        <id>https://sampatt.com/blog/2025-04-28-can-o3-beat-a-geoguessr-master</id>
        <link href="https://sampatt.com/blog/2025-04-28-can-o3-beat-a-geoguessr-master"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T16:48:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Samourai Wallet Prosecutors Are Considering Dropping Charges Under New DOJ Crypto Enforcement Priorities: Filing]]></title>
        <id>9b36b910-d4ee-462e-9886-3535208b8bf1</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2025/04/29/samourai-wallet-prosecutors-are-considering-dropping-charges-under-new-doj-crypto-enforcement-priorities-filing"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T16:46:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The co-founders are each facing up to 25 years in prison for alleged money laundering and unlicensed money transmitting.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cheyenne Ligon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Indian court orders blocking of Proton Mail]]></title>
        <id>https://techcrunch.com/2025/04/29/indian-court-orders-blocking-of-proton-mail/</id>
        <link href="https://techcrunch.com/2025/04/29/indian-court-orders-blocking-of-proton-mail/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T16:41:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WonderFi’s Dean Skurka on Bringing Users Onchain and Canada's Crypto Evolution]]></title>
        <id>a385b7d2-bf6b-439c-ac1f-788c4e93eea3</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/consensus-toronto-2025-coverage/2025/04/29/wonderfis-dean-skurka-on-bringing-users-onchain-and-canadas-crypto-evolution"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T16:26:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[WonderFi's CEO, a speaker at Consensus 2025, outlines the firm’s Layer-2 ambitions, Australia expansion, regulatory hopes for Canada, and how volatility impacts the industry.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Aoyon Ashraf</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Will Arizona Become the First State to Join Feds in Planning a Bitcoin Reserve?]]></title>
        <id>d9063668-1142-442c-8cc1-b523c9bc1b60</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2025/04/29/will-arizona-become-the-first-state-to-join-feds-in-planning-a-bitcoin-reserve"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T16:11:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new approval from Arizona lawmakers to form a digital assets stockpile must still survive a veto potential from the Democratic governor.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jesse Hamilton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase’s Base Network Achieves ‘Stage 1’ Status, Reducing Centralization Risk]]></title>
        <id>7d072d24-3f60-421a-a920-8e95c984d5c0</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/tech/2025/04/29/coinbases-base-network-achieves-stage-1-status-reducing-centralization-risk"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T16:00:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The move means that Base will now have a security council which will  help approve certain network upgrades if needed.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Margaux Nijkerk</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Create Accessible and User-Friendly Forms in React]]></title>
        <id>6810f59e8deee87383c1bc46</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-create-accessible-and-user-friendly-forms-in-react/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T15:51:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When designing web applications, you’ll often be asked the age old question “How accessible is your website” and “Does it offer the best user experience?”. These are both very valid questions, but they are often overlooked in favour of rich or fancy ...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Grant Riordan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Firefox tab groups are here]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.mozilla.org/en/firefox/tab-groups-community/</id>
        <link href="https://blog.mozilla.org/en/firefox/tab-groups-community/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T15:37:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn College Calculus and Implement with Python]]></title>
        <id>6810eebd43aa3d16a14700eb</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-college-calculus-and-implement-with-python/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T15:22:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Calculus is one of the cornerstones of higher mathematics and a powerful tool for understanding change, motion, and growth across countless disciplines. But for many students, Calculus can seem intimidating or abstract. What if you could learn it ste...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Robinhood Crypto Revenue Expected to Fall in Q1 After Record Late 2024 Gain: JPMorgan]]></title>
        <id>566c9f9c-b936-42b1-a04e-184afe5d0f85</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/04/29/robinhood-crypto-revenue-expected-to-fall-in-q1-after-record-late-2024-gain-jpmorgan"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T15:12:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After a 700% surge in Q4 crypto revenue, analysts now expect a pullback in Q1 as trading activity slows.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Helene Braun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The last masters of Afro-Colombian machete fencing]]></title>
        <id>https://globalvoices.org/2025/04/19/the-last-masters-of-afro-colombian-machete-fencing-fight-to-save-their-tradition/</id>
        <link href="https://globalvoices.org/2025/04/19/the-last-masters-of-afro-colombian-machete-fencing-fight-to-save-their-tradition/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T15:11:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[UK gov&#039;t proposes crypto rules in response to scams]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/uk-government-crypto-rules-consumer-protection</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/uk-government-crypto-rules-consumer-protection?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T15:08:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The United Kingdom’s Treasury and Chancellor of the Exchequer, Rachel Reeves, have proposed new crypto rules aimed at “support[ing] innovation while cracking down on fraudsters.”
In an April 29 notice, the UK government announced draft rules for cryptocurrencies, including Bitcoin (BTC) and Ether (ETH), that would bring “crypto exchanges, dealers and agents” in line with regulations, as many residents were “exposed to risky firms and scams.” It cited discussions with US government officials, including a proposed US-UK cross-border sandbox from the Securities and Exchange Commission’s Hester Peirce.
“Today’s announcement sends a clear signal: Britain is open for business — but closed to fraud, abuse, and instability,” said the notice. “The government will bring forward final cryptoasset leg…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Turner Wright</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AI has a trust problem — Decentralized privacy-preserving tech can fix it]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/ai-has-a-trust-problem</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/ai-has-a-trust-problem?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Opinion by: Felix Xu, co-founder of ARPA Network and Bella Protocol
AI has been a dominant narrative since 2024, but users and companies still cannot completely trust it. Whether it’s finances, personal data or healthcare decisions, hesitation around AI’s reliability and integrity remains high.
This growing AI trust deficit is now one of the most significant barriers to widespread adoption. Decentralized, privacy-preserving technologies are quickly being recognized as viable solutions that offer verifiability, transparency and stronger data protection without compromising AI’s growth.
The pervasive AI trust deficit 
AI was the second most popular category occupying crypto mindshare in 2024, with over 16% investor interest. Startups and multinational companies have allocated considerable re…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Felix Xu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin &#039;hot supply&#039; nears $40B as new investors flood in at $95K]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-hot-supply-nears-40b-new-investors-flood-in-at-95k</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-hot-supply-nears-40b-new-investors-flood-in-at-95k?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T14:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Key points:

Bitcoin’s most recently-moved supply segment is increasing as higher prices see an influx of “speculative capital.”

“Hot supply” has doubled in just five weeks versus local lows in March.

Active address numbers have yet to mimic a classic bull market comeback.

Bitcoin (BTC) short-term holders (STHs) are back in the game as a “speculative capital” enters the market.
In an X thread on April 29, onchain analytics firm Glassnode reported a surge in Bitcoin’s so-called “hot capital.”
Bitcoin sees “surge in capital turnover”
New investors are entering the market as BTC price action circles its highest levels in several months.
Glassnode reveals that the sum of coins which last moved up to a week ago has reached its largest figure since early February.
“This metric captures short-…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by William Suberg</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Register Models in Django Admin]]></title>
        <id>6810e5a2dc9845a2ab207f06</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-register-models-in-django-admin/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T14:43:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When you're building a website or an app with Django, one of the most exciting moments is when your database models finally come to life. But to manage your data easily – adding, editing, or deleting entries – you need Django’s Admin panel. Now, here...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Udemezue John</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ArkFlow: High-performance Rust stream processing engine]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/arkflow-rs/arkflow</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/arkflow-rs/arkflow"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T14:38:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Jepsen: Amazon RDS for PostgreSQL 17.4]]></title>
        <id>https://jepsen.io/analyses/amazon-rds-for-postgresql-17.4</id>
        <link href="https://jepsen.io/analyses/amazon-rds-for-postgresql-17.4"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T14:30:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[$649B stablecoin transfers linked to illicit activity in 2024: Report]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/stablecoin-risk-crypto-transactions-bitrace-2024-report</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/stablecoin-risk-crypto-transactions-bitrace-2024-report?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T14:28:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency compliance firm Bitrace found that $649 billion worth of stablecoins flowed through addresses classified as high-risk in 2024, according to an April 29 report.
Bitrace defines high-risk blockchain addresses as those used by illegal entities to receive, transfer or store stablecoins.
Crypto compliance firms typically score crypto wallet addresses based on their likelihood of involvement in illicit activities. The higher the risk, the higher the likelihood of foul play, and the less likely compliant crypto businesses are to accept the assets.
Per the report, the amount accounted for roughly 5.14% of all stablecoin transaction volume in 2024. This is down 0.8% from 5.94% the previous year, but significantly higher than the 2.8% reported in 2022 and 1.63% in 2021.
Proportion of …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Adrian Zmudzinski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[UK Government Targets Exchanges and Stablecoins With New Draft Crypto Rules]]></title>
        <id>fcb85fd8-4f27-4591-b2f0-903dd0f5a661</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2025/04/29/uk-government-releases-draft-crypto-rules"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T14:00:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The statutory instruments will see the creation of new regulated activities such as operating a cryptoasset trading exchange and stablecoin issuance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Camomile Shumba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Is XRP price going to crash again?]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/is-xrp-price-going-to-crash-again</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/is-xrp-price-going-to-crash-again?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T13:56:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Key takeaways:

XRP trades over 120% above its realized price, flashing heightened correction risk.

A rising wedge breakdown on the 4H chart could send XRP toward $1.89 by mid-May.

Weekly falling wedge pattern and 50-week EMA support suggest a possible 25% recovery to $2.92 by June.

XRP (XRP) price has rebounded by over 40% in the last three weeks to reach over $2.28 on April 29, but it’s still trading over 30% below its local high of $3.39.
XRP/USD daily price chart. Source: TradingView
Will XRP’s price sustain the recovery or drop further in the coming days?
XRP’s rising wedge flashes selloff risks
XRP is showing signs of a potential breakdown as a rising wedge pattern forms on its 4-hour chart, raising the risk of a sharp short-term correction.
As of April 29, XRP trades around $2.29…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Yashu Gola</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How $330M BTC Hacker May Have Doubled Down on Monero Derivatives]]></title>
        <id>c860b182-cbd2-4443-a40e-0c334598597a</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2025/04/29/did-the-usd330m-btc-hacker-deliberatley-pump-monero-to-make-even-more-money"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T13:56:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Monero rose by 45% after a flurry of spot buys, but open interest increased by 107%.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Oliver Knight</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum price has several reasons to break $2,000 next]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/ethereum-price-has-several-reasons-break-2000-next</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/ethereum-price-has-several-reasons-break-2000-next?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T13:33:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Key takeaways:

Strong Ethereum ETF inflows signal high institutional demand.

Ethereum’s $51.8B TVL and 30% DEX weekly volume rise show robust network strength.

A bull flag pattern on the ETH’s four-hour chart targets $2,100.

Ether’s (ETH) price rose to a new range high at $1,860 on April 28, its highest value since April 2.
Several analysts argue that the ETH price needs to hold above $1,800 to increase the chances of rising higher.
“Once ETH confirms this 4H close above resistance [$1,800], Ether and altcoins will finally get their time to shine,” trader Kiran Gadakh said in an April 29 post on X.  
“I can feel it in my bones, $2,000 ETH coming fast.” 
ETH/USD 12-hour chart. Source: Kiran Gadak
Popular analyst Nebraskangooner opined that if ETH faces high volume rejection from the $1,…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Nancy Lubale</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tripp launches Kōkua AI as mental wellness coach across multiple platforms]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3005798</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/games/tripp-launches-kokua-ai-as-mental-wellness-coach-across-multiple-platforms/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T13:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tripp launched Kōkua AI, a mental wellness guide designed to deliver real-time, personalized emotional support across multiple platforms.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dean Takahashi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Here’s what happened in crypto today]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/what-happened-in-crypto-today</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/what-happened-in-crypto-today?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T13:29:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today in crypto, the US Department of Justice has requested a 20-year prison sentence for Alex Mashinsky, the co-founder and former CEO of defunct crypto lender Celsius, a crypto group petitioned the White House to drop charges against crypto devs, including Tornado Cash’s Roman Storm, and Arizona’s House passed two crypto reserve bills.
US DOJ requests 20-year sentence for Celsius founder Alex Mashinsky
Alex Mashinsky, the founder and former CEO of the now-defunct cryptocurrency lending platform Celsius, faces a 20-year prison sentence as the US Department of Justice (DOJ) seeks a severe penalty for his role in a multibillion-dollar fraud.
The DOJ on April 28 filed the government’s sentencing memorandum against Mashinsky, recommending a 20-year prison sentence for his fraudulent actions, …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Cointelegraph</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CBDCs ‘costly fiat copy’, not fintech success so far: Ex-Binance exec]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/cbdc-costly-fiat-copy-not-fintech-success-ex-binance-exec</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/cbdc-costly-fiat-copy-not-fintech-success-ex-binance-exec?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T13:18:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The United States’ rejection of a central bank digital currency has not halted the progress of CBDCs globally, but their success has been questionable so far, according to a former Binance executive.
Global CBDC projects have not failed, but they have also not become what they were anticipated to be, according to Olga Goncharova, CEO at the consulting firm Rizz Go and former director of government relations in the Commonwealth of Independent States at Binance.
“CBDCs were conceived as a technological breakthrough, but so far they look like expensive imitations of existing traditional fiat currencies that citizens and businesses already use through online banking and payment apps,” Goncharova told Cointelegraph at the Blockchain Forum in Moscow.
Olga Goncharova during a panel on Web3 geopol…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Helen Partz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CoinDesk 20 Performance Update: Bitcoin Cash (BCH) Gains 6.3% as Index Trades Higher]]></title>
        <id>80eb4f67-7086-4331-82c2-98a06bfb7f69</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/coindesk-indices/2025/04/29/coindesk-20-performance-update-bitcoin-cash-bch-gains-6-3-as-index-trades-higher"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T13:14:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum (ETH) joined Bitcoin Cash (BCH) as a top performer, rising 1.8% from Monday.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CoinDesk Indices</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AirBorne: Wormable zero-click remote code execution (RCE) in AirPlay protocol]]></title>
        <id>https://www.oligo.security/blog/airborne</id>
        <link href="https://www.oligo.security/blog/airborne"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T13:09:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Vanishing $212M Bitcoin Order Caused Chaos for Traders. Is Spoofing Back in Crypto?]]></title>
        <id>9adbeb31-30dc-42b0-b1c9-0d9fb663c71e</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2025/04/29/a-vanishing-usd212m-bitcoin-order-caused-chaos-for-traders-is-spoofing-back-in-crypto"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T13:06:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Despite increased scrutiny, spoofing remains a challenge in crypto, highlighting the need for better surveillance and stricter regulations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Oliver Knight</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Beijing to invest in blockchain, integrate into infrastructure]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/beijing-to-invest-in-blockchain-integrate-into-infrastructure-and-host-nodes</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/beijing-to-invest-in-blockchain-integrate-into-infrastructure-and-host-nodes?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T13:03:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Beijing city administration has announced a plan for local blockchain development and implementation over the next two years.
According to an April 29 announcement, the plan was jointly developed by the Beijing Municipal Science and Technology Commission, the Zhongguancun Administrative Committee, the Cyberspace Administration Office, the Bureau of Government Services and Data, the Bureau of Economy and Information Technology and the Bureau of Commerce. The implementation is expected to start this year and continue until 2027.
The announcement. Source: Beijing government
The Beijing Blockchain Innovation and Application Development Action Plan recognizes blockchain as a “critical foundational technology for industrial digitalization and vital digital infrastructure.” 
Notably, the obje…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Adrian Zmudzinski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[xMEMS extends micro cooling fan-on-a-chip tech to AI data centers]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3005879</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/game-development/xmems-extends-micro-cooling-fan-on-a-chip-tech-to-ai-data-centers/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[xMEMS Labs, a pioneer of MEMS-based chips, announced that its innovative µCooling fan-on-a-chip tech will be expanded to AI data centers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dean Takahashi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BONK Bets Gain Favor as New Token Issuance Platform Nets $800K in 3 Days]]></title>
        <id>a0f905dc-a43b-4370-839c-8fffa965effe</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/04/29/bonk-bets-gain-favor-as-new-token-issuance-platform-nets-800k-in-3-days"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T12:53:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“I expect the platform's success to surprise many,” well-followed X user @theunipcs “Bonk Guy” told CoinDesk in a Telegram message.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shaurya Malwa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Performance optimization is hard because it's fundamentally a brute-force task]]></title>
        <id>https://purplesyringa.moe/blog/why-performance-optimization-is-hard-work/</id>
        <link href="https://purplesyringa.moe/blog/why-performance-optimization-is-hard-work/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T12:29:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Polygon Spin-Off Miden Secures $25M to Bring Speed, Privacy to Institutional Giants]]></title>
        <id>f84107fc-007e-4dfa-88d9-3fb439e5e114</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/tech/2025/04/29/polygon-spin-off-miden-secures-25m-to-bring-speed-privacy-to-institutional-giants"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T12:27:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The funding round was led by a16z crypto, 1kx and Hack VC.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Margaux Nijkerk</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Programming languages should have a tree traversal primitive]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.tylerglaiel.com/p/programming-languages-should-have</id>
        <link href="https://blog.tylerglaiel.com/p/programming-languages-should-have"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T12:23:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A16z leads $25M funding for Miden blockchain project]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/miden-raises-25m-to-scale-zk-blockchain-after-polygon-spinout</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/miden-raises-25m-to-scale-zk-blockchain-after-polygon-spinout?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T12:20:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A16z Crypto led a $25 million investment round into Miden, an independent blockchain project spun out of Polygon Labs.
Miden closed its $25 million seed rounds led by a16z Crypto, 1kx, and Hack VC, with participation from Finality Capital Partners, Symbolic Capital, P2 Ventures, Delta Fund, MH Ventures, as well as from angel investors, including MakerDAO’s Rune Christensen and EigenLayer’s Sreeram Kannan.
Miden is a zero-knowledge (ZK) proof-powered blockchain focused on high scalability through its hybrid consensus mode, which moves transaction execution from the mainnet on “edge devices,” referring to users’ devices.
Designed for institutions that value confidentiality, Miden enables applications to execute both public and private transactions with full privacy, according to an April 29 …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Zoltan Vardai</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Download: the AI Hype Index, and “normal” AI]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1115932</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/04/29/1115932/the-download-the-ai-hype-index-and-normal-ai/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T12:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is today’s edition of The Download, our weekday newsletter that provides a daily dose of what’s going on in the world of technology. The AI Hype Index: AI agent cyberattacks, racing robots, and musical models Separating AI reality from hyped-up fiction isn’t always easy. That’s why we’ve created the AI Hype Index—a simple, at-a-glance summary of…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rhiannon Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trump’s first 100 days ‘worst in history’ despite crypto promises]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/trump-first-100-days-worst-in-history-despite-crypto-promises</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/trump-first-100-days-worst-in-history-despite-crypto-promises?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T11:58:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The first 100 days of the administration of US President Donald Trump have deeply impacted the crypto industry, starting with his own memecoin and culminating in a Bitcoin reserve and a spate of blockchain policymaking. 
Trump’s trade war with the entire world has had the largest short-term impact on crypto markets, as crypto prices have wavered amid macroeconomic worry and uncertainty. Higher prices on electronics mean Bitcoin (BTC) miners are finding it harder to break even, and de-dollarization concerns abound. 
Still, crypto markets have shown some resilience and cause for optimism in the administration’s crypto-friendly policies. A number of pro-crypto leaders have been appointed to key government agencies, including the Securities and Exchange Commission and the Commodity Futures Tra…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Aaron Wood</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[$2B Bitcoin-Staking Protocol Solv Unveils First Shariah-Compliant BTC Yield Offering in the Middle East]]></title>
        <id>3d6f8d08-b349-4fff-8cfe-4784429221ee</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/04/29/2b-bitcoin-staking-protocol-solv-unveils-first-shariah-compliant-btc-yield-offering-in-the-middle-east"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T11:56:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The product allows BTC holders to earn yields while adhering to Islamic finance principles, expanding opportunities for investors in the Middle East.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Omkar Godbole</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Show HN: A Chrome extension that will auto-reject non-essential cookies]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.bymitch.com/posts/reject-cookies/</id>
        <link href="https://blog.bymitch.com/posts/reject-cookies/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T11:49:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Circle gets Abu Dhabi regulatory nod to expand in Middle East]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/circle-abu-dhabi-adgm-approval-middle-east-expansion</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/circle-abu-dhabi-adgm-approval-middle-east-expansion?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T11:47:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[USDC stablecoin issuer Circle has received in-principle approval (IPA) from the Financial Services Regulatory Authority (FSRA) of the Abu Dhabi Global Market (ADGM), the company announced on April 29.
The approval moves Circle closer to obtaining a full Financial Services Permission (FSP) license, allowing it to operate as a regulated money services provider in the United Arab Emirates, the firm said in an official press release.
Jeremy Allaire, Circle’s Co-Founder and CEO, said the approval “advances our strategy to establish deep roots in markets embracing the onchain economy.” He added:
“It also underscores Circle’s enduring commitment to global stablecoin oversight—strengthening trust, compliance, and adoption worldwide, while laying a resilient foundation for the internet financial sy…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Amin Haqshanas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Acer Malaysia Launches Multiple Predator Products]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=350037</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/350037/acer-malaysia-launches-multiple-predator-products/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T11:44:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Acer Malaysia today officially launched a large lineup of products. That list includes two gaming laptops, a new OLED monitor, a graphics card, a desktop rig, and a foldable controller for mobile devices. We’ll start with the Orion 7000 desktop PC. Now available via Acer eStore and the brand’s Shopee and Lazada digital store for […]
The post Acer Malaysia Launches Multiple Predator Products appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John Law</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin miner Phoenix Group adds 52 MW of mining capacity in Ethiopia]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-miner-phoenix-group-adds-52-megawatts-of-mining-capacity-in-ethiopia</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-miner-phoenix-group-adds-52-megawatts-of-mining-capacity-in-ethiopia?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T11:30:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin mining firm Phoenix Group announced the addition of 52 megawatts (MW) worth of mining capacity to its capabilities in Ethiopia.
According to an April 29 announcement, with this latest addition, Phoenix’s Bitcoin mining capacity in Ethiopia reaches 132 MW. The firm’s global capacity now reportedly exceeds 500 MW.
Phoenix’s co-founder and CEO, Munaf Ali, said the firm’s strategy relies on “securing prime locations with abundant, low-cost energy.”
“Initiatives like our latest expansion in Ethiopia are pivotal steps, not only creating significant value today but also solidifying our position,” he said.
Related: Arkansas city rejects crypto mining proposal after community pushback
Building on previous agreements
The news follows Phoenix Group signing an agreement that secures the right …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Adrian Zmudzinski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Your digital identity got stolen — Now what?]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/explained/your-digital-identity-got-stolen-now-what</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/explained/your-digital-identity-got-stolen-now-what?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T11:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What is digital identity?            
            
                
Your digital identity is the fingerprint you leave across the internet, a living map of who you are.
Your digital identity is more than just your name or email; it stretches from your social media profiles and crypto wallet addresses to your device fingerprints and even the rhythms of your daily browsing habits. In the fast-moving world of cryptocurrency, where identity and financial access often overlap, digital identity theft isn’t just a nuisance; it’s an open door to your assets. 

Without strong protection, even small pieces of stolen information can be stitched into a full profile, giving cybercriminals everything they need to impersonate you, seize your funds or lock you out of your accounts.
What many don’t realize…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Sasha Shilina</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Daybook Americas: Bitcoin Bulls Underpin Price After Pro-BTC Candidate Loses in Canada]]></title>
        <id>524ba9ab-b354-4610-9816-1f6f7ce92adc</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/daybook-us/2025/04/29/crypto-daybook-americas-bitcoin-bulls-underpin-price-after-pro-btc-candidate-loses-in-canada"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T11:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Your day-ahead look for April 29, 2025]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>James Van Straten</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Will Trump’s 100-day speech end Bitcoin’s &#039;compressing&#039; range?]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/will-trump-100-day-speech-end-bitcoin-compressing-range</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/will-trump-100-day-speech-end-bitcoin-compressing-range?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T10:27:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Key takeaways:

Bitcoin’s price consolidates as the market awaits President Trump’s 100-day speech.

Over $4.7 billion in BTC has been withdrawn from exchanges since April 22, reducing supply and boosting price sensitivity to demand.

Trump’s crypto policy clarity could spark a BTC surge, but tariffs may cap gains.

Traders say Bitcoin price must clear key hurdles above $95,000 before continuing the uptrend to $100,000 and beyond.


Bitcoin’s (BTC) price is consolidating in a tight range between $91,700 and $95,850, ahead of Trump’s 100-day commemorative rally.
BTC/USD daily chart. Source: Cointelegraph/TradingView 
Market awaits Trump’s 100-day speech
Bitcoin investors have adopted a wait-and-see approach ahead of US President Donald Trump’s speech to commemorate his 100th day in the Whit…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Nancy Lubale</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[iCAUR Teases First EV For Malaysia]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=350040</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/350040/icaur-teases-first-ev-for-malaysia/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T10:22:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We previously reported that Chery’s sub-brand iCAUR (or iCAR in China) will be entering the Malaysia during the Malaysia Auto Show 2025 (MAS). The brand has since confirmed the news through a teaser poster shared on their social media channels, which also features a silhouette of the vehicle it plans to introduce to the local […]
The post iCAUR Teases First EV For Malaysia appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Keran</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AirAsia MOVE Introduces “Easy Cancel” Feature]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=350021</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/350021/airasia-move-introduces-easy-cancel-feature/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T10:06:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AirAsia MOVE has introduced “Easy Cancel“, a new feature that allows users to receive a full refund when cancelling their trip bookings. Through this, customers can cancel their flights up to 48 hours before the departure time for any reason and receive their money through the original payment method. The refund covers not only the […]
The post AirAsia MOVE Introduces “Easy Cancel” Feature appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nurul Kamil</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SIGN Rises 60% on Upbit Listing Despite Slow Start on Binance]]></title>
        <id>01b9f3b6-e0c9-4be0-b80b-c264e4069cfd</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2025/04/29/sign-rises-60-on-upbit-listing-despite-slow-start-on-binance"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T10:04:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SIGN's rise is similar to FIL which also rose on an Upbit listing this month.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Oliver Knight</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DJI Ending Support For Phantom 4, Phantom 4 Pro On 1 June 2025]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=350047</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/350047/dji-ending-support-for-phantom-4-phantom-4-pro-on-1-june-2025/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T10:01:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[DJI has announced the ending of its support for two of its products: the Phantom 4 and Phantom 4 Pro drones. Through its official website, the company has stated that the service and support of the devices will be suspended starting 1 June 2025.  The Phantom 4 was released in Malaysia all the way back […]
The post DJI Ending Support For Phantom 4, Phantom 4 Pro On 1 June 2025 appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Newsdesk</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The AI Hype Index: AI agent cyberattacks, racing robots, and musical models]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1115918</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/04/29/1115918/the-ai-hype-index-ai-agent-cyberattacks-racing-robots-and-musical-models/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Separating AI reality from hyped-up fiction isn’t always easy. That’s why we’ve created the AI Hype Index—a simple, at-a-glance summary of everything you need to know about the state of the industry. AI agents are the AI industry’s hypiest new product—intelligent assistants capable of completing tasks without human supervision. But while they can be theoretically…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Editors</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BlackRock’s IBIT Sees Second-Largest Bitcoin Inflow Since Launch, Nearing $1 Billion]]></title>
        <id>d67edf66-110d-4528-8b46-e1a46fea781d</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/04/29/blackrocks-ibit-sees-second-largest-bitcoin-inflow-since-launch-nearing-1-billion"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T09:49:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CME Bitcoin Futures open interest falls for four straight days, according to CME data.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>James Van Straten</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Alleged OnePlus Ace 5 Racing Edition Specifications Appear Online]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=350027</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/350027/oneplus-ace-5-racing-edition-specs-appear-online/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T09:16:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[OnePlus launched its Ace 5 series late last year, and is now apparently gearing up to release a new variant within the series. Through a post on Weibo, known leakster Digital Chat Station is claiming that the phone may be called the Racing Edition, while also sharing details surrounding its specifications – including its chipset […]
The post Alleged OnePlus Ace 5 Racing Edition Specifications Appear Online appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Newsdesk</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Web3j Six Month Project Update]]></title>
        <id>68109495670a1300013504c2</id>
        <link href="https://blog.web3labs.com/web3j-six-month-project-update/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T09:10:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[November 2024 - April 2025
This report summarizes the activities and accomplishments of Web3j, an LF Decentralized Trust project, from November 2024 to April 2025. During this period, the project made significant strides in improving the framework’s functionality, enhancing user engagement, and bolstering overall community interaction. 
Key]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>George Tebrean</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Viant Technology Could Benefit From Buying Bitcoin, Eric Semler Says]]></title>
        <id>488f3a4a-64e8-4818-9be4-468979446862</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/04/29/viant-technology-could-benefit-from-buying-bitcoin-eric-semler-says"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T09:01:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Semler Scientific chairman flagged the ad tech firm as ripe for a bitcoin treasury strategy amid stock struggles and cash stockpile.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>James Van Straten</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Here’s why we need to start thinking of AI as “normal”]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1115928</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/04/29/1115928/is-ai-normal/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Right now, despite its ubiquity, AI is seen as anything but a normal technology. There is talk of AI systems that will soon merit the term “superintelligence,” and the former CEO of Google recently suggested we control AI models the way we control uranium and other nuclear weapons materials. Anthropic is dedicating time and money…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>James O'Donnell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Circle Wins Regulatory Nod From Abu Dhabi Watchdog as USDC Hits $62B]]></title>
        <id>46e567b1-6ccf-433b-88d7-c5d5b78c9a8f</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2025/04/29/circle-wins-regulatory-nod-from-abu-dhabi-watchdog-as-usdc-hits-usd62b"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T08:55:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The stablecoin issuer received in-principle approval from ADGM's Financial Services Regulatory Authority to operate as a money services provider.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Krisztian Sandor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Xiaomi’s Upcoming YU7 Electric SUV May Get Second Variant]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=349993</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/349993/xiaomi-yu7-electric-suv-may-get-second-variant/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T08:49:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Following the success of the SU7, Xiaomi is preparing to launch its second EV model, the YU7 SUV, in China between June or July this year. Now, a recent report by Car News China alleges that the upcoming vehicle will debut another variant alongside the original 820km trim, with a range of 835km. This detail […]
The post Xiaomi’s Upcoming YU7 Electric SUV May Get Second Variant appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Keran</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DOJ Seeks 20-Year Sentence for Celsius Founder Alex Mashinsky]]></title>
        <id>17f84d8f-dbf5-41c0-997c-3f0832a0247d</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2025/04/29/doj-seeks-20-year-sentence-for-celsius-founder-alex-mashinsky"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T07:43:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Federal prosecutors called Mashinsky the architect of a "years-long campaign of lies and self-dealing" that left customers with billions in losses.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sam Reynolds</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin, XRP, ETH Steady as BTC ETFs Attract $590M Inflows]]></title>
        <id>2af14240-b29b-4cf3-ad13-9873edfdf11e</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/04/29/bitcoin-xrp-eth-steady-as-btc-etfs-attract-590m-inflows"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T07:23:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“We are bullish on BTC in the medium term due to expectations of monetary and fiscal easing in response to tariff-driven slowdowns,” one trader said.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shaurya Malwa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[LibreLingo – FOSS Alternative to Duolingo]]></title>
        <id>https://librelingo.app/</id>
        <link href="https://librelingo.app/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T05:45:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin-Friendly Poilievre Loses Seat as Carney's Liberals Win 2025 Election]]></title>
        <id>b5cccd42-3fe4-44ce-b5af-ac176e8229b3</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2025/04/29/bitcoin-friendly-poilievre-loses-seat-as-carneys-liberals-win-2025-election"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T04:26:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Canada's 45th election turned out to be a close one as polls narrowed in the days leading up to the end of the campaign.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sam Reynolds</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[An illustrated guide to automatic sparse differentiation]]></title>
        <id>https://iclr-blogposts.github.io/2025/blog/sparse-autodiff/</id>
        <link href="https://iclr-blogposts.github.io/2025/blog/sparse-autodiff/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T03:18:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Alibaba launches open source Qwen3 model that surpasses OpenAI o1 and DeepSeek R1]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3005880</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/alibaba-launches-open-source-qwen3-model-that-surpasses-openai-o1-and-deepseek-r1/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-28T23:56:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Qwen3’s open-weight release under an accessible license marks an important milestone, lowering barriers for developers and organizations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carl Franzen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[I use zip bombs to protect my server]]></title>
        <id>https://idiallo.com/blog/zipbomb-protection</id>
        <link href="https://idiallo.com/blog/zipbomb-protection"/>
        <updated>2025-04-28T22:28:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ex-OpenAI CEO and power users sound alarm over AI sycophancy and flattery of users]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3005850</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/ex-openai-ceo-and-power-users-sound-alarm-over-ai-sycophancy-and-flattery-of-users/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-28T21:49:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crucially, the turbulence also nudges many organizations to explore open-source models they can host, monitor, and fine-tune themselves.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carl Franzen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Beyond A2A and MCP: How LOKA’s Universal Agent Identity Layer changes the game]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3005824</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/beyond-a2a-and-mcp-how-lokas-universal-agent-identity-layer-changes-the-game/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-28T20:35:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The LOKA protocol, a proposed standard for AI agents from Carnegie Mellon University researchers, will give identities and intentions to agents.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Emilia David</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build a Production-Ready DevOps Pipeline with Free Tools]]></title>
        <id>680fe1e69418a1165cb184a2</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-build-a-production-ready-devops-pipeline-with-free-tools/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-28T20:15:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A few months ago, I dove into DevOps, expecting it to be an expensive journey requiring costly tools and infrastructure. But I discovered you can build professional-grade pipelines using entirely free resources. If DevOps feels out of reach because y...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Opaluwa Emidowojo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[30 seconds vs. 3: The d1 reasoning framework that’s slashing AI response times]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3005393</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/30-seconds-vs-3-the-d1-reasoning-framework-thats-slashing-ai-response-times/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-28T19:31:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[d1 framework changes boosts diffusion LLMs with novel reinforcement learning, unlocking efficient, problem-solving AI possibilities.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ben Dickson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build a Website from Scratch – Start to Finish Walkthrough]]></title>
        <id>680fd51ef631538076304a73</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-build-a-website-from-scratch-start-to-finish-walkthrough/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-28T19:21:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, fellow developers! Building a website can feel overwhelming at first – especially when you're staring at a blank HTML file, wondering how it ever turns into a real website on the internet. If you're new to web development, you've probably asked y...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kunal Nalawade</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WorldGen: Open-source 3D scene generator for Game/VR/XR]]></title>
        <id>https://worldgen.github.io/</id>
        <link href="https://worldgen.github.io/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-28T18:39:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Writer releases Palmyra X5, delivers near GPT-4.1 performance at 75% lower cost]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3005734</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/writer-releases-palmyra-x5-delivers-near-gpt-4-performance-at-75-lower-cost/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-28T17:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Writer unveils Palmyra X5: The enterprise AI model that processes 1,500 pages at once, costs 75% less than GPT-4, and enables affordable autonomous agents for businesses seeking automation ROI.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Nuñez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[QuickNode: Building the Infrastructure for the Next Generation of Blockchain]]></title>
        <id>6807d5787fb8500001c39b99</id>
        <link href="https://blog.quicknode.com/quicknode-building-the-infrastructure-for-the-next-generation-of-blockchain/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-28T16:02:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Join QuickNode co-founder Dmitry Shklovsky as he discusses blockchain infrastructure, building decentralized applications, and the future of Web3 development on TheCube's Crypto Trailblazer Series.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>QuickNode</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Enable CORS in Django]]></title>
        <id>680fa40e9096ceb5eeedd90e</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-enable-cors-in-django/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-28T15:51:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you've ever tried to connect your frontend app to your Django backend and suddenly hit an error that looks something like "has been blocked by CORS policy", you're not alone. It’s frustrating, especially when your code seems fine. So what’s going ...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Udemezue John</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Turn Ubuntu 24.04 into a KVM Hypervisor – Quick Setup with Web Management]]></title>
        <id>680fa285102a9fb019d4fa34</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/turn-ubuntu-2404-into-a-kvm-hypervisor/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-28T15:45:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Virtualization lets you run multiple operating systems on one machine. It’s perfect for testing apps, hosting servers, or learning DevOps. A hypervisor is the software that lets you run multiple virtual machines on a single physical machine, and the ...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shamsuddoha Ranju</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Automate Mobile Testing: Strategies for Reliable, Scalable Tests]]></title>
        <id>680fa2440e43e5b002c3c7f4</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-automate-mobile-testing-strategies/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-28T15:44:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mobile test automation uses tools and frameworks to test mobile applications automatically. It replicates user interactions to evaluate the app's functions and detect possible issues early on. This automated approach is helpful since it accelerates t...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nazneen Ahmad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[China's Clinical Trial Boom]]></title>
        <id>https://www.asimov.press/p/china-trials</id>
        <link href="https://www.asimov.press/p/china-trials"/>
        <updated>2025-04-28T15:13:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[It's School time: Adventures in hacking an old Kindle]]></title>
        <id>https://samkhawase.com/blog/hacking-kindle/</id>
        <link href="https://samkhawase.com/blog/hacking-kindle/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-28T15:02:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Download: China’s manufacturers’ viral moment, and how AI is changing creativity]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1115909</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/04/28/1115909/the-download-chinas-manufacturers-viral-moment-and-how-ai-is-changing-creativity/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-28T12:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is today’s edition of The Download, our weekday newsletter that provides a daily dose of what’s going on in the world of technology. Why Chinese manufacturers are going viral on TikTok Since the video was posted earlier this month, millions of TikTok users have watched as a young Chinese man in a blue T-shirt sits beside…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rhiannon Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Does RAG make LLMs less safe?  Bloomberg research reveals hidden dangers]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3005592</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/does-rag-make-llms-less-safe-bloomberg-research-reveals-hidden-dangers/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-28T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[RAG is supposed to make enterprise AI more accurate, but it could potentially also make it less safe according to new research.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sean Michael Kerner</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Chinese manufacturers are going viral on TikTok]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1115876</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/04/28/1115876/why-chinese-manufacturers-are-going-viral-on-tiktok/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-28T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Since the video was posted earlier this month, millions of TikTok users have watched as a young Chinese man in a blue T-shirt sits beside a traditional tea set and speaks directly to the camera in accented English: “Let’s expose luxury’s biggest secret.”  He stands and lifts what looks like an Hermès Birkin bag, one…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Caiwei Chen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[UPDATED] Malaysia and Maldives explore new ties in solar, defence, and digital tech [WATCH]]]></title>
        <id>2ff00997f9c35cff9b55bf1c234d9fd9</id>
        <link href="https://www.nst.com.my/news/nation/2025/04/1208426/updated-malaysia-and-maldives-explore-new-ties-solar-defence-and-digital"/>
        <updated>2025-04-28T04:17:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[PUTRAJAYA: Malaysia is eager to explore new avenues of cooperation with the Maldives, including floating solar energy, defence, and digital technology, says Datuk Seri Anwar Ibrahim.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hakim Mahari</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Princeton Engineering Anomalies Research (2010)]]></title>
        <id>https://pearlab.icrl.org/theory.html</id>
        <link href="https://pearlab.icrl.org/theory.html"/>
        <updated>2025-04-27T21:49:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Is your AI product actually working? How to develop the right metric system]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3005642</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/is-your-ai-product-actually-working-how-to-develop-the-right-metric-system/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-27T19:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Metrics are critical for determining AI product performance. But where to begin? Here's a framework to apply across various use cases.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sharanya Rao, Intuit</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bits + Bytes: A Miscellany Of Technology]]></title>
        <id>92c9e6ae0de9449f2a2cd9808d52c95a</id>
        <link href="https://theedgemalaysia.com/node/752832"/>
        <updated>2025-04-27T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[NEWS

Malaysia sees tech salary surge in 2025, led by system engineers

Tech salaries in Malaysia have risen significantly this year, with system engineers recording the highest increase at 8%, according to NodeFlair’s Tech Salary Report 2...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Edge Malaysia</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FORKLIFTACTION, B2B news service and business platform about forklifts and materials handling]]></title>
        <id>20065c212264065b824a3328d06be4fc</id>
        <link href="https://www.forkliftaction.com/pagenotfound.aspx"/>
        <updated>2025-04-27T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[FORKLIFTACTION, B2B news service and business platform about forklifts and materials handling]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Forkliftaction</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DeepSeek’s success shows why motivation is key to AI innovation]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3005636</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/deepseeks-success-shows-why-motivation-is-key-to-ai-innovation/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-26T19:55:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How did DeepSeek attain such cost-savings while American companies could not? Let's dive into the technical details.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Debasish Ray Chawdhuri, Talentica Software</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Show HN: AgenticSeek – Self-hosted alternative to cloud-based AI tools]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/Fosowl/agenticSeek</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/Fosowl/agenticSeek"/>
        <updated>2025-04-26T17:23:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Show HN: I build a Fantasy NHL app in 3 days with Claude AI]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=43805275</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=43805275"/>
        <updated>2025-04-26T17:04:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Finding paths of least action with gradient descent (2023)]]></title>
        <id>https://greydanus.github.io/2023/03/05/ncf-tutorial/</id>
        <link href="https://greydanus.github.io/2023/03/05/ncf-tutorial/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-26T06:24:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Malaysia remains 9th largest global exporter of high-tech products]]></title>
        <id>ec83e12fc9489689eba3a736f7c0fd4e</id>
        <link href="https://e.vnexpress.net/news/tech/tech-news/malaysia-remains-9th-largest-global-exporter-of-high-tech-products-4878750.html"/>
        <updated>2025-04-26T02:41:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Malaysia successfully maintained its position as the ninth-largest exporter of high-tech goods out of 143 economies in 2023, the highest recognition it has achieved in the past decade, Bernama has reported.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>VnExpress</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Liquid AI is revolutionizing LLMs to work on edge devices like smartphones with new ‘Hyena Edge’ model]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3005611</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/liquid-ai-is-revolutionizing-llms-to-work-on-edge-devices-like-smartphones-with-new-hyena-edge-model/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-25T22:02:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hyena Edge’s success positions Liquid AI as one of the emerging players to watch in the evolving AI model landscape.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carl Franzen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The new AI calculus: Google’s 80% cost edge vs. OpenAI’s ecosystem]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3005571</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/the-new-ai-calculus-googles-80-cost-edge-vs-openais-ecosystem/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-25T20:26:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Explore the Google vs OpenAI AI ecosystem battle post-o3. Deep dive into Google's huge cost advantage (TPU vs GPU), agent strategies & model risks for enterprise]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matt Marshall</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Create Models in Your Django Project]]></title>
        <id>680be6e3dfe4e9c64b6b0997</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-create-models-in-your-django-project/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-25T19:47:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you're building something with Django, there's one thing you can't skip: creating models. Models are the heart of any Django app. They define how your data is structured, how it's stored in the database, and how Django can interact with it. Now, i...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Udemezue John</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Malaysia remains 9th largest global exporter of high-tech products]]></title>
        <id>e1054193ac5220fd5f3cf3fb0ac3fcbd</id>
        <link href="https://en.vietnamplus.vn/malaysia-remains-9th-largest-global-exporter-of-high-tech-products-post318075.vnp"/>
        <updated>2025-04-25T18:11:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Malaysia’s high-tech exports increased by 2 billion USD to reach 127 billion USD in 2023. He said high-tech exports comprised 58.69% of total manufacturing exports in 2023, up from 52.48% recorded in 2022.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Vietnam+ (VietnamPlus)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Harden Your Node.js APIs – Security Best Practices]]></title>
        <id>680bb2b3917896a550779bcb</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-harden-your-nodejs-apis-security-best-practices/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-25T16:05:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you’ve built an API with Node.js, chances are you’ve thought about security – at least a little. Maybe you’ve heard about SQL injection, brute force attacks, or data leaks. But here’s the thing: it’s not just about big hacks. Even small gaps in yo...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Manish Shivanandhan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[UK agrees to assist Malaysia in technology, new energy]]></title>
        <id>9bba1ab03b6cc59e6474a313d3bc9d9c</id>
        <link href="https://theedgemalaysia.com/node/753068"/>
        <updated>2025-04-25T15:31:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The UK has agreed to collaborate with Malaysia in various fields, including technology and new energy management, said Deputy Prime Minister Datuk Seri Fadillah Yusof.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Edge Malaysia</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Show HN: An MCP server for understanding AWS costs]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=43794120</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=43794120"/>
        <updated>2025-04-25T14:43:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Show HN: An interactive demo of QR codes' error correction]]></title>
        <id>https://qris.cool/</id>
        <link href="https://qris.cool/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-25T12:15:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Download: how Trump’s tariffs will affect US manufacturing, and AI architecture]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1115868</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/04/25/1115868/the-download-how-trumps-tariffs-will-affect-us-manufacturing-and-ai-architecture/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-25T12:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is today’s edition of The Download, our weekday newsletter that provides a daily dose of what’s going on in the world of technology. Sweeping tariffs could threaten the US manufacturing rebound Despite the geopolitical chaos and market collapses triggered by President Trump’s announcement of broad tariffs on international goods, some supporters still hope the strategy will…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rhiannon Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Need to embrace technological advancements, sustainable practices discussed at country's premier real estate event]]></title>
        <id>13ba8e804fd9567fa951b4f7cc51bead</id>
        <link href="https://theedgemalaysia.com/node/753073"/>
        <updated>2025-04-25T12:00:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Industry leaders, policymakers, investors and experts explored the future of Malaysia's real estate landscape at the National Real Estate Convention (NREC) 2025 held here recently.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Edge Malaysia</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sweeping tariffs could threaten the US manufacturing rebound]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1115827</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/04/25/1115827/sweeping-tariffs-could-threaten-the-us-manufacturing-rebound/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-25T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Despite the geopolitical chaos and market collapses triggered by President Trump’s announcement of broad tariffs on international goods, some supporters still hope the strategy will produce a “golden age” of American industry. Trump himself insists, “Jobs and factories will come roaring back into our country.” While it’s possible that very targeted tariffs could help protect…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Rotman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Is that really your boss calling? Jericho Security raises $15M to stop deepfake fraud that’s cost businesses $200M in 2025 alone]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3005473</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/is-that-really-your-boss-calling-jericho-security-raises-15m-to-stop-deepfake-fraud-thats-cost-businesses-200m-in-2025-alone/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-24T22:18:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Pentagon-backed Jericho Security raises $15 million to combat deepfake fraud that has already cost North American businesses $200 million in 2025, using AI to detect increasingly convincing voice and video impersonations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Nuñez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Intel’s new CEO signals streamlining efforts but does not spell out exact layoff numbers]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3005456</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/games/intels-new-ceo-signals-streamlining-efforts-but-does-not-spell-out-exact-layoff-numbers/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-24T21:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Lip-Bu Tan, the new CEO of Intel, sent out a blunt message to employees saying the company has to reorganize to be more efficient.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dean Takahashi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Zencoder buys Machinet to challenge GitHub Copilot as AI coding assistant consolidation accelerates]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3005445</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/zencoder-buys-machinet-to-challenge-github-copilot-as-ai-coding-assistant-consolidation-accelerates/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-24T20:36:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Zencoder acquires Machinet to strengthen its position in the rapidly consolidating AI coding assistant market, expanding its JetBrains ecosystem integration while outperforming competitors like GitHub Copilot with innovative features such as Repo Grokking and Coffee Mode.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Nuñez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethically trained AI startup Pleias releases new small reasoning models optimized for RAG with built-in citations]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3005435</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/ethically-trained-ai-startup-pleias-releases-new-small-reasoning-models-optimized-for-rag-with-built-in-citations/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-24T17:03:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Pleias emphasizes the models’ suitability for integration into search-augmented assistants, educational tools, and user support systems.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carl Franzen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Evil Geniuses and Theta Labs launch AI chatbot based on esports mascot Meesh]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3005327</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/games/evil-geniuses-and-theta-labs-launch-ai-chatbot-based-on-esports-mascot-meesh/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-24T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Evil Geniuses, the well-known esports organization and brand, has launched its Meesh AI chatbot in a partnership with Theta Labs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dean Takahashi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Driving business value by optimizing the cloud]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1115716</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/04/24/1115716/driving-business-value-by-optimizing-the-cloud/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-24T13:56:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Organizations are deepening their cloud investments at an unprecedented pace, recognizing its fundamental role in driving business agility and innovation. Synergy Research Group reports that companies spent $84 billion worldwide on cloud infrastructure services in the third quarter of 2024, a 23% rise over the third quarter of 2023 and the fourth consecutive quarter in…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>MIT Technology Review Insights</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Download: Apple’s eucalyptus carbon bet, and climate tech’s bad vibes]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1115809</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/04/24/1115809/the-download-apples-eucalyptus-carbon-bet-and-climate-techs-bad-vibes/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-24T12:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is today’s edition of The Download, our weekday newsletter that provides a daily dose of what’s going on in the world of technology. Inside the controversial tree farms powering Apple’s carbon neutral goal “We were losing the light, and still about 20 kilometers from the main road, when the car shuddered and died at the edge…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rhiannon Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The vibes are shifting for US climate tech]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1115718</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/04/24/1115718/climate-tech-investments-trump/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-24T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The past few years have been an almost nonstop parade of good news for climate tech in the US. Headlines about billion-dollar grants from the government, massive private funding rounds, and labs churning out advance after advance have been routine. Now, though, things are starting to shift.   About $8 billion worth of US climate tech…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Casey Crownhart</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google adds more AI tools to its Workspace productivity apps]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3005313</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/google-adds-more-ai-tools-to-its-workspace-productivity-apps/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-23T22:43:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google expanded Gemini's features, adding the popular podcast-style feature Audio Overviews to the platform.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Emilia David</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Former DeepSeeker and collaborators release new method for training reliable AI agents: RAGEN]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3005302</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/former-deepseeker-and-collaborators-release-new-method-for-training-reliable-ai-agents-ragen/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-23T20:04:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[RAGEN stands out not just as a technical contribution but as a conceptual step toward more autonomous, reasoning-capable AI agents.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carl Franzen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon’s SWE-PolyBench just exposed the dirty secret about your AI coding assistant]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3005166</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/amazon-swe-polybench-just-exposed-the-dirty-secret-about-your-ai-coding-assistant/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-23T19:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon launches SWE-PolyBench, a groundbreaking multi-language benchmark that exposes critical limitations in AI coding assistants across Python, JavaScript, TypeScript, and Java while introducing new metrics beyond simple pass rates for real-world development tasks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Nuñez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OpenAI makes ChatGPT’s image generation available as API]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3005253</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/openai-makes-chatgpts-image-generation-available-as-api/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-23T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Enterprises can now make Studio Ghibli-inspired images through OpenAI's API.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Emilia David</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[From friction to flow: Why Swissport scrapped its VPN maze for Cato’s SASE platform]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3004830</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/security/from-friction-to-flow-why-swissport-scrapped-its-vpn-maze-for-catos-sase-platform/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-23T16:53:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Swissport ditches legacy tech, deploying a global SASE architecture with Cato Networks securing 26,000 users, unlocking real-time control.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Louis Columbus</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft just launched powerful AI ‘agents’ that could completely transform your workday — and challenge Google’s workplace dominance]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3005118</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/microsoft-just-launched-powerful-ai-agents-that-could-completely-transform-your-workday-and-challenge-googles-workplace-dominance/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-23T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft unveils new AI reasoning agents and Copilot features to transform workplace productivity, with Chief Product Officer Aparna Chennapragada sharing exclusive insights on the company's vision for human-agent collaboration.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Nuñez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cooperations with China continue to drive Malaysia's tech ambitions: experts]]></title>
        <id>7cf31983f27357e33a7e7403d769042c</id>
        <link href="https://english.news.cn/20250423/23952d602d384abe9a3be2f40797fa2d/c.html"/>
        <updated>2025-04-23T09:33:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cooperations with China continue to drive Malaysia's tech ambitions: experts-]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>english.news.cn</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[IBM Tech Innovation Summit]]></title>
        <id>eb7b875c351e513c2d4750bb29a0ab40</id>
        <link href="https://www.malaysiakini.com/news/741130"/>
        <updated>2025-04-23T02:44:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Seats are limited. Register now!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Malaysiakini Team</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[$42.1 million poured into startup offering energy-efficient solutions for costly and unwieldy operational data and AI workloads]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3005163</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/data-infrastructure/42-1-million-poured-into-startup-offering-energy-efficient-solutions-for-costly-and-unwieldy-operational-data-and-ai-workloads/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-23T02:28:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The funding infusion sharpens a mission to make hyperscale analytics radically cheaper and greener at the very moment enterprises fear ballooning data‑center power bills.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ujas Patel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[More accurate coding: Researchers adapt Sequential Monte Carlo for AI-generated code]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3005146</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/more-accurate-coding-researchers-adapt-sequential-monte-carlo-for-ai-generated-code/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-23T00:09:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Researchers from MIT, Yale, McGill University and others found that adapting the Sequential Monte Carlo algorithm can make AI-generated code better.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Emilia David</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SWiRL: The business case for AI that thinks like your best problem-solvers]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3004781</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/swirl-the-business-case-for-ai-that-thinks-like-your-best-problem-solvers/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-22T23:53:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Training LLMs on trajectories of reasoning and tool use makes them superior at multi-step reasoning tasks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ben Dickson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Batch data processing is too slow for real-time AI: How open-source Apache Airflow 3.0 solves the challenge with event-driven data orchestration]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3004953</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/data-infrastructure/open-source-airflow-3-0-set-to-accelerate-data-orchestration-for-enterprise-ai-inference/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-22T20:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Open-source data orchestration gets a major rewrite to help support inference and enterprise AI]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sean Michael Kerner</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Retail & E-Commerce Innovation Marketing & Tech Summit: Malaysia 2025]]></title>
        <id>cd2a0d19be53d9723fc0475f09d0da2d</id>
        <link href="https://marketech-apac.com/conference/retail-e-commerce-innovation-marketing-tech-summit-malaysia-2025/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-22T07:49:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Retail & E-Commerce Innovation Marketing & Tech Summit: Malaysia 2025]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Zyra Kate Capilastique</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>