<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2025-05-27T06:20:18.676Z</id>
    <title>AngJianming RSS Feed</title>
    <updated>2025-05-27T06:20:18.676Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Alleged NVIDIA GeForce RTX 5080 Super Specs Leak]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=353984</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/353984/alleged-nvidia-geforce-rtx-5080-super-specs-leak/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-27T06:15:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[NVIDIA is barely through the first half of the year with its GeForce RTX 50 Series, yet rumours about an RTX 5080 Super are already beginning to surface. More recently, its alleged specifications appear to have been leaked by the industry’s most well known leakster, kopite7kimi. According to kopite, the alleged RTX 5080 Super will […]
The post Alleged NVIDIA GeForce RTX 5080 Super Specs Leak appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John Law</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Is a WAF? A Beginner’s Guide to Web App Firewalls]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/sharon_42e16b8da44dabde6d/what-is-a-waf-a-beginners-guide-to-web-app-firewalls-4g9f</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/sharon_42e16b8da44dabde6d/what-is-a-waf-a-beginners-guide-to-web-app-firewalls-4g9f"/>
        <updated>2025-05-27T06:12:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you've ever built a website or API, chances are you've worried about security—SQL injection, XSS, bots, DDoS... the list goes on. But have you ever wondered how to block those threats before they even hit your application logic?
That’s where a WAF, or Web Application Firewall, comes in.
In this article, we’ll break down what a WAF is, how it works, and why developers like you should care. Whether you're deploying a simple API or a full-stack app, understanding WAFs is essential for building secure software in 2025.
A Web Application Firewall is a filter that sits between your users and your web application. It analyzes HTTP/HTTPS traffic in real time and blocks malicious requests before they reach your backend.
Think of it like a bouncer at a club. It checks every request at the door—if…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sharon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Git clean local branches]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/bdavidxyz/git-clean-local-branches-14c7</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/bdavidxyz/git-clean-local-branches-14c7"/>
        <updated>2025-05-27T06:08:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Article originally published here https://alsohelp.com/blog/git-clean-local-branches
I have some problem with images here on dev.to, so article above may display everything in a better way
Article below :
Let's say you are on your machine, and your local repository has too many branches :
my_lovely_but_old_project> git branch
* Story-4965-password-complexity
  Story-4998-Clean-up-code-from-unnecesssary-comments
  PM25-modification
  blabla
  debug1
  debug2
  debug3
  debug4
  blabla2
  debugging-lm-4730
  doc-get-incident
  doc-incident
  docs/v5apiLocations
  document-api-separately
  main
  development
  refactor/gcalendar-sync
  .
  .
  .
  (... and much more branches)

You want to locally clean branches that are already destroyed on the remote repository
There you go:
git fetch -ap --…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Boureau</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Humanoid AI-powered robots duke it out in China fight comp]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/ai-powered-robots-fight-china-boxing</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/ai-powered-robots-fight-china-boxing?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-27T06:06:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Four artificial intelligence-enhanced robots have been put through their paces in a Chinese robot fighting competition, duking it out in kickboxing matches until one was declared the champion.
The World Robot Competition Mecha Fighting Series had four human-controlled robots built by China-based firm Unitree compete in three, two-minute rounds with winners crowned through a points system, according to a May 26 report from the China state-owned outlet the Global Times. 
Chen Xiyun, a Unitree team member, said the “robots fight in a human-machine collaborative way,” with the machines pre-taught moves, but ultimately, a person controls the bot’s movements.

The robots reportedly weighed 35 kilograms and stood 132 centimeters tall. Ahead of the boxing rounds, the pint-sized robots were put thr…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Stephen Katte</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[useCallback in React: Memoizing Functions to Prevent Re-Creation]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/devshefali/usecallback-in-react-memoizing-functions-to-prevent-re-creation-38bc</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/devshefali/usecallback-in-react-memoizing-functions-to-prevent-re-creation-38bc"/>
        <updated>2025-05-27T06:03:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In React applications, unnecessary function re-creation can lead to performance issues, especially when passing functions as props to child components. This is where the useCallback in React comes in.
In this blog, you’ll learn about the useCallback hook, including its use case and syntax with examples, and the key difference between the useCallback and useMemo hooks.
Before we get started, don’t forget to subscribe to my newsletter!
Subscribe here!
Now, let’s jump right into it!
useCallback is a React Hook that memoizes functions. This stores the reference of the function so that you can avoid creating a new function on each render.
This improves the performance, especially when you need to pass functions from parent components to child components.
If a function is creating unnecessary, t…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shefali</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Former CFTC Chair Christopher Giancarlo joins crypto bank Sygnum]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/former-cftc-chair-christopher-giancarlo-crypto-bank-sygnum</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/former-cftc-chair-christopher-giancarlo-crypto-bank-sygnum?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-27T06:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Christopher Giancarlo, former chairman of the US Commodity Futures Trading Commission (CFTC), has joined Sygnum in an advisory role, where he will help the crypto bank navigate global regulations amid growing institutional interest in digital assets. 
Giancarlo’s appointment as senior policy adviser places him alongside 11 other members of Sygnum’s Advisory Council, the company disclosed on May 27.
In his role, Giancarlo will advise on regulations and strategic partnerships in both the public and private sectors. 
Sygnum is a Swiss banking group dedicated to providing crypto asset services. It’s often called the first digital asset bank, having recently achieved unicorn status following a $58 million funding round. 
Giancarlo, who headed the CFTC between 2017 and 2019, said he is joining S…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Sam Bourgi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ChatGPT-4 vs Gemini 2.5: Which AI Powerhouse Will Rule 2025?]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/jane_watson_c27fd17f03341/chatgpt-4-vs-gemini-25-which-ai-powerhouse-will-rule-2025-2bmf</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/jane_watson_c27fd17f03341/chatgpt-4-vs-gemini-25-which-ai-powerhouse-will-rule-2025-2bmf"/>
        <updated>2025-05-27T05:59:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The competition with AI is gaining momentum, and two key competitors are at the center of attention: OpenAI's ChatGPT-4 and Google's Gemini series. ChatGPT-4 has been the benchmark for large language models (LLMs) for over a year, but Google is catching up with its Gemini models, particularly the highly anticipated Gemini 2.5.
In this post, we will discuss what each AI model can do, what they can do differently, and why their competition may be the best for AI users everywhere.
ChatGPT-4: The Current Benchmark for AI Chatbots


Since its launch in March 2023, ChatGPT-4 has become a household name in AI. Its strength lies in how smoothly it balances accuracy, creativity, and usability across a wide range of tasks—from coding help to creative writing, business planning, and image analysis (i…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jane Watson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Independent Development Tools Bimonthly Issue 001]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/immerse/independent-development-tools-bimonthly-issue-001-3md0</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/immerse/independent-development-tools-bimonthly-issue-001-3md0"/>
        <updated>2025-05-27T05:57:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SEO Beginner's Guide



Link: https://www.indietools.work/product/19fd73b7-67ad-4c64-a423-353eb10d5196
The "Beginner's Guide to SEO" is a specially designed SEO optimization tool for beginners, aiming to help users enhance their website's search engine performance from scratch. This guide covers multiple key SEO techniques, including selecting appropriate domain names, server-side rendering, optimizing page titles and descriptions, setting OG tags, adding structured data, customizing 404 pages, setting up redirects, and handling hreflang. By employing these methods, users can effectively improve their website's visibility and ranking, attracting more organic traffic.
The "Beginner's Guide to SEO" is suitable for various website administrators, content creators, and digital marketers. Wheth…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Immerse</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SteamOS Reportedly Improves Lenovo Legion Go S Framerates]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=353986</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/353986/steamos-improves-lenovo-legion-go-s-framerates/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-27T05:56:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Lenovo Legion Go S handheld was released with Windows, with SteamOS being an alternative that’s coming later. It’s also the only device that’s officially “Powered by SteamOS” that’s not the Steam Deck. But if you need to choose between the two, it looks like the one that’s not running the Microsoft operating system is […]
The post SteamOS Reportedly Improves Lenovo Legion Go S Framerates appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ian Chee</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google Stitch System Prompt Leaked- Analysis and Insights]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/yang_ella_f2a3e16ccb54550/google-stitch-system-prompt-leaked-analysis-and-insights-23dp</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/yang_ella_f2a3e16ccb54550/google-stitch-system-prompt-leaked-analysis-and-insights-23dp"/>
        <updated>2025-05-27T05:36:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On May 24, 2025, a significant leak surfaced, revealing the system prompt for Google Stitch, a tool designed to assist with mobile and web UX/Product design. This prompt offers a rare glimpse into Google’s approach to designing intuitive and user-friendly interfaces. 

get the whole system prompt text at: google-stitch_20250524
leaked-system-prompts.com to view more AI system prompts (ChatGPT, claude 3.7, claude 4, grok, gemini, cursor, V0, manus, deepseek,bolt new, etc.).  
Google Stitch is an AI-driven tool tailored for UX/Product designers, specializing in creating and editing mobile and web interfaces. The leaked prompt outlines a system that provides structured guidance for designing single or multiple screens, ensuring consistency across platforms while adhering to specific design ru…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yang ella</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[My Introduction To this New Tech World]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/pawan_malakar_7f/my-introduction-to-this-new-tech-world-3j4f</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/pawan_malakar_7f/my-introduction-to-this-new-tech-world-3j4f"/>
        <updated>2025-05-27T05:36:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hey everyone I am new To this community. I am Coding enthusiast with learning and interacting with new problem arises. I am currently learning ReactJs and DSA with Java, SQl, Tailwind Css and MongoDb, ExpressJs some more. I need your help boost this process of learning and do something big in my tech carrer. 
Console.log("thank you for being here and Read this post.")]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pawan Malakar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft Defender for Business Explained: Antivirus, EDR, and Ransomware Protection for SMEs]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/roshan_karki_f2b61b26c3a8/microsoft-defender-for-business-explained-antivirus-edr-and-ransomware-protection-for-smes-2n08</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/roshan_karki_f2b61b26c3a8/microsoft-defender-for-business-explained-antivirus-edr-and-ransomware-protection-for-smes-2n08"/>
        <updated>2025-05-27T05:34:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Protect your small or mid-sized business with Microsoft Defender for Business an all-in-one security solution designed to detect, prevent, and respond to cyber threats in real time.
In today’s digital world, cyber threats are more advanced than ever. Whether you're running a remote team or managing a growing office, your business needs protection that’s both smart and affordable. Microsoft Defender for Business delivers enterprise-grade security tailored for small and medium-sized enterprises (SMEs) without the complexity.
Microsoft Defender for Business is a cloud-powered cybersecurity solution that protects your devices, users, and data from modern threats like malware, ransomware, phishing, and more. Designed for businesses with up to 300 employees, it combines antivirus, endpoint detec…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Roshan karki</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin long-term holders ‘quietly capitalizing’ with drop to $109K]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-long-term-holders-capitalizing-drop-109000</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-long-term-holders-capitalizing-drop-109000?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-27T05:31:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin markets recently experienced two major liquidation events, causing a cascade of forced selling from over-leveraged traders, but analysts say a distinct pattern has emerged.
“Overleveraged short-term traders were flushed out, long-term holders have been quietly capitalizing on the reset,” CryptoQuant analyst Amr Taha said on May 26. 
They noted the first flush occurred when Bitcoin (BTC) fell below $111,000, and over $97 million in long positions were liquidated. As its price broke $109,000, another $88 million in longs were wiped out in the second wave.
However, as short-term traders faced margin calls and forced selling, long-term holders (LTH) responded very differently and increased their accumulation.
This caused the long-term holder realized capitalization to surge past $28 bi…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Martin Young</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Understanding the trends of a Developer API]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/author_shivani_9c765c8db9/understanding-the-trends-of-a-developer-api-27a1</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/author_shivani_9c765c8db9/understanding-the-trends-of-a-developer-api-27a1"/>
        <updated>2025-05-27T05:30:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Developers need powerful tools to build, scale, and innovate quickly. One of the most essential tools in a developer's arsenal is a developer API (Application Programming Interface). Whether you're creating web apps, mobile platforms, or enterprise software, APIs streamline development by enabling seamless communication between systems.
What is a Developer API?
A developer API is a set of rules and protocols that allows different software applications to communicate with each other. It acts as a bridge between systems, enabling developers to access specific features or data without having to build everything from scratch. These APIs are designed with developers in mind, providing structured documentation, authentication methods, and error handling mechanisms.
For example, rather than build…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Author Shivani</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Cloud Isn’t Just a Buzzword, It’s a Business Breakthrough (If Done Right)]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/shlok-talepa/the-cloud-isnt-just-a-buzzword-its-a-business-breakthrough-if-done-right-35m1</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/shlok-talepa/the-cloud-isnt-just-a-buzzword-its-a-business-breakthrough-if-done-right-35m1"/>
        <updated>2025-05-27T05:26:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cloud computing isn’t just about spinning up a few EC2 instances or dumping data in S3. For today’s tech-forward organizations, especially startups and growing SMBs, the cloud is the foundation for speed, scale, and innovation.
Yet, more than 70% of cloud initiatives underperform or exceed budgets not because cloud doesn’t deliver, but because businesses jump in without a roadmap.
So, how do you get cloud adoption right?
We’ve helped scaleups, SaaS providers, fintechs, and manufacturers transition from scattered infrastructure to strategic cloud foundations. This post explains what a successful cloud adoption strategy should include and why skipping this step can cost you more than just compute hours.
Cloud Adoption: Why Strategy Beats Speed
It’s tempting to start with a “lift-and-shift” a…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shlok Talepa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Neon Pulse: Interactive Cyberpunk Dashboard UI]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/preetha_vaishnavi_2b82358/neon-pulse-interactive-cyberpunk-dashboard-ui-35ni</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/preetha_vaishnavi_2b82358/neon-pulse-interactive-cyberpunk-dashboard-ui-35ni"/>
        <updated>2025-05-27T05:26:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Check out this Pen I made!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>preetha vaishnavi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Required Skills For Developers In The AI IDE Era]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/hulk-pham/required-skills-for-developers-in-the-ai-ide-era-1eec</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/hulk-pham/required-skills-for-developers-in-the-ai-ide-era-1eec"/>
        <updated>2025-05-27T05:23:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Executive Summary


The software development landscape is undergoing a profound
In this new era, developers require a blended skill set, encompassing
1. Introduction: The Changing Landscape of Software Development



  
  
  1.1. The Evolution of IDEs and the Rise of AI Integration



Integrated Development Environments (IDEs) have undergone a significant
A significant consequence of this evolution is the democratization of
1.2. Transformative Impact of AI on Developer Workflows and Productivity


AI is acting as a powerful collaborator, boosting productivity,
This shift is not merely about doing tasks faster; it's a fundamental

2. AI-Powered IDEs: Core Functionalities and Benefits



2.1. Automated Code Generation, Completion, and Refactoring


AI-powered IDEs, such as GitHub Copilot, Cu…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hulk Pham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Faces Risk of Pullback to $100K as Momentum Indicator Diverges Bearishly: Technical Analysis]]></title>
        <id>b51d6459-1192-4ec2-925d-9a9367e41f9a</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/27/bitcoin-faces-risk-of-pullback-to-usd100k-as-momentum-indicator-diverges-bearishly-technical-analysis"/>
        <updated>2025-05-27T05:11:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin could fall out of its bullish channel, possibly testing support at $100,000, though the broader outlook remains positive.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Omkar Godbole</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Migos Instagram account hacked in apparent blackmail bid on Solana co-founder]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/migos-instagram-hacked-apparent-blackmail-on-solana-co-founder</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/migos-instagram-hacked-apparent-blackmail-on-solana-co-founder?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-27T05:07:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Instagram account of former US rap trio Migos was hacked in an apparent attempt to blackmail Solana co-founder Raj Gokal.
On May 27, Migos’ Instagram account posted at least seven images seen by Cointelegraph that have since been deleted. Two of the images appeared to depict Gokal holding up his passport and driver’s license, clearly showing the full details of each document.
The account’s hacker tagged Gokal in one of the images that apparently showed him with the caption “you should’ve paid the 40 btc,” while another image depicting Gokal was captioned “it was only 40 btc.. should’ve paid,” in what appears to be a references to a failed extortion attempt.
Another image posted by the account hacker shows what the caption claimed was Gokal’s wife holding up a driver’s license, while a …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Martin Young</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mesa3D Drivers for Windows]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/pal1000/mesa-dist-win</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/pal1000/mesa-dist-win"/>
        <updated>2025-05-27T04:52:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WhatsApp Teases Possibility Of iPad App]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=353981</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/353981/whatsapp-tease-ipad-app/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-27T04:41:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[WhatsApp users have been asking for official iPad version of the app for years and the company might finally fulfil this wish. Up until now, iPad users have had to either settle for the web version of the messaging platform, with the app only available for mobile and desktop. Earlier today on X, the messaging […]
The post WhatsApp Teases Possibility Of iPad App appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ikmal Rozlan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Saylor says onchain proof-of-reserves a ‘bad idea’ due to security risks]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/michael-saylor-says-proof-of-reserves-bad-idea</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/michael-saylor-says-proof-of-reserves-bad-idea?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-27T04:26:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Michael Saylor, the executive chair of major Bitcoin-buying firm Strategy, formerly MicroStrategy, says institutions posting onchain proof-of-reserves is a “bad idea” that could pose security risks.
“The current, conventional way to publish proof of reserves is an insecure proof of reserves,” Saylor said when asked about institutions adopting the transparency measure at a May 26 event on the sidelines of the Bitcoin 2025 conference in Las Vegas.
“It actually dilutes the security of the issuer, the custodians, the exchanges and the investors. It’s not a good idea, it’s a bad idea.”
Saylor didn’t answer whether Strategy would publish its proof-of-reserves when asked by Blockware Solutions head analyst Mitchell Askew whether his firm would do so.

I asked @saylor if @MicroStrategy has any pla…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Brayden Lindrea</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Samsung Galaxy A57 May Come With Exynos 1680 Chipset]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=353978</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/353978/samsung-galaxy-a57-may-come-with-exynos-1680-chipset/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-27T03:59:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Samsung is reportedly working on the successor of this year’s Galaxy A56 model, the A57. A machine translated report by Dutch news site Galaxy Club alleges that the phone will come equipped with Samsung’s upcoming Exynos 1680 chip. The SoC is apparently currently being tested under the model number S5E8865, codenamed Terra. As per the […]
The post Samsung Galaxy A57 May Come With Exynos 1680 Chipset appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Newsdesk</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Show HN: Lazy Tetris]]></title>
        <id>https://lazytetris.com/</id>
        <link href="https://lazytetris.com/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-27T03:58:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Apple Smart Home Hub May Launch As Soon As later This Year]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=353975</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/353975/apple-smart-home-hub-launch-later-this-year/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-27T03:19:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Previously, Apple had reportedly delayed its smart display, or smart home hub, due to issues with getting the Apple Intelligence-powered Siri upgrade to work as intended. While work on the products are still underway, it looks like there’s now a chance that the lower end model – the one without the robotic arm – may […]
The post Apple Smart Home Hub May Launch As Soon As later This Year appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ian Chee</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meta’s AI boss says current AI lacks ‘intelligent behavior’ — Report]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/meta-ai-boss-ai-lacks-intelligent-behavior-report</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/meta-ai-boss-ai-lacks-intelligent-behavior-report?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-27T03:16:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Current artificial intelligence models lack the major traits of human intelligence, Meta’s AI chief has reportedly said, claiming that the firm’s latest model will solve this issue. 
Business Insider reported on May 26 that at the AI Action Summit in Paris earlier this year, Meta chief AI scientist Yann LeCun said that “there are four essential characteristics of intelligent behavior that every animal, or relatively smart animal, can do, and certainly humans.” 
“Understanding the physical world, having persistent memory, being able to reason and being able to plan complex actions, particularly planning hierarchically,” LeCun said.
He said current large language models (LLMs) that power popular AI chatbots have not hit this threshold, and “incorporating these capabilities would require a sh…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Martin Young</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Redmagic 10S Pro Series Launches In China]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=353954</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/353954/redmagic-10s-pro-series-launches-in-china/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-27T02:54:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nubia sub-brand Redmagic has released its latest gaming smartphones, the Redmagic 10S Pro series, in China. The lineup features the Redmagic 10S Pro, as well as the Redmagic 10S Pro+, although the two models only differ in terms of battery and storage options. The phone sports a 6.85-inch 1.5K OLED display with a 144Hz refresh […]
The post Redmagic 10S Pro Series Launches In China appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nurul Kamil</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[iQOO Neo 10 Goes Global With Snapdragon 8s Gen 4, 7,000mAh Battery]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=353958</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/353958/iqoo-neo-10-global/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-27T02:44:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The global version of the iQOO Neo 10 has finally made its debut in India. Compared to the Chinese version, it gets a much bigger battery, a smaller primary sensor, an upgraded chipset, and a brighter display. The Neo 10 sports a 6.78-inch 1260×2800 AMOLED display with a whopping 144Hz refresh rate, a global peak […]
The post iQOO Neo 10 Goes Global With Snapdragon 8s Gen 4, 7,000mAh Battery appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ikmal Rozlan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Grammars of Formal Uncertainty]]></title>
        <id>https://arxiv.org/abs/2505.20047</id>
        <link href="https://arxiv.org/abs/2505.20047"/>
        <updated>2025-05-27T02:27:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Asia Morning Briefing: Thai Banks May Soon Hold Crypto, SCB10X CEO Signals Sandbox Push]]></title>
        <id>655bf965-959e-46e9-a42e-b1e14e29d232</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/26/asia-morning-briefing-thai-banks-may-soon-hold-crypto-scb10x-ceo-signals-sandbox-push"/>
        <updated>2025-05-27T02:09:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[PLUS: SCB10X's new CEO, Kaweewut Temphuwapat, predicts clearer regulations and fintech innovation in Thailand will drive stronger crypto deal flow across Southeast Asia.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>AI Boost</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[France’s Blockchain Group to buy 590 Bitcoin after bond sale]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/france-blockchain-group-buy-590-bitcoin-bond-sale</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/france-blockchain-group-buy-590-bitcoin-bond-sale?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-27T02:08:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Paris-based crypto company Blockchain Group is adding more Bitcoin to its growing treasury through a 63.3 million euro ($72 million) bond sale.
The company hopes to buy another 590 Bitcoin (BTC) with the funds, increasing its total holdings to 1,437 BTC, the Blockchain Group said on May 26.
Bitcoin is trading at over $109,00, and at current prices, the Blockchain Group could buy 658 BTC with the total amount it raised, according to CoinGecko.
However, the company said only 95% of the proceeds from the issuance will be used to buy Bitcoin; the remainder is marked for “operational expenses and to pay management fees.”
Source: Alexandre Laizet
Venture capital firm Fulgur Ventures invested the lion’s share for the bond sale, with 55.3 million euros ($62.9 million), while crypto private inv…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Stephen Katte</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Another suspect to surrender in NYC crypto torture case: Reports]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/another-suspect-turn-into-cops-new-york-crypto-case-reports</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/another-suspect-turn-into-cops-new-york-crypto-case-reports?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-27T01:55:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A second person suspected of being involved in a high-profile crypto kidnapping case in New York City is expected to turn himself in to police, according to several reports.
The second man is a Swiss crypto investor who allegedly assisted business partner Joel Woeltz, who is accused of kidnapping Michael Valentino Teofrasto Carturan and torturing him in a Soho apartment in an attempt to pressure him into revealing his crypto wallet phrase, ABC7 New York reported on May 26.
A separate NBC report said the Swiss trader —  who is not named — would turn himself over to police within a week. However, FOX5 New York reported that the man may already be in custody, citing conflicting sources.
The New York Post reported that the man is the co-founder of a Swiss trading firm.
Woeltz, known as the “cr…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Brayden Lindrea</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amir Hamzah: RON95 Fuel Subsidy Rationalisation Set For Second Half Of 2025]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=353952</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/353952/amir-hamzah-ron95-fuel-subsidy-rationalisation-second-half-2025/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-27T01:54:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Malaysian government is on track to implement the rationalisation of RON95 petrol subsidies in the second half of 2025, Finance Minister II Datuk Seri Amir Hamzah Azizan confirmed. The move forms part of broader efforts to ensure that subsidies are more efficiently targeted to benefit those in genuine need. Speaking after officiating the Malaysian […]
The post Amir Hamzah: RON95 Fuel Subsidy Rationalisation Set For Second Half Of 2025 appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Heirul Kamel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The UI future is colourful and dimensional]]></title>
        <id>https://www.flarup.email/p/the-future-is-colourful-and-dimensional</id>
        <link href="https://www.flarup.email/p/the-future-is-colourful-and-dimensional"/>
        <updated>2025-05-27T01:23:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Yes-rs: A fast, memory-safe rewrite of the classic Unix yes command]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/jedisct1/yes-rs</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/jedisct1/yes-rs"/>
        <updated>2025-05-27T01:20:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Home Minister’s WhatsApp Account Hacked]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=353949</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/353949/home-minister-whatsapp-account-hacked/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-27T01:18:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The WhatsApp account of Home Minister Datuk Seri Saifuddin Nasution Ismail was hacked on Monday by an “unidentified and irresponsible party”. The incident has prompted immediate investigation by the authorities. According to an statement issued by the Office of the Home Minister’s official Facebook page, the breach has been reported to the relevant enforcement agencies […]
The post Home Minister’s WhatsApp Account Hacked appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Heirul Kamel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitlayer secures 31.5% of Bitcoin&#039;s hashrate to bring smart contracts to BTC]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitlayer-secures-40-of-bitcoin-s-hashrate-to-bring-smart-contracts-to-btc</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitlayer-secures-40-of-bitcoin-s-hashrate-to-bring-smart-contracts-to-btc?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-27T01:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitlayer’s Bitcoin smart-contract system is being implemented by mining pools behind 31.5% of the network’s hashrate, a development that will help ensure that its system will operate on the Bitcoin blockchain, the company said.
According to a May 27 announcement shared with Cointelegraph, Bitlayer’s BitVM implementation will be supported by major Bitcoin (BTC) mining pools including Antpool, F2Pool, and SpiderPool. Antpool CEO Andy Chow said:
"Antpool has become the bridge operator for Bitlayer to support Bitcoin innovation and protect miners’ interests.”
BitVM (Bitcoin Virtual Machine) is a framework that enables complex smart contracts to be deployed on the Bitcoin blockchain without changing the base protocol. The idea was introduced by Robin Linux in 2023, and allows for the complex co…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Adrian Zmudzinski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Calendars, Contacts and Files in Stalwart]]></title>
        <id>https://stalw.art/blog/collaboration/</id>
        <link href="https://stalw.art/blog/collaboration/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-27T01:11:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitlayer Joins Forces With Antpool, F2Pool, and SpiderPool to Supercharge Bitcoin DeFi]]></title>
        <id>ffb52dbd-7590-4b39-bf09-90b1f0e42d20</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2025/05/27/bitlayer-joins-forces-with-antpool-f2pool-and-spiderpool-to-supercharge-bitcoin-defi"/>
        <updated>2025-05-27T01:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitlayer has partnered with major Bitcoin mining pools to promote the adoption of BitVM, a technology enabling Bitcoin-native DeFi.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Omkar Godbole</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FromSoft's singular mech game Chromehounds is back online]]></title>
        <id>https://www.readonlymemo.com/interview-15-years-after-the-servers-shut-down-fromsofts-singular-mech-game-chromehounds-is-back-online/</id>
        <link href="https://www.readonlymemo.com/interview-15-years-after-the-servers-shut-down-fromsofts-singular-mech-game-chromehounds-is-back-online/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-27T00:52:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Here’s what happened in crypto today]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/what-happened-in-crypto-today</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/what-happened-in-crypto-today?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-26T22:02:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today in crypto, Dubai has launched the Middle East’s first tokenized real estate project. Meanwhile, a crypto investor lost $2.6 million after falling victim to two phishing scams. In US politics, House Speaker Mike Johnson dismissed concerns over President Donald Trump’s memecoin dinner.
Dubai launches first licensed tokenized real estate project in MENA region
Dubai has launched the first licensed tokenized real estate project in the Middle East and North Africa (MENA) region, previewing appetite for real-world tokenization in one of the world’s burgeoning crypto hubs.
Partners in the project include the Dubai Land Department (DLD), the Central Bank of the United Arab Emirates, and the Dubai Future Foundation, according to an announcement from the Dubai government. The tokens will be tr…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Cointelegraph</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Power Failure: The downfall of General Electric]]></title>
        <id>https://www.gwintrob.com/power-failure-review/</id>
        <link href="https://www.gwintrob.com/power-failure-review/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-26T21:54:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dubai launches first licensed tokenized real estate project in MENA region]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/dubai-launches-first-licensed-tokenized-real-estate-project-in-mena-region</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/dubai-launches-first-licensed-tokenized-real-estate-project-in-mena-region?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-26T21:43:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dubai has launched the first licensed tokenized real estate project in the Middle East and North Africa (MENA) region, previewing appetite for real-world tokenization in one of the world’s burgeoning crypto hubs.
Partners in the project include the Dubai Land Department (DLD), the Central Bank of the United Arab Emirates, and the Dubai Future Foundation, according to an announcement from the Dubai government. The tokens will be tradeable on the newly launched “Prypco Mint” platform, with Zand Digital Bank appointed as the bank for the project’s pilot phase.
On May 19, Dubai’s Virtual Assets Regulatory Authority (VARA) updated its rules to include real-world asset (RWA) tokenization, allowing such tokens to be traded on secondary markets.
Related: UAE saw 41% increase in crypto app download…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Christopher Tepedino</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Highlights from the Claude 4 system prompt]]></title>
        <id>https://simonwillison.net/2025/May/25/claude-4-system-prompt/</id>
        <link href="https://simonwillison.net/2025/May/25/claude-4-system-prompt/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-26T21:25:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Get PC BIOS back on UEFI only system]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/FlyGoat/csmwrap</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/FlyGoat/csmwrap"/>
        <updated>2025-05-26T21:25:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin stalls at $110K but institutional investors continue gobbling up BTC]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-stalls-at-110k-but-institutional-investors-continue-gobbling-up-btc</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-stalls-at-110k-but-institutional-investors-continue-gobbling-up-btc?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-26T21:00:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Key takeaways:

Bitcoin is stuck below $110,000 due to macroeconomic uncertainty and as Nvidia earnings anticipation caps risk appetite.

Strong spot BTC ETF inflows and Bitcoin options data are hints that US economic clarity could unlock BTC highs.

Investor sentiment improved on May 26 after US President Donald Trump postponed his retaliatory European Union 50% tariffs on imports. European stock markets responded positively to the development, but Bitcoin (BTC) was unable to hold the $110,000 level, leading traders to question whether a new all-time high remains within reach.
Even if Bitcoin revisits the $105,000 mark, rising institutional interest and robust derivatives markets indicate that bullish traders are neither overleveraged nor concerned about a potential correction.
Bitcoin 2-…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Marcel Pechman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto industry urges SEC to clarify staking stance]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/crypto-industry-groups-urge-sec-to-clarify-staking-stance</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/crypto-industry-groups-urge-sec-to-clarify-staking-stance?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-26T20:49:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency industry groups are urging the US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) to issue formal guidance on staking, citing continued regulatory uncertainty for Web3 infrastructure providers, according to Allison Muehr, head of staking policy for the Crypto Council for Innovation, a trade group.
Clarifying the SEC’s position on staking has become a top priority for the crypto industry, Muehr said during Solana’s Accelerate conference in New York.
“We’re about 25% of the way there,” Muehr said. “The SEC has done more constructive engagement with us in the past four months than in the last four years, but we still don’t have formal staking guidance.”
Allison Muehr, right, the Crypto Council for Innovation’s head of staking policy, speaks at Accelerate. Source: Cointelegraph
Related…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Alex O’Donnell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Owls in Towels]]></title>
        <id>https://owlsintowels.org/</id>
        <link href="https://owlsintowels.org/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-26T20:27:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Rally Stalls Below $110K as Short-Term Holders Take $11B Profits]]></title>
        <id>908b48b0-72b6-492c-bf7d-f2555ffdb9a9</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/26/bitcoin-rally-stalls-below-110k-as-short-term-holders-take-11b-profits"/>
        <updated>2025-05-26T19:58:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Most U.S. markets were closed for Monday's holiday, but European stocks reacted positively to Trump's moratorium on 50% tariffs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Krisztian Sandor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Difference Between Downloading and Streaming]]></title>
        <id>https://danq.me/2025/05/26/downloading-vs-streaming/</id>
        <link href="https://danq.me/2025/05/26/downloading-vs-streaming/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-26T19:56:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trying to teach in the age of the AI homework machine]]></title>
        <id>https://www.solarshades.club/p/dispatch-from-the-trenches-of-the</id>
        <link href="https://www.solarshades.club/p/dispatch-from-the-trenches-of-the"/>
        <updated>2025-05-26T19:20:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[From disruption to reinvention: How knowledge workers can thrive after AI]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008969</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/from-disruption-to-reinvention-how-knowledge-workers-can-thrive-after-ai/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-26T19:05:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We are beginning a cognitive migration: Away from what AI now does well, and toward a redefinition of what humans are now made for.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gary Grossman, Edelman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Price predictions 5/26: SPX, DXY, BTC, ETH, XRP, BNB, SOL, DOGE, ADA, HYPE]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/price-predictions-5-26-spx-dxy-btc-eth-xrp-bnb-sol-doge-ada-hype</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/price-predictions-5-26-spx-dxy-btc-eth-xrp-bnb-sol-doge-ada-hype?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-26T18:52:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Key points:

Bitcoin ETPs continue to witness solid buying, signaling that the bulls expect the uptrend to continue.

Several major altcoins witnessed a pullback, but lower levels continue to attract buyers.

Bitcoin (BTC) is attempting to sustain above $109,588, indicating buying on every minor dip. Bitcoin has risen for seven consecutive weeks, and if buyers can extend the streak to eight weeks, it clears the path for further upside. Crypto analyst and trader Carpe Noctom said in a post on X that Bitcoin has only seen three instances of eight consecutive weekly positive closes, and every time, Bitcoin has been higher in the following six- and 12-month time period.
Institutional investors sense a long-term opportunity and, hence, have continued to pump money into Bitcoin exchange-traded p…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Rakesh Upadhyay</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lossless video compression using Bloom filters]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/ross39/new_bloom_filter_repo/blob/main/README.md</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/ross39/new_bloom_filter_repo/blob/main/README.md"/>
        <updated>2025-05-26T18:32:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CSS Minecraft]]></title>
        <id>https://benjaminaster.com/css-minecraft/</id>
        <link href="https://benjaminaster.com/css-minecraft/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-26T18:28:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trump Media Group denies it’s raising $3B for crypto buys: Report]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/trump-media-group-raise-3b-buy-bitcoin-crypto</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/trump-media-group-raise-3b-buy-bitcoin-crypto?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-26T18:27:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Update (May 26, 9:27 pm UTC): This article has been updated to include a statement from Truth Media and Technology Group.
Trump Media and Technology Group, the company behind US President Donald Trump’s Truth Social platform, has rebuffed a report that it’s planning to raise $3 billion in a mix of equity and convertible bonds to buy Bitcoin and other cryptocurrencies.
The Financial Times reported the company’s plan on May 26, citing six people briefed on the matter, but Trump Media told the outlet that, “apparently the Financial Times has dumb writers listening to even dumber sources.”
Trump Media did not immediately respond to Cointelegraph’s request for comment.
If Trump Media implements the reported plan, it would position the company to follow the footsteps of crypto-buying companies l…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Christopher Tepedino</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TSMC bets on unorthodox optical tech]]></title>
        <id>https://spectrum.ieee.org/microled-optical-chiplet</id>
        <link href="https://spectrum.ieee.org/microled-optical-chiplet"/>
        <updated>2025-05-26T17:15:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trump Media Seeks to Raise $3B for Crypto Purchase: FT]]></title>
        <id>94d625e6-ed90-4546-a2b0-f141b0b28702</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2025/05/26/trump-media-seeks-to-raise-3b-for-crypto-purchase-ft"/>
        <updated>2025-05-26T17:00:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The capital raise would see the Trump-linked firm joining a slew of public companies following the playbook of Michael Saylor's Strategy.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Krisztian Sandor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Show HN: PgDog – Shard Postgres without extensions]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/pgdogdev/pgdog</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/pgdogdev/pgdog"/>
        <updated>2025-05-26T16:55:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hacker News now runs on top of Common Lisp]]></title>
        <id>https://lisp-journey.gitlab.io/blog/hacker-news-now-runs-on-top-of-common-lisp/</id>
        <link href="https://lisp-journey.gitlab.io/blog/hacker-news-now-runs-on-top-of-common-lisp/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-26T16:37:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin bulls start Memorial Day blitz on $110K — Will spot follow when US markets open?]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-bulls-start-memorial-day-blitz-on-110k-will-spot-follow-when-us-markets-open</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-bulls-start-memorial-day-blitz-on-110k-will-spot-follow-when-us-markets-open?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-26T16:34:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Key takeaways: 

Bitcoin price is capped at the $110,000 level due to sellers and a decrease in spot volumes. Leverage use is driving current rallies into this resistance level.

Traders are watching today’s volumes to see if emerging intraday trends are followed at the US open on May 27.

Bitcoin (BTC) price staged a mild recovery over the weekend, but gains above $110,000 are being capped by selling. Data from Glassnode shows “net distribution” (selling) from the cohort holding more than 10,000 Bitcoin, but cohorts below this level have continued to accumulate. 
Trend accumulation score. Source: X / Glassnode
The spot and futures cumulative volume delta at Binance exchange reflect persistent selling when BTC price approaches the $110,000 level.
BTC/USDT 4-hour chart CVD (spot and futures…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Big Smokey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Decentralized AI could be ‘bigger than Bitcoin’ — DNA Fund CEO Chris Miglino]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/decentralized-ai-bittensor-dna-fund-ceo</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/decentralized-ai-bittensor-dna-fund-ceo?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-26T16:25:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Some of blockchain’s earliest adopters are now deeply “entrenching” themselves in decentralized AI, with ecosystems like Bittensor (TAO) emerging as growth engines. These platforms are reshaping traditional venture capital models, enabling the best ideas to organically attract community support, staking and liquidity without the need for institutional gatekeepers.
That was one of the key takeaways from Cointelegraph’s interview with Chris Miglino, the co-founder and CEO of DNA Fund, a digital asset investment firm he runs alongside fellow serial entrepreneurs Brock Peirce and Scott Walker.
DNA Fund manages, among other things, five distinct funds across a range of strategies, such as a high-yield fund, an algorithmic trading fund, an AI compute fund, a liquid token fund and a venture fund …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Sam Bourgi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dubai Unveils Real Estate Tokenization Platform on XRP Ledger Amid $16B Initiative]]></title>
        <id>8b17001f-746f-4ccd-80c7-e70d30e185e6</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2025/05/26/dubai-unveils-real-estate-tokenization-platform-on-xrp-ledger-amid-usd16b-initiative"/>
        <updated>2025-05-26T16:05:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The new platform lets investors buy fractional ownership in Dubai property, with title deeds tokenized on the XRP Ledger network.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Krisztian Sandor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Launch HN: Nomi (YC X25) – Copilot for Sales]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=44098706</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=44098706"/>
        <updated>2025-05-26T16:05:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sam Bankman-Fried’s Prison Sentence Could Be Cut by Over 4 Years: Business Insider]]></title>
        <id>74f27ad0-7c9e-4a02-b567-7fda75d5522d</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2025/05/26/sam-bankman-frieds-prison-sentence-could-be-cut-by-over-4-years-business-insider"/>
        <updated>2025-05-26T15:50:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[His sentence could be reduced due to accumulated “Good Conduct Time” and participation in prison programs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Francisco Rodrigues</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum Surges 5% to Break $2,550 Resistance Amid Institutional Confidence]]></title>
        <id>d8655cee-8df1-4443-b1f9-add2ccac8eb2</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/26/ethereum-surges-5-to-break-usd2-550-resistance-amid-institutional-confidence"/>
        <updated>2025-05-26T15:37:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum breaks $2,550 with bullish momentum as traders eye $2,800, defying macro uncertainty and gaining strength from strong demand zones below.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>AI Boost</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WavePhoenix – open-source implementation of the Nintendo WaveBird protocol]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/loopj/wavephoenix</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/loopj/wavephoenix"/>
        <updated>2025-05-26T15:37:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Musk confirms X Money beta testing ahead of planned 2025 launch]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/elon-musk-confirms-x-money-beta-testing-launch-2025</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/elon-musk-confirms-x-money-beta-testing-launch-2025?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-26T15:33:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[X Money, the payment and banking app tipped by Elon Musk in 2022 after he acquired Twitter, has started beta testing, Musk confirmed in an X post on May 25.
Tesla Owners Silicon Valley, a fan X account focused on Elon Musk and Tesla, took to X on May 25 to report that Musk has confirmed that X is “launching X Money soon.”
Source: Elon Musk
The billionaire businessman subsequently jumped on the X thread to confirm the news, writing that the test will be a “very limited access beta at first.”
“When people’s saving are involved, extreme care must be taken,” he wrote.
X Money expects to launch in 2025
Musk’s confirmation comes amid X Money’s planned launch this year, according to the platform’s X account.
Source: X Money
Musk’s silent confirmation of X Money trials followed a series of reports…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Helen Partz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BlackRock issues rare warning: Is Bitcoin’s future at risk from quantum tech?]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/explained/blackrock-issues-rare-warning-is-bitcoins-future-at-risk-from-quantum-tech</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/explained/blackrock-issues-rare-warning-is-bitcoins-future-at-risk-from-quantum-tech?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-26T15:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BlackRock Bitcoin warning            
            
                
In a rare move, BlackRock has quietly added a new line to its iShares Bitcoin Trust (IBIT) filing — and it is turning heads. The update, submitted in early May 2025, flags quantum computing as a potential risk to Bitcoin’s long-term security.
The filing specifically warns that if quantum tech advances far enough, it could break the cryptographic systems that secure Bitcoin. 
In their words, it could “undermine the viability” of the cryptographic algorithms used not just in digital assets but across the global tech stack.
It’s the first time you’ve seen the world’s largest asset manager call out this threat so directly in a Bitcoin-related disclosure, and it says a lot about how seriously institutional players are starting …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Bradley Peak</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Binance Square Starts Livestream for Traders, Taking on Other Social Media Platforms]]></title>
        <id>75fac5dc-52ca-44c2-a7ce-9bb7ad01489b</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/tech/2025/05/26/binance-square-starts-livestream-for-traders-taking-on-other-social-media-platforms"/>
        <updated>2025-05-26T15:03:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Users will be able to watch experienced traders execute their strategies live.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tom Carreras</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AI needs better human data, not bigger models]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/ai-needs-better-human-data-not-bigger-models</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/ai-needs-better-human-data-not-bigger-models?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-26T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Opinion by: Rowan Stone, CEO at Sapien
AI is a paper tiger without human expertise in data management and training practices. Despite massive growth projections, AI innovations won’t be relevant if they continue training models based on poor-quality data. 
Besides improving data standards, AI models need human intervention for contextual understanding and critical thinking to ensure ethical AI development and correct output generation.
AI has a “bad data” problem
Humans have nuanced awareness. They draw on their experiences to make inferences and logical decisions. AI models are, however, only as good as their training data.
An AI model’s accuracy doesn’t entirely depend on the underlying algorithms’ technical sophistication or the amount of data processed. Instead, accurate AI performance…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Rowan Stone</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Veteran capital in crypto is shaping South Korea’s elections]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/crypto-south-korea-elections</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/crypto-south-korea-elections?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-26T14:47:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency has emerged as a defining issue in South Korea’s snap presidential election, with candidates vying for support from a growing base of digital asset investors across generations.
All three front-runners have rolled out crypto-friendly proposals. These include the legalization of spot Bitcoin (BTC) exchange-traded funds (ETFs) and the easing of banking rules that currently restrict fiat-to-crypto trading to just five platforms.
The June 3 vote is slated to come around two years early, triggered by the impeachment of former president Yoon Suk-yeol after his controversial declaration of martial law in late 2024. Though quickly overturned by lawmakers, the abrupt power grab led to a political crisis and his eventual removal from office.
Yoon’s 2022 campaign leaned heavily on prom…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Yohan Yun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ASUS ROG Flow Z13 2025 Review: This Tablet Laptop Games Hard]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=350205</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/350205/asus-rog-flow-z13-2025-review/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-26T14:28:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The ASUS ROG Flow Z13 2025 is this year’s contender for the award of being an engineering marvel, by my standards at least. That, by the way, is due more to the AMD APU that serves as the heart of this portable machine. Specifications Design And Functionality It’s safe to say that a fair bit […]
The post ASUS ROG Flow Z13 2025 Review: This Tablet Laptop Games Hard appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John Law</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[10 red flags that scream ‘fake airdrop,’ and how to avoid them]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/fake-airdrops-and-how-to-avoid-them</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/fake-airdrops-and-how-to-avoid-them?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-26T13:59:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Key takeaways

In 2024 and 2025, fake airdrop scams targeting Hamster Kombat, Wall Street Pepe and others led to millions in user losses, contributing to over $9.9 billion in global crypto scam damages.

Fake airdrops impersonate legitimate projects, tricking users into revealing private keys, signing malicious contracts or paying upfront fees that lead to irreversible crypto theft.

Warning signs include no official announcement, suspicious URLs, requests for private keys, grammar errors and unrealistic reward promises.

Future airdrops are shifting toward activity-based, retroactive and AI-monitored models that reward genuine user engagement while reducing exploitation.

While cryptocurrency airdrops are a legitimate way for projects to gain publicity and users, scammers exploit this hyp…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Dilip Kumar Patairya</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to set up stop-loss and take-profit orders]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/how-to-set-up-stop-loss-and-take-profit-orders</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/how-to-set-up-stop-loss-and-take-profit-orders?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-26T13:48:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Key takeaways

Bitcoin and crypto traders can rely on automated orders on their trading platform to limit losses and secure gains.

Stop-loss orders in Bitcoin trading started as manual risk management in the early 2010s. Now, they have become advanced, automated tools on today’s exchanges.


In the algorithm era and bot pestering, proper trading tools like stop-loss and take-profit orders will help you protect your trades.

Setting up advanced BTC trading strategies doesn’t guarantee a successful risk management plan. Monitoring the market regularly helps you understand current conditions. This way, you can avoid strategic mistakes.

Stop-loss and take-profit orders in trading were used long before Bitcoin. In traditional financial markets, they were already used as a risk management and …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Emi Lacapra</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub MCP exploited: Accessing private repositories via MCP]]></title>
        <id>https://invariantlabs.ai/blog/mcp-github-vulnerability</id>
        <link href="https://invariantlabs.ai/blog/mcp-github-vulnerability"/>
        <updated>2025-05-26T13:46:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin’s new highs may have been driven by Japan bond market crisis]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-all-time-high-by-japanese-bond-market-crisis</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-all-time-high-by-japanese-bond-market-crisis?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-26T13:37:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin’s recent all-time high may be linked to ongoing issues in the Japanese bond market, possibly signaling BTC’s growing recognition as a hedge against instability in the traditional financial (TradFi) system.
Bitcoin’s (BTC) price rose to a new all-time high of $112,000 on May 22, before retracing to change hands above $109,700 at the time of writing on May 26, Cointelegraph data shows.
While some attributed the rally to geopolitical developments, including US President Donald Trump’s announcement of Russia–Ukraine ceasefire talks on May 19, macroeconomic factors appear to be playing a larger role, according to market analysts.
BTC/USD, 1-year chart. Source: Cointelegraph
Japan bonds hit yield record
Bitwise’s head of European research, André Dragosch, pointed to growing concerns arou…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Zoltan Vardai</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A new class of materials that can passively harvest water from air]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.seas.upenn.edu/penn-engineers-discover-a-new-class-of-materials-that-passively-harvest-water-from-air/</id>
        <link href="https://blog.seas.upenn.edu/penn-engineers-discover-a-new-class-of-materials-that-passively-harvest-water-from-air/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-26T13:14:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to read Bitcoin candlestick charts (no experience needed)]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/how-to-read-bitcoin-candlestick-charts</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/how-to-read-bitcoin-candlestick-charts?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-26T13:12:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Key takeaways

Bitcoin candlesticks are a popular tool among Bitcoin traders because they’re simple to use and offer an intuitive way to understand market sentiment and trends.

Bitcoin candlesticks are a rather old tool. Rice trader Honma Munehisa invented them in Japan as far back as the 18th century. They were introduced to Western financial markets in the late 1980s.

They help you understand bullish and bearish patterns in technical analysis. This knowledge will get you started with Bitcoin trading.

They should not be your only tool for making informed decisions. Combine them with other Bitcoin technical indicators, such as MAs (moving averages) or the RSI (relative strength index). 

If you’re new to Bitcoin (BTC) trading, you may wonder when to buy or sell. Candlestick charts, like…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Emi Lacapra</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[In Final Days of Senate Stablecoin Debate, Trump's Crypto Ties to Remain in Spotlight]]></title>
        <id>bfea2075-5d59-4681-bdf9-57c5dfc55a00</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2025/05/23/in-final-days-of-senate-stablecoin-debate-trump-s-crypto-ties-to-remain-in-spotlight"/>
        <updated>2025-05-26T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Though the U.S. stablecoin bill is widely expected to clear its biggest hurdle soon, Trump's crypto interests will be targeted with an attempted amendment.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jesse Hamilton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pakistan appoints special assistant to PM on blockchain and crypto]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/pakistan-appoints-special-asstant-to-pm-on-blockchain-and-crypto</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/pakistan-appoints-special-asstant-to-pm-on-blockchain-and-crypto?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-26T12:46:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Pakistan Prime Minister Shehbaz Sharif appointed Pakistan Crypto Council CEO Bilal Bin Saqib as his special assistant on blockchain and crypto.
Saqib’s appointment takes effect immediately under Rule 4(6) of the Rules of Business, 1973. He has been granted the status of minister of state and will serve without salary or official benefits, according to a May 26 report in the English-language local news outlet, Pakistan Observer.
The move follows a series of government initiatives aimed at strengthening Pakistan’s presence in the digital asset space. Just one day prior, Pakistan allocated 2,000 megawatts of surplus electricity exclusively for Bitcoin mining and artificial intelligence centers.
In mid-May, Pakistan’s Ministry of Finance also endorsed the creation of a dedicated body to regula…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Adrian Zmudzinski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Solana following Bitcoin? Network activity, chart pattern point to $300 SOL price]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/solana-seguindo-o-bitcoin-atividade-da-rede-e-padrao-grafico-apontam-para-sol-a-us-300</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/solana-seguindo-o-bitcoin-atividade-da-rede-e-padrao-grafico-apontam-para-sol-a-us-300?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-26T12:45:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Key takeaways:

Solana's $9.4 billion TVL is a 54% increase since April 7.

Solana’s memecoin daily trading volume has more than doubled since early April. 

A bullish V-shaped recovery pattern projects SOL price to rise toward $300.

Solana’s native token, SOL, surged 86% between April 7 and May 26, following a broader altcoin market rally that also saw Bitcoin hit new all-time highs above $111,000. 
Since then, SOL has struggled to break above $180, but onchain and technical data still suggest further gains are in store for the altcoin. Can SOL hit all-time highs above $300?
Solana’s TVL up 54% since April 7
The total value locked (TVL) on the Solana blockchain has increased by over 54% to $9.44 billion on May 26 from multimonth lows of $6.12 billion on April 7. It’s also up by almost 20…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Nancy Lubale</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Strategy Buys 4,020 Bitcoin for $427M, Bringing Total Stash to Over 580,000 BTC]]></title>
        <id>34ac3134-8655-4677-9fe4-2077ae2fd57c</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/26/strategy-buys-4020-bitcoin-for-427m-brings-total-stash-to-over-580000-btc"/>
        <updated>2025-05-26T12:35:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Strategy, the largest corporate holder of bitcoin, has funded its latest acquisition through three different at-the-market programs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Francisco Rodrigues</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Particle Life simulation in browser using WebGPU]]></title>
        <id>https://lisyarus.github.io/blog/posts/particle-life-simulation-in-browser-using-webgpu.html</id>
        <link href="https://lisyarus.github.io/blog/posts/particle-life-simulation-in-browser-using-webgpu.html"/>
        <updated>2025-05-26T12:28:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pakistan Taps Surplus Power Capacity to Fuel Bitcoin Mining, AI Data Centers]]></title>
        <id>b65306c0-1b69-451d-8f51-fd72a896ec79</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2025/05/26/pakistan-taps-surplus-power-capacity-to-fuel-bitcoin-mining-ai-data-centers"/>
        <updated>2025-05-26T12:18:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The country plans on utilizing surplus energy from coal-fired power plants that are currently operating at 15% capacity to mine bitcoin.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Francisco Rodrigues</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Strategy bags 4,020 Bitcoin as price briefly breaks $110K]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/strategy-bags-bitcoin-price-record-past-110</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/strategy-bags-bitcoin-price-record-past-110?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-26T12:10:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Michael Saylor’s Strategy, the world’s largest corporate Bitcoin investor, bagged a fresh stash of BTC as the price briefly surged above $110,000 last week.
Strategy acquired 4,020 Bitcoin (BTC) for $427.1 million between May 19 and 23, the company announced on May 26.
The latest purchases were made at an average price of $106,237 per coin, with Bitcoin smashing past $110,000 on May 22.
The acquisition marked the fourth Bitcoin purchase by Strategy in May, bringing Strategy’s total BTC holdings to 580,250 BTC, acquired for about $40.6 billion at an average price of $69,979 per coin.
Strategy director sells 2,650 MSTR shares
Strategy’s new Bitcoin acquisition followed a series of Class A sales by Strategy director Jarrod Patten.
According to a Strategy report of the proposed sale of securit…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Helen Partz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hedera Africa Hackathon launches with $1M prize pool and Web3 focus]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/hedera-launches-hackathon-in-africa-to-uncover-emerging-talents</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/hedera-launches-hackathon-in-africa-to-uncover-emerging-talents?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-26T12:07:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Hashgraph Association and the Exponential Science Foundation have launched the Hedera Africa Hackathon 2025, a global event designed to accelerate Web3 and artificial intelligence adoption across the African continent. 
With a prize pool of $1 million, the hackathon will run from Aug. 1 to Sept. 30 and aims to attract over 10,000 participants across 15 African countries, according to a news release shared with Cointelegraph.
Organized by two nonprofit organizations — the Switzerland-based Hashgraph Association and the tech research-focused Exponential Science Foundation — the event is open to developers, students and entrepreneurs worldwide.
“We aim to use technologies that converge Web3 with AI to create transparent cognitive solutions that optimize processes and facilitate decision-m…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Lyne Qian</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum co-founder responds to Sweden’s cashless-society rethink]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/ethereum-alternative-sweden-cashless-plans</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/ethereum-alternative-sweden-cashless-plans?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-26T11:51:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As Sweden reconsiders its push toward a cashless society, Ethereum co-founder Vitalik Buterin highlighted the fragility of centralized digital payments and the opportunity presented by decentralized payment alternatives. 
In recent years, Sweden has led the charge toward a cashless future, with digital payment platforms becoming widespread. However, as concerns over cyber-threats, civil defense and instability have emerged, Swedish authorities are now actively encouraging citizens to keep some cash. 
Buterin noted the reversal illustrates that while centralized solutions may be efficient, they may not be reliable during times of crisis. 
“Nordics are walking back the cashless society initiative because their centralized implementation of the concept is too fragile,” Buterin wrote, citing a…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Ezra Reguerra</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TIL: timeout in Bash scripts]]></title>
        <id>https://heitorpb.github.io/bla/timeout/</id>
        <link href="https://heitorpb.github.io/bla/timeout/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-26T11:34:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[U.S. Crypto Investor Charged With Kidnapping and Torturing Victim Over Bitcoin]]></title>
        <id>3af78c88-d8aa-4858-bdff-b816459d0f86</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2025/05/26/u-s-crypto-investor-charged-with-kidnapping-and-torturing-victim-over-bitcoin"/>
        <updated>2025-05-26T11:23:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The investor, John Woeltz, allegedly held an Italian man captive in a $30K-a-month townhouse to steal his crypto.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Francisco Rodrigues</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Monero's Market Cap Flips Litecoin and Toncoin as XMR Enters Top 25 Tokens]]></title>
        <id>1509187a-b7da-4ed5-977a-3efa198161df</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/26/monero-s-market-cap-flips-litecoin-and-toncoin-as-xmr-enters-top-25-tokens"/>
        <updated>2025-05-26T10:10:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Monero's price has more than doubled this year.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Omkar Godbole</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dogecoin Extends Rally as Whale Accumulation Signals Growing Confidence]]></title>
        <id>7846ad46-5c02-44c6-acf4-3a934dc74ae4</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/26/dogecoin-extends-rally-as-whale-accumulation-signals-growing-confidence"/>
        <updated>2025-05-26T09:07:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The meme cryptocurrency breaks key resistance levels with strong volume, showing resilience as economic uncertainties push investors toward alternative assets.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>AI Boost</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[James Wynn, the Trader Who Bet $1B on Bitcoin, Is Now Long Pepe]]></title>
        <id>716db076-6d32-4071-9a4b-193eaf3d7c13</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/26/james-wynn-the-trader-who-bet-1b-on-bitcoin-is-now-long-pepe"/>
        <updated>2025-05-26T08:10:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The pseudonymous trader on Hyperliquid closed their billion-dollar notional position for a $17 million loss over the weekend and is now betting on downside.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shaurya Malwa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bearish Bets on Strategy Look Alluring, Says 10X Research as MSTR Diverges From Bitcoin's Bull Run]]></title>
        <id>f9a3bf05-91c2-423c-887e-586ed360ea48</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/26/bearish-bets-on-strategy-look-alluring-says-10x-research-as-mstr-diverges-from-bitcoin-s-bull-run"/>
        <updated>2025-05-26T07:57:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Despite bitcoin reaching record highs, MSTR's stock price has stalled, indicating waning investor enthusiasm.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Omkar Godbole</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SHIB Surges 5% After Mid-Day Dip, Defying Economic Tensions]]></title>
        <id>602f82da-6044-436d-a2aa-7b235c1a8820</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/26/shib-surges-5-after-mid-day-dip-defying-economic-tensions"/>
        <updated>2025-05-26T06:41:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Market volatility creates buying opportunity as Shiba Inu's SHIB token demonstrates remarkable resilience despite broader uncertainty.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>AI Boost</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Regains $110K After Weekend Sell-Off; ADA, DOGE Lead Uptick in Crypto Majors]]></title>
        <id>29272417-7a40-45d1-a190-3bf4038d29d9</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/26/bitcoin-regains-usd110k-after-weekend-sell-off-ada-doge-lead-uptick-in-crypto-majors"/>
        <updated>2025-05-26T06:34:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Traders eye renewed upside as President Donald Trump delayed a decision on EU tariffs, with sentiment recovering and options positioning turning bullish again.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shaurya Malwa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TRX Surges 1.25% as High-Volume Support Zone Propels Price Higher]]></title>
        <id>7250ed14-67df-4cb6-bc77-2a96c4dc54fb</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/26/trx-surges-1-25-as-high-volume-support-zone-propels-price-higher"/>
        <updated>2025-05-26T06:26:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Despite global economic tensions, TRX establishes new trading range with significant institutional interest.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>AI Boost</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google’s ‘world-model’ bet: building the AI operating layer before Microsoft captures the UI]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008900</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/googles-world-model-bet-building-the-ai-operating-layer-before-microsoft-captures-the-ui/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-25T17:42:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google doubles down on its ‘world-model’ vision, racing to build an AI operating layer to drive a universal personal assistant with Gemini. Even as Microsoft moves to capture the enterprise UI. Here's what's at stake.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matt Marshall</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum Surges After Holding $2,477, Fueled by Very Heavy Trading Volume]]></title>
        <id>76f8e53f-9f34-4263-b614-c54a680fbfb2</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/25/ethereum-surges-after-holding-usd2-477-fueled-by-very-heavy-trading-volume"/>
        <updated>2025-05-25T16:25:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum rebounds from $2,477 support on strong ETF inflows and rising volume, as bulls eye a breakout above the $2,530 resistance zone.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>AI Boost</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[XRP Plunges Below $2.30 Amid Heavy Selling Pressure]]></title>
        <id>341e2da4-6b9e-40aa-b40f-315604fef25e</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/25/xrp-plunges-below-usd2-30-amid-heavy-selling-pressure"/>
        <updated>2025-05-25T16:01:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Heavy volume trading creates a double-bottom pattern while institutional interest remains strong despite correction.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>AI Boost</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Drops Below $107.5K as Trump Tariff Threat Triggers Crypto Sell-Off]]></title>
        <id>191d7c44-6b20-49f2-bee3-1045162c8b40</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/25/bitcoin-drops-below-usd107-5k-as-trump-tariff-threat-triggers-crypto-sell-off"/>
        <updated>2025-05-25T15:40:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin faces selling pressure after Trump’s EU tariff warning, with price breaking key support and technicals signaling volatility near $107K.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>AI Boost</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chart of the Week: Bitcoin Soars, But ‘Wen Lambo’ Crowd Is Missing From the Rally]]></title>
        <id>adda456b-b7d8-44ba-9c27-af536272584f</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/25/chart-of-the-week-bitcoin-soars-but-wen-lambo-crowd-is-missing-from-the-rally"/>
        <updated>2025-05-25T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin hit new highs, but retail investors remain on the sidelines while institutional money fuels the steady rally.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Aoyon Ashraf</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Solana Plunges 5% as Midnight Sell-Off Signals Institutional Selling]]></title>
        <id>c821975c-57c5-45fa-bdcd-a6e3c7f30f69</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/25/solana-plunges-5-as-midnight-sell-off-signals-institutional-exit"/>
        <updated>2025-05-25T12:54:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Institutional investors dump SOL during high-volume trading hour, pushing price below critical $172 support level.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>AI Boost</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Clojure MCP]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/bhauman/clojure-mcp</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/bhauman/clojure-mcp"/>
        <updated>2025-05-25T06:48:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Beyond single-model AI: How architectural design drives reliable multi-agent orchestration]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008888</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/beyond-single-model-ai-how-architectural-design-drives-reliable-multi-agent-orchestration/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-24T22:35:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Successful AI agents require enterprises to orchestrate interactions, manage shared knowledge and plan for failure.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nikhil Gupta, Atlassian</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SVG Favicons in Action]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/svg-favicons-in-action/</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/svg-favicons-in-action/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-24T19:24:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OpenAI updates Operator to o3, making its $200 monthly ChatGPT Pro subscription more enticing]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008828</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/openai-updates-operator-to-o3-making-its-200-monthly-chatgpt-subscription-more-enticing/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-23T21:51:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Operator remains a research preview and is accessible only to ChatGPT Pro users. The Responses API version will continue to use GPT-4o.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carl Franzen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The battle to AI-enable the web: NLweb and what enterprises need to know]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008795</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/the-battle-to-ai-enable-the-web-nlweb-and-what-enterprises-need-to-know/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-23T21:05:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft's NLWeb protocol transforms websites into AI-powered apps with conversational interfaces.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sean Michael Kerner</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The 3 biggest bombshells from this week’s AI extravaganza]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008808</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/the-3-biggest-bombshells-from-this-weeks-ai-extravaganza/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-23T20:29:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Enterprises looking to build with AI should find plenty to look forward to with the announcements from Microsoft, Google & Anthropic this week.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nick Mokey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build a Testing Framework for E-Commerce Checkout and Payments]]></title>
        <id>68308f32f4205e3b843cfb37</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-build-a-testing-framework-for-e-commerce-checkout-and-payments/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-23T15:07:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When I first started working on E-commerce applications, I assumed testing checkout flows and payments would be straightforward. My expectation was simple: users select items, provide an address, pay, and receive confirmation. But I quickly learned t...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Venkata Sai Sandeep</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Architecture of Mathematics – And How Developers Can Use it in Code]]></title>
        <id>68308ee8ccde6bc325c82393</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/the-architecture-of-mathematics-and-how-developers-can-use-it-in-code/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-23T15:06:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA["To understand is to perceive patterns." - Isaiah Berlin Math is not just numbers. It is the science of finding complex patterns that shape our world. This means that to truly understand it, we need to see beyond numbers, formulas, and theorems and ...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tiago Capelo Monteiro</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Feature Fridays: dTelecom]]></title>
        <id>682f3eb8646f7c0001399182</id>
        <link href="https://blog.quicknode.com/feature-fridays-dtelecom/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-23T13:37:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[dTelecom is reshaping digital communication with decentralized, AI-powered infrastructure for Web3 developers and businesses.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>QuickNode</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use React 19 in Power Apps PCF Components]]></title>
        <id>6830767c62d9a28c0de11007</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-react-19-in-pcf-components/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-23T13:22:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Power Apps Component Framework – PCF for short – lets you create complex custom components using traditional web development tools like HTML, CSS, and JavaScript. When creating a new PCF project, you can choose from two types of controls: standar...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brandon Wozniewicz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why enterprise RAG systems fail: Google study introduces ‘sufficient context’ solution]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008684</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/why-enterprise-rag-systems-fail-google-study-introduces-sufficient-context-solution/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-23T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google's "sufficient context" helps refine RAG systems, reduce LLM hallucinations, and boost AI reliability for business applications.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ben Dickson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[High strength bio-concrete for the production of building components]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nature.com/articles/s44296-023-00004-6</id>
        <link href="https://www.nature.com/articles/s44296-023-00004-6"/>
        <updated>2025-05-23T12:40:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Download: meet Cathy Tie, and Anthropic’s new AI models]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1117399</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/05/23/1117399/the-download-meet-cathy-tie-and-anthropics-new-ai-models/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-23T12:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is today’s edition of The Download, our weekday newsletter that provides a daily dose of what’s going on in the world of technology. Meet Cathy Tie, Bride of “China’s Frankenstein” Since the Chinese biophysicist He Jiankui was released from prison in 2022, he has sought to make a scientific comeback and to repair his reputation after…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rhiannon Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rock, Paper, Scissors that learns how you play using markov chains]]></title>
        <id>https://luduxia.com/showdown/</id>
        <link href="https://luduxia.com/showdown/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-23T11:05:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Laid off but not afraid with X-senior Microsoft Dev MacKevin Fey [Podcast #173]]]></title>
        <id>68304756ecdb03ab557f3974</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/laid-off-but-not-afraid-with-x-senior-microsoft-dev-mackevin-fey-podcast-173/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-23T10:00:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On this week's episode of the podcast, freeCodeCamp founder Quincy Larson interviews MacKevin Fey. He just got laid off last week from his senior engineering role at Microsoft. We talk about: How Mack's approaching the job search after being laid of...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ask HN: What projects do you donate to?]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=44071321</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=44071321"/>
        <updated>2025-05-23T09:33:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The FDA plans to limit access to covid vaccines. Here’s why that’s not all bad.]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1117329</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/05/23/1117329/fda-limit-access-covid-vaccines/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-23T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This week, two new leaders at the US Food and Drug Administration announced plans to limit access to covid vaccines, arguing that there is not much evidence to support the value of annual shots in healthy people. New vaccines will be made available only to the people who are most vulnerable—namely, those over 65 and…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jessica Hamzelou</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meet Cathy Tie, Bride of “China’s Frankenstein”]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1117373</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/05/23/1117373/cathy-tie-he-jiankui-china-crispr-x-twitter-feed/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-23T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Since the Chinese biophysicist He Jiankui was released from prison in 2022, he has sought to make a scientific comeback and to repair his reputation after a three-year incarceration for illegally creating the world’s first gene-edited children.  While he has bounced between cities, jobs, and meetings with investors, one area of visible success on his…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Caiwei Chen, Antonio Regalado</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[After GPT-4o backlash, researchers benchmark models on moral endorsement—find sycophancy persists across the board]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008691</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/after-gpt-4o-backlash-researchers-benchmark-models-on-moral-endorsement-find-sycophancy-persists-across-the-board/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-22T23:46:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new benchmark can test how much LLMs become sycophants, and found that GPT-4o was the most sycophantic of the models tested.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Emilia David</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn Vue.js in This Beginner's Course]]></title>
        <id>682f84537a13a40bfa336307</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-vuejs-in-this-beginners-course/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-22T20:08:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you’ve been meaning to add Vue.js to your front-end toolbelt, today’s your day. We just published a full, 6-hour Vue 3 course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel. Instructor Bhrugen Patel walks you through everything you need to build modern, ...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Anthropic faces backlash to Claude 4 Opus behavior that contacts authorities, press if it thinks you’re doing something ‘egregiously immoral’]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008672</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/anthropic-faces-backlash-to-claude-4-opus-behavior-that-contacts-authorities-press-if-it-thinks-youre-doing-something-immoral/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-22T19:12:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bowman later edited his tweet and the following one in a thread to read as follows, but it still didn't convince the naysayers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carl Franzen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Anthropic’s new hybrid AI model can work on tasks autonomously for hours at a time]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1117338</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/05/22/1117338/anthropics-new-hybrid-ai-model-can-work-on-tasks-autonomously-for-hours-at-a-time/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-22T16:51:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Anthropic has announced two new AI models that it claims represent a major step toward making AI agents truly useful. AI agents trained on Claude Opus 4, the company’s most powerful model to date, raise the bar for what such systems are capable of by tackling difficult tasks over extended periods of time and responding…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rhiannon Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Anthropic overtakes OpenAI: Claude Opus 4 codes seven hours nonstop, sets record SWE-Bench score and reshapes enterprise AI]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008575</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/anthropic-claude-opus-4-can-code-for-7-hours-straight-and-its-about-to-change-how-we-work-with-ai/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-22T16:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Anthropic's Claude Opus 4 outperforms OpenAI's GPT-4.1 with unprecedented seven-hour autonomous coding sessions and record-breaking 72.5% SWE-bench score, transforming AI from quick-response tool to day-long collaborator.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Nuñez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Deploy Your FastAPI + PostgreSQL App on Render: A Beginner's Guide]]></title>
        <id>682f4900bcc94cb9bccbf905</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/deploy-fastapi-postgresql-app-on-render/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-22T15:55:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This guide is a comprehensive roadmap for deploying a FastAPI backend connected to a PostgreSQL database using Render, a cloud platform that supports hosting Python web apps and managed PostgreSQL databases.   You can find the complete source code he...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Preston Osoro</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[An Animated Introduction to Elixir]]></title>
        <id>682f44e3dcb21c615cf1a12d</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/an-animated-introduction-to-elixir/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-22T15:38:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Elixir is a dynamic, functional programming language designed for building scalable and maintainable applications. It leverages the battle-tested Erlang VM, known for running low-latency, distributed, and fault-tolerant systems. Elixir is based on an...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mark Mahoney</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Time Magazine appears to accidentally publish embargoed story confirming new Anthropic model]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008649</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/time-magazine-appears-to-accidentally-publish-embargoed-story-confirming-anthropic-claude-4-opus/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-22T15:26:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Someone also appears to have published a full scrape of the Time article online on the news aggregator app Newsbreak.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carl Franzen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Enchant launches zero-equity accelerator for gaming and AI startups]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008571</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/games/enchant-launches-zero-equity-accelerator-for-gaming-and-ai-startups/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-22T12:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Enchant is launching a new zero-equity accelerator for gaming and AI startups, with applications now open for its three-month program.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dean Takahashi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Download: the desert data center boom, and how to measure Earth’s elevations]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1117300</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/05/22/1117300/the-download-the-desert-data-center-boom-and-how-to-measure-earths-elevations/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-22T12:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is today’s edition of The Download, our weekday newsletter that provides a daily dose of what’s going on in the world of technology. The data center boom in the desert In the high desert east of Reno, Nevada, construction crews are flattening the golden foothills of the Virginia Range, laying the foundations of a data center…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rhiannon Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Three takeaways about AI’s energy use and climate impacts]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1117277</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/05/22/1117277/ai-energy-three-takeaways/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-22T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This week, we published Power Hungry, a package all about AI and energy. At the center of this package is the most comprehensive look yet at AI’s growing power demand, if I do say so myself.  This data-heavy story is the result of over six months of reporting by me and my colleague James O’Donnell…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Casey Crownhart</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A new atomic clock in space could help us measure elevations on Earth]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1117294</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/05/22/1117294/a-new-atomic-clock-in-space-could-help-us-measure-elevations-on-earth/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-22T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In 2003, engineers from Germany and Switzerland began building a bridge across the Rhine River simultaneously from both sides. Months into construction, they found that the two sides did not meet. The German side hovered 54 centimeters above the Swiss side. The misalignment occurred because the German engineers had measured elevation with a historic level…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sophia Chen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[At Google I/O, Sergey Brin makes surprise appearance — and declares Google will build the first AGI]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008490</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/at-google-i-o-sergey-brin-makes-surprise-appearance-and-declares-google-will-build-the-first-agi/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-21T22:20:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google co-founder Sergey Brin makes surprise appearance at Google I/O, declaring "Gemini will be the very first AGI," revealing philosophical tensions with DeepMind CEO Hassabis who urges scientific caution in the high-stakes AI race.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Nuñez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Master Database Management Systems]]></title>
        <id>682e3c04117e792e5f46edc3</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/master-database-management-systems/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-21T20:48:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Understanding how to manage data effectively is a critical skill for anyone pursuing a career in tech. And we just published a course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will teach you all about Database Management Systems (DBMS). This in-de...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Roundtables: A New Look at AI’s Energy Use]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1117287</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/05/21/1117287/roundtables-a-new-look-at-ais-energy-use-2/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-21T19:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Recorded on May 21, 2025 Big Tech’s appetite for energy is growing rapidly as adoption of AI accelerates. But just how much energy does even a single AI query use? And what does it mean for the climate? Hear from MIT Technology Review editor in chief Mat Honan, senior climate reporter Casey Crownhart, and AI reporter James…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>MIT Technology Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Refactor Complex Codebases – A Practical Guide for Devs]]></title>
        <id>682df5a0f2057ab279952dbe</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-refactor-complex-codebases/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-21T15:47:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Developers often see refactoring as a secondary concern that they can delay indefinitely because it doesn’t immediately contribute to revenue or feature development. And managers frequently view refactoring as "not a business need" until it boils ove...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ankur Tyagi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Vibe Coding Won't Destroy Software Engineering]]></title>
        <id>682df55da72360814bcae9ef</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/why-vibe-coding-wont-destroy-software-engineering/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-21T15:46:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AI is disrupting all industries at a pace not seen at any time in history. Technologies and industries that were once dominated by one or two companies or were very much “human-focused” are coming under threat. Google is losing ground to AI search, t...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ben</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OpenAI updates its new Responses API rapidly with MCP support, GPT-4o native image gen, and more enterprise features]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008465</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/programming-development/openai-updates-its-new-responses-api-rapidly-with-mcp-support-gpt-4o-native-image-gen-and-more-enterprise-features/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-21T15:30:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Support for remote Model Context Protocol servers, integration of image generation and Code Interpreter tools, and upgrades to file search...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carl Franzen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mistral AI launches Devstral, powerful new open source SWE agent model that runs on laptops]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008458</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/mistral-ai-launches-devstral-powerful-new-open-source-swe-agent-model-that-runs-on-laptops/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-21T14:57:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Beyond performance and portability, its Apache 2.0 license offers a compelling proposition for commercial applications.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carl Franzen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Download: Google’s AI mission, and America’s reliance on natural gas]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1117249</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/05/21/1117249/the-download-googles-ai-mission-and-americas-reliance-on-natural-gas/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-21T12:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is today’s edition of The Download, our weekday newsletter that provides a daily dose of what’s going on in the world of technology. By putting AI into everything, Google wants to make it invisible If you want to know where AI is headed, this year’s Google I/O has you covered. The company’s annual showcase of next-gen…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rhiannon Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[By putting AI into everything, Google wants to make it invisible]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1117251</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/05/21/1117251/by-putting-ai-into-everything-google-wants-to-make-it-invisible/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-21T11:49:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you want to know where AI is headed, this year’s Google I/O has you covered. The company’s annual showcase of next-gen products, which kicked off yesterday, has all of the pomp and pizzazz, the sizzle reels and celebrity walk-ons, that you’d expect from a multimillion-dollar marketing event. But it also shows us just how…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Will Douglas Heaven</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AMD unveils new Threadripper CPUs and Radeon GPUs for gamers at Computex 2025]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008206</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/games/amd-unveils-new-threadripper-cpus-and-radeon-gpus-for-gamers-at-computex-2025/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-21T03:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AMD held a Computex press event to introduce its Radeon RX 9060 XT graphics cards and Threadripper CPUs for next-gen gaming and workstations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dean Takahashi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google finally launches NotebookLM mobile app at I/O: hands-on, first impressions]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008400</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/google-finally-launches-notebooklm-mobile-app-at-i-o-hands-on-first-impressions/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T19:29:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As NotebookLM matures, its emerging business-tier capabilities suggest growing alignment with the productivity and compliance...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carl Franzen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google just leapfrogged every competitor with mind-blowing AI that can think deeper, shop smarter, and create videos with dialogue]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008346</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/google-just-leapfrogged-every-competitor-with-mind-blowing-ai-that-can-think-deeper-shop-smarter-and-create-videos-with-dialogue/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T17:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google unveiled major AI advancements at I/O 2025, including Gemini 2.5 with Deep Think, AI Mode in Search, Veo 3 for video with audio, and a $249 Ultra plan aimed at power users and enterprises.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Nuñez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google’s Jules aims to out-code Codex in battle for the AI developer stack]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008361</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/googles-jules-aims-to-out-code-codex-in-battle-for-the-ai-developer-stack/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T17:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google released Jules, its coding agent, into beta as autonomous coding agents are quickly gaining market share.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Emilia David</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Inside Google’s AI leap: Gemini 2.5 thinks deeper, speaks smarter and codes faster]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008366</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/inside-google-ai-leap-gemini-2-5-thinks-deeper-speaks-smarter-codes-faster/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T17:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google is moving closer to its goal of autonomous agentic AI with a series of enhancements to Gemini 2.5 Pro and Flash.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Taryn Plumb</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blazing-fast Solana data via gRPC: access the freshest Solana data from Shredstream leaders]]></title>
        <id>68273f14bf73460001094b35</id>
        <link href="https://blog.quicknode.com/yellowstone-grpc/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T15:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Access the fastest Solana data with the Yellowstone Geyser gRPC self-serve add-on or with the premium hybrid dedicated gRPC node.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>QuickNode</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Demonstrating end-to-end scientific discovery with Robin: a multi-agent system]]></title>
        <id>https://www.futurehouse.org/research-announcements/demonstrating-end-to-end-scientific-discovery-with-robin-a-multi-agent-system</id>
        <link href="https://www.futurehouse.org/research-announcements/demonstrating-end-to-end-scientific-discovery-with-robin-a-multi-agent-system"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T15:32:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft just launched an AI that discovered a new chemical in 200 hours instead of years]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008310</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/microsoft-just-launched-an-ai-that-discovered-a-new-chemical-in-200-hours-instead-of-years/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T18:34:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft launches Discovery platform that uses agentic AI to compress years of scientific research into days, transforming R&D across pharmaceuticals, materials science, and semiconductor industries.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Nuñez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Is your AI app pissing off users or going off-script? Raindrop emerges with AI-native observability platform to monitor performance]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008299</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/is-your-ai-app-pissing-off-users-or-going-off-script-raindrop-emerges-with-ai-native-observability-platform-to-monitor-performance/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T18:09:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With its rebrand and product expansion, Raindrop is betting that the next generation of software observability will be AI-first by design.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carl Franzen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft just taught its AI agents to talk to each other—and it could transform how we work]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008254</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/microsoft-just-taught-its-ai-agents-to-talk-to-each-other-and-it-could-transform-how-we-work/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T16:01:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft unveils multi-agent systems, WhatsApp integration, and Python-powered analytics for Copilot Studio at Build 2025, transforming how enterprises build and deploy AI solutions.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Nuñez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Microsoft Fabric has already been adopted by 70% of the Fortune 500 — and what’s next]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3007980</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/70-of-the-fortune-500-already-use-microsoft-fabric-and-its-now-getting-even-more-features-including-cosmosdb-support/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft integrates CosmosDB into Fabric, open sources DiskANN vector search, and unifies its data platforms to eliminate integration complexity that has slowed enterprise AI adoption.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sean Michael Kerner</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub Copilot evolves into autonomous agent with asynchronous code testing]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008231</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/github-copilot-evolves-into-autonomous-agent-with-asynchronous-code-testing/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub adds agentic capabilities to its Copilot coding assistant, competing with other more asynchronous coding platforms.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Emilia David</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft announces over 50 AI tools to build the ‘agentic web’ at Build 2025]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008229</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/microsoft-announces-over-50-ai-tools-to-build-the-agentic-web-at-build-2025/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T15:59:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft reveals its ambitious AI agent strategy, showcasing how multi-agent systems with persistent memory will transform enterprise workflows and accelerate development timelines.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Nuñez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Reddit, Webflow, and Superhuman are already customers—now GrowthX has $12M to grow]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008276</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/reddit-webflow-and-superhuman-are-already-customers-now-growthx-has-12m-to-grow/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[GrowthX secures $12M in funding for its "service-as-software" platform that combines AI with human expertise to boost content marketing results by up to 300%.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Nuñez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Quantum Machines launches Qualibrate open source framework to speed quantum computer calibration]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008032</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/games/quantum-machines-launches-qualibrate-open-source-framework-to-speed-quantum-computer-calibration/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Quantum Machines, a provider of advanced hybrid quantum-classical control solutions, announced today the release of Qualibrate.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dean Takahashi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is Sui: A Comprehensive Guide to Web3 Scalability]]></title>
        <id>6823533984101f00013a5ca4</id>
        <link href="https://blog.quicknode.com/what-is-sui-a-comprehensive-guide-to-web3-scalability/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-15T23:34:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Explore how Sui Network achieves 300,000 TPS through parallel processing, and its applications in gaming, DeFi, and supply chain management.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>QuickNode</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AI Meets Blockchain: Transforming Technology for the Next Era]]></title>
        <id>682354c584101f00013a5cb9</id>
        <link href="https://blog.quicknode.com/ai-and-blockchain-transforming-technology-together/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-15T23:34:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discover how AI and blockchain integration enhances security, efficiency, and innovation in healthcare, supply chains, and financial services.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>QuickNode</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Adventure Layer: AI Native Onchain Games, Unleashed]]></title>
        <id>6824c55abf73460001094973</id>
        <link href="https://blog.quicknode.com/adventure-layer-launches-on-quicknode-raas/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-15T12:04:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Adventure Layer launches layer-2 chain leveraging QuickNode's Rollup-as-a-Service (RaaS) product.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>QuickNode</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[QuickLee V2: An Improved Transparent Look into RPC Provider Latency]]></title>
        <id>680fc8e1f8ae810001969b47</id>
        <link href="https://blog.quicknode.com/quicklee-v2/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-14T13:57:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[View public and real-time dashboards to better understand latency and speed when evaluating RPC providers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>QuickNode</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>