<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2025-05-08T03:56:04.491Z</id>
    <title>AngJianming RSS Feed</title>
    <updated>2025-05-08T03:56:04.491Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Set Up Azure OpenAI in Msty Studio - A Step-by-Step Guide]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/armiedema/how-to-set-up-azure-openai-in-msty-studio-a-step-by-step-guide-4iip</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/armiedema/how-to-set-up-azure-openai-in-msty-studio-a-step-by-step-guide-4iip"/>
        <updated>2025-05-08T03:39:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you're looking to combine the power of OpenAI’s large language models (LLMs) with the security and scalability of Microsoft’s cloud infrastructure, Azure OpenAI is the way to go. With this service, you can access state-of-the-art models like GPT in a way that's enterprise-ready. Meaning, you get all the cutting-edge AI capabilities, plus the security, compliance, and integration tools your organization needs.
In this guide, we’ll walk through how to set up Azure OpenAI and connect it to Msty Studio.
Before diving in, make sure you have an Azure account and access to the Azure OpenAI service. Once that’s ready, follow these steps to deploy your first model.
Head to the Azure Portal.
Use the top search bar to look for Azure OpenAI.
If you don’t already have a resource, click Create Azure …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Adam Miedema</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Open Source Project Financial Transparency and Budget Management: A Holistic Guide]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/jennythomas498/open-source-project-financial-transparency-and-budget-management-a-holistic-guide-2io8</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/jennythomas498/open-source-project-financial-transparency-and-budget-management-a-holistic-guide-2io8"/>
        <updated>2025-05-08T03:37:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Abstract


This post explores the evolving landscape of open source project financial transparency and budget management. It covers the historical context, core concepts, and innovative funding methods such as donations, sponsorships, grants, crowdfunding, and NFT tokenization. We explain how blockchain integration, licensing models, and emerging technologies are transforming open source funding. Practical use cases, challenges, and future trends are discussed, giving developers, maintainers, and technical contributors a detailed guide to building sustainable, transparent financial systems for open source projects.
Open source projects have revolutionized the software development world, but maintaining and scaling them financially is now more critical than ever. With limited financial reso…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>JennyThomas498</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SQL Optimization Techniques for Better Performance]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/jing_li/sql-optimization-techniques-for-better-performance-4meb</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/jing_li/sql-optimization-techniques-for-better-performance-4meb"/>
        <updated>2025-05-08T03:36:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Optimizing SQL queries is crucial for efficient database operations and maintaining data integrity. Well-optimized queries can significantly reduce resource consumption and improve application speed. This article explores various common SQL optimization techniques with practical examples.
Note: For brevity in the examples below, * might be used in SELECT statements when the focus is on other clauses. However, the first point emphasizes why this should generally be avoided.
SELECT *



  
  
  Anti-Pattern (Bad Example):





SELECT * FROM Products;

Pro-Pattern (Good Example):





SELECT product_id, product_name, unit_price FROM Products;

Reasoning:




Saves resources and reduces network overhead: Fetching only necessary columns transmits less data.
Enables covering indexes: If all sele…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jing</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Optimize SQL Queries for Better Performance]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/media_geneous_bb80d6b5563/how-to-optimize-sql-queries-for-better-performance-4554</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/media_geneous_bb80d6b5563/how-to-optimize-sql-queries-for-better-performance-4554"/>
        <updated>2025-05-08T03:35:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How to Optimize SQL Queries for Better Performance
SQL query optimization is essential for improving database performance, reducing load times, and ensuring efficient data retrieval. Whether you're working with a small application or a large-scale enterprise system, poorly optimized queries can lead to slow response times and increased server costs. In this guide, we’ll explore practical techniques to optimize SQL queries for better performance.
1. Use Indexes Wisely
Indexes are one of the most powerful tools for speeding up SQL queries. They work like a book’s index, allowing the database engine to locate data faster without scanning the entire table.
When to Use Indexes:
Columns frequently used in WHERE, JOIN, or ORDER BY clauses.
Columns with high selectivity (unique or near-unique valu…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>MediaGeneous</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Efficiently Join Multiple Change History Tables in SQL?]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/generatecodedev/how-to-efficiently-join-multiple-change-history-tables-in-sql-4ki0</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/generatecodedev/how-to-efficiently-join-multiple-change-history-tables-in-sql-4ki0"/>
        <updated>2025-05-08T03:30:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction
Joining multiple change history tables can be a complex task, especially when dealing with overlapping intervals. This can lead to performance issues and convoluted queries. In this article, we will explore an efficient way to join change history tables in SQL, specifically focusing on how to simplify the join logic and improve scalability.
Understanding Change History Tables
Change history tables are crucial for tracking changes within an entity over time. Each record typically contains the entity's identifier, relevant attributes, and time intervals indicating the record's validity. For instance, in our example, the emp_history table captures employee title changes along with their start and end dates, while the dept_history table captures changes in department costs.
Why Jo…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Generatecode</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TNG eWallet Now Allows Tourists To Register And Use QR Payments In Malaysia]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=350919</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/350919/tng-ewallet-tourists/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-08T03:28:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[TNG Digital has announced that its e-wallet platform, TNG eWallet, now enables international tourists to sign up for an account and make cashless transactions. This allows foreigners to easily make QR payments to local vendors and even reload their enhanced Touch ‘n Go cards. To sign up for the e-wallet as a foreigner, you only […]
The post TNG eWallet Now Allows Tourists To Register And Use QR Payments In Malaysia appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ikmal Rozlan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Type-Safe Theming in Tailwind CSS Using CSS Variables and TypeScript]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/abtahitajwar/type-safe-theming-in-tailwind-css-using-css-variables-and-typescript-1e6j</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/abtahitajwar/type-safe-theming-in-tailwind-css-using-css-variables-and-typescript-1e6j"/>
        <updated>2025-05-08T03:16:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Modern frontend development demands scalable theming, responsive design tokens, and runtime flexibility. With the recent enhancements in Tailwind CSS v3.4+, namely @theme and @custom-variant, developers can now implement fully dynamic, type-safe theming using CSS variables, TypeScript, and zero runtime JS logic. This article outlines a theming strategy I came up with, which I believe is a clean and scalable approach built around those tools. It enables easy support for light/dark modes and beyond (daylight, retro, etc.) with minimal complexity.
tailwind.config.js Isn't Enough for Theming


Traditionally, developers define colors like primary, accent, or background directly in tailwind.config.js:
module.exports = {
  theme: {
    colors: {
      primary: '#571089',
      accent: '#ea698b',
…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>abtahi-tajwar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Retrieve Selected Index from Gtk DropDown in Rust?]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/generatecodedev/how-to-retrieve-selected-index-from-gtk-dropdown-in-rust-5kp</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/generatecodedev/how-to-retrieve-selected-index-from-gtk-dropdown-in-rust-5kp"/>
        <updated>2025-05-08T03:15:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In Rust, when using GTK's DropDown widget, you may want to execute a closure to retrieve the selected index upon the selection change. A common issue developers face is accessing the selected choice directly from the ParamSpec. Let's dive into how to do this effectively.
Understanding the DropDown and Connect Closure
When you create a DropDown in GTK, you define the choices it contains. In your example, you have created a DropDown with two options:
let choix = [&quot;Choice 1&quot;,&quot;Choice 2&quot;];
let drop_down2 = gtk::DropDown::from_strings(&amp;choix);

Here, choix is an array containing the two options. The DropDown will display these choices in the user interface. To respond to user interaction, you set up a closure that will be executed whenever the selected choice changes.
The…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Generatecode</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[realme Introduces 10,000mAh Concept Phone]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=350911</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/350911/realme-introduces-10000mah-concept-phone/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-08T03:13:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After teasing the launch of its GT 7 series of smartphones in Malaysia, realme has unveiled the GT 10,000mAh, a prototype smartphone with a massive battery. As its name suggests, the concept phone packs a 10,000mAh battery and is designed to address users’ battery woes. The prototype features a slim body that is less than […]
The post realme Introduces 10,000mAh Concept Phone appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nurul Kamil</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Visual Studio Code: The Unexpected Bridge Between Worlds]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/ljvasquezr/visual-studio-code-the-unexpected-bridge-between-worlds-52bi</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/ljvasquezr/visual-studio-code-the-unexpected-bridge-between-worlds-52bi"/>
        <updated>2025-05-08T03:11:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the vast universe of software development, Visual Studio Code has emerged as a key tool—an unexpected bridge connecting worlds that once seemed incompatible. It has become a lifeline for developers coming from the GNU/Linux ecosystem, desperately seeking a way to write desktop applications, something they thought was lost in their environment.
Its versatility allows for development in C#, C++, and FPC Pascal, avoiding alternatives like Lazarus, and offering a more modern and robust option. Personally, I’ve found myself using it as an alternative to Visual Studio 2022, since developing a .NET 6, 7, or 8 application on Linux is financially more viable for my business than doing so on Windows.
But here’s the question: Why does Visual Studio Code feel like an orphaned and underappreciated sibling compared to Visual Studio 2022?
Both serve incredible purposes. Visual Studio 2022 is the enterprise-grade powerhouse, while VS Code is the agile alternative—the gateway for many developers coming from GNU/Linux, looking to explore Windows and its tools, or simply wanting to use .NET Core on Linux. That in itself is a massive achievement, a step forward in software evolution.
Because in the end, bluntly speaking, Linux is great... but if it doesn’t pay the bills, what can I do? As developers, we need to produce high-quality software using high-quality tools. That’s why Visual Studio Code becomes the logical and efficient choice—a path that allows us to keep programming in diverse environments while maintaining productivity and financial sustainability.
Ultimately, VS Code isn’t just a code editor… it’s the bridge that unites worlds that once seemed irreconcilable.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>LUIS JOSE VASQUEZ</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[VC写Windows服务程序]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/second/vcxie-windowsfu-wu-cheng-xu-1bpm</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/second/vcxie-windowsfu-wu-cheng-xu-1bpm"/>
        <updated>2025-05-08T03:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[之前写的后台的控制程序，我采用的都是用VC或者是C#写完之后然后采用AlwaysUp或者是nssm把自己写的后台程序再给做成一个Windows的服务程序。但后来想了想为什么不自己直接写一个Windows的服务程序呢。所以就开始了写服务程序的历程。
首先大致的说一下C#语言写一个Windwos服务程序的方法。说实话C#想写一个Windows服务程序相对的要简单的多。因为C#已经都给准备好了。就在创建项目的选择Windows服务项目就可以了。然后再添加一个服务安装的组件，改一下相关的配置，如：服务名、启动类型、启动权限或者叫启动时的用户。这些信息就可以了。在写代码的时候只要在开始的里面写上服务启动时需要做的工作，在结束里面写上服务停止时需要收尾的工作就大功告成了。
下面主要是说一下采用VC写Windows服务程序。这个我个人觉得相对来说有几个坑需要避。
第一个坑就是如果你从网上查的话都会说用VC写Windows服务程序的入口主函数是ServiceMain()这个函数。而实际并不是，实际上的程序入口还是从main()这个函数开始的。只不过在这个函数中我们不能做太多的事情，必须要尽快的调用StartServiceCtrlDispatcher()这函数来启动ServiceMain()函数。而且ServiceMain()这个函数的名字也并不一定就是这个，可以自定义。只不过你在网上查的人都会采用这个函数名而已。并非VC语言的规定或者约束。这个函数也只不过是在调用StartServiceCtrlDispatcher()函数的时候的一个参数而已叫什么名字并不重要。
第二坑就是服务状态的变换问题，只有你有ServiceMain()函数中调用了SetServiceStatus()函数来告诉Windows操作系统你的服务程序是开始启动了还时正在运行之中还是正在停止之中才可以。在这方面我从网上查了好长时间没有一个写的清楚的。我开始的时候以为这个函数没什么大用于是把相关的代码给删掉了，结果就会发生服务程序的状态无法改变。比如你在启动服务的时候没有及时的状态改成正在运行的话那么Windows的服务控制台就会一直启动这个服务直到启动超时而报错最后服务的状态就会卡在启动状态无法将服务停止或者删除。如果你能将服务状态进入到正在运行状态，但在发出停止服务的时候如果不能将服务的状修改成停止的话那么Windows也会一直停止这个服务直到停止超时而报错。而且这个服务的状态也会卡在停止的状态无法改变。
第三个坑就是在ServiceMain()函数中在用SetServiceStatus()函数把服务的状态修改成“正在运行”的状态之后必须要调用WaitForSingleObject()函数把这个服务的主线程给卡住然就是是一直等待发出服务停止的信号。所以在真正的主线程中你是无法再做其它的任何的工作的。故如果要想写好一个完整的Windwos服务程序就必须在ServiceMain()函数调用WaitForSingleObject()函数之前将你想做的事情都给加载完毕之后再调用WaitForSingleObject()函数将主线程卡住一直等待停止服务的指令。当停止服务的指令来临的时候再调用SetServiceStatus()函数把服务的状态修改成已经停止。
第四个这个不算是坑了这个算是一个常识。就是服务程序的调试问题。如果想调试Windows服务程序那么就只能采用“附加到进程”的方式。即先从Windows的服务管理器中启动服务，然后从Visual Studio的“调试”菜单中选择“附加到进程”的选项然后再选择自己程序的那个进程就可以了。
总结一下，那就是不论是VC写Windows服务程序还是C#写Windwos服务程序，都会有一个开始服务的初始化函数。而初始化函数中不能有死循环，但一般的服务程序又必须要用死循环，所以一个完整的Windwos服务程序一定是一个多线程的，在初始化的时候就启动其它的想要加载的死循环的线程。还会有一个程序的销毁函数，同样在销毁函数中也不能有无法完成的循环。最后就是Windwos服务程序的调试必须采用附加到进程的方式来进行。]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>YuDi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why React is Better for Multi-Page Websites?]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/deansaiful/why-react-is-better-for-multi-page-websites-5dhm</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/deansaiful/why-react-is-better-for-multi-page-websites-5dhm"/>
        <updated>2025-05-08T03:06:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction


When it comes to building multi-page websites, developers often face the challenge of maintaining scalability, performance, and reusability. Traditionally, multi-page websites were built using plain HTML, CSS, and JavaScript. This approach works well for small, simple sites but becomes increasingly difficult to manage as the number of pages grows.
This is where React comes in. React, developed by Facebook, has become one of the most popular JavaScript libraries for building user interfaces. Its component-based architecture and powerful routing capabilities make it an ideal choice for multi-page applications. In this article, we’ll explore why React is a better choice for building multi-page websites and how it solves many of the challenges that come with traditional HTML-bas…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>DeanSaiful</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Fix Clerk AuthMiddleware Errors in TypeScript?]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/generatecodedev/how-to-fix-clerk-authmiddleware-errors-in-typescript-27l8</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/generatecodedev/how-to-fix-clerk-authmiddleware-errors-in-typescript-27l8"/>
        <updated>2025-05-08T03:00:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction
When working with authentication in Next.js, integrating Clerk can be quite straightforward—but you may encounter issues along the way. One common error developers face is the message: "Clerk: auth() was called but it looks like you aren't using authMiddleware in your middleware file." This can leave you scratching your head, especially if you're sure you've configured everything correctly.
In this article, we'll explore the reasons behind this error and provide you with a comprehensive guide on how to properly use the authMiddleware with Clerk in your Next.js TypeScript application. Let's dive in and ensure your authentication setup is smooth and error-free!
Why Does This Error Occur?
The error occurs when the middleware system in Next.js is not correctly configured to route …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Generatecode</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DAY 40: Array in Looping JAVA]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/sangamithra_k_78d83d6fb9d/day-40-array-in-looping-java-18ff</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/sangamithra_k_78d83d6fb9d/day-40-array-in-looping-java-18ff"/>
        <updated>2025-05-08T02:57:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In Java, an array is a data structure that stores a fixed-size, sequential collection of elements of the same data type. It is a container object that holds a fixed number of values of a single type. The length of an array is established when the array is created and remains fixed throughout its lifetime. Arrays are used to organize data efficiently and can be defined and initialized in various ways.
Array - Group of similar datatypes
Why do you use an array?
Arrays are handy when you want to work with multiple values of the same data type. Instead of declaring individual variables for each value, you can group them together in an array, making your code more concise and easier to manage.
Index / Subscript:  0   1   2   3   4

marks[0] = 90;  
marks[1] = 95; 
marks[2] = 100; 
marks[3] = 78…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sangamithra K</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin returns to $98K as Fed holds rates steady despite Trump’s demand]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-price-98k-federal-reserve-interest-rate-cuts-donald-trump-demands</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-price-98k-federal-reserve-interest-rate-cuts-donald-trump-demands?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-08T02:49:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin has reclaimed $98,000 for the first time in almost three months after the US Federal Reserve said it would keep interest rates the same for another month.
The Fed’s decision to keep interest rates unchanged comes despite mounting pressure from US President Donald Trump, who just weeks ago threatened to fire Fed chair Jerome Powell for being “too late” in cutting rates.
Fed cites higher unemployment, inflation risk
Powell said on May 7 that the Federal Reserve rate-setting committee held rates in the 4.25% to 4.50% range due to the rising risks of higher unemployment and higher inflation.
He added inflation has “come down a great deal but has been running above our 2% longer objective.” Powell said surveys in households and businesses showed a “sharp decline in sentiment” mainly due…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Ciaran Lyons</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin miner Core Scientific posts $580M Q1 profit but misses revenue estimates]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/core-scientific-misses-q1-revenue-posts-580-million-q1-profit</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/core-scientific-misses-q1-revenue-posts-580-million-q1-profit?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-08T02:32:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nasdaq-listed Bitcoin mining firm Core Scientific Inc. posted a net profit of $580 million with its first quarter results, but missed analyst revenue estimates after a drop in its mining profits.
Core Scientific’s Q1 2025 results, shared on May 7, saw it more than double its $210 million net income from the year-ago quarter, while its total revenue reached $79.5 million, missing Zacks analysts' estimates by 8.11%, and falling from its $179.3 million in revenues for Q1 2024. 
The firm’s primary source of revenue came from $67.2 million in self-mining revenue, $3.8 million in hosted mining revenue, and $8.6 million in colocation, formerly listed as high-performance computing (HPC) hosting.
Source: Core Scientific
Core Scientific said its drop in Bitcoin (BTC) mined and revenue was due to the…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Stephen Katte</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Arizona governor signs law for state to keep unclaimed crypto]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/arizona-governor-signs-bitcoin-reserve-keep-unclaimed-crypto</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/arizona-governor-signs-bitcoin-reserve-keep-unclaimed-crypto?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-08T02:05:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Arizona Governor Katie Hobbs has signed a bill into law allowing the US state to keep unclaimed crypto and establish a “Bitcoin Reserve Fund” that won’t use any taxpayer money or state funds.
Hobbs signed House Bill 2749 into law on May 7, which allows Arizona to claim ownership of abandoned digital assets if the owner fails to respond to communications within three years.
The state’s custodians can stake the crypto to earn rewards or receive airdrops, which can then be deposited into what Arizona has called a Bitcoin and Digital Asset Reserve Fund.
“This law ensures Arizona doesn’t leave value sitting on the table and puts us in a position to lead the country in how we secure, manage, and ultimately benefit from abandoned digital currency,” the bill’s sponsor, Jeff Weninger, said in a May…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Brayden Lindrea</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Radiation-tolerant ML framework for space]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/r0nlt/Space-Radiation-Tolerant</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/r0nlt/Space-Radiation-Tolerant"/>
        <updated>2025-05-08T02:03:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tune Talk Epik 50+ Plan Gets Bundled With PandaPro Subscription]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=350887</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/350887/tune-talk-epik-50-plan-bundled-pandapro-subscription/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-08T02:00:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tune Talk and Foodpanda have announced that subscribers to the former’s Epik 50+ Plan will also be getting the latter’s PandaPro subscription bundled in at no extra cost. Despite the announcement, the companies say that the bundle promo started back in April. In case you missed it, Tune Talk replaced its previous Epik packages with […]
The post Tune Talk Epik 50+ Plan Gets Bundled With PandaPro Subscription appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ian Chee</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dyson’s Customisable OnTrac Headphones Quietly Launches In Malaysia]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=350904</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/350904/dysons-ontrac-headphones-available-in-malaysia/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-08T01:00:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This one seems to have quietly flown under the radar. As it turns out, Dyson’s customisable OnTrac headphones have finally launched in Malaysia. According to staff at the brand’s experience store in The Gardens Mall, the headphones were released locally quite recently – albeit without much fanfare. In case you missed the initial announcement, here’s […]
The post Dyson’s Customisable OnTrac Headphones Quietly Launches In Malaysia appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Heirul Kamel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Binance founder CZ asked Trump to pardon money laundering conviction]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/changpeng-zhao-cz-binance-asked-trump-pardon</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/changpeng-zhao-cz-binance-asked-trump-pardon?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-08T00:04:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Binance founder and convicted felon Changpeng Zhao says that he applied for a pardon from US President Donald Trump shortly after denying reports that he was seeking one.
Zhao, also known as CZ, said on a Farokh Radio podcast episode aired May 6 that he “wouldn’t mind” a pardon and that his lawyers have already filed the paperwork on his behalf
“I got lawyers applying,” Zhao said, adding that he submitted the request after Bloomberg and The Wall Street Journal reported in March that he was seeking a pardon from Trump amid discussions of a business deal between the Trump family and Binance.US.
Zhao denied the reports at the time, but said on the podcast that he thought “if they’re writing this article, I may as well just officially apply.”
He added that Trump’s pardon of three BitMEX founde…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Brayden Lindrea</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Parametric Modeling with Grasshopper]]></title>
        <id>https://baharmon.github.io/basics</id>
        <link href="https://baharmon.github.io/basics"/>
        <updated>2025-05-07T23:57:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Show HN: US Routing – Python library for fast local routing in the United States]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/ivanbelenky/us-routing</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/ivanbelenky/us-routing"/>
        <updated>2025-05-07T23:51:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Yggdrasil is an experimental compact routing scheme that is fully decentralised]]></title>
        <id>https://yggdrasil-network.github.io/about.html</id>
        <link href="https://yggdrasil-network.github.io/about.html"/>
        <updated>2025-05-07T23:45:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Here’s what happened in crypto today]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/what-happened-in-crypto-today</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/what-happened-in-crypto-today?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-07T22:22:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today in crypto, Robinhood is planning a new blockchain for tokenized securities offering in Europe. Meanwhile, Ethereum developers have activated the network’s Pectra upgrade, introducing smart accounts and other features. In US politics, Democrats have launched a new offensive targeting Donald Trump’s crypto ventures.
Robinhood plans blockchain for US asset trading in Europe — Report
Brokerage fintech Robinhood is reportedly developing a blockchain network that will enable retail investors in Europe to trade US securities.
According to a May 7 Bloomberg report citing sources familiar with the matter, the move seeks to expand the company's local presence by offering trading of tokenized securities, such as stocks.
Two crypto firms, Arbitrum and the Solana Foundation, are reportedly vying …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Cointelegraph</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Stripe rolls out stablecoin accounts in over 100 countries]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/stripe-announces-stablecoin-financial-accounts</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/stripe-announces-stablecoin-financial-accounts?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-07T22:15:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Stripe, a global payments platform, has introduced stablecoin-based accounts to clients in over 100 countries. 
According to a May 7 announcement, the new feature will allow the platform's clients "to send, receive, and hold US-dollar stablecoin account balances, similar to how a traditional fiat bank account works."
The product's technical page shows that the new account feature will support Circle's USDC (USDC) and Bridge's USDB (USDB) stablecoins. Stripe acquired the Bridge platform in October 2024.
The product will be available to clients in more than 100 countries, including Argentina, Chilé, Turkey, Colombia, and Peru, among others.
Stripe's newly launched product comes at a time when stablecoins are increasingly seen as stores of value in developing economies struggling with high in…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Vince Quill</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Anthropic launches Claude web search API, betting on the future of post-Google information access]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3006849</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/anthropic-launches-claude-web-search-api-betting-on-the-future-of-post-google-information-access/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-07T22:01:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Anthropic launches web search API for Claude as Apple considers AI search alternatives to Google, signaling a major shift in how users discover information online.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Nuñez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Robinhood plans blockchain for US asset trading in Europe — Report]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/robinhood-blockchain-us-asset-trading-tokenization-europe</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/robinhood-blockchain-us-asset-trading-tokenization-europe?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-07T21:54:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Brokerage fintech Robinhood is reportedly developing a blockchain network that will enable retail investors in Europe to trade US securities.
According to a May 7 Bloomberg report citing sources familiar with the matter, the move seeks to expand the company's local presence by offering trading of tokenized securities, such as stocks. 
Two crypto firms, Arbitrum and the Solana Foundation, are reportedly vying to become partners in the project. Tokenization is the process of turning real-world assets, like stocks, real estate, or commodities, into digital tokens that can be traded on a blockchain.
Tokenizing securities instead of providing direct exposure can offer several advantages: reduced costs by eliminating traditional financial infrastructure, enhanced accessibility, faster settlement…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Christopher Tepedino</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Foundation DB Record Layer SQL API]]></title>
        <id>https://foundationdb.github.io/fdb-record-layer/SQL_Reference.html</id>
        <link href="https://foundationdb.github.io/fdb-record-layer/SQL_Reference.html"/>
        <updated>2025-05-07T21:48:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[June Huh dropped out to become a poet, now he’s won a Fields Medal (2022)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.quantamagazine.org/june-huh-high-school-dropout-wins-the-fields-medal-20220705/</id>
        <link href="https://www.quantamagazine.org/june-huh-high-school-dropout-wins-the-fields-medal-20220705/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-07T21:34:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OCC: Banks Can Buy and Sell Their Customers' Crypto Assets Held in Custody]]></title>
        <id>cd316845-0400-4981-b1ec-3fabddcf4997</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2025/05/07/occ-banks-can-buy-and-sell-their-customers-crypto-assets-held-in-custody"/>
        <updated>2025-05-07T21:31:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new policy directive from the U.S. regulator of national banks says the institutions can also outsource crypto custody and execution to outside parties.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jesse Hamilton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Falling DXY part of US financial system’s ‘long-term transition’ — Will Bitcoin continue to shine?]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/falling-dxy-part-of-us-financial-system-s-long-term-transition-will-bitcoin-continue-to-shine</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/falling-dxy-part-of-us-financial-system-s-long-term-transition-will-bitcoin-continue-to-shine?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-07T21:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What to know:

Lyn Alden says a weaker dollar is necessary for the US to stabilize its financial system.

Bitcoin and gold are well-positioned to benefit from de-dollarization.

Sovereign wealth funds and various nations are already increasing their Bitcoin exposure as the dollar’s global dominance starts to wane.

The weakening of the US dollar (DXY) is no longer headline news. With mounting disruptions across the US economy, a declining greenback has become part of the backdrop. Since the start of 2025, the US Dollar Index has dropped 11%, now hovering around levels last seen in April 2022. Markets have largely responded with a shrug. After all, in times of deep restructuring, isn’t some dollar weakness to be expected?
The trouble is, this might not be a temporary dip. The dollar’s slide…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Marie Poteriaieva</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ex-SafeMoon CEO claims innocence, blames founder as trial begins]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/safemoon-trial-john-karony-blames-founder</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/safemoon-trial-john-karony-blames-founder?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-07T21:21:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Braden John Karony, the former CEO of crypto firm SafeMoon, made an out-of-court statement claiming innocence as his criminal trial began in New York.
In a May 6 X post after court proceedings had likely ended for the day, Karony said he was innocent and “did not commit fraud” in response to media coverage of his trial. The former CEO, as well as SafeMoon creator Kyle Nagy and former chief technology officer Thomas Smith, were charged in 2023 for having allegedly “diverted and misappropriated millions of dollars’ worth” of the platform’s SFM token.
According to reporting from the US District Court for the Eastern District of New York (EDNY) on May 6, Karony implied that Nagy, who reportedly fled to Russia after authorities filed charges, was responsible for some of the alleged fraud at Saf…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Turner Wright</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fed Stagflation Risk Signal Could Be Bullish for Bitcoin, Analyst Says]]></title>
        <id>bc2bd97c-6b5b-43ac-9eb8-3a5b840fd4a1</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/07/fed-stagflation-risk-signal-could-be-bullish-for-bitcoin-analyst-says"/>
        <updated>2025-05-07T21:09:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Holding rates steady, the U.S. central bank took note of the possibility of higher inflation and unemployment.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Krisztian Sandor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OpenAI for Countries]]></title>
        <id>https://openai.com/global-affairs/openai-for-countries/</id>
        <link href="https://openai.com/global-affairs/openai-for-countries/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-07T21:05:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Binance&#039;s BNB Chain rebounds amid institutional, DeFi adoption]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/binance-bnbchain-stages-comeback-institutional-defi-adoption</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/binance-bnbchain-stages-comeback-institutional-defi-adoption?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-07T21:05:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Binance-affiliated BNB Chain has rebounded after a period of stagnation in 2023 amid accelerating institutional and decentralized finance (DeFi) adoption. 
During the past year, BNB Chain has benefited from multibillion-dollar inflows into DeFi, US exchange-traded funds (ETFs), and rising trading volume at affiliated centralized exchange (CEX) Binance. 
Consequently, the blockchain network’s native BNB token (BNB) has emerged as among the market’s most resilient cryptocurrencies, surpassing all-time highs in the first quarter of 2025 even as the broader crypto market trended downward. 
“This resilience isn't just about price action — strong fundamentals also back it,” Joao Wedson, CEO of investing analytics platform Alphractal, said in an April X post. “Binance has built a massive ecosyste…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Alex O’Donnell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GovEagle (YC W23) Is Hiring]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ycombinator.com/companies/goveagle/jobs/ogNRCkd-platform-engineering-contractor-short-term</id>
        <link href="https://www.ycombinator.com/companies/goveagle/jobs/ogNRCkd-platform-engineering-contractor-short-term"/>
        <updated>2025-05-07T21:00:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trump Crypto Advisor David Bailey In Talks to Launch Bitcoin Investment Company: The Information]]></title>
        <id>af82fce7-9435-4c50-8ffe-492d8243bd17</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/07/trump-crypto-advisor-david-bailey-in-talks-to-launch-bitcoin-investment-company-the-information"/>
        <updated>2025-05-07T20:46:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bailey, who advised President Donald Trump on crypto policy during his 2024 presidential campaign, is reportedly raising $300 million to buy bitcoin.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Helene Braun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum Pectra upgrade adds new features — How long before ETH price reacts?]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/ethereum-pectra-upgrade-adds-new-features-how-long-before-eth-price-reacts</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/ethereum-pectra-upgrade-adds-new-features-how-long-before-eth-price-reacts?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-07T20:20:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Key takeaways:

Reclaiming the $2,200 level remains the first price challenge for ETH. 

ETH price could recover if the Pectra upgrade leads to a surge in DApp and Ethereum network activity. 

Ethereum successfully implemented a key network upgrade on May 7, but Ether (ETH) price and its derivatives metrics showed little response to the upgrade. The lackluster response surprised traders and led analysts to question whether ETH still has a real chance of climbing 22% to retake the $2,200 level.
Ether 30-day futures annualized premium. Source: Laevitas.ch
The ETH futures premium has remained below the 5% neutral threshold, indicating a lack of appetite from leveraged bulls. More significantly, this indicator was unchanged at 3% after the Pectra upgrade, suggesting traders did not adjust thei…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Marcel Pechman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Web search on the Anthropic API]]></title>
        <id>https://www.anthropic.com/news/web-search-api</id>
        <link href="https://www.anthropic.com/news/web-search-api"/>
        <updated>2025-05-07T20:18:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[$45 million stolen from Coinbase users in the last week — ZackXBT]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/45-million-stolen-coinbase-users-last-week-zack-xbt</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/45-million-stolen-coinbase-users-last-week-zack-xbt?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-07T19:57:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Onchain sleuth and security analyst ZackXBT claims to have identified an additional $45 million in funds stolen from Coinbase users through social engineering scams in the past seven days alone.
According to the onchain detective, the $45 million figure represents the latest financial losses in a string of social engineering scams targeting Coinbase users, which ZackXBT said is a problem unique among crypto exchanges:
"Over the past few months, I have reported on nine figures stolen from Coinbase users via similar social engineering scams. Interestingly, no other major exchange has the same problem."
Cointelegraph reached out to Coinbase but was unable to get a response by the time of publication.
Source: ZachXBT
The claims made by ZackXBT place the total amount lost by Coinbase users to s…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Vince Quill</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Average in Prolog (2017)]]></title>
        <id>https://storytotell.org/how-to-average-in-prolog</id>
        <link href="https://storytotell.org/how-to-average-in-prolog"/>
        <updated>2025-05-07T19:54:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Robinhood Developing Blockchain-Based Program To Trade U.S. Securities in Europe: Bloomberg]]></title>
        <id>5bfab0b3-4c79-4a29-8794-3f6c2b2a9e5f</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2025/05/07/robinhood-developing-blockchain-based-program-to-trade-u-s-securities-in-europe-bloomberg"/>
        <updated>2025-05-07T19:49:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The brokerage firm is reportedly considering Arbitrum, Ethereum and Solana for the new platform.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Helene Braun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mac Themes Garden]]></title>
        <id>https://damien.zone/introducing-mac-themes-garden/</id>
        <link href="https://damien.zone/introducing-mac-themes-garden/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-07T19:44:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Protocol: Ethereum’s Pectra Upgrade Finally Goes Live]]></title>
        <id>1c5a33d5-771d-4b01-af8a-98a3bdbe8621</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/tech/2025/05/07/the-protocol-ethereum-s-pectra-upgrade-finally-goes-live"/>
        <updated>2025-05-07T19:29:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Also: Bitcoin Devs Debate OP_RETURN, World Network Launches in U.S., and Aztec Testnet Launches]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Margaux Nijkerk</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[US Treasury Secretary expresses support for crypto bills at hearing]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/us-treasury-secretary-crypto-bills-during-hearing</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/us-treasury-secretary-crypto-bills-during-hearing?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-07T19:24:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Speaking at a hearing, US Treasury Secretary Scott Bessent suggested support for two crypto-related bills moving through Congress.
Bessent addressed lawmakers at a May 7 hearing of the House Financial Services Committee, saying that the United States should be the “premier destination for digital assets” in response to a question about American dominance over China in crypto-related innovation. The Treasury Secretary added that “good market structure” and “stablecoin legislation” could help ensure this outcome.
US Treasury Secretary speaking at a May 7 hearing. Source: Scott Bessent
Bessent’s remarks echoed those of other Republican lawmakers and President Donald Trump, who initially claimed he wanted to make the US the “crypto capital of the world” during his 2024 campaign. The Treasury S…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Turner Wright</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[COLDRIVER using new malware to steal from Western targets — Google]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/coldriver-new-malware-steal-western-targets-google</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/coldriver-new-malware-steal-western-targets-google?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-07T18:43:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Threat group COLDRIVER is using new malware to steal documents from Western targets, according to a May 7 report from Google Threat Intelligence. The malware, called LOSTKEYS, shows the evolution of the group from credential phishing to more sophisticated attacks.
According to the Google report, the new malware is installed through four steps. The process involves a “lure website” with a fake CAPTCHA, a PowerShell script downloaded to the user’s clipboard, some device evasion, and retrieval of the final payload. Lastly, the malware is installed.
LOSTKEYS payload delivery. Source: Google
LOSTKEYS is capable of stealing files from extensions and directories. It can also send system information and running processes back to COLDRIVER. The address from which the parts of the attack come is “16…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Christopher Tepedino</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Strive Asset Management to Go Public, Launch Bitcoin Treasury Strategy With Merger]]></title>
        <id>15117a1c-c5cc-4c0e-9ddb-9fc242150d45</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2025/05/07/strive-asset-management-to-go-public-launch-bitcoin-treasury-strategy-in-merger"/>
        <updated>2025-05-07T18:11:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The combined company plans to stockpile Bitcoin and offer tax-free equity swaps to accredited holders.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Helene Braun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin &#039;Realized Cap&#039; hits $890B as BTC traders focus on recapturing $100K]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-realized-cap-hits-890-b-as-btc-traders-focus-on-recapturing-100-k</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-realized-cap-hits-890-b-as-btc-traders-focus-on-recapturing-100-k?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-07T18:09:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Key Takeaways: 

Bitcoin’s realized capitalization hit a record $890 billion, reflecting strong investor conviction as long-term and short-term holders increased allocations. 

Large Bitcoin holders with over 1,000 BTC have accumulated significantly since March 2025, reflecting the Q1 2024 trend. 

Bitcoin (BTC) price saw a short-squeeze above $97,000 on May 6, shortly after US Treasury Secretary Scott Bessent announced that trade talks would commence with China on May 10. At the same time, BTC’s realized capitalization, a metric adding the dollar value of all coins at their last moved price, soared to a new all-time high of $890 billion on May 7, 2025. The surge also marks the metric’s third consecutive week of record-breaking growth.
Bitcoin realized cap. Source: CryptoQuant
The realized…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Biraajmaan Tamuly</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fed Holds Rates Steady, Says Risks of Higher Unemployment, Higher Inflation Have Risen]]></title>
        <id>8d2cb3b7-1a1e-47e0-811b-e9aa21671f67</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/07/fed-holds-rates-steady-says-risks-of-higher-unemployment-higher-inflation-have-risen"/>
        <updated>2025-05-07T18:05:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[All eyes will now turn to Fed Chair Jerome Powell's post-meeting press conference for further clues about the central bank's thinking on monetary policy.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Krisztian Sandor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Strive to become Bitcoin treasury company]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/strive-to-become-bitcoin-treasury-company</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/strive-to-become-bitcoin-treasury-company?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-07T18:00:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Strive Asset Management, founded by entrepreneur and former presidential candidate Vivek Ramaswamy, has revealed plans to transition into a Bitcoin treasury company.
According to a May 7 announcement, Strive is going public through a reverse merger and plans to use the combined company’s stock to accumulate Bitcoin (BTC).
The deal will see Strive merging with Asset Entities — a social media marketing company listed on the Nasdaq. The combined entity will operate under the Strive brand and use its access to the public equity markets to finance Bitcoin purchases, the company said. 
Once the deal closes, Strive plans to issue approximately $1 billion in equity and debt and use the proceeds to accumulate BTC. The asset manager “intends to use all available mechanisms to build a Bitcoin war che…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Alex O’Donnell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Open source Google Analytics replacement]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/rybbit-io/rybbit</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/rybbit-io/rybbit"/>
        <updated>2025-05-07T17:45:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ty: A fast Python type checker and language server]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/astral-sh/ty</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/astral-sh/ty"/>
        <updated>2025-05-07T17:32:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Samsung is paying $350M for audio brands B&W, Denon, Marantz and Polk]]></title>
        <id>https://www.engadget.com/audio/samsung-is-paying-350-million-for-audio-brands-bowers--wilkins-denon-marantz-and-polk-131514754.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.engadget.com/audio/samsung-is-paying-350-million-for-audio-brands-bowers--wilkins-denon-marantz-and-polk-131514754.html"/>
        <updated>2025-05-07T17:28:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Price predictions 5/7: BTC, ETH, XRP, BNB, SOL, DOGE, ADA, SUI, LINK, AVAX]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/price-predictions-5-7-btc-eth-xrp-bnb-sol-doge-ada-sui-link-avax</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/price-predictions-5-7-btc-eth-xrp-bnb-sol-doge-ada-sui-link-avax?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-07T17:06:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Key points:

Bitcoin price hangs near $97,000 as traders await today’s FOMC minutes.

Bitcoin holding $95,000 as support is key for bullish price expansion in the short term.

Select altcoins are holding their respective support levels, opening the gates for a short-term rally.

Bitcoin (BTC) bulls are trying to knock down the immediate resistance at $97,895 and challenge the all-important $100,000 level. Crypto analytics platform Santiment said in a post on X that Bitcoin wallets holding between 10 and 10,000 Bitcoin are positive about further gains as they have acquired 81,338 Bitcoin over the past six weeks.
Investors have also been piling into BlackRock’s spot Bitcoin exchange-traded fund for the past 16 days, which has boosted its new capital inflows to about $4.7 billion, according t…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Rakesh Upadhyay</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bybit recovers liquidity levels 30 days after hack — Kaiko]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/bybit-recovers-liquidity-30-days-after-hack</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/bybit-recovers-liquidity-30-days-after-hack?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-07T16:50:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Bybit exchange has recovered its liquidity to pre-hack levels just 30 days following the February 2025 attack that drained nearly $1.5 billion in funds.
According to a report from crypto research and analytics firm Kaiko, Bitcoin's (BTC) 1% market depth, a measure of liquidity, returned to pre-hack levels of around $13 million per day in March 2025.
Bitcoin liquidity on Bybit exchange rebounds to pre-hack levels. Source: Kaiko
Altcoin liquidity levels on the exchange have been slower to recover than Bitcoin but have rebounded to around 80% of the pre-hack levels. The authors of the Kaiko report added:
"This lag is largely due to the risk-off market environment, which has impacted altcoins more severely. While Bitcoin is still seen as a risky asset, it remains the crypto market’s safe h…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Vince Quill</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trump memecoin dinner attendees could include foreign nationals — Report]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/donald-trump-memecoin-dinner-foreign</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/donald-trump-memecoin-dinner-foreign?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-07T16:14:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At least some of the top holders of Donald Trump’s memecoin who apply to attend a private dinner with the president could be based outside the United States.
According to a May 7 Bloomberg report based on an analysis of the top TRUMP tokenholders, 19 of the top 25 wallets on the leaderboard used foreign exchanges that exclude US-based customers, suggesting either foreign nationals or Americans living abroad. In addition, more than half of the top 220 holders — the group eligible to apply for a dinner with the president — also used exchanges in other countries.
Top 10 TRUMP memecoin holders as of May. 7. Source: Trump meme
As of May 7, the identities of the top tokenholders and those who might choose to apply for the May 22 Trump dinner and “special VIP tour” were unknown. However, the proj…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Turner Wright</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Create and edit images with Gemini 2.0 in preview]]></title>
        <id>https://developers.googleblog.com/en/generate-images-gemini-2-0-flash-preview/</id>
        <link href="https://developers.googleblog.com/en/generate-images-gemini-2-0-flash-preview/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-07T16:06:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ghost students are creating problems for California colleges]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sfgate.com/bayarea/article/ghost-students-creating-problem-calif-colleges-20311708.php</id>
        <link href="https://www.sfgate.com/bayarea/article/ghost-students-creating-problem-calif-colleges-20311708.php"/>
        <updated>2025-05-07T16:05:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin $1B daily realized profits signal &#039;late-stage bull market&#039;]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-1b-daily-realized-profits-signal-late-stage-bull-market</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-1b-daily-realized-profits-signal-late-stage-bull-market?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-07T15:52:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Key points:

Bitcoin investors are making the most of the highest price levels in several months by cashing out profits.

These are averaging $1 billion per day, leading to concerns that the market comeback may stall or even reverse.

Institutional participation has not led to a change in mindset, CryptoQuant says.

Bitcoin (BTC) risks a “local top or sharp correction” if current levels of profit-taking continue, new research warns.
In a “Quicktake” blog post on May 8, onchain analytics platform CryptoQuant flagged elevated realized profits among BTC investors.
BTC profit-taking spikes to January highs
Bitcoin realized profits have spiked to multimonth highs this week as BTC/USD reached close to $98,000.
For CryptoQuant, the market is becoming comparable to late 2024, when the pair broke t…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by William Suberg</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Code a Dropbox Clone with NextJS]]></title>
        <id>681b80ee1a1a4e16cffa1a50</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/code-a-dropbox-clone-with-nextjs/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-07T15:49:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Building modern full-stack applications requires a strong grasp of various interconnected technologies. And what better way to learn than by creating a real-world project that mimics a widely used tool like Dropbox? That’s exactly what this new cours...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase Earnings Pain Likely as Retail Activity Slumps, Wall Street Analysts Warn]]></title>
        <id>912e4e4f-e38f-4547-9cb7-486932144db5</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/07/coinbase-earnings-pain-likely-as-retail-activity-slumps-wall-street-analysts-warn"/>
        <updated>2025-05-07T15:48:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Barclays, JPMorgan, Compass Point and Oppenheimer all cut their first-quarter forecasts last month, citing weaker crypto trading.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Helene Braun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Roundtables: A New Look at AI’s Energy Use]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1116168</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/05/07/1116168/roundtables-a-new-look-at-ais-energy-use/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-07T15:38:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Wednesday, May 21, 2025 Big Tech’s appetite for energy is growing rapidly as adoption of AI accelerates. But just how much energy does even a single AI query use? And what does it mean for the climate? Join editor in chief Mat Honan, senior climate reporter Casey Crownhart, and AI reporter James O’Donnell for a…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>MIT Technology Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase's SEC Documents Reveal NY Attorney General Wanted ETH Declared Security]]></title>
        <id>69b783b1-ca61-4831-b830-a719c8bd102b</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2025/05/07/coinbase-s-sec-documents-reveal-ny-attorney-general-wanted-eth-declared-security"/>
        <updated>2025-05-07T15:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On the U.S. exchange's online site for the documents obtained by Freedom of Information Act requests, it's illuminating some internal SEC discussions.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jesse Hamilton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Show HN: eInk optimized manga with Kindle Comic Converter (+Kobo/ReMarkable)]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/ciromattia/kcc</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/ciromattia/kcc"/>
        <updated>2025-05-07T15:26:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Payments App Strike to Offer BTC Lending in Boost to Reemergent Sector]]></title>
        <id>db54278f-0757-4780-8a71-9319008444d2</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2025/05/07/bitcoin-payments-app-strike-to-offer-btc-lending-in-boost-to-reemergent-sector"/>
        <updated>2025-05-07T15:26:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA["You shouldn’t have to sell the best-performing asset in human history to access cash. Now you don't have to," founder Jack Mallers wrote.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Crawley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why One of Uniswap DAO’s Most Outspoken Members Just Walked Away in Frustration]]></title>
        <id>00ab9546-ba9a-4b93-ab7e-b2f74f6061bd</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/tech/2025/05/07/why-one-of-uniswap-dao-most-outspoken-members-just-walked-away-in-frustration"/>
        <updated>2025-05-07T15:25:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The situation highlights the struggle of balancing DeFi protocol interests.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tim Craig</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Market Reaction to Trump's Tariffs Signals a Broader Acceptance of Bitcoin's ‘Digital Gold’ Narrative]]></title>
        <id>f5509ba1-2471-421e-849b-eec2ea48e7e5</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/coindesk-indices/2025/05/07/the-market-reaction-to-trump-s-tariffs-signals-a-broader-acceptance-of-bitcoin-s-digital-gold-narrative"/>
        <updated>2025-05-07T15:20:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The response of bitcoin prices to the destabilizing announcement of U.S. tariffs in April suggests the digital asset may be achieving one of its fundamental promises, says Hashdex’s Gerry O’Shea.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gerry O’Shea</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ether ETFs and Institutional Staking: What’s at Stake?]]></title>
        <id>b6327ea8-559a-4267-bcea-66519012cb34</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/coindesk-indices/2025/05/07/ether-etfs-and-institutional-staking-what-s-at-stake"/>
        <updated>2025-05-07T15:18:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The rise of staking represents a critical point in Ethereum’s development, says SenseiNode’s Pablo Larguía.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pablo Larguía</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mistral comes out swinging for enterprise AI customers with new Le Chat Enterprise, Medium 3 model]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3006803</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/mistral-comes-out-swinging-for-enterprise-ai-customers-with-new-le-chat-enterprise-medium-3-model/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-07T15:13:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mistral AI is making a concerted push to lower the barriers to scalable, privacy-respecting AI adoption for modern enterprises.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carl Franzen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Recursive Types in TypeScript: A Brief Exploration]]></title>
        <id>681b77a47396438eaee0c5ce</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/recursive-types-in-typescript-a-brief-exploration/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-07T15:09:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It is said that there are two different worlds in TypeScript that exist side by side: the type world and the value world. Consider this line of code: const firstName: string = 'Maynard'; While firstName and 'Maynard' live in the value world, string ...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eda Eren</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SocialFi has failed to take off — Here&#039;s what needs to change]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/social-fi-has-failed-to-take-off</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/social-fi-has-failed-to-take-off?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-07T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Opinion by: Anurag Arjun, co-founder of Avail 
On paper, SocialFi is a no-brainer. It promises to shift the balance of power in social media — giving people control over how their content and personal data are used and monetized. It even offers users a stake in the $200+ billion social media advertising market, a pie currently devoured almost entirely by giants like Meta.
And yet, SocialFi platforms today feel more like digital ghost towns than the bustling hubs of Web2. Friend.tech, hailed as a breakout star in 2023, peaked at just 80,000 daily active users before falling below 10,000. What's holding SocialFi back? Why does it seem to be following Friend.tech's fade into obscurity rather than rising to rival Facebook's dominance?
The harsh reality is that decentralized social networks hav…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Anurag Arjun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Waiting for Postgres 18: Accelerating Disk Reads with Asynchronous I/O]]></title>
        <id>https://pganalyze.com/blog/postgres-18-async-io</id>
        <link href="https://pganalyze.com/blog/postgres-18-async-io"/>
        <updated>2025-05-07T14:57:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WeightWatchers files bankruptcy]]></title>
        <id>https://www.wsj.com/articles/weightwatchers-files-bankruptcy-to-adapt-to-chemically-induced-weight-loss-future-a63aa8ac</id>
        <link href="https://www.wsj.com/articles/weightwatchers-files-bankruptcy-to-adapt-to-chemically-induced-weight-loss-future-a63aa8ac"/>
        <updated>2025-05-07T14:44:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Safeheron introduces open-source Intel SGX TEE framework for Web3 security]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/safeheron-intel-sgx-tee-framework-web3-security</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/safeheron-intel-sgx-tee-framework-web3-security?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-07T14:43:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Safeheron, a digital asset infrastructure provider based in Singapore, has introduced an open-source Trusted Execution Environment (TEE) framework. This solution could bolster security and privacy for Web3 in sectors like decentralized finance (DeFi), payment services, and decentralized autonomous organizations.
The TEE framework is the first built upon the native Intel SGX SDK and developed using modern C++, a general-purpose object-oriented programming language often used for operating systems, game development, and high-powered computing.
Safeheron decided to open-source the framework because the company had seen growing concerns across the industry about closed, opaque systems, especially as security incidents have become more widespread.
Related: Fully onchain AI agents can be the key…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Christopher Tepedino</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Can XRP price reach $4 in May? Analysts are watching these key levels]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/can-xrp-price-rise-to-4-in-may-watch-these-key-levels-analysts</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/can-xrp-price-rise-to-4-in-may-watch-these-key-levels-analysts?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-07T14:39:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Key takeaways:

XRP price is up 2% on May 7, buoyed by US-China trade talk optimism, with key support at $2.08 critical for sustained recovery.

Whale accumulation signals XRP price strength.

XRP price must hold above $1.83–$2.00 support to continue upside, analysts say.

XRP (XRP) price displayed strength on May 7, rising 2% over the last 24 hours after news of possible US-China trade talks flipped investor sentiment. 
XRP price remains above $2.00 at the time of writing, as several analysts highlight the key support levels the asset should hold for a sustainable recovery to new all-time highs.
Whale accumulation supports bullish XRP view
Certain indicators show that XRP’s ongoing price rise may not be just a short-term reaction to the positive macroeconomic news. 
For instance, Santimen…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Nancy Lubale</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mistral ships le chat – enterprise AI assistant that can run on prem]]></title>
        <id>https://mistral.ai/news/le-chat-enterprise</id>
        <link href="https://mistral.ai/news/le-chat-enterprise"/>
        <updated>2025-05-07T14:24:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The business of the future is adaptive]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1116098</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/05/07/1116098/the-business-of-the-future-is-adaptive/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-07T14:14:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Manufacturing is in a state of flux. From supply chain disruptions to rising costs, tougher environmental regulations, and a changing consumer market, the sector faces a series of competing challenges. But a new way of operating offers a way to tackle complexities head-on: adaptive production hardwires flexibility and resilience into the enterprise, drawing on powerful…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>MIT Technology Review Insights</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Revolut to Roll Out Bitcoin Lightning Payments for Europe Users Through Lightspark]]></title>
        <id>95a8b419-f6e0-4cda-8a3f-462a9889c751</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2025/05/07/revolut-to-roll-out-bitcoin-lightning-payments-for-europe-users-through-lightspark"/>
        <updated>2025-05-07T13:51:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The integration will offer users cheaper, faster transactions using Lightspark's payment infrastructure built on top of the Bitcoin-based Lightning Network.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Krisztian Sandor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Front-End Performance Optimization Handbook – Tips and Strategies for Devs]]></title>
        <id>681b5e61b1ed0b90facd0adf</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/the-front-end-performance-optimization-handbook/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-07T13:21:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When you’re building a website, you’ll want it to be responsive, fast, and efficient. This means making sure the site loads quickly, runs smoothly, and provides a seamless experience for your users, among other things. So as you build, you’ll want to...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gordan Tan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Growing Institutional Adoption of Crypto: An Interview with Nick Hammer, CEO, BlockFills]]></title>
        <id>04dd0ef8-871a-4012-8a82-a2c9f495bef6</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/coindesk-indices/2025/05/07/the-growing-institutional-adoption-of-crypto-an-interview-with-nick-hammer-ceo-blockfills"/>
        <updated>2025-05-07T13:19:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Institutions are starting to embrace crypto as a legitimate investment, helping drive mainstream acceptance and foster needed regulatory clarity.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kim Greenberg Klemballa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Visa invests in stablecoin payment platform BVNK amid pro-crypto push]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/visa-invests-in-stablecoin-payment-platfrom</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/visa-invests-in-stablecoin-payment-platfrom?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-07T13:16:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Payments behemoth Visa has invested in BVNK, a London-based startup focused on stablecoin payment infrastructure, signaling continued interest in digital asset innovation.
According to a May 7 BVNK announcement, the startup “secured a strategic investment from Visa through their Visa Ventures arm.” Furthermore, while the company does not explain fully what it entails, it refers to the investment as “more than capital” and describes it as a partnership. The company’s CEO, Jesse Hemson-Struthers, wrote:
“I’m particularly excited about what it means to partner with Visa—the original payments innovator. Their deep expertise in building global payment networks, combined with our stablecoin infrastructure, creates powerful possibilities for redefining how businesses operate in today’s digital ec…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Adrian Zmudzinski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CoinDesk 20 Performance Update: Litecoin (LTC) Gains 7.7%, Leading Index Higher]]></title>
        <id>8fc2d421-84ea-4be5-8706-3c1029d25301</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/coindesk-indices/2025/05/07/coindesk-20-performance-update-litecoin-ltc-gains-7-7-leading-index-higher"/>
        <updated>2025-05-07T13:09:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sui (SUI) joined Litecoin (LTC) as a top performer, gaining 3.9%.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CoinDesk Indices</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Exchange Gemini Hires Brad Vopni to Lead Institutional Push]]></title>
        <id>a01eb598-0050-44de-aefe-b72e14e7431a</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2025/05/07/crypto-exchange-gemini-hires-brad-vopni-to-lead-institutional-push"/>
        <updated>2025-05-07T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Vopni will be responsible for overseeing and executing the firm's institutional strategy.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Will Canny</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blockchain ‘Baddies’ on how to bring more women into crypto]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/women-in-web3-how-to-bring-more-women-into-crypto</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/women-in-web3-how-to-bring-more-women-into-crypto?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-07T12:53:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In an industry filled with complexity, jargon and mistrust, women in Web3 say that the way to attract more women into the crypto space starts with clarity, education and community. 
At the Blockchain Baddies side event during Token2049 in Dubai, women shared personal experiences of entering the Web3 world and why they believe more female participation is essential for the future of crypto.
In interviews with Cointelegraph, community members said the path forward begins with simplifying technical concepts and fostering environments where women can learn and grow.  
Women in Web3 share experiences in the crypto space. Source: Cointelegraph
From providing clarity to building skills 
From simplifying technical language to creating safe spaces for learning, women in Web3 said that demystifying …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Ezra Reguerra</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trump-backed USD1 is now the seventh-largest stablecoin worldwide]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/trump-backed-usd1-is-now-the-seventh-largest-stablecoin-worldwide</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/trump-backed-usd1-is-now-the-seventh-largest-stablecoin-worldwide?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-07T12:45:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[USD1, the US dollar stablecoin launched by the President Donald Trump-backed World Liberty Financial (WLFI), has become the seventh-largest stablecoin worldwide in just two months since its launch.
WLFI’s snapshot vote for a USD1 airdrop proposal is underway, and USD1’s market capitalization has continued to climb.
Launched in early March with a $3.5 million supply, USD1 has expanded into a market cap of $2.2 billion at the time of writing, leaving rival stablecoins First Digital USD (FDUSD), PayPal USD (PYUSD) and Tether Gold (XAUT) behind, according to data from CoinGecko.
Top 10 stablecoins by market capitalization. Source: CoinGecko
Although rising fast, the USD1 market cap is still far from the market value of major stablecoins like Tether’s USDt (USDT) and USDC (USDC), whose market c…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Helen Partz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Breathe lands $21M Series B to predict battery performance]]></title>
        <id>https://techcrunch.com/?p=3003769</id>
        <link href="https://techcrunch.com/2025/05/07/breathe-lands-21m-series-b-to-predict-battery-performance/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-07T12:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Breathe has developed a suite of tools that it says helps automakers and others get the most out of their batteries.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tim De Chant</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Netflix unveils new TV experience with GenAI search and AI-based recommendations]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3006789</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/games/netflix-unveils-new-tv-experience-with-genai-search-and-ai-based-recommendations/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-07T12:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Netflix unveiled its new TV experience that features generative AI search, AI-based recommendations and an enhanced design.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dean Takahashi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Asus ROG Ally 2 Leaks; Features Up To AMD Ryzen Z2 Extreme, 64GB LPDDR5 RAM]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=350817</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/350817/asus-rog-ally-2-leaks-features-up-to-amd-ryzen-z2-extreme-64gb-lpddr5-ram/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-07T12:14:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Pictures allegedly showing off the ASUS ROG Ally 2, plus technical specifications, have made their way to the internet. Supposedly, the company will be launching two versions of the gaming handhelds. The (partial) hardware specs reveal that the ROG Ally 2 will be equipped with AMD’s latest Ryzen Z2 SoCs. More precisely, one will be […]
The post Asus ROG Ally 2 Leaks; Features Up To AMD Ryzen Z2 Extreme, 64GB LPDDR5 RAM appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John Law</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Download: Neuralink’s AI boost, and Trump’s tariffs]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1116147</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/05/07/1116147/the-download-neuralinks-ai-boost-and-trumps-tariffs/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-07T12:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is today’s edition of The Download, our weekday newsletter that provides a daily dose of what’s going on in the world of technology. This patient’s Neuralink brain implant gets a boost from generative AI Last November, Bradford G. Smith got a brain implant from Elon Musk’s company Neuralink. The device, a set of thin wires attached…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rhiannon Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Accumulation Strengthens as BTC Approaches Key Resistance]]></title>
        <id>e0706a07-f53d-4b58-bc23-9af837d74a1c</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/07/bitcoin-accumulation-strengthens-as-btc-approaches-key-resistance"/>
        <updated>2025-05-07T12:05:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On-chain data reveals rising confidence among both long- and short-term holders, with $99.9K flagged as a potential profit-taking zone.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>James Van Straten</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Visa Doubles Down on Stablecoins With Investment in Blockchain Payments Firm BVNK]]></title>
        <id>49c7af19-d985-4e21-88b1-1d5ae6be5c30</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2025/05/07/visa-doubles-down-on-stablecoins-with-investment-in-blockchain-payments-firm-bvnk"/>
        <updated>2025-05-07T11:59:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The deal follows BVNK's $50 million fundraising round that included Haun Ventures, Coinbase Ventures and Tiger Global.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Krisztian Sandor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto miner deserts Pennsylvania site, fails to plug wells: Report]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/diversified-energy-crypto-mine-abandonment-pennsylvania</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/diversified-energy-crypto-mine-abandonment-pennsylvania?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-07T11:52:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency miner Diversified Energy quietly vacated a natural gas-powered crypto mining site in Elk County, Pennsylvania, reportedly leaving behind unplugged wells and regulatory violations.
The site, known as Longhorn Pad A, was revived in 2022 after sitting dormant for nearly a decade when Diversified began using it to fuel on-site generators powering cryptocurrency mining computers, according to a report by the Erie Times-News.
Per the report, the operation was launched without obtaining an air quality permit from the Pennsylvania Department of Environmental Protection (DEP).
Though the company was later granted the permit in December 2023, a March 2025 inspection revealed that Diversified had already removed the mining infrastructure.
Empty metallic sheds and missing production equ…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Amin Haqshanas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Massive Bitcoin Bull Run Ahead? Two Chart Patterns Mirror BTC's Rally to $109K]]></title>
        <id>cf53ad6d-1024-4364-8b60-0bef4e44525d</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/07/massive-bitcoin-bull-run-ahead-two-chart-patterns-mirror-btc-s-rally-to-usd109k"/>
        <updated>2025-05-07T11:42:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Key bearish indicators recently trapped bears on the wrong side of the market in a pattern observed in August-September 2024.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Omkar Godbole</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Daybook Americas: Powell Will Set the Tone While Markets Eye Asia Battles, Trade]]></title>
        <id>de5f06a2-3f43-4f20-bcc8-0036243fe753</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/daybook-us/2025/05/07/crypto-daybook-americas-powell-will-set-the-tone-while-markets-eye-asia-battles-trade"/>
        <updated>2025-05-07T11:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Your day-ahead look for May 7, 2025]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Francisco Rodrigues</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CelcomDigi’s Skuad 5G Brings Malaysia’s Widest and Fastest Network to Borneo’s Rainforests]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=350827</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/350827/celcomdigi-skuad-5g-borneo/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-07T11:17:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The lush rainforests of Malaysian Borneo are witnessing a new era of connectivity, as CelcomDigi’s Skuad 5G team reaches a major milestone in their nationwide journey. In doing so, they are delivering Malaysia’s No. 1 Widest and Fastest Network to communities across Sabah and Sarawak. Beyond Signal Bars: A Mission Of Connection This initiative goes […]
The post CelcomDigi’s Skuad 5G Brings Malaysia’s Widest and Fastest Network to Borneo’s Rainforests appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Newsdesk</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[My quest to make motorcycle riding that tad bit safer]]></title>
        <id>https://gill.net.in/posts/my-quest-to-make-motorcycle-riding-safer/</id>
        <link href="https://gill.net.in/posts/my-quest-to-make-motorcycle-riding-safer/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-07T11:06:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MOG Coin Rallies as Elon Musk, Garry Tan Embrace ‘Mog/Acc’ Identity]]></title>
        <id>f948c5b4-e927-438c-b36d-2a6230978ea2</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/07/mog-coin-rallies-as-elon-musk-garry-tan-embrace-mog-acc-identity"/>
        <updated>2025-05-07T10:42:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The “mog/acc” is quickly gaining ground among everyone from Elon Musk to Garry Tan, a move that bumps the project’s visibility - and eventually prices.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shaurya Malwa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TnG Unveils Exclusive Hot Wheels NFC Card For MAS 2025]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=350866</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/350866/tng-exclusive-hot-wheels-card-mas-2025/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-07T10:22:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In conjunction with this year’s Malaysia Auto Show (MAS 2025), Touch ’n Go (TnG) has unveiled a new limited-edition NFC card featuring Hot Wheels designs. The card is only available for purchase during the auto show for a price of RM25 starting from 9 to 15 May 2025, with only 3,000 units available. This is […]
The post TnG Unveils Exclusive Hot Wheels NFC Card For MAS 2025 appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Keran</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum Activates ‘Pectra’ Upgrade, Raising Max Stake to 2,048 ETH]]></title>
        <id>4fced237-427d-441f-b8d6-883edd499464</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/tech/2025/05/07/ethereum-activates-pectra-upgrade-raising-max-stake-to-2048-eth"/>
        <updated>2025-05-07T10:08:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The update aims to streamline staking, enhance wallet functionality, and improve overall efficiency.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Margaux Nijkerk</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin-backed loans ‘obvious’ next step — Xapo Bank CEO]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-backed-loans-growth-xapo-bank-ceo</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-backed-loans-growth-xapo-bank-ceo?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-07T10:03:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin holders are becoming more comfortable borrowing against their crypto as market confidence grows, according to Seamus Rocca, CEO of the Gibraltar-based private bank, Xapo Bank. 
In an interview at the Token2049 event in Dubai, Rocca told Cointelegraph that with Bitcoin (BTC) hovering around $95,000 and institutional adoption starting to catch on, the mood among investors has shifted from short-term speculation to a more long-term outlook. 
“I’m not sure that confidence would have been there three or four years ago,” Rocca told Cointelegraph. “But today, people are more comfortable to borrow against Bitcoin because we’re nowhere near the levels that would trigger liquidation.”
On March 18, Xapo Bank launched a lending product that allows users to borrow US dollars using their Bitcoin…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Ezra Reguerra</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why is Bitcoin price up today?]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/why-is-bitcoin-price-up-today</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/why-is-bitcoin-price-up-today?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-07T09:57:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Key takeaways:

Bitcoin gained 2% to $96,530 on May 7, fueled by US-China trade deal hopes.

BTC price rises with $83.6 million in short liquidations, with open interest up 26% to $64.4 billion, signaling strong bullish momentum.

A classic bullish reversal pattern is still in play, targeting BTC price at $100,000 and beyond.

Bitcoin (BTC) is up today, rising over 3% in the last 24 hours to over $97,000 on May 7. Its daily trading volume has jumped 37% to $31.7 billion.
BTC/USD daily chart. Source: Cointelegraph/TradingView
Let’s take a look at the factors driving Bitcoin price up today.
Bitcoin rises on hopes of a US-China trade deal
Bitcoin briefly hit $97,700 during the early Asian trading hours on May 7, driven by optimism over potential US-China trade talks. 
Disclosing plans to trav…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Nancy Lubale</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin miner Hive taps Paraguay for low-cost energy partnership]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/hive-digital-expands-bitcoin-mining-paraguay-latam</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/hive-digital-expands-bitcoin-mining-paraguay-latam?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-07T09:54:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Several crypto-focused organizations — including Bitcoin (BTC) mining companies — are eyeing a US return, primarily driven by uncertain geopolitical tensions. Still, BTC miner Hive Digital Technologies is doubling down on the untapped potential of the Latin American (LATAM) market.
In an exclusive interview with Cointelegraph, Hive Digital Technologies’ president and CEO, Aydin Kilic, said that Paraguay presents a compelling long-term opportunity equipped with “geopolitical stability, low-cost hydro energy, and a government open to foreign investment”.
Picking up from where Bitfarms left off
Hive acquired Bitfarms’ 200 megawatt (MW) Yguazú facility for $56 million in January. Phase one infrastructure of a 100 MW data center at the site was completed in April, supporting five exahashes per …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Lyne Qian</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[So Much Blood]]></title>
        <id>https://dynomight.net/blood/</id>
        <link href="https://dynomight.net/blood/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-07T09:41:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Malaysia Airlines and Batik Air Suspend, Cancel Flights Amid India-Pakistan Conflict]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=350823</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/350823/malaysia-airlines-batik-air-suspend-cancel-flights-india-pakistan-conflict/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-07T09:38:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Malaysia Airlines and Batik Air have suspended flights to and from Amritsar, India due to heightened tensions in the region. Both airlines have cited security and safety concerns as reasons for the cancellations, promising to monitor the situation closely. In addition to suspending flights between Kuala Lumpur and Amritsar, Malaysia Airlines had rerouted flights MH2 […]
The post Malaysia Airlines and Batik Air Suspend, Cancel Flights Amid India-Pakistan Conflict appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nurul Kamil</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Volvo Announces The XC70 As Its First Range-Extended PHEV]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=350825</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/350825/volvo-announces-the-xc70-as-its-first-range-extended-phev/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-07T09:28:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Volvo XC70 is returning as the company’s first Range-Extended Plug-In Hybrid (RE-PHEV). The automaker claims that it will be able to provide up to 200km of pure CLTC electric range, meaning it will be available for in China first. Nevertheless, the automaker did mention that it is exploring the possibility of introducing it in […]
The post Volvo Announces The XC70 As Its First Range-Extended PHEV appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Keran</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BlackRock’s Spot Bitcoin ETF Tops World’s Largest Gold Fund in Inflows This Year]]></title>
        <id>23fb8d69-5ee0-4462-9f62-2f67830e1ec7</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/07/blackrock-s-spot-bitcoin-etf-tops-world-s-largest-gold-fund-in-inflows-this-year"/>
        <updated>2025-05-07T09:24:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[IBIT's outperformance indicates institutions' confidence in bitcoin's long-term prospects despite the cryptocurrency's relatively dour price performance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Omkar Godbole</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[KTMB Adds Train Service To East Coast For Hari Raya Aidiladha]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=350854</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/350854/ktmb-adds-train-service-to-east-coast-for-hari-raya-aidiladha/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-07T09:21:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In conjunction with Hari Raya Aidiladha taking place next month, Keretapi Tanah Melayu Berhad (KTMB) has added a special train service to the East Coast. This was apparently done to accommodate travellers returning home for the religious holiday. According to KTMB’s statement today, the KTMB Ekspres Lambaian Aidiladha will have two scheduled services, with 436 […]
The post KTMB Adds Train Service To East Coast For Hari Raya Aidiladha appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Newsdesk</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This patient’s Neuralink brain implant gets a boost from generative AI]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1116139</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/05/07/1116139/this-brain-implant-gets-a-boost-from-generative-ai/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-07T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Last November, Bradford G. Smith got a brain implant from Elon Musk’s company Neuralink. The device, a set of thin wires attached to a computer about the thickness of a few quarters that sits in his skull, lets him use his thoughts to move a computer pointer on a screen.  And by last week he…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Antonio Regalado</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Metaplanet Lifts Bitcoin Stash by 555 BTC, Plans to Sell Debt to Buy More]]></title>
        <id>179bb279-b719-4ecd-b59c-644f2f0c72b0</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/07/metaplanet-lifts-bitcoin-stash-by-555-btc-plans-to-sell-debt-to-buy-more"/>
        <updated>2025-05-07T08:55:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Tokyo-based company earmarked the entire offering for EVO FUND only days after previously selling $25 million in bonds to the same buyer.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Crawley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Zed: High-performance AI Code Editor]]></title>
        <id>https://zed.dev/blog/fastest-ai-code-editor</id>
        <link href="https://zed.dev/blog/fastest-ai-code-editor"/>
        <updated>2025-05-07T06:38:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS report: Generative AI overtakes security in global tech budgets for 2025]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3006670</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/aws-report-generative-ai-overtakes-security-in-global-tech-budgets-for-2025/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T21:33:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New AWS report reveals 45% of global IT leaders now prioritize generative AI over cybersecurity in 2025 tech budgets as companies race to hire AI talent and implement AI strategies despite persistent skills shortages.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Nuñez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Secure Mobile APIs in Flutter]]></title>
        <id>681a707658599a397b11b418</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-secure-mobile-apis-in-flutter/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T20:26:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As mobile applications continue to evolve in functionality and scope, securing the APIs that power these apps has become more critical than ever. In the context of Flutter, a framework that enables cross-platform development, understanding how to sec...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Atuoha Anthony</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meet the new king of AI coding: Google’s Gemini 2.5 Pro I/O Edition dethrones Claude 3.7 Sonnet]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3006623</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/meet-the-new-king-of-ai-coding-googles-gemini-2-5-pro-i-o-edition-dethrones-claude-3-7-sonnet/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T18:39:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One of the standout features of the update is its ability to build full, interactive web apps or simulations from a single prompt.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carl Franzen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Create Documentation with docs.page – A Beginner's Tutorial]]></title>
        <id>681a558b9791d0e469b84519</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-create-documentation-with-docspage/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T18:31:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One of the most tedious tasks for every startup, company, and open-source project is often building and managing documentation – especially for medium to large-scale documentation websites. docs.page is an open-source documentation tool that helps yo...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rajdeep Singh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lightricks just made AI video generation 30x faster — and you won’t need a $10,000 GPU]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3006613</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/lightricks-just-made-ai-video-generation-30x-faster-and-you-wont-need-a-10000-gpu/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T17:56:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Lightricks unveils groundbreaking LTXV-13B AI video model that runs 30X faster than competitors on consumer hardware through innovative "multiscale rendering" technology.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Nuñez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ServiceNow lets users see more of their AI]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3006589</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/servicenow-lets-users-see-more-of-their-ai/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ServiceNow also announced a way for agents to communicate with others along with its new observability platform.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Emilia David</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build Your Own Local AI: Create Free RAG and AI Agents with Qwen 3 and Ollama]]></title>
        <id>681a35d4d5da806f5e9467b1</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-a-local-ai/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T16:16:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The landscape of Artificial Intelligence is rapidly evolving, and one of the most exciting trends is the ability to run powerful Large Language Models (LLMs) directly on your local machine. This shift away from reliance on cloud-based APIs offers sig...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chaitanya Rahalkar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A new hairlike electrode for long-term, high-quality EEG monitoring]]></title>
        <id>https://www.psu.edu/news/research/story/future-brain-activity-monitoring-may-look-strand-hair</id>
        <link href="https://www.psu.edu/news/research/story/future-brain-activity-monitoring-may-look-strand-hair"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T15:53:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Create Serverless AI Agents with Langbase Docs MCP Server in Minutes]]></title>
        <id>681a2ce0aebfc718f4e6da03</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-create-serverless-ai-agents-with-langbase-docs-mcp-server-in-minutes/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T15:38:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Building serverless AI agents has recently become a lot simpler. With the Langbase Docs MCP server, you can instantly connect AI models to Langbase documentation – making it easy to build composable, agentic AI systems with memory without complex inf...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maham Codes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Report: OpenAI is buying AI-powered developer platform Windsurf — what happens to its support for rival LLMs?]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3006587</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/report-openai-is-buying-ai-powered-developer-platform-windsurf-what-happens-to-its-support-for-rival-llms/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T14:37:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[OpenAI could see which types of developers use rival models such as the Meta Llama variants and Anthropic's Claude, and for what purposes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carl Franzen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Startup Korl unveils multimodal, multi-agent tool for custom communication across disparate systems]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3006451</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/how-openai-gemini-and-anthropic-help-korl-prepare-customer-materials-in-minutes/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Korl's platform works across multiple systems, using multi-agent and multimodal AI to create highly-customized customer messaging.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Taryn Plumb</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ōura adds AI-driven meal and glucose tracking features with Stelo by Dexcom]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3006449</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/games/oura-adds-ai-driven-meal-and-glucose-tracking-features-with-stelo-by-dexcom/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ōura, maker of a health-monitoring smart ring, announced that it will use AI to track and analyze two new metabolic health features: meals and glucose.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dean Takahashi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Download: a longevity influencer’s new religion, and humanoid robots’ shortcomings]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1116114</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/05/06/1116114/the-download-a-longevity-influencers-new-religion-and-humanoid-robots-shortcomings/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T12:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is today’s edition of The Download, our weekday newsletter that provides a daily dose of what’s going on in the world of technology. Bryan Johnson wants to start a new religion in which “the body is God” Bryan Johnson is on a mission to not die. The 47-year-old multimillionaire has already applied his slogan “Don’t Die”…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rhiannon Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Inheritance was invented as a performance hack]]></title>
        <id>https://catern.com/inheritance.html</id>
        <link href="https://catern.com/inheritance.html"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T10:59:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NSA spied through Angry Birds, other apps: report (2014)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nbcnews.com/tech/tech-news/nsa-spied-through-angry-birds-other-apps-report-flna2d12006530</id>
        <link href="https://www.nbcnews.com/tech/tech-news/nsa-spied-through-angry-birds-other-apps-report-flna2d12006530"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T10:34:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why the humanoid workforce is running late]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1116108</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/05/06/1116108/why-the-humanoid-workforce-is-running-late/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On Thursday I watched Daniela Rus, one of the world’s top experts on AI-powered robots, address a packed room at a Boston robotics expo. Rus spent a portion of her talk busting the notion that giant fleets of humanoids are already making themselves useful in manufacturing and warehouses around the world.  That might come as…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>James O'Donnell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Join the 2025 Web3j Mentorships: Build the Future of Ethereum on the JVM]]></title>
        <id>6819c8dc41eeeb000183d37b</id>
        <link href="https://blog.web3labs.com/join-the-2025-web3j-mentorships-build-the-future-of-ethereum-on-the-jvm/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T08:32:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Linux Foundation’s Decentralized Trust (LFDT) mentorship program is back in 2025 with two exciting opportunities for developers passionate about Ethereum, Android, and the Java Virtual Machine (JVM). Whether you’re a seasoned blockchain developer or an Android enthusiast eager to dive into Web3, these mentorships offer]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>George Tebrean</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[IBM thinks that over a billion new applications will be built with gen AI : Here’s how they’re going to help that happen with agentic AI]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3006455</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/agents-are-key-to-enterprise-ai-success-heres-ibms-plan-on-how-to-make-it-happen/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T04:01:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[IBM details its plans to help enterprises to actually do more with AI, with an expanded set of agentic AI capabilities.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sean Michael Kerner</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meta, Cisco put open-source LLMs at the core of next-gen SOC workflows]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3006384</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/rsac-2025-cisco-and-meta-put-open-source-ai-at-the-heart-of-enterprise-threat-defense/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T00:08:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cisco’s Foundation-sec-8B LLM & Meta’s AI Defenders redefine cybersecurity with open-source AI for scalable SOCs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Louis Columbus</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nvidia launches fully open source transcription AI model Parakeet-TDT-0.6B-V2 on Hugging Face]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3006438</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/nvidia-launches-fully-open-source-transcription-ai-model-parakeet-tdt-0-6b-v2-on-hugging-face/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-05T19:17:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An attractive proposition for commercial enterprises and indie developers looking to build speech recognition and transcription services...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carl Franzen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Improve Your C++ Skills by Coding an Audio Plugin]]></title>
        <id>68190b8f1abafc5ea9d7efbf</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/improve-you-c-skills-by-coding-an-audio-plugin/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-05T19:03:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Do you want to build a practical project to help improve your C++ skills? Have you ever wanted to create your own unique audio effects? Then diving into C++ audio plugin development with the JUCE framework might be your next great step We just publis...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Visa launches ‘Intelligent Commerce’ platform, letting AI agents swipe your card—safely, it says]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3006416</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/visa-launches-intelligent-commerce-platform-letting-ai-agents-swipe-your-card-safely-it-says/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-05T18:01:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Visa launches Intelligent Commerce platform enabling AI assistants to make secure purchases with your credit card, transforming online shopping with personalized automation and consumer-controlled spending limits.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Nuñez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build a Dynamic Wardrobe App with React Drag and Drop]]></title>
        <id>6818d1793c6be4514080aea9</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-build-a-dynamic-wardrobe-app-with-react-drag-and-drop/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-05T14:55:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Have you ever found yourself stuck deciding what color outfit to wear? Maybe you’re mixing and matching different tops and bottoms, unsure if the colors go together. It’s a common dilemma – so common that many of us turn to friends or family for a se...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Timothy Olanrewaju</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bryan Johnson wants to start a new religion in which “the body is God”]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1116090</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/05/05/1116090/bryan-johnson-new-religion-body-is-god/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-05T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bryan Johnson is on a mission to not die. The 47-year-old multimillionaire has already applied his slogan “Don’t Die” to events, merchandise, and a Netflix documentary. Now he’s founding a Don’t Die religion. Johnson, who famously spends millions of dollars on scans, tests, supplements, and a lifestyle routine designed to slow or reverse the aging…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jessica Hamzelou</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Show HN: Ductape – Build back end integrations once, reuse them anywhere]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ductape.app/</id>
        <link href="https://www.ductape.app/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-05T08:04:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bootstrapping Lisp in a Boot Sector]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/jart/sectorlisp</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/jart/sectorlisp"/>
        <updated>2025-05-05T07:52:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bell's 1881 Metal detector]]></title>
        <id>http://www.scitechantiques.com/belldiscovery/</id>
        <link href="http://www.scitechantiques.com/belldiscovery/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-04T22:24:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A cycle-accurate IBM PC emulator in your web browser]]></title>
        <id>https://martypc.net/?mount=fd:0:Area%205150%20(Compo%20Version).img</id>
        <link href="https://martypc.net/?mount=fd:0:Area%205150%20(Compo%20Version).img"/>
        <updated>2025-05-04T17:19:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The great cognitive migration: How AI is reshaping human purpose, work and meaning]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3006326</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/the-great-cognitive-migration-ai-will-win-at-intelligence-but-only-we-can-make-it-matter/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-04T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Humans need to embrace domains where AI still falters, and where human creativity, ethics and emotion emain indispensable.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gary Grossman, Edelman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Not everything needs an LLM: A framework for evaluating when AI makes sense]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3006312</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/not-everything-needs-an-llm-a-framework-for-evaluating-when-ai-makes-sense/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-03T19:35:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The answer to 'What customer needs requires an AI solution?' isn’t always 'Yes.' LLMs are still expensive and not always accurate.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sharanya Rao</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[RSAC 2025: Why the AI agent era means more demand for CISOs]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3006066</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/security/rsac-2025-why-the-ai-agent-era-means-more-demand-for-cisos/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-02T23:02:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[RSAC 2025 made one thing clear: AI agents are entering security workflows, but boards want proof they work.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Louis Columbus</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Write Good API Documentation]]></title>
        <id>68151f0be5850fcb8543375a</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-write-good-api-docs/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-02T19:37:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Imagine purchasing a standing fan straight out of the box, all parts dismantled, and you have no manual or guide to put them together. Did you imagine that just now? Cool. Here is another scenario: imagine purchasing an LG product, such as a smart TV...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Okoro Emmanuel Nzube</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OpenAI overrode concerns of expert testers to release sycophantic GPT-4o]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3006276</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/openai-overrode-concerns-of-expert-testers-to-release-sycophantic-gpt-4o/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-02T17:57:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Once again, it shows the importance of incorporating more domains beyond the traditional math and computer science into AI development.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carl Franzen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Roblox breaks ground on data center in Brazil for early 2026]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3006251</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/games/roblox-breaks-ground-on-data-center-in-brazil-for-early-2026/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-02T16:55:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At Gamescom Latam, Roblox announced it has broken ground on a new data center in Brazil -- slated to go live in early 2026.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dean Takahashi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Download: foreign disinformation intel, and gene-edited pork]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1116079</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/05/02/1116079/the-download-foreign-disinformation-intel-and-gene-edited-pork/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-02T12:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is today’s edition of The Download, our weekday newsletter that provides a daily dose of what’s going on in the world of technology. A senior State Department official demanded records of communications with journalists, European officials, and Trump critics A previously unreported document distributed by senior US State Department official Darren Beattie reveals a sweeping effort…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rhiannon Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The US has approved CRISPR pigs for food]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1116059</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/05/02/1116059/the-us-approves-crispr-pigs-for-food/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-02T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Most pigs in the US are confined to factory farms where they can be afflicted by a nasty respiratory virus that kills piglets. The illness is called porcine reproductive and respiratory syndrome, or PRRS. A few years ago, a British company called Genus set out to design pigs immune to this germ using CRISPR gene…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Antonio Regalado</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hidden costs in AI deployment: Why Claude models may be 20-30% more expensive than GPT in enterprise settings]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3006096</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/hidden-costs-in-ai-deployment-why-claude-models-may-be-20-30-more-expensive-than-gpt-in-enterprise-settings/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-01T20:14:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It is a well-known fact that different model families can use different tokenizers. However, there has been limited analysis on how the process of “tokenization” itself varies across these tokenizers. Do all tokenizers result in the same number of tokens for a given input text? If not, how different are the generated tokens? How significant […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lavanya Gupta</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Senior State Department official sought internal communications with journalists, European officials, and Trump critics]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1115988</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/05/01/1115988/senior-state-department-official-sought-internal-communications-with-journalists-european-officials-and-trump-critics/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-01T17:41:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A previously unreported document distributed by senior US State Department official Darren Beattie reveals a sweeping effort to uncover all communications between the staff of a small government office focused on online disinformation and a lengthy list of public and private figures—many of whom are longtime targets of the political right.  The document, originally shared…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eileen Guo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Astronomer’s $93M raise underscores a new reality: Orchestration is king in AI infrastructure]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3006195</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/astronomer-93m-raise-underscores-a-new-reality-orchestration-is-king-in-ai-infrastructure/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-01T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Astronomer secures $93 million in Series D funding to solve the AI implementation gap through data orchestration, helping enterprises streamline complex workflows and operationalize AI initiatives at scale.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Nuñez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft launches Phi-4-Reasoning-Plus, a small, powerful, open weights reasoning model!]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3006213</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/microsoft-launches-phi-4-reasoning-plus-a-small-powerful-open-weights-reasoning-model/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-01T12:41:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The release demonstrates that with carefully curated data and training techniques, small models can deliver strong reasoning performance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carl Franzen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Salesforce takes aim at ‘jagged intelligence’ in push for more reliable AI]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3006124</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/salesforce-tackles-jagged-intelligence-problem-with-new-ai-benchmarks-and-models/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-01T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Salesforce unveils groundbreaking AI research tackling "jagged intelligence," introducing new benchmarks, models, and guardrails to make enterprise AI agents more intelligent, trusted, and consistently reliable for business use.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Nuñez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[UiPath’s new orchestrator guides AI agents to follow your enterprise’s rules]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3006059</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/uipaths-new-orchestrator-guides-ai-agents-to-follow-your-enterprises-rules/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T21:20:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[UiPath's agent orchestration layer Maestro moves prompts through three layers: the agent, a human and the robotic process automation system.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Emilia David</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The ‘era of experience’ will unleash self-learning AI agents across the web—here’s how to prepare]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3005579</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/the-era-of-experience-will-unleash-self-learning-ai-agents-across-the-web-heres-how-to-prepare/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T20:38:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AI visionaries predict an 'Era of Experience' where AI learns autonomously, and it will have important implications for application design.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ben Dickson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Qwen swings for a double with 2.5-Omni-3B model that runs on consumer PCs, laptops]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3006114</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/qwen-swings-for-a-double-with-2-5-omni-3b-model-that-runs-on-consumer-pcs-laptops/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T20:31:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Qwen2.5-Omni-3B model is licensed for non-commercial use only under Alibaba Cloud’s Qwen Research License Agreement.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carl Franzen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Breaking the ‘intellectual bottleneck’: How AI is computing the previously uncomputable in healthcare]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3005667</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/breaking-the-intellectual-bottleneck-how-ai-is-computing-the-previously-uncomputible-in-healthcare/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T19:03:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How University of Texas Medical Branch is using AI to identify patients at high cardiovascular risk, flag for stroke and catch 'basic stuff.']]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Taryn Plumb</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Web3j Six Month Project Update]]></title>
        <id>68109495670a1300013504c2</id>
        <link href="https://blog.web3labs.com/web3j-six-month-project-update/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T09:10:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[November 2024 - April 2025
This report summarizes the activities and accomplishments of Web3j, an LF Decentralized Trust project, from November 2024 to April 2025. During this period, the project made significant strides in improving the framework’s functionality, enhancing user engagement, and bolstering overall community interaction. 
Key]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>George Tebrean</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[QuickNode: Building the Infrastructure for the Next Generation of Blockchain]]></title>
        <id>6807d5787fb8500001c39b99</id>
        <link href="https://blog.quicknode.com/quicknode-building-the-infrastructure-for-the-next-generation-of-blockchain/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-28T16:02:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Join QuickNode co-founder Dmitry Shklovsky as he discusses blockchain infrastructure, building decentralized applications, and the future of Web3 development on TheCube's Crypto Trailblazer Series.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>QuickNode</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>