<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2025-05-19T19:11:08.287Z</id>
    <title>AngJianming RSS Feed</title>
    <updated>2025-05-19T19:11:08.287Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Paul Atkins: &#039;Crypto markets have been languishing in SEC limbo&#039;]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/paul-atkins-crypto-markets-sec-limbo</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/paul-atkins-crypto-markets-sec-limbo?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T19:06:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In one of his first speeches since becoming chair of the US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) in April, Paul Atkins addressed some of the regulatory concerns around the cryptocurrency industry.
In prepared remarks for a May 19 speech, Atkins said it was a “new day” for the crypto industry under the current leadership of the SEC. He suggested that the financial regulator  would be more open to “adapt to and accommodate new developments” while still abiding by its statutes.
“The crypto markets have been languishing in SEC limbo for years,” said Atkins, adding:

“While I have directed Commission staff across our policy Divisions to begin drafting rule proposals related to crypto, the staff continue to ‘clear the brush’ through staff-level statements.”
Even before Atkins stepped into th…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Turner Wright</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incredible way to turn solitude into strategy.]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/zaramercer89/incredible-way-to-turn-solitude-into-strategy-36mk</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/zaramercer89/incredible-way-to-turn-solitude-into-strategy-36mk"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T18:59:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What Ashkan Rajaee Taught Me About Remote Work, Structure, and Focus
Reynaldo Dayola ・ May 13
#remote
        #productivity
        #workfromanywhere
        #saas]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Zara Mercer</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[🤖 AI Meets CLI: Let Amazon Q CLI Do the Work 🚀]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/aws-builders/ai-meets-cli-let-amazon-q-cli-do-the-work-3n61</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/aws-builders/ai-meets-cli-let-amazon-q-cli-do-the-work-3n61"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T18:49:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[👋 Hey there, tech enthusiasts! 
I'm Sarvar, a Cloud Architect with a passion for transforming complex technological challenges into elegant solutions. With extensive experience spanning Cloud Operations (AWS & Azure), Data Operations, Analytics, DevOps, and Generative AI, I've had the privilege of architecting solutions for global enterprises that drive real business impact. Through this article series, I'm excited to share practical insights, best practices, and hands-on experiences from my journey in the tech world. Whether you're a seasoned professional or just starting out, I aim to break down complex concepts into digestible pieces that you can apply in your projects.
Let's dive in and explore the fascinating world of cloud technology together! 🚀
The way we write and test code is ch…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sarvar Nadaf</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[10 Microsoft Word AI Hacks That Will Transform Your Work in 2025]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/squaredtech/10-microsoft-word-ai-hacks-that-will-transform-your-work-in-2025-51d5</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/squaredtech/10-microsoft-word-ai-hacks-that-will-transform-your-work-in-2025-51d5"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T18:48:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you've ever stared at a blank page wondering how to start a proposal, blog post, or project doc, Copilot is here to change that. In 2025, Word's AI writing assistant has leveled up—it's like having a smart teammate sitting right beside you. 
Just type something like “Write a 500-word proposal for a SaaS product”, and Copilot will build out a solid draft in seconds. Want to tweak the tone or rewrite a section? Highlight the text, ask Copilot to improve it, and boom—it’s done. 
It even pulls from your recent files to suggest what to create next. So, if you’re working on a roadmap, it might prompt you to build a summary, task list, or proposal—tailored to what you’ve been working on. 
Why it matters: It slashes writing time by 30–50%, and you don’t need to be a pro writer to create polishe…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SquaredTech</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[# 🎭 Frontend vs. Backend — Explained Like You’re 5 (But Smarter)]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/itsaryanchauhan/-frontend-vs-backend-explained-like-youre-5-but-smarter-501</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/itsaryanchauhan/-frontend-vs-backend-explained-like-youre-5-but-smarter-501"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T18:47:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ever visited a website and thought, “How does this even work?!”
Let’s break it down — with a puppet show 🎪
You're at a puppet show.
  On stage: You see colorful puppets dancing, singing, doing tricks.
  Behind the curtain: People (the puppeteers) pulling strings, telling the puppets what to do, reacting to your applause.
That’s exactly how web development works.
The frontend is everything you see and interact with on a website:
  Buttons you click
  Colors and layouts
  Fonts, animations, menus
  That cool “Dark Mode” toggle 😎
It’s like the stage, the lights, and the beautifully crafted puppets putting on a show just for you.
  HTML = the structure (the puppet itself)
  CSS = the style (painted puppets and fancy costumes)
  JavaScript = the interaction (puppets moving when you clap!)
Pro…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Aryan Chauhan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Optimizing File Handling and Data Processing in C# Windows Forms App]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/bohardani/optimizing-file-handling-and-data-processing-in-c-windows-forms-app-1cc2</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/bohardani/optimizing-file-handling-and-data-processing-in-c-windows-forms-app-1cc2"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T18:45:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I’m working on a C# Windows Forms application and I’m looking for suggestions to improve my code. Specifically:
What’s the best way to handle file reading and writing, especially when working with large files?
How can I optimize the filtering logic in my app (e.g., searching for movie titles by year)?
Any tips for improving performance or user experience in a Windows Forms app like this?
Any feedback would be really appreciated. Thanks in advance! 🙏
using System;
using System.Collections.Generic;
using System.ComponentModel;
using System.Data;
using System.Drawing;
using System.IO;
using System.Linq;
using System.Text;
using System.Threading.Tasks;
using System.Windows.Forms;

namespace oscar
{


    public partial class Form1 : Form
    {
        class Opera
        {
            public …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>bohardani</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The forbidden railway: Vienna-Pyongyang (2008)]]></title>
        <id>http://vienna-pyongyang.blogspot.com/2008/04/how-everything-began.html</id>
        <link href="http://vienna-pyongyang.blogspot.com/2008/04/how-everything-began.html"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T18:45:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Optimize and Improve C# Console App for File Handling and Data Processing?]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/bohardani/how-to-optimize-and-improve-c-console-app-for-file-handling-and-data-processing-32h8</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/bohardani/how-to-optimize-and-improve-c-console-app-for-file-handling-and-data-processing-32h8"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T18:44:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I'm working on a C# console application and would love some feedback. Specifically:
What's the best way to optimize performance when counting repeated items in a list?
How can I improve resource management (e.g., file handling)?
Any general tips to improve the readability and maintainability of my code?
Thanks in advance for any advice! 🙏
using System.Linq.Expressions;

namespace muz_app
{
    internal class muzeum
    {
        class Muzeum
        {
            public string teremaz { get; set; }
            public string muveszneve { get; set; }
            public string alkotascime { get; set; }
            public string tipusa { get; set; }
        }
        static List<Muzeum> muzeumok = new List<Muzeum>();
        static void Main(string[] args)
        {
            void beolvasas…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>bohardani</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Practical Cases of Using the Singleton Pattern in Frontend Development]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/maximlogunov/practical-cases-of-using-the-singleton-pattern-in-frontend-development-30he</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/maximlogunov/practical-cases-of-using-the-singleton-pattern-in-frontend-development-30he"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T18:42:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Singleton pattern is one of the most fundamental design patterns in software engineering, and it has several practical applications in frontend development. While often debated (as overuse can lead to issues), when applied judiciously, the Singleton pattern can solve specific problems elegantly in client-side applications.
A Singleton is a design pattern that restricts a class to a single instance and provides global access to that instance. In JavaScript/TypeScript terms, it ensures that no matter how many times you try to create an instance of a class, you always get the same instance.
Modern frontend frameworks often use Singleton-like patterns for state management:
// Redux store (typically a Singleton)
import { createStore } from 'redux';
import rootReducer from './reducers';

con…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maxim Logunov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Observation#2]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/jalajb/observation2-29h5</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/jalajb/observation2-29h5"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T18:39:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The AI has already started showing its affects on my habits now...just like ChatGPT or Copilot, I try to search on Google in a conversational way or requesting manner. XD]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jalaj Bankar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[FM] How can I improve this employee directory with live search and API integration?]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/bohardani/fm-how-can-i-improve-this-employee-directory-with-live-search-and-api-integration-213d</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/bohardani/fm-how-can-i-improve-this-employee-directory-with-live-search-and-api-integration-213d"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T18:39:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi everyone! 👋
I'm working on a simple employee directory using HTML, Bootstrap, and JavaScript. The data is fetched from the https://dummyjson.com/users API. I added a search function that filters employees by last name, and there's also an input listener for live filtering as the user types.
Here is a simplified version of the code:
`<!DOCTYPE html>
<html lang="hu">
  <head>
    <meta charset="UTF-8" />
    <title>Dolgozóink</title>
    <meta name="viewport" content="width=device-width, initial-scale=1" />
    <link rel="stylesheet" href="bootstrap.min.css" />
    <script src="jquery.slim.min.js"></script>
    <script src="popper.min.js"></script>
    <script src="bootstrap.bundle.min.js"></script>
    <style>
      .card img {
        width: 60px;
        height: 60px;
        border-r…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>bohardani</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lima Meme Coin Teratas untuk Diamati di Indonesia 2025: Dogecoin, Shiba Inu, dan Lainnya – Panduan Teknikal dan Strategis]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/laetitiaperraut/lima-meme-coin-teratas-untuk-diamati-di-indonesia-2025-dogecoin-shiba-inu-dan-lainnya-panduan-mab</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/laetitiaperraut/lima-meme-coin-teratas-untuk-diamati-di-indonesia-2025-dogecoin-shiba-inu-dan-lainnya-panduan-mab"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T18:34:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Abstract:

Artikel ini menyajikan analisis mendalam tentang lima meme coin teratas di Indonesia pada tahun 2025, yaitu Dogecoin, Shiba Inu, Pepe, Floki Inu, dan Bonk. Dengan latar belakang sejarah, definisi, dan konteks ekosistem cryptocurrency, posting blog ini mengulas fitur inti masing-masing coin, aplikasi praktis, tantangan yang ada, dan inovasi masa depan. Di samping itu, artikel ini menyertakan tabel perbandingan, bullet list strategi keamanan, dan beberapa referensi dari sumber otoritatif seperti CoinMarketCap dan Analytics Insight. Artikel ini juga dilengkapi dengan backlink ke Original Article serta referensi dari platform seperti Dev.to untuk menambah perspektif dari komunitas open source dan blockchain.
Meme coin telah menjadi fenomena global di dunia cryptocurrency. Popularita…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Laetitia Perraut</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft just launched an AI that discovered a new chemical in 200 hours instead of years]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008310</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/microsoft-just-launched-an-ai-that-discovered-a-new-chemical-in-200-hours-instead-of-years/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T18:34:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft launches Discovery platform that uses agentic AI to compress years of scientific research into days, transforming R&D across pharmaceuticals, materials science, and semiconductor industries.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Nuñez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Evaluating AI with LLM as a Judge: A New Standard for Modern Language Model Assessment]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/kapusto/evaluating-ai-with-llm-as-a-judge-a-new-standard-for-modern-language-model-assessment-4a1k</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/kapusto/evaluating-ai-with-llm-as-a-judge-a-new-standard-for-modern-language-model-assessment-4a1k"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T18:30:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Traditional AI evaluation methods are struggling to keep pace with the rapid evolution of language models. Metrics like BLEU and ROUGE scores, which rely on deterministic measurements, fall short when assessing the creative, non-deterministic outputs of modern AI systems. Enter "LLM as a judge" — an innovative approach that uses language models themselves to evaluate AI outputs. This method harnesses the sophisticated understanding capabilities of LLMs to provide nuanced, context-aware assessments that better match the complexity of today's AI systems. Unlike conventional evaluation methods, LLM judges can adapt to varied contexts and offer detailed, qualitative feedback that more closely resembles human judgment.
Language model judges function by implementing sophisticated prompt engineer…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mikuz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub Bootcamp: Day 2 - Setting Up GitHub]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/harshpandhe/github-for-developers-day-2-setting-up-github-hh6</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/harshpandhe/github-for-developers-day-2-setting-up-github-hh6"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T18:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome to Day 2 of our 5-day GitHub series! Today we’re setting up GitHub, the digital garage where developers store, collaborate on, and show off their code. If GitHub were a superhero, it’d be Batman: mysterious, powerful, and full of cool gadgets (like Actions and Pull Requests). Let's get you set up and ready to push code like a pro.
Step 1: Create a GitHub Account



  
  
  Go to github.com and hit Sign up



Pick a memorable username (bonus points for geeky puns).
Add your email and a strong password.
Choose your plan (the free one is plenty to get started).
You're officially a GitHubber now. 🎉
Step 2: Create Your First Repository


A repository (or “repo”) is where your project lives—kind of like a folder, but cooler.
Click the + icon on the top-right → New repository.
Give it a …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Harsh Pandhe</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto.com and Canary Capital to launch US CRO fund]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/crypto-com-canary-capital-launch-us-fund</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/crypto-com-canary-capital-launch-us-fund?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T18:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto.com and asset manager Canary Capital are launching a US investment fund designed to provide exposure to the Cronos blockchain’s native token, CRO, the cryptocurrency exchange said in a statement.
The Canary CRO Trust will hold the Cronos (CRO) token in a regulated fund wrapper, Crypto.com said, adding that the trust is not an exchange-traded fund (ETF) and is only available to accredited investors. 
Creating regulated funds such as CRO Trust is part of Crypto.com’s plan for “further mainstreaming crypto,” Eric Anziani, president and chief operating officer of Crypto.com, said in a statement.
In March, the crypto exchange partnered with Trump Media & Technology Group, a company affiliated with US President Donald Trump, to launch a series of Trump-branded ETFs, including one holding …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Alex O’Donnell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Is your AI app pissing off users or going off-script? Raindrop emerges with AI-native observability platform to monitor performance]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008299</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/is-your-ai-app-pissing-off-users-or-going-off-script-raindrop-emerges-with-ai-native-observability-platform-to-monitor-performance/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T18:09:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With its rebrand and product expansion, Raindrop is betting that the next generation of software observability will be AI-first by design.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carl Franzen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Claude Code SDK – Anthropic]]></title>
        <id>https://docs.anthropic.com/en/docs/claude-code/sdk</id>
        <link href="https://docs.anthropic.com/en/docs/claude-code/sdk"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T18:04:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Price predictions 5/19: SPX, DXY, BTC, ETH, XRP, BNB, SOL, DOGE, ADA, SUI]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/price-predictions-5-19-spx-dxy-btc-eth-xrp-bnb-sol-doge-ada-sui</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/price-predictions-5-19-spx-dxy-btc-eth-xrp-bnb-sol-doge-ada-sui?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T18:02:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Key points:

Bitcoin’s rejection at $107,000 shows sellers are active at higher levels, but the recovery from the intraday low shows solid buying.

Strategy and Metaplanet continue to accumulate Bitcoin, adding steady buy-side pressure to BTC price. 

Select altcoins have pulled back, but they have not yet turned negative.

Bitcoin’s (BTC) attempt to challenge the all-time high faced a strong rejection near $107,100 on May 19, signaling that the bears are unlikely to give up without a fight. However, the long tail on the candlestick shows solid buying at lower levels.
The short-term uncertainty has not deterred the long-term buyers from accumulating more Bitcoin. Strategy, formerly MicroStrategy, announced the purchase of 7,390 Bitcoin for an average price of about $103,500, taking its tot…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Rakesh Upadhyay</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘Before Bitcoin, my most successful investment was shorting the Bolivar’ — Ledn co-founder]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/before-bitcoin-shorting-bolivar-ledn</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/before-bitcoin-shorting-bolivar-ledn?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T18:00:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Before discovering Bitcoin (BTC), Ledn co-founder Mauricio di Bartolomeo found success shorting the Venezuelan Bolivar as it rapidly lost value against the stronger US dollar. Now, with the US dollar depreciating against Bitcoin, borrowing against Bitcoin instead of selling it has become a more viable strategy.
“Prior to Bitcoin, my most successful investment was shorting the Bolivar with dollars,” di Bartolomeo told Cointelegraph in an exclusive interview at the Consensus conference in Toronto, Canada. 
“I was borrowing Bolivars and buying dollars with them, holding the hard dollars and having a borrow [position] on the weaker currency,” he said.
The arrival of Bitcoin-backed loans means investors can now effectively implement the same strategy by using a harder currency as collateral. 
L…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Sam Bourgi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft's ICC blockade: digital dependence comes at a cost]]></title>
        <id>https://www.techzine.eu/news/privacy-compliance/131536/microsofts-icc-blockade-digital-dependence-comes-at-a-cost/</id>
        <link href="https://www.techzine.eu/news/privacy-compliance/131536/microsofts-icc-blockade-digital-dependence-comes-at-a-cost/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T17:59:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ripple launches cross-border blockchain payments in UAE]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/ripple-launches-cross-border-blockchain-payments-uae</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/ripple-launches-cross-border-blockchain-payments-uae?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T17:55:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ripple, the creator of cryptocurrency XRP (XRP), launched cross-border blockchain payments in the United Arab Emirates (UAE), a development that could spur the adoption of cryptocurrency in a country receptive to digital assets.
Zand Bank, the UAE’s first all-digital bank, and Mamo, a fintech company that offers a digital payment platform for businesses, will be the principal users of the blockchain payments system, according to a May 19 Ripple announcement.

Zand Bank and Mamo will use “Ripple Payments” to facilitate cross-border blockchain payments. 
Ripple Payments is a platform that combines stablecoins, cryptocurrency, and fiat to enable payments and quick settlement times, a feature of Web3 that cross-border traditional finance payment systems often lack. Ripple was licensed to offer…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Christopher Tepedino</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JPMorgan To Allow Clients To Buy Bitcoin, Says Jamie Dimon]]></title>
        <id>b04a21af-101a-496d-9474-83683d8d624f</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2025/05/19/jpmorgan-to-allow-clients-to-buy-bitcoin-says-jamie-dimon"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T17:47:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A longtime vocal critic of bitcoin, Dimon said the bank he runs will now let clients to buy the crypto.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Helene Braun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[So why *did* U.S. wages stagnate for 20 years?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.noahpinion.blog/p/so-why-did-us-wages-stagnate-for</id>
        <link href="https://www.noahpinion.blog/p/so-why-did-us-wages-stagnate-for"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T17:43:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Show HN: Windows 98 themed website in 1 HTML file for my post punk band]]></title>
        <id>https://corp.band/</id>
        <link href="https://corp.band/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T17:39:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin ignores Moody’s US debt downgrade, rallies back to $105K after profit-taking sell-off]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-ignores-moody-s-us-debt-downgrade-rallies-back-to-105k-after-profit-taking-sell-off</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-ignores-moody-s-us-debt-downgrade-rallies-back-to-105k-after-profit-taking-sell-off?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T17:17:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Key takeaways:

Bitcoin recovered from its sharp sell-off from $107,000, suggesting it functions as a hedge against uncertainty for investors reacting to Moody’s recent downgrade of US debt.

Moody’s downgraded the US credit rating to Aa1, citing a $36 trillion debt and rising deficits, causing market turbulence and a spike in US Treasury yields.

Despite short-term pressure from macroeconomic shifts, Bitcoin’s long-term outlook remains bullish due to cautious shorting and a weakening US dollar.

Bitcoin (BTC) price faced a sharp 4% correction during the Asian trading session on May 19, tumbling from an “important level” as noted by Glassnode. The data analytics platform indicated that Bitcoin’s surge stalled just below $106,600, a critical level where 31,000 BTC are held. This supply clus…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Biraajmaan Tamuly</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Company Reminder for Everyone to Talk Nicely About the Giant Plagiarism Machine]]></title>
        <id>https://www.mcsweeneys.net/articles/a-company-reminder-for-everyone-to-talk-nicely-about-the-giant-plagiarism-machine</id>
        <link href="https://www.mcsweeneys.net/articles/a-company-reminder-for-everyone-to-talk-nicely-about-the-giant-plagiarism-machine"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T17:15:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Glasskube (YC S24) is hiring in Vienna to build Open Source deployment tools]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ycombinator.com/companies/glasskube/jobs/wjB77iZ-founding-engineer-go-typescript-kubernetes-docker</id>
        <link href="https://www.ycombinator.com/companies/glasskube/jobs/wjB77iZ-founding-engineer-go-typescript-kubernetes-docker"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T17:00:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Is the Asset, Ethereum Is the Platform]]></title>
        <id>998de6a9-7312-43f3-aa9e-95df6e0a18db</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/opinion/2025/05/19/bitcoin-is-the-asset-ethereum-is-the-platform"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T16:56:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[But it is the Layer 0 that matters, says Paul Brody, head of blockchain at EY.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paul Brody</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[XRP Futures Start Trading on CME]]></title>
        <id>7d4d5bd9-3ba1-4770-971f-82790f8cc957</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/19/xrp-futures-start-trading-on-cme"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T16:53:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Spot XRP ETFs are only a matter of time, according to one industry expert.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Helene Braun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Game theory illustrated by an animated cartoon game]]></title>
        <id>https://ncase.me/trust/</id>
        <link href="https://ncase.me/trust/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T16:28:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Edit is now open source]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/commandline/edit-is-now-open-source/</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/commandline/edit-is-now-open-source/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T16:27:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub Copilot Coding Agent]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2025-05-19-github-copilot-coding-agent-in-public-preview/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2025-05-19-github-copilot-coding-agent-in-public-preview/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T16:17:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Windows Subsystem for Linux is now open source]]></title>
        <id>https://blogs.windows.com/windowsdeveloper/2025/05/19/the-windows-subsystem-for-linux-is-now-open-source/</id>
        <link href="https://blogs.windows.com/windowsdeveloper/2025/05/19/the-windows-subsystem-for-linux-is-now-open-source/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T16:14:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[European Investment Bank to inject €70B in European tech]]></title>
        <id>https://ioplus.nl/en/posts/european-investment-bank-to-inject-70-billion-in-european-tech</id>
        <link href="https://ioplus.nl/en/posts/european-investment-bank-to-inject-70-billion-in-european-tech"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T16:05:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin bull market &#039;almost over?&#039; Traders split over BTC price at $105K]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-bull-market-almost-over-traders-split-over-btc-price-105k</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-bull-market-almost-over-traders-split-over-btc-price-105k?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T16:05:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Key points:

BTC price action retargets $105,000 after the Wall Street open, rising 2.5% from the day’s lows.

Volatility continues, leading market participants to varying conclusions over what will happen to BTC/USD next.

Perspectives include the Bitcoin bull market being in its final stages.

Bitcoin (BTC) sought a rebound from a 4% dive at the May 19 Wall Street open as traders diverged on bull market strength.
BTC/USD 1-hour chart. Source: Cointelegraph/TradingView
$106,000 becomes BTC price zone to watch
Data from Cointelegraph Markets Pro and TradingView showed BTC/USD passing $104,500, up 2.5% from the day’s low.
The pair had seen flash volatility around the weekly close, which although the highest ever recorded swiftly saw bulls lose control.
Now, opinions differed about when, or …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by William Suberg</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft just taught its AI agents to talk to each other—and it could transform how we work]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008254</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/microsoft-just-taught-its-ai-agents-to-talk-to-each-other-and-it-could-transform-how-we-work/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T16:01:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft unveils multi-agent systems, WhatsApp integration, and Python-powered analytics for Copilot Studio at Build 2025, transforming how enterprises build and deploy AI solutions.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Nuñez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Microsoft Fabric has already been adopted by 70% of the Fortune 500 — and what’s next]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3007980</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/70-of-the-fortune-500-already-use-microsoft-fabric-and-its-now-getting-even-more-features-including-cosmosdb-support/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft integrates CosmosDB into Fabric, open sources DiskANN vector search, and unifies its data platforms to eliminate integration complexity that has slowed enterprise AI adoption.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sean Michael Kerner</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub Copilot evolves into autonomous agent with asynchronous code testing]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008231</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/github-copilot-evolves-into-autonomous-agent-with-asynchronous-code-testing/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub adds agentic capabilities to its Copilot coding assistant, competing with other more asynchronous coding platforms.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Emilia David</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dogecoin Finds Support After Sharp Drop as Bulls Regain Momentum]]></title>
        <id>5ddbc57e-50ae-4222-b8ff-ee6173d489b7</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/19/dogecoin-finds-support-after-sharp-drop-as-bulls-regain-momentum"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T15:59:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The popular meme-based cryptocurrency shows resilience at $0.215 level as buyers step in following significant downtrend.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>AI Boost</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft announces over 50 AI tools to build the ‘agentic web’ at Build 2025]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008229</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/microsoft-announces-over-50-ai-tools-to-build-the-agentic-web-at-build-2025/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T15:59:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft reveals its ambitious AI agent strategy, showcasing how multi-agent systems with persistent memory will transform enterprise workflows and accelerate development timelines.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Nuñez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Binance's Former Russia Head, Blum Co-Founder Arrested in Connection to Fraud Case]]></title>
        <id>f81f7746-9b24-4a4b-9d46-d92df8e2ea48</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2025/05/19/binances-former-russia-head-blum-co-founder-arrested-in-connection-to-fraud-case"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T15:53:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Smerkis worked for Binance from 2022 for just under two years.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Camomile Shumba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Wikipedia's Most Translated Articles]]></title>
        <id>https://sohom.dev/most-translated-articles-on-wikipedia/pretty.html</id>
        <link href="https://sohom.dev/most-translated-articles-on-wikipedia/pretty.html"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T15:53:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Too Much Go Misdirection]]></title>
        <id>https://flak.tedunangst.com/post/too-much-go-misdirection</id>
        <link href="https://flak.tedunangst.com/post/too-much-go-misdirection"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T15:40:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why is Bitcoin price down today?]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/why-is-bitcoin-price-down-today</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/why-is-bitcoin-price-down-today?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T15:37:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Key takeaways:

Bitcoin price fell 1.4% to $102,460 amid US economic concerns, with daily trading volume up 94%, indicating the return of sellers.

Moody’s US credit downgrade to Aa1 and a class-action lawsuit against Strategy add to BTC’s headwinds.

Bitcoin’s (BTC) price has dropped by over 1.4% over the last 24 hours to $102,460 as concerns over the health of the US economy sour investor sentiment. Its daily trading volume has jumped by 94% to $66.6 billion, suggesting that the sell-side activity is intensifying. 
BTC/USD daily chart. Source: Cointelegraph/TradingView
Macroeconomic uncertainty drives Bitcoin price down
Moody’s downgrade of the US credit rating from Aaa to Aa1 on May 16, citing rising debt and deficits. This has heightened macroeconomic uncertainty, contributing to a dec…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Nancy Lubale</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[23andMe Sells Gene-Testing Business to DNA Drug Maker Regeneron]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2025-05-19/23andme-sells-gene-testing-business-to-dna-drug-maker-regeneron</id>
        <link href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2025-05-19/23andme-sells-gene-testing-business-to-dna-drug-maker-regeneron"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T15:27:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Zod 4]]></title>
        <id>https://zod.dev/v4</id>
        <link href="https://zod.dev/v4"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T15:24:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Telegram-Associated Toncoin (TON) Plunges 8% as Critical $3.00 Support Crumbles]]></title>
        <id>0218deb4-70c5-4f7a-ad4b-705d94178ae5</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/19/telegram-associated-toncoin-ton-plunges-8-as-critical-usd3-00-support-crumbles"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T15:10:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Despite late recovery signs, TON faces mounting pressure amid global market uncertainty and ecosystem concerns.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>AI Boost</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SDB Scans the Ruby Stack Without the GVL]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/yfractal/blog/blob/master/blog/2025-01-15-non-blocking-stack-profiler.md</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/yfractal/blog/blob/master/blog/2025-01-15-non-blocking-stack-profiler.md"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T15:10:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Who’s got the charm, cash and code to be a crypto hub?]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/cash-code-crypto-hub-uk-us-singapore</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/cash-code-crypto-hub-uk-us-singapore?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T15:01:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kazakhstan, the Maldives and Pakistan have recently outlined ambitions to position themselves as crypto hubs and build out their digital economies.
Historically, these countries haven’t been top of mind for global crypto firms — though Kazakhstan did have a brief moment in the spotlight as a go-to destination for Bitcoin (BTC) miners after China’s mining ban.
Meanwhile, established financial centers are now in a race to become the world’s leading crypto hub by finding the right balance of regulation, talent, capital and infrastructure.
Here’s how five of them are backing their crypto dreams.
Singapore is the crypto hub with parental guidance
Singapore has long stood out as a financial hub, bolstered by its AAA credit rating, low corporate tax rates and pro-business regulations. With the em…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Yohan Yun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Reddit, Webflow, and Superhuman are already customers—now GrowthX has $12M to grow]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008276</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/reddit-webflow-and-superhuman-are-already-customers-now-growthx-has-12m-to-grow/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[GrowthX secures $12M in funding for its "service-as-software" platform that combines AI with human expertise to boost content marketing results by up to 300%.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Nuñez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AI can do a better job of persuading people than we do]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1116779</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/05/19/1116779/ai-can-do-a-better-job-of-persuading-people-than-we-do/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Millions of people argue with each other online every day, but remarkably few of them change someone’s mind. New research suggests that large language models (LLMs) might do a better job. The finding suggests that AI could become a powerful tool for persuading people, for better or worse.   A multi-university team of researchers found that…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rhiannon Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Community sales are the future of crypto fundraising]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/community-sales</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/community-sales?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Opinion by: Darius Moukhtarzadeh, Research Strategist at 21Shares
A new wave of crypto fundraising is emerging, changing how Web3 projects launch and who can invest at an early stage: Community Sales. At first glance, community sales may seem reminiscent of the ICO (Initial Coin Offering) era from 2016–2017. Yet, they represent a significant evolution that better aligns with crypto's core values of democratization, transparency, and inclusivity.
Projects should include community sales as a core element of their fundraising strategy, besides raising from angel investors and VCs. Professional investors should embrace community sales as they highly increase the chances of sustainable success of Web3 projects. 
The ICO era
The original ICO boom promised broad retail participation and democrati…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Darius Moukhtarzadeh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kelp – simple replacement for homebrew on macOS]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/crhuber/kelp</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/crhuber/kelp"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T14:55:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Launch HN: Better Auth (YC X25) – Authentication Framework for TypeScript]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=44030492</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=44030492"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T14:48:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chinese printer maker spread Bitcoin stealing malware — Report]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-stealer-malware-found-in-official-printer-drivers</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-stealer-malware-found-in-official-printer-drivers?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T14:24:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Chinese printer manufacturer Procolored distributed Bitcoin-stealing malware alongside its official drivers, according to local media reports.
Chinese news outlet Landian News reported on May 19 that Shenzhen-based printer company Procolored has been distributing Bitcoin-stealing (BTC) malware alongside official drivers. The company reportedly used USB drivers to distribute malware-ridden drivers and uploaded the compromised software to cloud storage for global download.
A total of 9.3 BTC worth over $953,000 have been stolen, according to the report. Crypto tracking and compliance firm Slow Mist described how the malware operates in a May 19 X post:
“The official driver provided by this printer carries a backdoor program. It will hijack the wallet address in the user’s clipboard and repla…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Adrian Zmudzinski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Roman Storm's Defense Team Wants to Know if DOJ Withheld Evidence]]></title>
        <id>5c0d6dc2-aacf-4601-9ee7-6740fe20e42d</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2025/05/19/roman-storms-defense-team-wants-to-know-if-doj-withheld-evidence"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T14:11:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Storm's attorneys filed a letter Friday asking a judge to order prosecutors to review their records.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nikhilesh De</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Franklin taps blockchain to offer yield on idle payroll funds]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/franklin-launches-payroll-treasury-yield-defi</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/franklin-launches-payroll-treasury-yield-defi?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Franklin, a hybrid cash and crypto payroll provider, is launching a new initiative that aims to turn idle-sitting payroll into an opportunity for yield.
The new solution, dubbed Payroll Treasury Yield, uses blockchain lending protocols to help firms earn returns on payroll funds that would otherwise sit idle, the company told Cointelegraph in an exclusive statement.
Franklin said its new offering integrates Summer.fi, a decentralized finance (DeFi) lending platform, to allow companies to deposit stablecoin-denominated payroll reserves into smart contract-based lending pools.
These funds are lent to vetted borrowers, and companies earn yields while retaining access to their capital. Companies maintain full custody throughout the process, and smart contracts used are audited to reduce risk.
…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Amin Haqshanas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Cybercriminals Crack Your Passwords (And How to Stay One Step Ahead)]]></title>
        <id>682b3930e99a22ce9f9199c8</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-cybercriminals-crack-your-passwords-and-how-to-stay-one-step-ahead/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T13:59:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Passwords are the keys to your digital life  –  email, bank accounts, social media, and even your workplace systems. Unfortunately, they’re also one of the weakest links in cybersecurity.  Every year, billions of credentials are stolen and sold on th...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Manish Shivanandhan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Network Hashrate Rose Slightly in First Two Weeks of May: JPMorgan]]></title>
        <id>6469ccb1-8fe1-443a-b18f-da6ab0d204dd</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/19/bitcoin-network-hashrate-rose-slightly-in-first-two-weeks-of-may-jpmorgan"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T13:48:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mining gross margins expanded sequentially this month, which is encouraging, the bank said.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Will Canny</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Here’s what happened in crypto today]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/what-happened-in-crypto-today</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/what-happened-in-crypto-today?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T13:37:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today in crypto, Michael Saylor’s Strategy bagged another 7,390 Bitcoin last week as prices rallied above $100,000 and also got hit with a class-action lawsuit, Bitcoin has notched its highest-ever weekly close, and Telegram co-founder Pavel Durov said he rejected pressure from France to censor Romanian election content.
Strategy adds 7,390 BTC for $765 million, gets hit with class-action lawsuit
Strategy, formerly MicroStrategy, the top corporate Bitcoin holder, acquired nearly $765 million of Bitcoin last week. The purchase came as the company faced a class-action lawsuit.
According to a May 19 announcement, Strategy acquired 7,390 BTC for about $764.9 million at an average price just under $103,500. Strategy reported a Bitcoin yield of 16.3% year-to-date. Strategy executive chairman Mic…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Cointelegraph</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Visualizing 100k Years of Earth in WebGL]]></title>
        <id>https://technistuff.com/posts/visualizing-100000-years-of-earth-in-webgl/</id>
        <link href="https://technistuff.com/posts/visualizing-100000-years-of-earth-in-webgl/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T13:24:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CoinDesk 20 Performance Update: Index Drops 4.7% Over Weekend as All Assets Decline]]></title>
        <id>dede3152-8533-49cb-8571-d6464eb50678</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/coindesk-indices/2025/05/19/coindesk-20-performance-update-index-drops-4-7-over-weekend-as-all-assets-decline"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T13:15:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Avalanche (AVAX) fell 8.6% and Uniswap (UNI) declined 8.5%, leading the index lower.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CoinDesk Indices</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hoskinson promises audit, is ‘deeply hurt’ by $600M Cardano treasury claims]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/hoskinson-audit-deeply-hurt-600-m-cardano-treasury</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/hoskinson-audit-deeply-hurt-600-m-cardano-treasury?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T13:09:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Cardano Foundation is preparing to release an audit report on its treasury holdings after fresh allegations surfaced claiming misappropriation of roughly $600 million worth of ADA tokens.  
Cardano founder Charles Hoskinson is facing renewed scrutiny from community members, including non-fungible token artist Masato Alexander, who alleged that Hoskinson manipulated the Cardano ledger using a “genesis key to rewrite it and take control” of $619 million worth of Cardano (ADA) during the network’s 2021 Allegra hard fork.
Source: Masato Alexander
Related: Nasdaq-listed GDC plans to buy Bitcoin and TRUMP memecoin for $300M
A secondary, “Move Instantneous Rewards” transaction dated Oct. 24, 2021, shows a transfer of over 318 million ADA tokens, which enabled the funds to flow from reserve po…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Zoltan Vardai</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Diffusion Models Explained Simply]]></title>
        <id>https://www.seangoedecke.com/diffusion-models-explained/</id>
        <link href="https://www.seangoedecke.com/diffusion-models-explained/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T13:06:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to read a Bitcoin liquidation map (without getting liquidated)]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/how-to-read-a-bitcoin-liquidation-map-without-getting-liquidated</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/how-to-read-a-bitcoin-liquidation-map-without-getting-liquidated?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T13:05:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Understanding a Bitcoin liquidation map is imperative in dealing with the inherent volatility of the crypto market. The visual tool showcases probable liquidation levels, indicating where large orders may cause cascading price changes. 
This post explores how to interpret a Bitcoin liquidation map, allowing you to trade smarter in the volatile world of cryptocurrency.
What is liquidation in crypto trading?
In cryptocurrency trading, liquidation happens when an exchange forcefully closes a trader's leveraged position due to insufficient margin to pay losses. This usually occurs when the market moves sharply against the position. 
Long liquidations occur when prices fall, affecting traders who bet on an uptrend. Short liquidations happen when prices unexpectedly rise, impacting those who bet…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Dilip Kumar Patairya</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Quantum Machines launches Qualibrate open source framework to speed quantum computer calibration]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008032</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/games/quantum-machines-launches-qualibrate-open-source-framework-to-speed-quantum-computer-calibration/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Quantum Machines, a provider of advanced hybrid quantum-classical control solutions, announced today the release of Qualibrate.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dean Takahashi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BounceBit Pilots Bitcoin Trading Strategy Using BlackRock's BUIDL as Collateral]]></title>
        <id>411f3bbb-2cd5-48cc-995e-54d73157cca6</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/19/bouncebit-pilots-bitcoin-trading-strategy-using-blackrocks-buidl-as-collateral"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The strategy, offering an annualized yield exceeding 24%, will be soon rolled out to institutions and retail users.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Omkar Godbole</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Strategy adds 7,390 BTC for $765M, gets hit with class-action lawsuit]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/strategy-buys-7390-bitcoin-hit-with-lawsuit</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/strategy-buys-7390-bitcoin-hit-with-lawsuit?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T12:42:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Strategy, formerly MicroStrategy, the top corporate Bitcoin holder, acquired nearly $765 million of Bitcoin last week. The purchase came as the company faced a class-action lawsuit.
According to a May 19 announcement, Strategy acquired 7,390 BTC for about $764.9 million at an average price just under $103,500. Strategy reported a Bitcoin yield of 16.3% year-to-date. Strategy executive chairman Michael Saylor made his usual hint at the purchase in a May 18 X post. 
Source: Michael Saylor
According to a May 19 filing with the US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC), the company was also the recipient of a class-action lawsuit. The suit accuses Strategy officials of having failed to represent the nature of Bitcoin investments accurately.
As of May 18, Strategy holds 576,230 BTC acquired f…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Adrian Zmudzinski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Investment Products Fully Recover From $7B Outflows Seen in February-March]]></title>
        <id>706d83e0-0b2f-4054-b427-4ea0a19f2a14</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/19/crypto-investment-products-fully-recover-from-7b-outflows-seen-in-february-march"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T12:32:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin products attracted the most inflows, while ether products saw a recovery linked to the successful Pectra upgrade.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Francisco Rodrigues</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ClawPDF – Open-Source Virtual/Network PDF Printer with OCR and Image Support]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/clawsoftware/clawPDF</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/clawsoftware/clawPDF"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T12:31:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[XRP price risks falling to $2 after classic bearish chart pattern confirms]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/xrp-price-falling-2-classic-bearish-pattern-confirms</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/xrp-price-falling-2-classic-bearish-pattern-confirms?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T12:30:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Key takeaways:

XRP could be headed down to $2 following a breakdown of a classic head-and-shoulders pattern.

Declining open interest in XRP futures signals weakening trader confidence.

The XRP (XRP) price is flashing warning signs as a bearish technical pattern resolves on lower timeframes, coinciding with massive long liquidations and decreasing open interest.
XRP H&S pattern hints at a 14% price drop
XRP price action has formed a head-and-shoulders (H&S) pattern on its four-hour chart since May 9, projecting a likely down-move.
The head-and-shoulders pattern is a bearish reversal pattern that can signal a change in trend. It consists of three peaks: a higher peak (head) and two lower peaks (shoulders). 
It is resolved when the price breaks below the neckline (the line connecting the l…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Nancy Lubale</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum's Vitalik Buterin Proposes Design to Make Running Nodes Easier]]></title>
        <id>93691e08-6187-4b36-83e4-7db9f22abb7d</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/tech/2025/05/19/ethereums-vitalik-buterin-proposes-design-to-make-running-nodes-easier"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T12:12:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new proposal from Ethereum’s co-founder would let users run lightweight nodes without storing the entire blockchain, trimming costs for node operators.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shaurya Malwa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Download: chaos at OpenAI, and the spa heated by bitcoin mining]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1116740</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/05/19/1116740/the-download-chaos-at-openai-and-the-spa-heated-by-bitcoin-mining/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T12:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is today’s edition of The Download, our weekday newsletter that provides a daily dose of what’s going on in the world of technology. Inside the story that enraged OpenAI —Niall Firth, executive editor, MIT Technology Review In 2019, Karen Hao, a senior reporter with MIT Technology Review, pitched me a story about a then little-known company,…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rhiannon Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Strategy Expands Bitcoin Holdings With Latest Multi-Million Dollar Purchase]]></title>
        <id>5fc7f414-f8c0-482c-8d1d-c34735d2fe8e</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/19/strategy-expands-bitcoin-holdings-with-latest-multi-billion-dollar-purchase"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T12:09:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Company buys additional BTC via stock offerings, bringing total holdings to record levels.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>James Van Straten</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Samsung boosts OLED TV gaming with Nvidia G-Sync compatibility]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008019</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/games/samsung-boosts-oled-tv-gaming-with-nvidia-g-sync-compatibility/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Samsung said its 2025 OLED TV lineup will feature Nvidia G-Sync compatibility, delivering smooth gameplay, low latency, and more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dean Takahashi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Salesforce just unveiled AI ‘digital teammates’ in Slack — and they’re coming for Microsoft Copilot]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008273</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/salesforce-just-unveiled-ai-digital-teammates-in-slack-and-theyre-coming-for-microsoft-copilot/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Salesforce launches Agentforce in Slack, transforming workplace productivity with specialized AI agents that operate as digital teammates, replacing one-size-fits-all AI assistants with purpose-built solutions.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Nuñez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin's Volatile Liquidity Run Could Lead to New Record Highs]]></title>
        <id>3932d78a-fe31-4977-af90-e80d0e6f5629</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/19/bitcoin-s-volatile-liquidity-run-could-lead-to-new-record-highs"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T11:58:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin behaved differently on Sunday, with CME futures leading the volatile price action.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Oliver Knight</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Australian court ruling could lead to $640M in Bitcoin tax refunds]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/australia-bitcoin-tax-ruling-cgt-refunds</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/australia-bitcoin-tax-ruling-cgt-refunds?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T11:49:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A court decision in Australia could open the door to as much as $640 million in capital gains tax (CGT) refunds on Bitcoin transactions after a judge ruled that crypto should be treated as money rather than a taxable asset. 
On May 19, the Australian Financial Review (AFR) reported that the decision arose within a criminal case involving federal police officer William Wheatley, who allegedly stole 81.6 Bitcoin (BTC) in 2019. At the time, the assets were worth roughly $492,000. At current market prices, the tokens are valued at more than $13 million.
In the case, Judge Michael O’Connell of Victoria ruled that Bitcoin qualifies as a form of money rather than property, likening the digital asset to Australian dollars rather than to shares, gold or foreign currency.
The interpretation could se…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Ezra Reguerra</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Daybook Americas: Bitcoin Whiplash Shakes Market as U.S. Yield Spike Threatens Bull Run]]></title>
        <id>ed1f64b7-698d-405a-8a44-319919085216</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/daybook-us/2025/05/19/crypto-daybook-americas-bitcoin-whiplash-shakes-market-as-u-s-yield-spike-threatens-bull-run"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T11:18:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Your day-ahead look for May 19, 2025]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>James Van Straten</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[US crypto funds top $7.5B inflows in 2025 as investor appetite grows]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/crypto-funds-7-5-b-2025-recover-march-sell-off</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/crypto-funds-7-5-b-2025-recover-march-sell-off?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T11:15:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto investment products in the United States have attracted over $7.5 billion worth of investment in 2025, with a fifth week of net positive inflows last week signaling growing investor demand for digital assets.
US-based crypto investment products attracted $785 million worth of investment last week, pushing the year-to-date (YTD) total to over $7.5 billion, according to a May 19 report by digital asset manager CoinShares. 
The latest figure marks the fifth consecutive week of net positive flows, following nearly $7 billion in outflows during February and March.
Weekly crypto asset flows, USD, million. Source: CoinShares
The United States accounted for the bulk of inflows, with $681 million, followed by Germany at $86.3 million and Hong Kong at $24.4 million.  
Crypto flows by country.…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Zoltan Vardai</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ARM Teases Next-Generation Lumex CSS Chipset]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=352195</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/352195/arm-teases-next-generation-lumex-css-chipset/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T11:04:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Earlier today, ARM gave the attending media a very brief taste on its next-generation Lumex CSS chipset, with a heavy emphasis on “brief”. By that, we mean that the semiconductor maker didn’t share a lot of details, save for the name of the CPU and GPU modules that shape the chipset. The CPU cores will […]
The post ARM Teases Next-Generation Lumex CSS Chipset appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John Law</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Neta Auto Malaysia Denies Parent Company Bankruptcy Claims]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=352185</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/352185/neta-auto-malaysia-denies-parent-company-bankruptcy-claims/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T10:55:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Neta Auto Malaysia (Intro Synergy Sdn Bhd) has issued an official statement in response to recent social media allegations concerning the bankruptcy of its parent company, Hozon Auto. The company has denied these claims, and further explained that a bankruptcy application was filed by a creditor, Yuxing Advertising, over a debt dispute with the parent […]
The post Neta Auto Malaysia Denies Parent Company Bankruptcy Claims appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Keran</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Revolut eyes French license and $1.1B expansion amid EU growth]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/crypto-neobank-revolut-to-invest-1-billion-in-france-apply-for-license</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/crypto-neobank-revolut-to-invest-1-billion-in-france-apply-for-license?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T10:54:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Revolut, a European neobank with crypto support, plans to invest more than 1 billion euro ($1.1 billion) in France and apply for a local banking license.
According to a May 19 Fortune report, Revolut representatives announced the initiative during the Choose France business summit hosted by President Emmanuel Macron in Paris. The London-based neobank also plans to set up its new European Union-serving headquarters in Paris, promising to invest 1 billion euro and hire at least 200 people within three years.
Revolut spokespeople also said that the firm is in the process of submitting an application to the French banking regulator Prudential Supervision and Resolution Authority. According to an anonymous source cited by Fortune, the regulator has been pushing the neobank to get a license to i…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Adrian Zmudzinski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Analyst: No AirPods Announcement Until AirPods Pro 3 In 2026]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=352175</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/352175/analyst-no-airpods-announcement-until-airpods-pro-3-in-2026/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T10:36:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you are a fan of personal audio products made by Apple, and were looking forward to an AirPods-related announcement anytime soon, you may be a bit disappointed. Analyst Ming-Chi Kuo shared on X, previously Twitter, his own prediction of what sort of announcements the fruit company has in schedule. And it looks like there’s […]
The post Analyst: No AirPods Announcement Until AirPods Pro 3 In 2026 appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ian Chee</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Telum II at Hot Chips 2024: Mainframe with a Unique Caching Strategy]]></title>
        <id>https://chipsandcheese.com/p/telum-ii-at-hot-chips-2024-mainframe-with-a-unique-caching-strategy</id>
        <link href="https://chipsandcheese.com/p/telum-ii-at-hot-chips-2024-mainframe-with-a-unique-caching-strategy"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T10:27:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Can crowdsourced fact-checking curb misinformation on social media?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1116367</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/05/19/1116367/can-crowdsourced-fact-checking-curb-misinformation-on-social-media/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T10:20:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a 2019 speech at Georgetown University, Mark Zuckerberg famously declared that he didn’t want Facebook to be an “arbiter of truth.” And yet, in the years since, his company, Meta, has used several methods to moderate content and identify misleading posts across its social media apps, which include Facebook, Instagram, and Threads. These methods…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Prof. Preslav Nakov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dubai regulator sets compliance deadline for updated crypto rules]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/dubai-crypto-regulator-updates-rulebooks-tightens-margin-trading</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/dubai-crypto-regulator-updates-rulebooks-tightens-margin-trading?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T09:59:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dubai’s crypto regulator has given licensed digital asset companies until June 19 to comply with its updated activity-based Rulebooks to enhance market integrity and risk oversight. 
On May 19, Dubai’s Virtual Assets Regulatory Authority (VARA) announced that it had released Version 2.0 of the Rulebooks. 
The regulator said it had strengthened controls around margin trading and token distribution services, harmonised compliance requirements across all licensed activities and given clearer definitions for collateral wallet arrangements. 
VARA’s team will engage with licensed entities and expects the companies to comply with the updated rules after a 30-day transition period.
“In line with global regulatory best practices, a 30-day transition period has been granted to all impacted virtual a…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Ezra Reguerra</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[China Is Building An AI Supercomputer In Space]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=352163</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/352163/china-is-building-an-ai-supercomputer-in-space/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T09:58:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[China has successfully launched the first 12 satellites for its planned orbital supercomputer network project. The satellites were created by ADA Space and form what the company calls the “Three-Body Computing Constellation”, which is part of a wider program. The program, known as “Star Compute”, is a collaboration with Zhejiang Lab that aims to create […]
The post China Is Building An AI Supercomputer In Space appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nurul Kamil</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Qualcomm Confirms Snapdragon Summit 2025 Dates]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=352177</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/352177/qualcomm-confirms-snapdragon-summit-2025-dates/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T09:36:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Qualcomm has officially announced the dates for its annual Snapdragon Summit for this year. Speaking during its Computex 2025 keynote today, company president and CEO Cristiano Amon confirmed that this year’s event will take place from 23 to 25 September, once again in Hawaii. Amon also revealed that Qualcomm will unveil its next Snapdragon X […]
The post Qualcomm Confirms Snapdragon Summit 2025 Dates appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Heirul Kamel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[VARA Fortifies Controls on Crypto Margin Trading in Dubai, Refreshes Rulebook]]></title>
        <id>64a27131-a681-436e-9c3c-9cccdf8e1f8d</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2025/05/19/vara-fortifies-controls-on-crypto-margin-trading-in-dubai-refreshes-rulebook"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T09:33:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[VARA has introduced greater leverage controls and collateralization requirements through provisions in its Broker-Deal and Exchange Rulebooks]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Crawley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tether surpasses Germany’s $111B of US Treasury holdings]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/tether-us-treasury-holdings-surpass-germany-q1-2025</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/tether-us-treasury-holdings-surpass-germany-q1-2025?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T09:33:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tether, the $151 billion stablecoin issuance giant, has surpassed Germany in United States Treasury bill holdings, showcasing the benefits of a diversified reserve strategy that has helped the firm navigate the volatility of the cryptocurrency market.
Tether, the issuer of the world’s largest stablecoin, USDt (USDT), has surpassed Germany’s $111.4 billion worth of US Treasurys, data from the US Department of the Treasury shows.
Foreign countries by US Treasury holdings. Source: Ticdata.treasury.gov
Tether has surpassed $120 billion worth of Treasury bills, the firm shared in its attestation report for the first quarter of 2025. That makes Tether the 19th largest entity among all counties in terms of T-bill investments.
“This milestone not only reinforces the company’s conservative reserve …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Zoltan Vardai</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Road Closures, Diversions In Klang Valley Scheduled For ASEAN Summit 2025]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=352155</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/352155/road-closures-diversions-in-klang-valley-scheduled-for-asean-summit-2025/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T09:23:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There will be major road closures across Klang Valley in conjunction with the ASEAN Summit 2025, which is set to occur on 26 and 27 May. A total of six major highways and 25 main roads will be closed in stages from 23 to 28 May. The Bukit Aman Traffic Investigation and Enforcement Department (JSPT) […]
The post Road Closures, Diversions In Klang Valley Scheduled For ASEAN Summit 2025 appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Newsdesk</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Side projects I've built since 2009]]></title>
        <id>https://naeemnur.com/side-projects/</id>
        <link href="https://naeemnur.com/side-projects/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T09:17:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[$107K fakeout or new all-time highs? 5 things to know in Bitcoin this week]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/107k-fakeout-or-new-all-time-highs-5-things-bitcoin-this-week</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/107k-fakeout-or-new-all-time-highs-5-things-bitcoin-this-week?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T09:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin (BTC) starts a new week with a long-awaited breakout from a narrow trading range around $103,000. 

BTC price action grabs liquidity before reversing to its starting position, liquidating many an emotional trader on the way. A fakeout or a taste of things to come?

The May 18  daily and weekly close nonetheless became Bitcoin’s highest ever.

US trade deals remain high on the list of macro volatility triggers for risk asset traders this week.

Crypto’s correlation with stocks paints a mixed picture, adding to uncertainty over how macro developments will influence Bitcoin and altcoins going forward.

Bitcoin exchange volume delta becomes a key ingredient in assessing the staying power of BTC price breakouts, per analysis from CryptoQuant.

 
A liquidity grab for the ages
Bitcoin pri…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by William Suberg</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Qualcomm Announces Development Of Data Centre Chips]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=352166</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/352166/qualcomm-announces-development-of-data-centre-chips/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T09:08:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[During his keynote at Computex 2025 in Taipei today, Qualcomm president and CEO Cristiano Amon announced that the company will re-enter the data centre market with the development of its own specialised CPU chips. The new processor will incorporate technology from NVIDIA, enabling tight integration with the latter’s AI chips. NVIDIA’s graphics processing units (GPUs) […]
The post Qualcomm Announces Development Of Data Centre Chips appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Heirul Kamel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mazda Introduces The Sports Edition Of The EZ-6]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=352140</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/352140/mazda-introduces-the-sports-edition-of-the-ez-6/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T09:00:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mazda revealed a sportier edition of the EZ-6 in China. This Sports Edition is a model produced with its joint venture Changan. The saloon was developed with the input that was gathered from the company’s team in Japan, China and Europe. So what does the Sports Edition of the Mazda EZ-6 offer? Well, as for […]
The post Mazda Introduces The Sports Edition Of The EZ-6 appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Keran</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Inside the story that enraged OpenAI]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1116614</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/05/19/1116614/hao-empire-ai-openai/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In 2019, Karen Hao, a senior reporter with MIT Technology Review, pitched me on writing a story about a then little-known company, OpenAI. It was her biggest assignment to date. Hao’s feat of reporting took a series of twists and turns over the coming months, eventually revealing how OpenAI’s ambition had taken it far afield…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Karen Hao</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto drainers as a service: What you need to know]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/explained/crypto-drainers-as-a-service-what-you-need-to-know</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/explained/crypto-drainers-as-a-service-what-you-need-to-know?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T08:55:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What is a crypto drainer?            
            
                
A crypto drainer is a malicious script designed to steal cryptocurrency from your wallet. Unlike regular phishing attacks that try to capture login credentials, a crypto drainer tricks you into connecting your wallets, such as MetaMask or Phantom, and unknowingly authorizing transactions that grant them access to your funds.
Disguised as a legitimate Web3 project, a crypto drainer is usually promoted via compromised social media accounts or Discord groups. Once you fall prey to the fraud, the drainer can instantly transfer assets from the wallet.
Crypto drainers may take various forms:

Malicious smart contracts that initiate unauthorized transfers.
Fake NFTs or token systems that create deceptive exchanges or assets.

Cry…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Dilip Kumar Patairya</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Apple KYC glitch on Bybit draws swift executive response to recover $100K]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/bybit-fixes-kyc-glitch-100-k-crypto-recovery</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/bybit-fixes-kyc-glitch-100-k-crypto-recovery?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T08:46:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency exchange Bybit said it had involved team members, including an executive, to fix a glitch that affected a single user who could not go through an Apple-based know-your-client (KYC) system.
In a May 18 X post, the Bybit China Team said it received reports about users experiencing withdrawal restrictions on the Bybit platform due to a KYC verification anomaly when logging in with an Apple ID. The team claimed to have immediately responded and taken action involving multiple departments, including the firm’s chief operating officer, Helen Liu.
Other people involved in the operation were the heads of customer service, risk control, the Chinese-language division, product managers and the technical team. The exchange coordinated its actions with the user.
After an internal investi…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Adrian Zmudzinski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin bulls should &#039;be careful with longs&#039; as BTC price risks $100K breakdown]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-bulls-careful-with-longs-btc-price-risks-100k-breakdown</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-bulls-careful-with-longs-btc-price-risks-100k-breakdown?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T08:29:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Key takeaways:

Bitcoin dropped over 4.5% on May 19, confirming a bearish divergence and threatening a break below $100,000.

Analysts highlight $97,000–$98,500 as key support that the bulls must hold. 

A potential inverse head-and-shoulders pattern points to a retest of $91,000 before any bullish continuation.

Bitcoin (BTC) is down over 4.5% from its intraday high on May 19, falling to around $102,000 in its worst daily drop in over a month.
BTC/USD daily price chart. Source: TradingView
BTC’s drop accompanied downside moves elsewhere in the risk market, prompted by Moody’s latest downgrade of the US government due to a rising budget deficit and the lack of a credible fiscal consolidation plan.
The decline confirms a bearish divergence and, combined with other technical factors, raises …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Yashu Gola</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[realme GT 7, GT 7T Listed By Local Retailer Ahead Of Global Launch]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=352151</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/352151/realme-gt-7-gt-7t-price/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T08:25:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[realme will be launching more affordable models of the GT 7 lineup this month, following the release of the Pro model. The brand will have a global debut for both the vanilla GT 7 and 7T on 27 May 2025, but it is unclear when exactly it will be landing in Malaysia. While the company […]
The post realme GT 7, GT 7T Listed By Local Retailer Ahead Of Global Launch appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ikmal Rozlan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bulls and Bears Get Caught off Guard as Bitcoin Jumps to $106K, Then Falls Back to $103K]]></title>
        <id>d7f71c03-1b3b-42fb-a8b5-2ada6d5563cd</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/19/bulls-and-bears-get-caught-off-guard-as-bitcoin-jumps-to-usd106k-then-falls-back-to-usd103k"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T08:16:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The sudden price gyrations wiped out over $460 million in long positions and $220 million in shorts, across futures tracking majors like ether (ETH), solana (SOL), and dogecoin (DOGE).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shaurya Malwa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Samsung Galaxy Z Fold7, G Fold May Feature Titanium Backplate]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=352134</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/352134/samsung-galaxy-z-fold7-g-fold-may-feature-titanium-backplate/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T08:16:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A report from The Elec has emerged, claiming that Samsung will be equipping its upcoming Galaxy Z Fold7 and Galaxy G Fold with titanium back plates. The latter phone is slated to be the brand’s first tri-fold model. As per the report, Samsung will be using titanium for the Galaxy Z Fold7 and G Fold […]
The post Samsung Galaxy Z Fold7, G Fold May Feature Titanium Backplate appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Newsdesk</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why is Ethereum (ETH) price down today?]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/why-is-ethereum-eth-price-down-today</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/why-is-ethereum-eth-price-down-today?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T08:03:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Key takeaways:

Ether’s price fell over 5% to $2,380 on May 19, mirroring similar downward moves across the wider cryptocurrency market.

Long liquidations accompanied ETH’s price drop.

Below $2,400 could be a buy-the-dip opportunity.

Ether (ETH) price declined by over 4.5% in the last 24 hours to around $2,380 on May 19. 
Data from Cointelegraph Markets Pro and TradingView shows ETH lost as much as 10% of its value, dropping to an intraday low of $2,353 on May 19 from a high of $2,587 on May 18. Its daily trading volume has jumped by 110% over the last 24 hours to $30.4 billion, reinforcing the intensity of the sell-side activity.
ETH/USD hourly chart. Source: Cointelegraph/TradingView
Let’s look at the factors behind Ether’s losses today.
Ethereum leads crypto market sell-off
ETH’s dro…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Nancy Lubale</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vitalik Buterin proposes partially stateless nodes for Ethereum scaling]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/vitalik-buterin-partially-stateless-nodes-ethereum-scaling-privacy</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/vitalik-buterin-partially-stateless-nodes-ethereum-scaling-privacy?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T07:55:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum co-founder Vitalik Buterin unveiled a proposal to preserve trustless, censorship-resistant access to Ethereum, even as the network scales. 
On May 19, Buterin shared a post outlining how to make Ethereum’s layer-1 scaling “more friendly” to users running local nodes for personal use. The Ethereum co-founder highlighted the importance of independent users running nodes, saying that a market dominated by a few Remote Procedure Call (RPC) providers risks censorship. 
RPC providers let wallets, users and apps interact with the blockchain without running their own nodes. Crypto wallets are usually connected to an RPC provider behind the scenes. Buterin said there are risks to this setup. 
“A market structure dominated by a few RPC providers is one that will face strong pressure to depl…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Ezra Reguerra</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[U.S. 30-Year Treasury Yield Breaches 5% Amid Moody's Rating Downgrade, Fiscal Concerns]]></title>
        <id>7b3bb411-34bf-447e-8808-3dd87f427ff8</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/19/us-30-year-treasury-yield-breaches-5-amid-moodys-rating-downgrade-fiscal-concerns"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T07:53:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Rising deficits, reduced foreign demand, and investor unease over trade policy drive bond market turbulence and broader risk aversion.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>James Van Straten</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ripple Signs Two More Payment System Customers in UAE Expansion]]></title>
        <id>2ecfb1df-2865-4b44-9c43-de8eb030ba90</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2025/05/19/ripple-signs-two-more-payment-system-customers-in-uae-expansion"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T07:42:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The agreements follow Ripple securing a license from the Dubai Financial Services Authority (DFSA) in March.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shaurya Malwa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Foxconn builds AI factory in partnership with Taiwan and Nvidia]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008261</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/games/foxconn-builds-ai-factory-in-partnership-with-taiwan-and-nvidia/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T07:14:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nvidia and Foxconn announced they are working with the Taiwan government to build an AI factory supercomputer.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dean Takahashi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nvidia launches AI-first DGX Personal Computing Systems]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008256</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/games/nvidia-launches-ai-first-dgx-personal-computing-systems/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T07:06:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nvidia announced that Taiwan’s leading system manufacturers are set to build Nvidia DGX Spark and DGX Station systems.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dean Takahashi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nvidia-powered supercomputer to enable quantum leap for Taiwan’s research]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008257</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/games/nvidia-powered-supercomputer-to-enable-quantum-leap-for-taiwans-research/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T06:58:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nvidia is powering a supercomputer at Taiwan’s National Center for High-Performance Computing that’s set to deliver over eight times more AI performance than before.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dean Takahashi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nvidia powers world’s largest quantum research supercomputer]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008248</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/games/nvidia-powers-worlds-largest-quantum-research-supercomputer/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T06:48:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nvidia announced the opening of the Global Research and Development Center for Business by Quantum-AI Technology.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dean Takahashi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Metaplanet Buys Another 1,004 Bitcoin, Lifts Holdings to Over $800M Worth of BTC]]></title>
        <id>65261613-9f36-4ccf-982b-6a9ca1b304ce</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/19/metaplanet-buys-another-1004-bitcoin-lifts-holdings-to-over-800m-worth-of-btc"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T06:46:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The average purchase price for this latest tranche was $103,873 per bitcoin, according to a Monday disclosure.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shaurya Malwa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nvidia provides Omniverse Blueprint for AI factory digital twins]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008243</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/games/nvidia-provides-omniverse-blueprint-for-ai-factory-digital-twins/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T06:34:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nvidia today announced a significant expansion of the Nvidia Omniverse Blueprint for AI factory digital twins, now available as a preview.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dean Takahashi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Bull Case for Galaxy Digital Is AI Data Centers Not Bitcoin Mining, Research Firm Says]]></title>
        <id>32ad31f0-2549-4827-8de5-23fb4f649096</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/19/the-bull-case-for-galaxy-digital-is-ai-data-centers-not-bitcoin-mining-research-firm-says"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T06:16:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Rittenhouse Research, a new firm covering fintech, AI, and crypto, is giving GLXY a strong buy rating because of its BTC mining to AI transition]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sam Reynolds</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Metaplanet scoops 1,004 Bitcoin in 2nd-biggest buy ever]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/metaplanet-scoops-1004-bitcoin-second-largest-buy</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/metaplanet-scoops-1004-bitcoin-second-largest-buy?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T06:12:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Japanese investment firm Metaplanet has made its second-largest single Bitcoin purchase ever, scooping up more than 1,000 Bitcoin as the cryptocurrency came within 3% of its all-time high.
Metaplanet said on May 19 that it purchased 1,004 Bitcoin (BTC) for a total cost of around 15.2 billion yen ($104.6 million), bringing its total holdings to 7,800 Bitcoin worth around $807 million at current market prices.
It is the second-largest purchase the firm has made following its buy of 1,241 BTC for $129 million on May 12 in a move that pushed its Bitcoin holdings above that of El Salvador.
Metaplanet has the largest Bitcoin holdings of a public company in Asia and has the tenth largest holdings among public firms globally, according to BiTBO data.
The firm reported a first-quarter BTC Yield of …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Martin Young</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase hit with wave of lawsuits over customer data breaches]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/coinbase-wave-of-lawsuits-over-customer-data-breaches</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/coinbase-wave-of-lawsuits-over-customer-data-breaches?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T06:01:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase has been hit with a flood of lawsuits after it recently disclosed its user data was breached, with users accusing the crypto exchange of mishandling the incident.
At least six lawsuits were filed against Coinbase between May 15 and May 16, which all made various claims that the exchange failed to keep stringent security protocols to protect user data and handled the data breach aftermath poorly.
In one of the lawsuits, filed in a New York federal court on May 16, plaintiff Paul Bender argued that Coinbase failed to protect the sensitive personal information of millions of users during the data breach. 
Users are suing Coinbase, alleging the exchange failed to protect their sensitive data. Source: PACER
Coinbase reported on May 15 that four days earlier it had been hit with a $20 m…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Stephen Katte</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nvidia charges ahead with humanoid robotics aided by the cloud]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008144</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/games/nvidia-charges-ahead-with-humanoid-robotics-aided-by-the-cloud/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T06:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nvidia said it is racing ahead with humanoid robotics technology, providing more Blackwell systems to accelerate humanoid robot development.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dean Takahashi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Binance, Kraken Thwarted Social Engineering Attacks Similar to Coinbase Hack]]></title>
        <id>ab41e8eb-40c4-483d-9cef-6519c9206f19</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/web3/2025/05/19/binance-kraken-thwarted-social-engineering-attacks-similar-to-coinbase-hack"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T05:15:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Attackers reportedly tried bribing support agents, but Binance and Kraken’s internal systems blocked the attempts.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Francisco Rodrigues</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[“There are people who can see and others who cannot even look”]]></title>
        <id>https://worldhistory.substack.com/p/there-are-people-who-can-see-and</id>
        <link href="https://worldhistory.substack.com/p/there-are-people-who-can-see-and"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T00:31:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[From dot-com to dot-AI: How we can learn from the last tech transformation (and avoid making the same mistakes)]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3007969</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/from-dot-com-to-dot-ai-how-we-can-learn-from-the-last-tech-transformation-and-avoid-making-the-same-mistakes/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-18T19:05:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The AI winners won’t be the ones slapping “AI” on a landing page — they’ll be creating products enterprises can't live without.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kailiang Fu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Nears Golden Cross Weeks After 'Trapping Bears' as U.S. Debt Concerns Mount]]></title>
        <id>7c62efb2-7b44-4d03-a19c-75ee592eeafe</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/18/bitcoin-nears-bullish-golden-cross-following-failed-death-cross-echoing-2024-pattern"/>
        <updated>2025-05-18T16:58:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BTC nears golden cross, as Moody's downgrade validates bond markets' concerns about the sustainability of the U.S. fiscal debt.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Omkar Godbole</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[InventWood is about to mass-produce wood that's stronger than steel]]></title>
        <id>https://techcrunch.com/2025/05/12/inventwood-is-about-to-mass-produce-wood-thats-stronger-than-steel/</id>
        <link href="https://techcrunch.com/2025/05/12/inventwood-is-about-to-mass-produce-wood-thats-stronger-than-steel/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-18T12:22:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[XRP Price Surges After V-Shaped Recovery, Targets $3.40]]></title>
        <id>22282d22-1502-416f-8550-b19a4462336d</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/18/xrp-price-surges-after-v-shaped-recovery-targets-usd3-40"/>
        <updated>2025-05-18T08:23:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Institutional buyers step in after sharp sell-off, establishing strong support at critical levels.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>AI Boost</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SUI Surges After Finding Strong Support at $3.75 Level]]></title>
        <id>dccf97d1-13bb-47c4-a0c9-78f9636b452b</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/18/sui-surges-after-finding-strong-support-at-usd3-75-level"/>
        <updated>2025-05-18T08:05:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The resilient cryptocurrency shows remarkable recovery amid broader market volatility, establishing higher lows throughout trading session.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>AI Boost</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Adopting agentic AI? Build AI fluency, redesign workflows, don’t neglect supervision]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3007933</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/adopting-agentic-ai-build-ai-fluency-redesign-workflows-dont-neglect-supervision/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-17T19:05:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How can organizations decide how to use human-in-the-loop mechanisms and collaborative frameworks with AI agents?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Imran Aftab, 10Pearls</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google’s AlphaEvolve: The AI agent that reclaimed 0.7% of Google’s compute – and how to copy it]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3007997</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/googles-alphaevolve-the-ai-agent-that-reclaimed-0-7-of-googles-compute-and-how-to-copy-it/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-17T00:31:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google's AlphaEvolve is the epitome of a best-practice AI agent orchestration. It offers a lesson in production-grade agent engineering. Discover its architecture & essential takeaways for your enterprise AI strategy.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matt Marshall</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Shrink exploit windows, slash MTTP: Why ring deployment is now a must for enterprise defense]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3007233</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/security/slash-mttp-block-exploits-ring-deployment-now-essential/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-16T20:48:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ring deployment slashes MTTP and legacy CVE risk. Learn how Ivanti and Southstar Bank are modernizing patch strategy with real-time intel.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Louis Columbus</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Extend Power Apps with Reusable Components]]></title>
        <id>682779afad5694b25984f6b1</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/powerapps-component-crash-course/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-16T17:45:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you have experience in traditional software development, low-code tools may feel a bit sparse at first. But to many people’s surprise, traditional techniques often translate quite well to low-code development. Not always one-for-one – but usually ...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brandon Wozniewicz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Write Math Equations in Google Docs]]></title>
        <id>68275cf15ed8a1db0cf8769b</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/write-math-equations-in-google-docs/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-16T15:42:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Math equations are a critical part of academic papers, research reports, and technical documentation. While LaTeX is widely used for professional typesetting, Google Docs offers a robust set of features for inserting and formatting math equations and...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Vikram Aruchamy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OpenAI launches research preview of Codex AI software engineering agent for developers — with parallel tasking]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3007915</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/programming-development/openai-launches-research-preview-of-codex-ai-software-engineering-agent-for-developers-with-parallel-tasking/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-16T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Starting today it will be available as a research preview for ChatGPT Pro, Enterprise, and Team users, with support later for Plus and Edu.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carl Franzen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rivers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.futilitycloset.com/2025/05/15/rivers/</id>
        <link href="https://www.futilitycloset.com/2025/05/15/rivers/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-16T13:19:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Acer unveils AI-powered wearables at Computex 2025]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3007872</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/games/acer-unveils-ai-powered-wearables-at-computex-2025/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-16T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Acer Gadget, a subsidiary of Acer, unveiled AI-powered wearables at the Computex 2025 trade show in Taiwan.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dean Takahashi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Download: the first personalized gene-editing drug, and Montana’s Right to Try experiment]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1116619</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/05/16/1116619/the-download-the-first-personalized-gene-editing-drug-and-montanas-right-to-try-experiment/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-16T12:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is today’s edition of The Download, our weekday newsletter that provides a daily dose of what’s going on in the world of technology. This baby boy was treated with the first personalized gene-editing drug Doctors say they constructed a bespoke gene-editing treatment in less than seven months and used it to treat a baby with a…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rhiannon Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to make Developer Friends When You Don't Live in Silicon Valley, with Iraqi Engineer Code;Life [Podcast #172]]]></title>
        <id>68271ae2c90fa4a071c44a2b</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-make-developer-friends-when-you-dont-live-in-silicon-valley-with-iraqi-engineer-codelife-podcast-172/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-16T11:00:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On this week's episode of the podcast, freeCodeCamp founder Quincy Larson interviews software engineer and live coding streamer Code;Life.   For those of you watching the video version of this interview, she lives in Iraq and she uses a 3D avatar to ...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Access to experimental medical treatments is expanding across the US]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1116526</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/05/16/1116526/access-to-experimental-medical-treatments-expanding-us/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-16T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A couple of weeks ago I was in Washington, DC, for a gathering of scientists, policymakers, and longevity enthusiasts. They had come together to discuss ways to speed along the development of drugs and other treatments that might extend the human lifespan. One approach that came up was to simply make experimental drugs more easily…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jessica Hamzelou</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Remarks on AI from NZ]]></title>
        <id>https://nealstephenson.substack.com/p/remarks-on-ai-from-nz</id>
        <link href="https://nealstephenson.substack.com/p/remarks-on-ai-from-nz"/>
        <updated>2025-05-16T03:54:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elon Musk’s xAI tries to explain Grok’s South African race relations freakout the other day]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3007876</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/elon-musks-xai-tries-to-explain-groks-south-african-race-relations-freakout-the-other-day/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-16T02:47:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With its prompts now public and a team of human babysitters on call, Grok is supposedly back on script. But the incident underscores...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carl Franzen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn A1 Level Spanish]]></title>
        <id>68269a8eb0cc91a6c87a682d</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-a1-level-spanish/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-16T01:53:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learning a new language can open doors to new cultures, connections, and opportunities, and Spanish is one of the most widely spoken languages in the world. Whether you're dreaming of traveling to Spanish-speaking countries, connecting with Spanish-s...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Software engineering-native AI models have arrived: What Windsurf’s SWE-1 means for technical decision-makers]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3007851</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/software-engineering-native-ai-models-have-arrived-what-windsurfs-swe-1-means-for-technical-decision-makers/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-16T00:30:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Windsurf's new SWE-1 AI models tackle the complete software engineering workflow, potentially reducing development cycles and technical debt.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sean Michael Kerner</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is Sui: A Comprehensive Guide to Web3 Scalability]]></title>
        <id>6823533984101f00013a5ca4</id>
        <link href="https://blog.quicknode.com/what-is-sui-a-comprehensive-guide-to-web3-scalability/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-15T23:34:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Explore how Sui Network achieves 300,000 TPS through parallel processing, and its applications in gaming, DeFi, and supply chain management.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>QuickNode</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AI Meets Blockchain: Transforming Technology for the Next Era]]></title>
        <id>682354c584101f00013a5cb9</id>
        <link href="https://blog.quicknode.com/ai-and-blockchain-transforming-technology-together/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-15T23:34:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discover how AI and blockchain integration enhances security, efficiency, and innovation in healthcare, supply chains, and financial services.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>QuickNode</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Reduce model integration costs while scaling AI: LangChain’s open ecosystem delivers where closed vendors can’t]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3007838</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/reduce-model-integration-costs-while-scaling-ai-langchains-open-ecosystem-delivers-where-closed-vendors-cant/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-15T23:16:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Through the LangGraph Platform, organizations can deploy agents with one-click deployment, horizontal scaling to handle “bursty, long-running traffic."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Emilia David</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The $1 Billion database bet: What Databricks’ Neon acquisition means for your AI strategy]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3007813</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/data-infrastructure/the-1-billion-database-bet-what-databricks-neon-acquisition-means-for-your-ai-strategy/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-15T22:54:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Databricks' $1 billion acquisition of Neon highlights how serverless PostgreSQL has become essential for agentic AI development.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sean Michael Kerner</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[From OAuth bottleneck to AI acceleration: How CIAM solutions are removing the top integration barrier in enterprise AI agent deployment]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3007718</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/from-oauth-bottleneck-to-ai-acceleration-how-ciam-solutions-are-removing-the-top-integration-barrier-in-enterprise-ai-agent-deployment/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-15T21:43:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New CIAM platforms are addressing a significant barrier to enterprise AI adoption: identity management for autonomous agents.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Chen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[About Asteroids, Atari's biggest arcade hit]]></title>
        <id>https://www.goto10retro.com/p/about-asteroids-ataris-biggest-arcade</id>
        <link href="https://www.goto10retro.com/p/about-asteroids-ataris-biggest-arcade"/>
        <updated>2025-05-15T18:50:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This baby boy was treated with the first personalized gene-editing drug]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1116524</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/05/15/1116524/this-baby-boy-was-treated-with-the-first-personalized-gene-editing-drug/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-15T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Doctors say they constructed a bespoke gene-editing treatment in less than seven months and used it to treat a baby with a deadly metabolic condition. The rapid-fire attempt to rewrite the child’s DNA marks the first time gene editing has been tailored to treat a single individual, according to a report published in the New…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Antonio Regalado</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Arm is rebranding its system-on-a-chip product designs to showcase power savings for AI workloads, targeting a surprising sector]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3007796</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/arm-is-rebranding-its-system-on-a-chip-product-designs-to-showcase-power-savings-for-ai-workloads-targeting-a-surprising-sector/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-15T16:17:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For engineers orchestrating AI pipelines across environments, the modularity and performance tiering within Arm’s new architecture...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carl Franzen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Show HN: Cogitator – A Python Toolkit for Chain-of-Thought Prompting]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/habedi/cogitator</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/habedi/cogitator"/>
        <updated>2025-05-15T16:15:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[You.com’s ARI Enterprise crushes OpenAI in head-to-head tests, aims at deep research market]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3007729</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/you-coms-ari-enterprise-crushes-openai-in-head-to-head-tests-aims-at-deep-research-market/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-15T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You.com launches ARI Enterprise, an AI research platform that outperforms OpenAI in 76% of head-to-head tests and integrates with enterprise data sources to transform business intelligence with 400+ source analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Nuñez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Download: Montana’s experimental treatments, and Google DeepMind’s new AI agent]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1116516</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/05/15/1116516/the-download-montanas-experimental-treatments-and-google-deepminds-new-ai-agent/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-15T12:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is today’s edition of The Download, our weekday newsletter that provides a daily dose of what’s going on in the world of technology. The first US hub for experimental medical treatments is coming The news: A bill that allows clinics to sell unproven treatments has been passed in Montana. Under the legislation, doctors can apply for…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rhiannon Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Adventure Layer: AI Native Onchain Games, Unleashed]]></title>
        <id>6824c55abf73460001094973</id>
        <link href="https://blog.quicknode.com/adventure-layer-launches-on-quicknode-raas/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-15T12:04:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Adventure Layer launches layer-2 chain leveraging QuickNode's Rollup-as-a-Service (RaaS) product.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>QuickNode</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How US research cuts are threatening crucial climate data]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1116485</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/05/15/1116485/climate-data/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-15T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Over the last few months, and especially the last few weeks, there’s been an explosion of news about proposed budget cuts to science in the US. One trend I’ve noticed: Researchers and civil servants are sounding the alarm that those cuts mean we might lose key data that helps us understand our world and how…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Casey Crownhart</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OpenAI brings GPT-4.1 and 4.1 mini to ChatGPT — what enterprises should know]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3007689</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/openai-brings-gpt-4-1-and-4-1-mini-to-chatgpt-what-enterprises-should-know/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-14T23:46:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As OpenAI continues to evolve its model offerings, GPT-4.1 represents a step forward in democratizing advanced AI for enterprise environments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carl Franzen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How DNS Works: A Guide to Understanding the Internet's Address Book]]></title>
        <id>6824f1ac04a60b4a58654ddc</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-dns-works-the-internets-address-book/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-14T19:40:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Domain Name System (DNS) translates domain names (like example.com) into IP addresses (like 192.0.2.1) so we can easily access websites. In this guide, you’ll learn how DNS resolution starts, its step-by-step process, how caching works, and the r...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dhruv Prajapati</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Load Balancing with Azure Application Gateway and Azure Load Balancer – When to Use Each One]]></title>
        <id>6824f10a7d203c180e5ea4b2</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/load-balancing-with-azure-application-gateway-and-azure-load-balancer/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-14T19:37:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You’ve probably heard someone mention load balancing when talking about cloud apps. Maybe even names like Azure Load Balancer, Azure Application Gateway, or something about Virtual Machines and Scale Sets. 😵‍💫 It all sounds important...but also a l...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Prince Onukwili</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build Slim and Fast Docker Images with Multi-Stage Builds]]></title>
        <id>6824b1638a2b26e9d2d0fe86</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-slim-fast-docker-images-with-multi-stage-builds/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-14T15:06:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Apps don’t stay simple forever. More features mean more dependencies, slower builds, and heavier Docker images. That’s where things start to hurt. Docker helps, but without the right setup, your builds can quickly get bloated. Multi-stage builds make...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniel Adeboye</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google DeepMind’s new AI agent cracks real-world problems better than humans can]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1116438</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/05/14/1116438/google-deepminds-new-ai-uses-large-language-models-to-crack-real-world-problems/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-14T15:00:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google DeepMind has once again used large language models to discover new solutions to long-standing problems in math and computer science. This time the firm has shown that its approach can not only tackle unsolved theoretical puzzles, but improve a range of important real-world processes as well. Google DeepMind’s new tool, called AlphaEvolve, uses the…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Will Douglas Heaven</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn Vite for a Better Web Development Workflow]]></title>
        <id>6824ae178a2b26e9d2d0fe4c</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-vite-for-a-better-web-development-workflow/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-14T14:52:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Speed and simplicity are at the heart of modern web development. As applications grow more complex and the demand for rapid iteration increases, developers are constantly searching for tools that minimize friction and maximize productivity. Tradition...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Web Services Work – The Unseen Engines of the Connected World]]></title>
        <id>6824ad336ea9fe84cfb4d0c4</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-web-services-work-with-examples/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-14T14:48:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Have you ever wondered how your weather app instantly knows the forecast, how you can book flights from multiple airlines on one travel site, or how logging into one service can magically log you into another? The answer often lies in a powerful, yet...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kumar Anand</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[QuickLee V2: An Improved Transparent Look into RPC Provider Latency]]></title>
        <id>680fc8e1f8ae810001969b47</id>
        <link href="https://blog.quicknode.com/quicklee-v2/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-14T13:57:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[View public and real-time dashboards to better understand latency and speed when evaluating RPC providers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>QuickNode</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Breathe lands $21M Series B to predict battery performance]]></title>
        <id>https://techcrunch.com/?p=3003769</id>
        <link href="https://techcrunch.com/2025/05/07/breathe-lands-21m-series-b-to-predict-battery-performance/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-07T12:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Breathe has developed a suite of tools that it says helps automakers and others get the most out of their batteries.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tim De Chant</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Join the 2025 Web3j Mentorships: Build the Future of Ethereum on the JVM]]></title>
        <id>6819c8dc41eeeb000183d37b</id>
        <link href="https://blog.web3labs.com/join-the-2025-web3j-mentorships-build-the-future-of-ethereum-on-the-jvm/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T08:32:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Linux Foundation’s Decentralized Trust (LFDT) mentorship program is back in 2025 with two exciting opportunities for developers passionate about Ethereum, Android, and the Java Virtual Machine (JVM). Whether you’re a seasoned blockchain developer or an Android enthusiast eager to dive into Web3, these mentorships offer]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>George Tebrean</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>