<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2025-05-07T06:50:57.495Z</id>
    <title>AngJianming RSS Feed</title>
    <updated>2025-05-07T06:50:57.495Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bolt Now Includes Tolls In Its Ride Fares]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=350802</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/350802/bolt-tolls-ride-fares/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-07T06:48:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bolt has officially announced that its ride-hailing service now includes toll fares into every ride, ensuring no surprise fees. It is the first e-hailing platform to do so, at least in Malaysia, where the norm is for drivers to manually input the toll fares after the ride is completed. With this new policy, what you […]
The post Bolt Now Includes Tolls In Its Ride Fares appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ikmal Rozlan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Design a UFO Using 3D CAD Software]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/julia970/how-to-design-a-ufo-using-3d-cad-software-4hc</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/julia970/how-to-design-a-ufo-using-3d-cad-software-4hc"/>
        <updated>2025-05-07T06:39:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How to Design a UFO Using 3D CAD Software
This article provides a comprehensive guide to designing a UFO using SelfCAD. It outlines the core stages of the modeling process, including 3D sketching, symmetry adjustments and detailing. Through this structured approach, readers will gain practical knowledge of SelfCAD’s modeling workflow while also learning how to apply design thinking to conceptualize and execute a believable extraterrestrial vehicle model.
https://www.selfcad.com/tutorials/255y94q1y2t35h1i2d2gx25so4x3v1a5g12n
Once you’ve launched the editor;




















https://www.selfcad.com/tutorials) available on the SelfCAD website. The tutorials page provides a treasure trove of guides, tips, and tricks that cater to designers of all levels.
https://www.selfcad.com/academy/curriculum/), https://www.youtube.com/@3dmodeling101, and 3D Modeling 101 series (https://www.youtube.com/playlist?list=PL74nFNT8yS9DcE1UlUUdiR1wFGv9DDfTB). This comprehensive resource offers in-depth courses taught by industry experts, allowing you to master the intricacies of SelfCAD at your own pace]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Juliana Misiko</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Fun Afternoon Troubleshooting OIDC/OAuth SSO Errors in Grafana and Keycloak]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/patimapoochai/a-fun-afternoon-troubleshooting-oidcoauth-sso-errors-in-grafana-and-keycloak-2mb5</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/patimapoochai/a-fun-afternoon-troubleshooting-oidcoauth-sso-errors-in-grafana-and-keycloak-2mb5"/>
        <updated>2025-05-07T06:38:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I'm working on adding a simple IAM stack to my home lab to enable SSO for my services like Grafana. I configured the Grafana instance to allow for SSO authentication using Keycloak as the provider and OIDC/OAuth as the protocols. When I clicked the SSO option on the Grafana login page, however, I got an error after it redirected the browser to Keycloak's sign-in page.

The page said that the redirect_uri was invalid, and online forums described this error as being caused by the Valid redirect URI list in Keycloak not matching the URL of the Grafana instance. The instance is being accessed on http://nextcloud.home.internal:30007, and when I check the redirection URI list on Keycloak, this URL is included in the list. If this isn't the cause of this error, then what is?


Maybe there's a clu…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patima Poochai</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Async Annotation In Spring Boot]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/codingshuttle/the-async-annotation-in-spring-boot-1nen</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/codingshuttle/the-async-annotation-in-spring-boot-1nen"/>
        <updated>2025-05-07T06:36:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you’re using Spring Boot, you’ve probably bumped into the @Async annotation at some point, but what does it actually do, and why should you care? Let’s break it down in a way that actually makes sense, without all the jargon.
@Async is like telling Spring, “Hey, this task? Let it run in the background while I get on with other stuff.” When you throw @Async on a method, Spring takes that method and hands it off to a different thread, leaving your main thread free to keep doing its thing. It’s like delegating a long-running task to someone else so you don’t have to sit there waiting for it to finish. So, whether it’s pulling data from an API or doing some heavy lifting in your code, @Async helps keep things moving without holding up the rest of your app.
So, how does Spring make all this …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Coding Shuttle</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to set up a global .gitignore]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/maiobarbero/how-to-set-up-a-global-gitignore-4e09</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/maiobarbero/how-to-set-up-a-global-gitignore-4e09"/>
        <updated>2025-05-07T06:33:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you work with multiple Git repositories, you’ve likely run into the frustration of ignoring the same files (like .DS_Store, Thumbs.db, or your IDE settings) over and over again. Fortunately, Git allows you to define a global .gitignore file that applies to all repositories on your system. This is done through the core.excludesfile configuration option.
In this article, I'll walk you through how to set up a global .gitignore file using git config.
Some files are specific to your system or development environment and should never be committed to any project. Examples include:
macOS system files (.DS_Store)
Windows thumbnails (Thumbs.db)
IDE configs (.idea/, .vscode/)
Log files (*.log)
Local environment files (.env)
Instead of duplicating the same ignore rules in every repo, a global .gitignore keeps things DRY (Don't Repeat Yourself).
Start by creating a .gitignore_global file in your home directory (or anywhere you prefer):
touch ~/.gitignore_global

Then, edit it and add the rules you want:
# macOS
.DS_Store

# Windows
Thumbs.db

# IDEs
.vscode/
.idea/

# Logs
*.log

# Env files
.env

Tell Git to use this file globally:
git config --global core.excludesfile ~/.gitignore_global

You can verify it worked with:
git config --global core.excludesfile

This should output the path you just set.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matteo Barbero</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meta Awarded Over US$167 Million In WhatsApp Case Against Israeli Firm]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=350775</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/350775/meta-awarded-us167-million-whatsapp-case-nso/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-07T06:33:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Back in 2019, Meta filed a lawsuit against NSO Group over the latter’s Pegasus spyware, which was used to target more than a thousand WhatsApp users in 20 countries, including journalists, human rights activists and diplomats. Now, a jury has ruled that the Israeli firm must pay Meta more than US$167 million (~RM707 million) in […]
The post Meta Awarded Over US$167 Million In WhatsApp Case Against Israeli Firm appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nurul Kamil</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Liquibase Makes Life Easy for DB Admins]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/sonichigo/how-liquibase-makes-life-easy-for-db-admins-23ej</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/sonichigo/how-liquibase-makes-life-easy-for-db-admins-23ej"/>
        <updated>2025-05-07T06:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Let’s be honest - managing database changes can sometimes feel like juggling fire. You’ve got multiple developers making updates, environments to manage, rollbacks to worry about, and let’s not forget those late-night “It worked on dev!” surprises.
But guess what? There's a tool that can help you stay ahead of the chaos. It’s called Liquibase, and it's like having a helpful assistant who always remembers what changes were made, who made them, and when. Today, we're going to break it down - what Liquibase is, how it works (especially with YAML), why it's useful, and how it's being used in real projects like mux-sql.
So grab your favourite cup of coffee ☕️, and let’s dive in!
Liquibase is an open-source database change management tool. Think of it as version control, but for your database.
J…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Animesh Pathak</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MSP40: The Iron Throne of Industrial Networks]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/ersajay/msp40-the-iron-throne-of-industrial-networks-4e13</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/ersajay/msp40-the-iron-throne-of-industrial-networks-4e13"/>
        <updated>2025-05-07T06:28:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the smoldering forges of Old Valyria, where data flows like wildfire and downtime is the true enemy, there sits a sovereign of steel and silicon—the MSP40. Forged in the fires of precision and armored against chaos, this managed Ethernet switch defends the Seven Realms of Industry 4.0 with the ruthlessness of Tywin Lannister and the foresight of Bran the Broken. Let us declare why this switch claims the Iron Throne of industrial IoT.

Chapter 1: The Forge of Dragonstone
MSP40 is no mere ironborn gadget. Tempered in the Foundries of Valyrian Steel, it wields powers unseen since the Age of Heroes:
Dragonflame Resilience: Operates from -40°C to +85°C—hotter than Drogon’s breath, colder than the Night King’s touch.
Why it shatters the old order:
Legacy Switches: As reliable as Joffrey’s promises—crumbling under pressure.
Chapter 2: The War of Five Ports
The Battle of Blackwater Bay (Smart Factories):
MSP40 commands robotic arms with the precision of Arya’s Needle, slashing downtime like Lannister soldiers. “Chaos isn’t a pit. It’s a 40% productivity gain,” it whispers.
The Siege of Winterfell (Power Grids):
Guards substations against EMP storms, steadfast as Brienne’s oath. “The North remembers… surge protection.”
The Red Wedding (Traffic Systems):
Halts data collisions at smart intersections, sparing cities from King’s Landing-level gridlock. “The network sends its regards.”

The Words of House MSP40
Ports: 12 channels of fury—8 RJ45 knights and 4 SFP dragons.
The Dragons of Innovation
The Dark Threats Beyond the Wall
Legacy Switches: Bloat like Robert Baratheon’s reign, guzzling budgets and sanity.
The Prophecy of the Prince That Was Plugged In
Epilogue: Winter is Here (And It’s Buffering)
the MSP40 is to court chaos—a realm of molten slag and screaming CFOs. The night is dark and full of packet loss.
References
The Song of Silicon & Packets (Maester Luwin’s Tech Scrolls)
Fire & Bandwidth: A History of Industrial Ethernet (Dragonstone Archives)
A Clash of Latency (King’s Landing IoT Reports)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ersajay</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Design a Height Adjustment Tool Using 3D CAD Software]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/julia970/how-to-design-a-height-adjustment-tool-using-3d-cad-software-n72</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/julia970/how-to-design-a-height-adjustment-tool-using-3d-cad-software-n72"/>
        <updated>2025-05-07T06:28:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How to Design a Height Adjustment Tool Using 3D CAD Software
This article outlines the process of designing a height adjustment tool from concept to digital prototype using SelfCAD. It explores how to model key components such as the adjustable shaft, locking mechanism, and base support, while emphasizing accuracy, dimensional planning, and assembly compatibility. Through this tutorial, users will gain insight into translating mechanical design requirements into practical 3D models ready for visualization or 3D printing.
https://www.selfcad.com/tutorials/3a395t6eve1f4m6p4z551ar1l5x156l641k2
Once you’ve launched the editor;












https://www.selfcad.com/tutorials) available on the SelfCAD website. The tutorials page provides a treasure trove of guides, tips, and tricks that cater to designers of all levels.
https://www.selfcad.com/academy/curriculum/), https://www.youtube.com/@3dmodeling101, and 3D Modeling 101 series (https://www.youtube.com/playlist?list=PL74nFNT8yS9DcE1UlUUdiR1wFGv9DDfTB). This comprehensive resource offers in-depth courses taught by industry experts, allowing you to master the intricacies of SelfCAD at your own pace]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Juliana Misiko</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Responsive Dashboard | Bento Style]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/preetha_vaishnavi_2b82358/responsive-dashboard-bento-style-bk4</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/preetha_vaishnavi_2b82358/responsive-dashboard-bento-style-bk4"/>
        <updated>2025-05-07T06:28:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Check out this Pen I made!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>preetha vaishnavi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Alleged Sony WH-1000XM6 Product Visual Leaks]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=350787</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/350787/alleged-sony-wh-1000xm6-product-visual-leaks/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-07T06:26:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An alleged key visual of what is believed to be the render of the yet-to-launch Sony WH-1000XM6 has been leaked, giving us a first look at the successor of 2022’s WH-1000XM5. The leaked key visual was discovered on Reddit, where it is believed to have been posted first. The image is believed to have been […]
The post Alleged Sony WH-1000XM6 Product Visual Leaks appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John Law</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Radar animation CSS only]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/preetha_vaishnavi_2b82358/radar-animation-css-only-40me</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/preetha_vaishnavi_2b82358/radar-animation-css-only-40me"/>
        <updated>2025-05-07T06:23:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Check out this Pen I made!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>preetha vaishnavi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Installing a Kubernetes Cluster on a Virtualized Platform (VM): how many VMs you need?]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/aairom/installing-a-kubernetes-cluster-on-a-virtualized-platform-vm-how-many-vms-you-need-2h8o</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/aairom/installing-a-kubernetes-cluster-on-a-virtualized-platform-vm-how-many-vms-you-need-2h8o"/>
        <updated>2025-05-07T06:22:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A YAML to VM conversion app I wrote for myself.

In my daily work, a recurring task involves estimating the hardware requirements for on-premise Kubernetes or, more frequently, OpenShift clusters tailored to specific application needs. These estimations typically target bare-metal server deployments, where direct access to physical resources is assumed. However, scenarios arise where the hosting platform is not bare-metal but a virtualized environment. In such cases, the estimation focus shifts from physical server capacity to determining the appropriate virtual machine capacity to adequately support the cluster and its applications.

To streamline this often repetitive process, I embarked on automating the initial steps through a simple scripting solution. The script aims to take Kubernet…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alain Airom</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Standard Protocols Matter for AI Agents]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/mcphubs/why-standard-protocols-matter-for-ai-agents-4k5l</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/mcphubs/why-standard-protocols-matter-for-ai-agents-4k5l"/>
        <updated>2025-05-07T06:22:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A post by MCPhubs]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>MCPhubs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Quantum-Resistant Encryption: Preparing for the Next Era of Cybersecurity]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/rubyjane/quantum-resistant-encryption-preparing-for-the-next-era-of-cybersecurity-5bhl</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/rubyjane/quantum-resistant-encryption-preparing-for-the-next-era-of-cybersecurity-5bhl"/>
        <updated>2025-05-07T06:22:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction
Imagine a world where even the most secure data can be cracked open like a candy wrapper. This might sound like a scene from a sci-fi movie, but it’s a real concern as quantum computing continues to advance. Quantum computers are powerful machines that can solve complex problems much faster than today’s computers. But while they promise many exciting possibilities, they also pose a serious threat to data security. The encryption methods that protect our personal and financial information today may not be strong enough to withstand a quantum attack.
In this blog, we will explore what quantum-resistant encryption is, why it’s necessary, and how it can protect our data in the future. We will also discuss practical steps we can take to stay secure in a quantum-powered world.
What …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ruby Jane</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DJI Teases Drone With Spinning Triple Camera; Launching 13 May]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=350778</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/350778/dji-teases-drone-with-spinning-triple-camera-launching-13-may/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-07T06:15:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Drone maker DJI has posted a teaser clip on its social medial channels, including X and YouTube, for an upcoming launch. Being a teaser, details from just the seven-second clip is scarce, but the most obvious takeaway is the camera system being shown in the second half. Said system consists of three cameras, with the […]
The post DJI Teases Drone With Spinning Triple Camera; Launching 13 May appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ian Chee</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Owners Of BYD Atto 3, Audi e-tron GT Share Incidents Concerning Safety Of EV Vehicles]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=350703</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/350703/byd-atto-3-audi-e-tron-gt-ev-safety/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-07T05:54:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Electric vehicles (EVs) have become a growing trend in the automotive industry, with many Malaysians increasingly embracing the shift to cleaner mobility. However, recent posts on social media involving brands like BYD and Audi have sparked public concern about EV reliability and safety. On 1 May 2025, a BYD Atto 3 owner reported a troubling […]
The post Owners Of BYD Atto 3, Audi e-tron GT Share Incidents Concerning Safety Of EV Vehicles appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Keran</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Movement Labs Terminates Rushi Manche After MOVE Token Deals]]></title>
        <id>513c4134-11de-4fad-979a-eb53c21a86d1</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/07/movement-labs-terminates-rushi-manche-after-move-token-deals"/>
        <updated>2025-05-07T05:50:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It has yet to name a replacement or outline next steps for governance restructuring.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shaurya Malwa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[China To Soon Extend Visa-Free Stay For Malaysians To 90 Days]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=350781</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/350781/china-visa-free-stay-malaysians-90-days/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-07T05:27:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As previously teased following Chinese President Xi Jinping’s visit to Malaysia last month, China has confirmed in a statement that it will soon allow Malaysian travellers to stay in its country visa-free for up to 90 days, reciprocating Malaysia’s policy for Chinese tourists. This comes as the two countries recently signed MOUs that included a […]
The post China To Soon Extend Visa-Free Stay For Malaysians To 90 Days appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ikmal Rozlan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Voltage Finance exploiter moves $182K in ETH to Tornado Cash]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/hacker-from-2022-voltage-finance-exploit-moves-eth-to-tornado-cash</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/hacker-from-2022-voltage-finance-exploit-moves-eth-to-tornado-cash?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-07T05:09:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A hacker involved in the $4.67 million exploit of the decentralized finance lending protocol Voltage Finance in 2022 has moved some of the stolen Ether to Tornado Cash after a short hibernation. 
Blockchain security firm CertiK said in a May 6 post to X that the 100 Ether (ETH), worth $182,783 at current prices, was moved from a different address initially used in the exploit but can be traced back to the hacker.  
In March 2022, the exploiter took advantage of a “built-in callback function” in the ERC677 token standard and allowed them to drain the platform’s lending pool through a reentrancy attack, according to CertiK.
Source: CertiK
After the exploit, Voltage Finance reported that the hacker stole various stablecoins and other crypto, including USDC (USDC), Binance USD (BUSD), wrapped …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Stephen Katte</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bigger Bitcoin wallets are stacking while others sell: Santiment]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/big-bitcoin-wallets-accumulate-smaller-retail-investors-fade-santiment</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/big-bitcoin-wallets-accumulate-smaller-retail-investors-fade-santiment?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-07T05:09:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Key takeaways:

Large Bitcoin holders have accumulated 81,338 BTC over the past six weeks, showing confidence in a future price uptrend.

Wallets with less than 0.1 BTC sold around 290 BTC, indicating smaller retail investors are either panic selling or selling out of boredom. 

Spot Bitcoin ETFs have seen $4.41 billion in inflows since March 26.

While larger Bitcoin holders remain confident and continue accumulating the asset, data from a crypto analytics platform shows that smaller retail investors have been shedding BTC amid the asset’s prolonged consolidation below the $100,000 price level.
The contrasting behavior between Bitcoin (BTC) whales and retail investors often signals that Bitcoin may be heading toward another upward trend, Santiment said in a May 6 X post. 
Bitcoin smaller …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Ciaran Lyons</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Samsung Galaxy Z Flip7 FE Specs Leak, Rather Similar To Z Flip6]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=350768</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/350768/samsung-galaxy-z-flip7-fe-specs-leak-rather-similar-to-z-flip6/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-07T04:53:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Samsung may launch its Galaxy Z Fold7 and Z Flip7 sometime in July this year, and as recently reported, its Z Flip7 FE as well. TechManiacs have now listed the apparent specs of the device, which seem to be quite alike to that of the Z Flip6. It is speculated that the Flip7 FE may […]
The post Samsung Galaxy Z Flip7 FE Specs Leak, Rather Similar To Z Flip6 appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Newsdesk</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Forecasting Fed-Induced Price Swings in Bitcoin, Ether, Solana and XRP]]></title>
        <id>d3424248-1bab-45f4-b706-6eac98f0fcf8</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/07/forecasting-fomc-induced-price-swings-in-bitcoin-ether-solana-and-xrp"/>
        <updated>2025-05-07T04:51:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Traders looking for cues on potential Fed-led moves in major tokens might want to see what implied volatility indices are saying.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Omkar Godbole</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NVIDIA Confirms 19 May As Launch Day For GeForce RTX 5060 GPUs]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=350764</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/350764/nvidia-confirms-19-may-as-launch-day-for-geforce-rtx-5060-gpus/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-07T04:33:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[NVIDIA has officially confirmed that the GeForce RTX 5060 will be available to gamers from 19 May onwards. The availability goes for both desktop and laptop GPU variants. The card was announced at the same as the more powerful Ti variant last month, and starts from US$299 (~RM1,266). Unlike its Ti counterpart, the card only […]
The post NVIDIA Confirms 19 May As Launch Day For GeForce RTX 5060 GPUs appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John Law</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BlackRock Bitcoin ETF clocks 16 days of inflow as BTC reclaims $97K]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/blackrock-bitcoin-etf-sees-16-day-inflow-streak-btc-reclaims-97k</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/blackrock-bitcoin-etf-sees-16-day-inflow-streak-btc-reclaims-97k?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-07T04:26:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Investors have been piling into BlackRock’s spot Bitcoin exchange-traded fund for over three weeks straight, culminating in the asset’s run up to $97,000 on May 7.
The BlackRock iShares Bitcoin Trust has seen 16 days of inflows for the spot BTC ETF, with a further 280 Bitcoin (BTC) or around $36 million piling into the fund on May 6, according to HODL15Capital.  
The inflow streak was noted by ETF Store President Nate Geraci, who also observed on X that the fund was approaching $5 billion in new capital. 
“I remember when naysayers didn’t think spot Bitcoin ETFs would take in $5 billion in total last year,” he added. 
“IBIT alone has done this in a few weeks, more than a year after launch.”
The BlackRock fund (IBIT) has seen around $4.7 billion in inflows since its last outflow day on Apri…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Martin Young</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft Announces Windows 11 Start Menu Update]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=350741</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/350741/microsoft-announces-windows-11-start-menu-update/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-07T04:25:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft has announced that it is updating the Windows 11 Start menu, in addition to introducing new AI features over the coming month. In a recent blog post, the company clarified that these upgrades will first be rolled out to Windows Insiders, with many of the AI upgrades being exclusive to Copilot+ PCs. The Start […]
The post Microsoft Announces Windows 11 Start Menu Update appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nurul Kamil</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[South Korea presidential front-runner pledges to approve Bitcoin ETFs]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/south-korean-presidential-front-runner-pledges-approve-crypto-etfs</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/south-korean-presidential-front-runner-pledges-approve-crypto-etfs?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-07T04:15:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[South Korea’s Democratic Party leader Lee Jae-myung has reportedly become the latest presidential candidate to promise the approval of spot crypto exchange-traded funds (ETFs) and other crypto-friendly measures, should he be elected.
Lee announced his crypto promises on May 6 as part of a broader initiative to provide more investment opportunities for Korea’s youth, one of the main target demographics for the fast-approaching June 3 election.
“I will create a safe investment environment so that young people can [build] assets and plan for the future,” The Korea Economic Daily (KED) quoted Lee as saying in Korean.
He also promised the legalization of spot crypto ETFs, lower transaction fees, and more consumer protection measures.
Lee’s Democratic Party of Korea is the favorite to win the pr…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Brayden Lindrea</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[vivo X200 FE Reported Specs Leak; May Get Indian Launch In July]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=350762</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/350762/vivo-x200-fe-reported-specs-leak-may-get-indian-launch-in-july/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-07T04:03:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[vivo recently launched its X200 Ultra and X200s smartphones in China. A new report now indicates that the brand is planning to unveil the X200 FE in India, possibly in July. The purported specs of the phone have also been leaked, detailing its supposed chipset, battery, and camera system, among others. The vivo X200 FE […]
The post vivo X200 FE Reported Specs Leak; May Get Indian Launch In July appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Newsdesk</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[World Liberty Financial floats USD1 airdrop to WLFI holders]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/world-liberty-financial-plans-airdrop-usd1-wlfi-holders</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/world-liberty-financial-plans-airdrop-usd1-wlfi-holders?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-07T03:20:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Trump family-backed crypto platform World Liberty Financial (WLFI) is proposing to airdrop a small amount of its new US dollar-pegged stablecoin to reward early WLFI holders in a test of its airdrop mechanism. 
With over 99% of votes in favor of the proposal already, the airdrop will distribute a small amount of USD1 to eligible holders of the WLFI token, according to the May 6 proposal in the WLFI governance forum.
“Testing the airdrop mechanism in a live setting is a necessary step to ensure smart contract functionality and readiness. This distribution also serves as a meaningful way to thank our earliest supporters and introduce them to USD1,” the proposal states. 
“This will allow World Liberty Financial to validate the technical functionality of its airdrop system in a live environmen…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Stephen Katte</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase x402 payments protocol to make AI agents more autonomous]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/coinbase-x402-payments-protocol-make-ai-agents-more-autonomous</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/coinbase-x402-payments-protocol-make-ai-agents-more-autonomous?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-07T03:03:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase has introduced a new payments protocol for online payments that enables stablecoin transfers over standard internet protocols and AI agents to transact autonomously.  
On May 6, Coinbase announced that it is launching a protocol called x402 for instant stablecoin payments directly over the internet communication protocol HTTP (Hypertext Transfer Protocol).
It allows Application Programming Interface (APIs), apps, and AI agents to transact seamlessly, “unlocking a faster, automated internet economy,” the firm stated. 
Coinbase said that x402 “is fixing the internet’s first mistake.” The protocol resurrects the experimental HTTP 402 “Payment Required” status code to create a seamless payment system native to the internet.
The firm noted that traditional payment rails, such as credit…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Martin Young</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin must hold above $95K or face short-term rejection: Bitfinex]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-price-95k-hold-short-term-rejection-bitfinex-crypto-analysts</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-price-95k-hold-short-term-rejection-bitfinex-crypto-analysts?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-07T02:45:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Key takeaways:

Bitcoin must maintain above $95,000 to have a chance at retesting its $109,000 all-time high; failure to hold could lead to a deeper correction, crypto analysts warn.

Several crypto analysts told Cointelegraph in March that Bitcoin may have a chance of reaching new all-time highs in June.

The upcoming Federal Reserve decision on May 7 could influence Bitcoin’s price movement over the coming days.

Bitcoin needs to continue to hold above the $95,000 level for a chance to climb back and retest its all-time high, or face an even deeper correction, crypto analysts say.
It comes after several analysts told Cointelegraph earlier this year that June could be the month Bitcoin (BTC) reaches new all-time highs.
“The $95,000 level — currently under consolidation — is a critical piv…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Ciaran Lyons</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Zerebro dev’s death in question as ‘proof’ surfaces on X]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/zerebro-devs-death-speculated-fake-as-proof-surfaces-x</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/zerebro-devs-death-speculated-fake-as-proof-surfaces-x?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-07T02:24:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Members of the crypto community are circulating apparent “proof” that Zerebro developer Jeffy Yu faked his suicide as he promoted his new memecoin during a Pump.fun livestream on May 4.
The belief appears to come from an unverified private letter supposedly sent by Yu to a Zerebro investor, trading activity linked to crypto wallets owned by Yu, and the removal of his obituary from Legacy.com.
Others speculate that Yu used a tool to pass off a pre-edited video as if it were filmed in real-time during the Pump.fun livestream.
Source: Hash
The unverified letter from Yu to an early investor states that he deliberately created a livestream pretending to shoot himself as it was the only “viable exit” from persistent harassment, blackmail, threats and hate crimes.
“Being fully doxxed has placed m…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Brayden Lindrea</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Democrats aim at Trump’s crypto profits with a 3-prong pincer move]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/us-senator-proposes-bill-would-prevent-trump-from-profiting-from-memecoins</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/us-senator-proposes-bill-would-prevent-trump-from-profiting-from-memecoins?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-07T02:24:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[US Democrat lawmakers have launched a multi-angle attack on President Donald Trump’s crypto ventures with two bills and a subcommittee inquiry aimed at cutting his ability to profit from the initiatives.   
The Modern Emoluments and Malfeasance Enforcement Act, or the MEME Act, aims to prevent federal officials from using their position to profit from memecoins, Democrat Senator Chris Murphy said in a May 6 statement. 
If passed, the MEME Act prohibits the president, vice president, members of Congress, senior executive branch officials, their spouses and children from issuing, sponsoring, or promoting a security, future, commodity, or digital asset, according to the bill’s description. 

Today I’m introducing a bill - the MEME Act - to ban a President or Member of Congress from issuing a …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Stephen Katte</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[EPA Plans to Shut Down the Energy Star Program]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nytimes.com/2025/05/06/climate/epa-energy-star-eliminated.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.nytimes.com/2025/05/06/climate/epa-energy-star-eliminated.html"/>
        <updated>2025-05-07T01:11:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Races Above $97K on U.S./China Trade Deal Progress]]></title>
        <id>b79cca00-5ab4-4bce-8e18-7f7b07263ab5</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/06/bitcoin-races-above-97k-on-uschina-trade-deal-progress"/>
        <updated>2025-05-07T00:57:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Treasury Secretary Scott Bessent is headed to Switzerland for talks with Chinese representatives.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephen Alpher</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Jury orders NSO to pay $167M for hacking WhatsApp users]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/security/2025/05/jury-orders-nso-to-pay-167-million-for-hacking-whatsapp-users/</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/security/2025/05/jury-orders-nso-to-pay-167-million-for-hacking-whatsapp-users/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-07T00:54:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bloat is still software's biggest vulnerability (2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://spectrum.ieee.org/lean-software-development</id>
        <link href="https://spectrum.ieee.org/lean-software-development"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T23:33:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Alignment is not free: How model upgrades can silence your confidence signals]]></title>
        <id>https://www.variance.co/post/alignment-is-not-free-how-a-model-silenced-our-confidence-signals</id>
        <link href="https://www.variance.co/post/alignment-is-not-free-how-a-model-silenced-our-confidence-signals"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T23:22:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[VVVVVV Source Code]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/TerryCavanagh/VVVVVV</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/TerryCavanagh/VVVVVV"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T23:22:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Show HN: Whippy Term - GUI terminal for embedded development (Linux and Windows)]]></title>
        <id>https://whippyterm.com/</id>
        <link href="https://whippyterm.com/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T23:02:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sutton and Barto book implementation]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/ivanbelenky/RL</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/ivanbelenky/RL"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T22:43:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Senate Democrat Says He's Looking Into Trump's Crypto Businesses]]></title>
        <id>bc00aadf-da85-4d94-a4e7-f04b0fa248e2</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2025/05/06/senate-democrat-says-hes-looking-into-trumps-crypto-businesses"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T22:30:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sen. Richard Blumenthal wrote letters to Trump-affiliated business executives, asking about their ownership and investment structure.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nikhilesh De</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitwise throws spot NEAR ETF in race for SEC approval]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitwise-files-s-1-near-etf-sec-approval-s1-filing</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitwise-files-s-1-near-etf-sec-approval-s1-filing?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T22:23:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Digital asset manager Bitwise has filed to list a spot Near exchange-traded fund with the US Securities and Exchange Commission, adding to a growing list of altcoins currently vying to win regulatory approval.
The Bitwise Near (NEAR) ETF will track the price movements of the NEAR token, minus expenses, through a traditional brokerage, Bitwise’s May 6 registration statement shows.
Bitwise named Coinbase Custody as the proposed custodian of the Bitwise NEAR ETF. The management fee, ticker and stock exchange it seeks to list on weren’t named yet. 
Source: Cointelegraph
Bitwise must also file a 19b-4 filing with the SEC to kickstart the regulator's approval process for the fund. The crypto native asset manager indicated it would make such a filing when it registered a trust linked to the NEAR …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Brayden Lindrea</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS report: Generative AI overtakes security in global tech budgets for 2025]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3006670</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/aws-report-generative-ai-overtakes-security-in-global-tech-budgets-for-2025/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T21:33:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New AWS report reveals 45% of global IT leaders now prioritize generative AI over cybersecurity in 2025 tech budgets as companies race to hire AI talent and implement AI strategies despite persistent skills shortages.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Nuñez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Dominance Soars Ahead of FOMC as Volatility Burst Looms, Says Analyst]]></title>
        <id>16a745db-3737-443d-b1b5-6860e516673b</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/06/bitcoin-dominance-soars-ahead-of-fomc-as-volatility-burst-looms-says-analyst"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T21:04:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto markets are in a holding pattern as capital rotation from altcoins pushed bitcoin's market share to fresh 4-year high.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Krisztian Sandor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Continue (YC S23) is hiring software engineers in San Francisco]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ycombinator.com/companies/continue/jobs/smcxRnM-software-engineer</id>
        <link href="https://www.ycombinator.com/companies/continue/jobs/smcxRnM-software-engineer"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T21:01:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[US regulator moves to drop appeal against Kalshi]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/cftc-dismiss-appeal-kalshi</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/cftc-dismiss-appeal-kalshi?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T20:55:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The US Commodity Futures Trading Commission (CFTC) is seeking permission from the court to drop an appeal against prediction market Kalshi. The move could allow the platform to offer political event contracts to users without contest.
In a May 5 filing in the US Court of Appeals for the District of Columbia Circuit, lawyers for the CFTC filed an unopposed motion for voluntary dismissal, suggesting an agreement with Kalshi. The motion, subject to approval by the court, could end the CFTC’s appeal against a federal court ruling that the financial regulator could not bar Kalshi from listing political event contracts, i.e., bets on elections.
Motion to dismiss appeal filed by the CFTC on May 5. Source: Courtlistener
Kalshi stipulated in a joint filing that the company would “bear its own costs…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Turner Wright</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Here’s what happened in crypto today]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/what-happened-in-crypto-today</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/what-happened-in-crypto-today?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T20:48:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today in Crypto, US Democrats have launched a new assault targeting President Donald Trump’s involvement in various memecoin and crypto ventures, New Hampshire has greenlit state crypto investments and Binance founder Changpeng “CZ” Zhao forecasts Bitcoin could surge to $500,000–$1 million this cycle.
Democrats aim at Trump’s crypto profits with a 3-prong pincer move
US Democrat lawmakers have launched a multi-angle attack on President Donald Trump’s crypto ventures with two bills and a subcommittee inquiry aimed at cutting his ability to profit from the initiatives.   
The Modern Emoluments and Malfeasance Enforcement Act, or the MEME Act, aims to prevent federal officials from using their position to profit from memecoins, Democrat Senator Chris Murphy said in a May 6 statement. 

With h…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Cointelegraph</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[India launches attack on 9 sites in Pakistan and Pakistani Jammu and Kashmir]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reuters.com/world/india/india-launches-attack-9-sites-pakistan-pakistan-occupied-jammu-kashmir-2025-05-06/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reuters.com/world/india/india-launches-attack-9-sites-pakistan-pakistan-occupied-jammu-kashmir-2025-05-06/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T20:41:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Claude's system prompt is over 24k tokens with tools]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/asgeirtj/system_prompts_leaks/blob/main/claude.txt</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/asgeirtj/system_prompts_leaks/blob/main/claude.txt"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T20:39:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ACE-Step: A step towards music generation foundation model]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/ace-step/ACE-Step</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/ace-step/ACE-Step"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T20:38:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Secure Mobile APIs in Flutter]]></title>
        <id>681a707658599a397b11b418</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-secure-mobile-apis-in-flutter/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T20:26:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As mobile applications continue to evolve in functionality and scope, securing the APIs that power these apps has become more critical than ever. In the context of Flutter, a framework that enables cross-platform development, understanding how to sec...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Atuoha Anthony</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tether adds Chainalysis tokenization platform for compliance, monitoring]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/tether-adds-chainalysis-tokenization-platform-compliance-monitoring</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/tether-adds-chainalysis-tokenization-platform-compliance-monitoring?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T20:24:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tether, the issuer of the world’s largest stablecoin by market cap USDt (USDT), has announced a partnership with Chainalysis that will integrate the company’s compliance and monitoring tools onto Tether’s tokenization platform. The move comes amid expanding oversight across the crypto industry.
Launched in November 2024, the Hadron by Tether platform is designed for institutions, corporations and governments, entities that may be interested in tokenizing real-world assets ranging from financial instruments and real estate to debt and commodities.

The months following the launch have seen increased adoption of real-world asset (RWA) tokenization. According to RWA.xyz, the total RWA market amounts to $22.1 billion, up 10.5% in the past 30 days. There are a total of 100,115 holders of RWA to…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Christopher Tepedino</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FT report suggests advance knowledge of Melania Trump memecoin launch]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/report-advance-knowledge-melania-trump-memecoin</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/report-advance-knowledge-melania-trump-memecoin?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T19:53:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A group of crypto traders reportedly purchased millions of dollars worth of Melania Trump’s memecoins minutes before she announced the launch on social media.
According to a May 6 Financial Times report, the crypto traders earned roughly $100 million from buying $2.6 million worth of MELANIA tokens before the public launch on Jan. 19. Shortly after Trump announced the memecoin launch on social media, the price surged from roughly $2.00 to $12.95 — a 550% increase. The traders reportedly sold their holdings within 12 hours.
“In total, the 24 accounts bought up 16.7mn of the 200mn total $MELANIA tokens scheduled for sale during the launch period,” the Financial Times reported. “[...] the run of sales that started pre-launch continued. About $900,000 worth of tokens bought by an additional 22…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Turner Wright</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin could rally regardless of what the Federal Reserve FOMC decides this week: Here’s why]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-could-rally-regardless-of-what-the-federal-reserve-fomc-decides-this-week-here-s-why</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-could-rally-regardless-of-what-the-federal-reserve-fomc-decides-this-week-here-s-why?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T19:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Key Takeaways:

The Fed may pause rates but inject liquidity. Crypto could rally as a recession hedge.

The weak US dollar and gold rally signal a shift to scarce assets.

The US Federal Reserve Open Market Committee (FOMC) interest rate decision on May 7 will be a defining moment for risk-on assets, including cryptocurrencies. While the consensus points to no change in interest rates, Bitcoin (BTC) and altcoins could see gains if the US Treasury is compelled to inject liquidity to stave off an economic recession.
A more accommodative monetary policy could stimulate activity, but the Federal Reserve (Fed) is also contending with a weakening US dollar. Some analysts argue that a US interest rate cut may fail to stimulate growth as recession risks persist, potentially creating an ideal envir…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Marcel Pechman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[21Shares launches ETP for Crypto.com&#039;s Cronos token]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/21-shares-launches-cronos-etp</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/21-shares-launches-cronos-etp?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T19:24:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[21Shares has launched an exchange traded product (ETP) in Europe, providing investors with exposure to Crypto.com’s Cronos token, the asset manager said. 
The ETP is listed on Euronext’s Paris and Amsterdam exchanges, 21Shares said in a May 6 announcement. 
Cronos (CRO) is a layer-1 blockchain network affiliated with Crypto.com, a centralized exchange. 
The chain is designed to integrate with the Ethereum and Cosmos ecosystems and support “decentralised finance (DeFi), NFTs, and Web3 applications,” 21Shares said. 
The ETP aims to provide investors with a “straightforward way to integrate CRO into their portfolios through traditional banks and brokers, eliminating the need to directly handle digital wallets or exchanges,” 21Shares said. 
The CRO token’s historical performance. Source: CoinM…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Alex O’Donnell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brush (Bo(u)rn(e) RUsty SHell) a POSIX and Bash-Compatible Shell in Rust]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/reubeno/brush</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/reubeno/brush"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T18:47:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin bulls rush into long positions ahead of May 7 Fed FOMC interest rate decision]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-bulls-rush-into-long-positions-ahead-of-may-7-fed-fomc-interest-rate-decision</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-bulls-rush-into-long-positions-ahead-of-may-7-fed-fomc-interest-rate-decision?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T18:44:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Key Takeaways:

Data shows Bitcoin bulls opening margin long positions from $94,400.

A $189 million increase in Bitcoin futures open interest and a 15% increase in trading volume show sustained buying interest.

BTC momentum tends to slow before FOMC meetings and then turns volatile afterward. The same could happen following this week’s Federal Reserve statements.

Bitcoin (BTC) bulls are holding strong around the $94,500 level as the market awaits the Federal Open Market Committee (FOMC) meeting on May 7. Bitcoin analyst Axel Adler Jr. noted BTC’s price strength and pointed out a bullish cluster of long positions forming around $94,400 in the futures market. A similar cluster was observed at the end of April, which pushed BTC prices to $97,500.
Bitcoin futures position dominance data. So…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Biraajmaan Tamuly</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meet the new king of AI coding: Google’s Gemini 2.5 Pro I/O Edition dethrones Claude 3.7 Sonnet]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3006623</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/meet-the-new-king-of-ai-coding-googles-gemini-2-5-pro-i-o-edition-dethrones-claude-3-7-sonnet/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T18:39:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One of the standout features of the update is its ability to build full, interactive web apps or simulations from a single prompt.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carl Franzen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Create Documentation with docs.page – A Beginner's Tutorial]]></title>
        <id>681a558b9791d0e469b84519</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-create-documentation-with-docspage/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T18:31:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One of the most tedious tasks for every startup, company, and open-source project is often building and managing documentation – especially for medium to large-scale documentation websites. docs.page is an open-source documentation tool that helps yo...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rajdeep Singh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CFTC Drops Appeal in Kalshi Election Betting Case]]></title>
        <id>85951e45-a13e-4284-bbf8-b177d7c6170e</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2025/05/06/cftc-drops-appeal-in-kalshi-election-betting-case"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T18:14:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The CFTC appealed a federal judge’s ruling last year clearing Kalshi’s listing of a political prediction market, arguing that it presented a “profound” harm to the public.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cheyenne Ligon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lightricks just made AI video generation 30x faster — and you won’t need a $10,000 GPU]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3006613</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/lightricks-just-made-ai-video-generation-30x-faster-and-you-wont-need-a-10000-gpu/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T17:56:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Lightricks unveils groundbreaking LTXV-13B AI video model that runs 30X faster than competitors on consumer hardware through innovative "multiscale rendering" technology.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Nuñez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Matt Godbolt sold me on Rust by showing me C++]]></title>
        <id>https://www.collabora.com/news-and-blog/blog/2025/05/06/matt-godbolt-sold-me-on-rust-by-showing-me-c-plus-plus/</id>
        <link href="https://www.collabora.com/news-and-blog/blog/2025/05/06/matt-godbolt-sold-me-on-rust-by-showing-me-c-plus-plus/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T17:51:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Is Planet Nine Alone in the Outer System?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.centauri-dreams.org/2025/05/06/is-planet-nine-alone-in-the-outer-system/</id>
        <link href="https://www.centauri-dreams.org/2025/05/06/is-planet-nine-alone-in-the-outer-system/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T17:29:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Hampshire Becomes First State to Approve Crypto Reserve Law]]></title>
        <id>859dba7b-b33d-4dab-8b80-15d692542d64</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2025/05/06/new-hampshire-becomes-first-state-to-approve-crypto-reserve-law"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T17:25:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Governor Kelly Ayotte signed a bill into law that allows the investment of a portion of the state's public funds in precious metals and crypto assets.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jesse Hamilton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Solana bull flag, rising stablecoin market cap hint at SOL price rally to $220]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/solana-bull-flag-rising-stablecoin-market-cap-hint-at-sol-price-rally-to-220</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/solana-bull-flag-rising-stablecoin-market-cap-hint-at-sol-price-rally-to-220?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T17:24:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Key takeaways:

Solana’s stablecoin supply rose by 156% in 2025, to hit a new record at $12 billion.

Solana’s TVL grew by 25% to $7.65 billion, with 27.7% decentralized exchange volume share, leading Ethereum and BNB Chain.

SOL price formed a bull flag, with a price target at $220.

Solana’s native token, SOL (SOL) failed to maintain its bullish momentum after reaching $156 on April 25, but an assortment of data points suggests that the altcoin’s upside is not over.
SOL stablecoin market cap hits $13 billion
Solana’s stablecoin supply has skyrocketed by 156% in 2025, surging past $13 billion to hit a new all-time high.

Stablecoins on Solana recently surged past $13B in issuance, setting a new ATH@calilyliu on why Solana is purpose-built for moving digital dollars at internet speed pic.t…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Nancy Lubale</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Hampshire governor signs crypto reserve bill into law]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/new-hampshire-bitcoin-reserve-law</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/new-hampshire-bitcoin-reserve-law?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T17:08:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New Hampshire became the first US state to allow its government to invest in crypto currencies including Bitcoin (BTC), after Governor Kelly Ayotte signed a bill passed by the legislature into law. 
In a May 6 notice, Ayotte announced on social media that New Hampshire would be permitted to “invest in cryptocurrency and precious metals” through a bill passed in the state Senate and House of Representatives. House Bill 302, introduced in New Hampshire in January, will allow the state’s treasury to use funds to invest in cryptocurrencies with a market capitalization of more than $500 billion, eliminating many tokens and memecoins.
“The Live Free or Die state is leading the way in forging the future of commerce and digital assets,” said New Hampshire Republicans in a May 6 X post.
Signing New…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Turner Wright</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ServiceNow lets users see more of their AI]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3006589</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/servicenow-lets-users-see-more-of-their-ai/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ServiceNow also announced a way for agents to communicate with others along with its new observability platform.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Emilia David</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Stabledollars: The Third Act of Dollar Reinvention]]></title>
        <id>48fcb34c-2602-47d8-80b2-989a6941b07a</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/opinion/2025/05/06/stabledollars-the-third-act-of-dollar-reinvention"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T16:39:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Blockchain-based dollar infrastructure holds enormous opportunities for the U.S. But only if it treats the technology wisely, says John deVadoss.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John deVadoss</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Planned Crypto Hearing in U.S. House Derailed by Democrat Revolt]]></title>
        <id>57b4aa63-7cac-486b-b717-dd966a2ca409</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2025/05/06/planned-crypto-hearing-in-u-s-house-derailed-by-democrat-revolt"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T16:26:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Democrats abandoned a joint hearing of two committees on crypto policy, inviting people to instead attend their own discussion of Trump's "crypto corruption."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jesse Hamilton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Standard Chartered predicts BNB will more than double in 2025]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/standard-chartered-forecasts-bnb-price-more-than-doubling-this-year</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/standard-chartered-forecasts-bnb-price-more-than-doubling-this-year?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T16:23:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Asset manager Standard Chartered predicts that Binance’s ecosystem token, BNB, could more than double in price this year, according to an analyst report reviewed by Cointelegraph. 
The asset manager sees BNB’s price rising to approximately $1,275 per token by the end of 2025 and as high as $2,775 by the end of 2028, according to the research report. 
As of May 6, BNB trades at nearly $600 per coin, for a fully diluted value (FDV) of approximately $84 billion, according to data from CoinMarketCap.
Price forecasts for BNB. Source: Standard Chartered
“BNB has traded almost exactly in line with an unweighted basket of Bitcoin and Ethereum since May 2021 in terms of both returns and volatility,” Geoff Kendrick, an analyst at Standard Chartered, wrote in the research note. 
“We expect this relat…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Alex O’Donnell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MARA Holdings Cut to Sell at Compass Point Ahead of Earnings, Citing Cash Burn]]></title>
        <id>ed7e6fd2-d48d-411a-8148-b9c68e8cee49</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/06/marathon-digital-downgraded-to-sell-at-compass-point-citing-unsustainable-cash-burn"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T16:20:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Compass Point slashed Marathon’s price target to $9.50, warning of dilution and premium bitcoin exposure.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Helene Braun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Launch HN: Exa (YC S21) – The web as a database]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=43906841</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=43906841"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T16:18:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build Your Own Local AI: Create Free RAG and AI Agents with Qwen 3 and Ollama]]></title>
        <id>681a35d4d5da806f5e9467b1</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-a-local-ai/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T16:16:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The landscape of Artificial Intelligence is rapidly evolving, and one of the most exciting trends is the ability to run powerful Large Language Models (LLMs) directly on your local machine. This shift away from reliance on cloud-based APIs offers sig...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chaitanya Rahalkar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Show HN: Sheet Music in Smart Glasses]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=43906442</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=43906442"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T15:47:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin price rallied 1,550% the last time the ‘BTC risk-off’ metric fell this low]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-price-rallied-1-550-the-last-time-the-btc-risk-off-metric-fell-this-low</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-price-rallied-1-550-the-last-time-the-btc-risk-off-metric-fell-this-low?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T15:44:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Key Takeaways:

The Bitcoin Risk-Off signal dropped to 23.7, its lowest since March 2019, indicating low correction risk and a high likelihood of a bullish trend developing.

Despite the recent decline in network activity, bullish macro indicators like the Macro Chain Index (MCI) suggest Bitcoin could soon rally above $100,000.

On May 5, the Bitcoin Risk-Off signal, an indicator that uses onchain and exchange data to assess correction risk, dropped to its lowest level (23.7) for the first time since March 27, 2019, when Bitcoin (BTC) traded at $4,000. 
The signal is currently in the blue zone, which historically suggests low correction risk and a high probability of a bullish trend. When the oscillator rises above 60 or turns red, it implies a high risk of bearish movement. 
Bitcoin Risk-…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Biraajmaan Tamuly</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Is it a bull or bear market? How to tell the difference]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/is-it-a-bull-or-bear-market-how-to-tell-the-difference</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/is-it-a-bull-or-bear-market-how-to-tell-the-difference?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T15:41:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[TL;DR:
Not sure if you’re in a bull or bear market? This guide breaks down how to spot the difference using price action, volume, sentiment and onchain data. Learn how to recognize market cycles, what signals to watch for and how to adjust your strategy for each phase so you can trade smarter.
Crypto markets can feel like emotional rollercoasters, prices soaring one month, then crashing the next. You're not alone if you’ve ever wondered whether you are in a bull or a bear market.
In the simplest terms:

A bull market is when prices keep going up, people are excited and there’s a general sense that the future is bright. Think back to late 2020 and early 2021; Bitcoin (BTC) climbed from around $10,000 to nearly $70,000. New projects were launching daily and it felt like everyone from your co…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Bradley Peak</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Create Serverless AI Agents with Langbase Docs MCP Server in Minutes]]></title>
        <id>681a2ce0aebfc718f4e6da03</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-create-serverless-ai-agents-with-langbase-docs-mcp-server-in-minutes/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T15:38:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Building serverless AI agents has recently become a lot simpler. With the Langbase Docs MCP server, you can instantly connect AI models to Langbase documentation – making it easy to build composable, agentic AI systems with memory without complex inf...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maham Codes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Show HN: Plexe – ML Models from a Prompt]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/plexe-ai/plexe</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/plexe-ai/plexe"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T15:38:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[North Korean spy slips up, reveals ties in fake job interview]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/north-korean-spy-reveals-ties-in-fake-job-interview</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/north-korean-spy-reveals-ties-in-fake-job-interview?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T15:19:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For months, Cointelegraph took part in an investigation centered around a suspected North Korean operative that uncovered a cluster of threat actors attempting to score freelancing gigs in the cryptocurrency industry.
The investigation was led by Heiner Garcia, a cyber threat intelligence expert at Telefónica and a blockchain security researcher. Garcia uncovered how North Korean operatives secured freelance work online even without using a VPN.
Garcia’s analysis linked the applicant to a network of GitHub accounts and fake Japanese identities believed to be associated with North Korean operations. In February, Garcia invited Cointelegraph to take part in a dummy job interview he had set up with a suspected Democratic People’s Republic of Korea (DPRK) operative who called himself “Motoki.”…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Yohan Yun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gemini 2.5 Pro Preview]]></title>
        <id>https://developers.googleblog.com/en/gemini-2-5-pro-io-improved-coding-performance/</id>
        <link href="https://developers.googleblog.com/en/gemini-2-5-pro-io-improved-coding-performance/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T15:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Show HN: Clippy – 90s UI for local LLMs]]></title>
        <id>https://felixrieseberg.github.io/clippy/</id>
        <link href="https://felixrieseberg.github.io/clippy/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T15:02:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Frictionless flows are Ethereum&#039;s path to economic dominance]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/frictionless-flows-are-ethereum-s-path</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/frictionless-flows-are-ethereum-s-path?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Opinion by: Barna Kiss, CEO of Malda
An idea recently floated by some prominent thinkers in the Ethereum space to reclaim value for the mainnet is the taxing of its Layer-2s. The future of Ethereum does not depend on policy but on enabling frictionless capital movement between the L2s in question. Tariffing rollups may appear a neat way to reclaim value for the mainnet. In practice, it would fragment the ecosystem, drain liquidity, push users toward centralized platforms, and avoid decentralized finance altogether. In a permissionless system, capital flows to where it is treated best, and Ethereum's rollups mistreat it.

Liquidity fragmentation is Ethereum's real threat
In traditional finance, the link between fluidity and growth is well established. Lower barriers to capital inflows lead …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Barna Kiss</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ECB Establishes Innovation Hub to Test Digital Euro as Preparation Phase Nears End]]></title>
        <id>932c193f-a0e2-4908-9e44-fef4f3800a40</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2025/05/06/ecb-establishes-innovation-hub-to-test-digital-euro-as-preparation-phase-nears-end"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T14:51:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The hub has 70 participants including Accenture, KPMG and CaixaBank.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Camomile Shumba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DeFi Development Adds $11.2M in SOL, Bringing Holdings to More Than 400K Tokens]]></title>
        <id>d4cf9af1-e8ad-4a42-abfd-57df47608336</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/06/defi-development-adds-usd11-2m-in-sol-bringing-holdings-to-more-than-400k-tokens"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T14:47:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Formerly known as Janover, the company's SOL holdings are worth more than $57 million at current prices.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Francisco Rodrigues</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Report: OpenAI is buying AI-powered developer platform Windsurf — what happens to its support for rival LLMs?]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3006587</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/report-openai-is-buying-ai-powered-developer-platform-windsurf-what-happens-to-its-support-for-rival-llms/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T14:37:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[OpenAI could see which types of developers use rival models such as the Meta Llama variants and Anthropic's Claude, and for what purposes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carl Franzen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Will Crypto Values Survive the Regulatory Wave?]]></title>
        <id>74e3106c-868a-4cdc-9407-092818a1a538</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/opinion/2025/05/06/will-crypto-values-survive-the-regulatory-wave"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T14:32:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ahead of the People’s Regulatory Roundtable at Consensus 2025, six leading crypto lawyers discuss whether core crypto principles, like decentralization and privacy, will be included in upcoming legislation and regulation.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ivo Entchev</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trump's Crypto Play Fuels Senators' Backlash and Bill to Ban President Memecoins]]></title>
        <id>b95b85bc-3f1c-4cbf-abca-23b1e9859ea5</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2025/05/06/trump-s-crypto-play-fuels-senators-backlash-and-bill-to-ban-president-memecoins"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T14:30:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Democratic Senator Chris Murphy pushed a bill to block presidential coins while Elizabeth Warren described how to get Dems to move forward on stablecoins.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jesse Hamilton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SOL Strategies Buys $18M of Solana Tokens With First Tranche of $500M Note Deal]]></title>
        <id>8522ebda-a761-4edd-aea5-0d8800e95e62</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/06/sol-strategies-buys-18m-of-solana-tokens-with-first-tranche-of-500m-note-deal"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T14:25:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Canadian firm is betting on Solana by using debt financing to scale its validator footprint and crypto holdings.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Krisztian Sandor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What bankers, CPAs and CFOs need to know about blockchain]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/explained/what-bankers-cpas-and-cfos-need-to-know-about-blockchain</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/explained/what-bankers-cpas-and-cfos-need-to-know-about-blockchain?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T14:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Why finance veterans are still skeptical about blockchain            
            
                
Blockchain has been part of the finance conversation for over a decade now. Yet many professionals remain cautious. 
Many seasoned professionals in finance, wealth management and economics often question blockchain’s relevance, asking, How exactly is blockchain supposed to fit into what we already do?

This question reflects a few key ongoing skepticisms about blockchain within finance.
Uncertainty about practical applications
Blockchain offers some big promises: faster settlements, stronger security and better transparency. But actually applying those promises across banking, accounting and operations is still complicated.
A 2021 APQC survey identified the main hurdles: a lack of industry-w…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Bradley Peak</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[VanEck Submits Proposal to Launch First BNB ETF in the U.S.]]></title>
        <id>96cfffe4-6b3a-45f5-8f4e-733208bd4e43</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2025/05/06/vaneck-submits-proposal-to-launch-first-bnb-etf-in-the-u-s"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T14:15:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If approved, the fund would be the first exchange-traded fund tied to BNB in the U.S.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Helene Braun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Accents in latent spaces: How AI hears accent strength in English]]></title>
        <id>https://accent-strength.boldvoice.com/</id>
        <link href="https://accent-strength.boldvoice.com/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T14:07:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Startup Korl unveils multimodal, multi-agent tool for custom communication across disparate systems]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3006451</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/how-openai-gemini-and-anthropic-help-korl-prepare-customer-materials-in-minutes/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Korl's platform works across multiple systems, using multi-agent and multimodal AI to create highly-customized customer messaging.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Taryn Plumb</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Democrat lawmakers object to hearing, citing ‘Trump’s crypto corruption’]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/digital-asset-hearing-objection-donald-trump-crypto-corruption</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/digital-asset-hearing-objection-donald-trump-crypto-corruption?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T13:59:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[US Representative Maxine Waters, ranking member of the House Financial Services Committee (HFSC), led some Democratic lawmakers out of a joint hearing on digital assets in response to what she called “the corruption of the President of the United States” concerning cryptocurrencies.
In a May 6 joint hearing of the HFSC and House Committee on Agriculture, Waters remained standing while addressing Republican leadership, saying she intended to block proceedings due to US President Donald Trump’s “ownership of crypto” and oversight of government agencies. 
Digital asset subcommittee Chair Bryan Steil, seemingly taking advantage of a loophole in committee rules, said Republican lawmakers would continue with the event as a “roundtable” rather than a hearing.
HFSC Chair French Hill urged lawmaker…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Turner Wright</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nnd – a TUI debugger alternative to GDB, LLDB]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/al13n321/nnd</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/al13n321/nnd"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T13:58:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BNB Coin Could Hit $2,775 by Year-End 2028, Standard Chartered Says]]></title>
        <id>30f232ba-36b9-44cb-8aa7-5ae1d555a057</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/06/bnb-coin-could-hit-2775-by-year-end-2028-standard-chartered-says"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T13:57:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The token has traded like an unweighted mix of bitcoin and ether since May 2021, the report said.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Will Canny</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[21Shares Launches ETP Linked to Crypto.com's Cronos]]></title>
        <id>6a70328c-6e4b-4729-9f1f-477a776cf317</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/06/21shares-launches-etp-linked-to-cryptocoms-cronos"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T13:23:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The product allows investors to add CRO exposure to their portfolios without handling crypto wallets or exchanges.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Francisco Rodrigues</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CoinDesk 20 Performance Update: Index Drops 2.2% as All Assets Trade Lower]]></title>
        <id>43299b7f-f086-4d0b-a85e-7f768d3e67a4</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/coindesk-indices/2025/05/06/coindesk-20-performance-update-index-drops-2-2-as-all-assets-trade-lower"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T13:16:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sui (SUI) fell 7.7% and Aave (AAVE) declined 7.5%, leading the index lower.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CoinDesk Indices</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Mining Rig Maker Canaan Could Have 5X Upside, Says Wall Street Analyst]]></title>
        <id>e459b496-aeee-4386-a66b-c3bdca554008</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/06/bitcoin-mining-rig-maker-canaan-could-have-5x-upside-says-wall-street-analyst"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T13:08:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Benchmark's Mark Palmer initiated coverage on the firm's roughed-up shares with a buy rating and $3 price target.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Will Canny</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ōura adds AI-driven meal and glucose tracking features with Stelo by Dexcom]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3006449</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/games/oura-adds-ai-driven-meal-and-glucose-tracking-features-with-stelo-by-dexcom/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ōura, maker of a health-monitoring smart ring, announced that it will use AI to track and analyze two new metabolic health features: meals and glucose.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dean Takahashi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DogeOS Raises $6.9M to Launch Dogecoin App Layer]]></title>
        <id>3ea4be2f-eb52-4702-b451-8236cfadd034</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/06/dogeos-raises-usd6-9m-to-launch-dogecoin-app-layer"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The funding will enable DogeOS to support a variety of consumer apps, enhancing the Dogecoin ecosystem and its decentralized finance services.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shaurya Malwa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Binance founder CZ says Bitcoin could hit $500K–$1M this cycle]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/cz-says-bitcoin-could-hit-500-k-1-m-this-cycle</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/cz-says-bitcoin-could-hit-500-k-1-m-this-cycle?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T12:40:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Binance co-founder Changpeng “CZ” Zhao expects Bitcoin’s price to top at $500,000 to $1 million during this market cycle.
During an interview with Rug Radio published on May 5, Zhao said that he expects Bitcoin to reach up to one million dollars during this market cycle. He also highlighted the role of Bitcoin spot exchange-traded funds (ETFs) in this rise, saying that the increasing institutionalization of Bitcoin is a good thing for the market:
“There’s the ETFs. There’s this institutionalization of Bitcoin [ … ] it’s a positive in terms of price action, obviously. Our bags are up  —  not the alt‑coins as much, but at least Bitcoin is.”
Zhao explained that the ETFs are “bringing the traditional institution money into crypto” and “most of the money in the US is institutional money.” He sa…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Adrian Zmudzinski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Traders Seek Downside Protection Ahead of Fed Chair Powell’s Comments]]></title>
        <id>e9e20408-1ab5-456d-b406-2cc03272ba33</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/06/bitcoin-traders-seek-downside-protection-ahead-of-fed-chair-powell-s-comments"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T12:36:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We have only seen some nuanced demand for protective BTC puts, reflecting limited caution among sophisticated traders, Deribit's CEO told CoinDesk.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Omkar Godbole</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Singapore’s Grab taps Solana DePIN project Natix to ‘reshape mapping’]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/singapore-grab-solana-depin-autonomous-driving-mapping</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/singapore-grab-solana-depin-autonomous-driving-mapping?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T12:32:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Southeast Asia’s superapp Grab has partnered with Natix, a project within Solana’s decentralized physical infrastructure network (DePIN), to cooperate on mapping and autonomous driving technologies.
The joint collaboration aims to combine Natix’s blockchain-based mapping data with Grab’s camera hardware and mapmaking technology featuring artificial intelligence support, Natix said in an announcement on May 6.
“This partnership brings together the best of both worlds,” the announcement noted, pointing to Grab’s expertise in crowdsourced mapping and Natix’s unique DePIN model that rewards users for providing decentralized data input.
Source: Natix
“By combining GrabMaps’ AI-powered mapping technology with Natix’s decentralized data network, we’re enabling real-time, high-fidelity map updates…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Helen Partz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin risks sub-$92K retest as BTC price fails to match 4% gold gains]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-faces-91-6-k-retest-btc-price-fails-match-gold-gains</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-faces-91-6-k-retest-btc-price-fails-match-gold-gains?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T12:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Key points:

Bitcoin is struggling again as gold retakes the limelight with week-to-date gains of nearly 5%.

Bitcoin’s correlation with gold is under scrutiny amid ongoing macroeconomic shifts.

Traders see a short-term slump amid a wider BTC price rebound.

Bitcoin (BTC) eyed fresh month-to-date lows into the May 6 Wall Street open as “directionless” crypto markets contrasted with a gold rebound.
BTC/USD 1-hour chart. Source: Cointelegraph/TradingView
Analysis: Bitcoin, crypto “largely directionless”
Data from Cointelegraph Markets Pro and TradingView showed BTC price momentum stalling at $95,000 before the latest daily close. 
Inching closer to the key yearly open support level at $93,500, BTC/USD appeared caught in limbo while gold returned to outperform.
XAU/USD was up 1.5% on the day…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by William Suberg</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[US stablecoin bill loses democrats amid Trump corruption concerns]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/us-stablecoin-bill-loses-democratic-support-trump-corruption-concerns</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/us-stablecoin-bill-loses-democratic-support-trump-corruption-concerns?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T12:28:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Democratic lawmakers in Washington are backing off support for crypto legislation amid heightened concerns over corruption, including the conduct of the Trump family’s World Liberty Financial (WLFI).
In March, the GENIUS Act, which would regulate stablecoins in the US, passed a critical committee reading with the support of several pro-crypto Democrats. Democratic Senators Ruben Gallego, Mark Warner, Lisa Blunt Rochester, Andy Kim and Angela Alsobrooks voted with Republicans, opposite lead Democrat and prominent crypto critic Senator Elizabeth Warren.
The bill passed the committee only after a number of changes were made, including stricter requirements for stablecoin issuers and provisions for Anti-Money Laundering, countering terrorism financing and risk management procedures. 
Now, it s…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Aaron Wood</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Download: a longevity influencer’s new religion, and humanoid robots’ shortcomings]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1116114</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/05/06/1116114/the-download-a-longevity-influencers-new-religion-and-humanoid-robots-shortcomings/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T12:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is today’s edition of The Download, our weekday newsletter that provides a daily dose of what’s going on in the world of technology. Bryan Johnson wants to start a new religion in which “the body is God” Bryan Johnson is on a mission to not die. The 47-year-old multimillionaire has already applied his slogan “Don’t Die”…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rhiannon Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Daybook Americas: Can Bitcoin's Regulatory Worry be Bullish for DeFi Tokens?]]></title>
        <id>43ae5db8-dc9e-46b3-8da8-84550f823d54</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/daybook-us/2025/05/06/crypto-daybook-americas-bitcoin-threatened-by-regulation-hiccup-weakening-demand"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T11:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Your day-ahead look for May 6, 2025]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Omkar Godbole</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Citi, Switzerland’s SDX Join Forces to Tokenize $75B Pre-IPO Shares Market]]></title>
        <id>04745cbf-1995-485a-8f3e-8eb0c1e2eb18</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2025/05/06/citi-switzerland-s-sdx-join-forces-to-tokenize-usd75b-pre-ipo-shares-market"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T10:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Citi will act as a custodian and issuer agent for tokenized assets on SDX’s digital Central Securities Depository (CSD) platform.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ian Allison</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FTC rule on unfair or deceptive fees to take effect on May 12]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ftc.gov/news-events/news/press-releases/2025/05/ftc-rule-unfair-or-deceptive-fees-take-effect-may-12-2025</id>
        <link href="https://www.ftc.gov/news-events/news/press-releases/2025/05/ftc-rule-unfair-or-deceptive-fees-take-effect-may-12-2025"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T10:10:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[IntoTheBlock and Trident Merge With $25M Backing to Build Institutional DeFi Gateway]]></title>
        <id>cb2296f1-a439-480a-8f41-100c9a802dd2</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2025/05/05/intotheblock-and-trident-merge-secure-usd25m-backing-to-build-institutional-defi-gateway"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The newly formed Sentora aims to offer a compliant DeFi platform for sophisticated investors looking for yield, liquidity and risk management.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Krisztian Sandor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why the humanoid workforce is running late]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1116108</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/05/06/1116108/why-the-humanoid-workforce-is-running-late/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On Thursday I watched Daniela Rus, one of the world’s top experts on AI-powered robots, address a packed room at a Boston robotics expo. Rus spent a portion of her talk busting the notion that giant fleets of humanoids are already making themselves useful in manufacturing and warehouses around the world.  That might come as…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>James O'Donnell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Join the 2025 Web3j Mentorships: Build the Future of Ethereum on the JVM]]></title>
        <id>6819c8dc41eeeb000183d37b</id>
        <link href="https://blog.web3labs.com/join-the-2025-web3j-mentorships-build-the-future-of-ethereum-on-the-jvm/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T08:32:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Linux Foundation’s Decentralized Trust (LFDT) mentorship program is back in 2025 with two exciting opportunities for developers passionate about Ethereum, Android, and the Java Virtual Machine (JVM). Whether you’re a seasoned blockchain developer or an Android enthusiast eager to dive into Web3, these mentorships offer]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>George Tebrean</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DoorDash to acquire Deliveroo]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cnbc.com/2025/05/06/doordash-to-buy-uk-food-delivery-firm-deliveroo-in-3point9-billion-deal.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.cnbc.com/2025/05/06/doordash-to-buy-uk-food-delivery-firm-deliveroo-in-3point9-billion-deal.html"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T06:27:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[IBM thinks that over a billion new applications will be built with gen AI : Here’s how they’re going to help that happen with agentic AI]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3006455</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/agents-are-key-to-enterprise-ai-success-heres-ibms-plan-on-how-to-make-it-happen/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T04:01:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[IBM details its plans to help enterprises to actually do more with AI, with an expanded set of agentic AI capabilities.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sean Michael Kerner</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Scientists have found a way to 'tattoo' tardigrades]]></title>
        <id>https://phys.org/news/2025-04-scientists-tattoo-tardigrades.html</id>
        <link href="https://phys.org/news/2025-04-scientists-tattoo-tardigrades.html"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T01:51:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OpenAI reaches agreement to buy Windsurf for $3B]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2025-05-06/openai-reaches-agreement-to-buy-startup-windsurf-for-3-billion</id>
        <link href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2025-05-06/openai-reaches-agreement-to-buy-startup-windsurf-for-3-billion"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T00:57:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meta, Cisco put open-source LLMs at the core of next-gen SOC workflows]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3006384</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/rsac-2025-cisco-and-meta-put-open-source-ai-at-the-heart-of-enterprise-threat-defense/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T00:08:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cisco’s Foundation-sec-8B LLM & Meta’s AI Defenders redefine cybersecurity with open-source AI for scalable SOCs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Louis Columbus</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[docker2exe: Convert a Docker image to an executable]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/rzane/docker2exe</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/rzane/docker2exe"/>
        <updated>2025-05-05T20:47:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nvidia launches fully open source transcription AI model Parakeet-TDT-0.6B-V2 on Hugging Face]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3006438</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/nvidia-launches-fully-open-source-transcription-ai-model-parakeet-tdt-0-6b-v2-on-hugging-face/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-05T19:17:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An attractive proposition for commercial enterprises and indie developers looking to build speech recognition and transcription services...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carl Franzen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Improve you C++ skills by coding an audio plugin]]></title>
        <id>68190b8f1abafc5ea9d7efbf</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/improve-you-c-skills-by-coding-an-audio-plugin/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-05T19:03:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Do you want to build a practical project to help improve your C++ skills? Have you ever wanted to create your own unique audio effects? Then diving into C++ audio plugin development with the JUCE framework might be your next great step We just publis...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Visa launches ‘Intelligent Commerce’ platform, letting AI agents swipe your card—safely, it says]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3006416</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/visa-launches-intelligent-commerce-platform-letting-ai-agents-swipe-your-card-safely-it-says/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-05T18:01:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Visa launches Intelligent Commerce platform enabling AI assistants to make secure purchases with your credit card, transforming online shopping with personalized automation and consumer-controlled spending limits.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Nuñez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Loving 21st century gaming like an 18th century furniture expert]]></title>
        <id>https://kimimithegameeatingshemonster.com/2023/04/26/loving-21st-century-gaming-like-an-18th-century-furniture-expert/</id>
        <link href="https://kimimithegameeatingshemonster.com/2023/04/26/loving-21st-century-gaming-like-an-18th-century-furniture-expert/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-05T16:26:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[(ab?)using Node module hooks to speed up development]]></title>
        <id>https://immaculata.dev/blog/hacking-nodejs-modules.html</id>
        <link href="https://immaculata.dev/blog/hacking-nodejs-modules.html"/>
        <updated>2025-05-05T16:13:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build a Dynamic Wardrobe App with React Drag and Drop]]></title>
        <id>6818d1793c6be4514080aea9</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-build-a-dynamic-wardrobe-app-with-react-drag-and-drop/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-05T14:55:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Have you ever found yourself stuck deciding what color outfit to wear? Maybe you’re mixing and matching different tops and bottoms, unsure if the colors go together. It’s a common dilemma – so common that many of us turn to friends or family for a se...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Timothy Olanrewaju</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bryan Johnson wants to start a new religion in which “the body is God”]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1116090</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/05/05/1116090/bryan-johnson-new-religion-body-is-god/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-05T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bryan Johnson is on a mission to not die. The 47-year-old multimillionaire has already applied his slogan “Don’t Die” to events, merchandise, and a Netflix documentary. Now he’s founding a Don’t Die religion. Johnson, who famously spends millions of dollars on scans, tests, supplements, and a lifestyle routine designed to slow or reverse the aging…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jessica Hamzelou</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The great cognitive migration: How AI is reshaping human purpose, work and meaning]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3006326</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/the-great-cognitive-migration-ai-will-win-at-intelligence-but-only-we-can-make-it-matter/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-04T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Humans need to embrace domains where AI still falters, and where human creativity, ethics and emotion emain indispensable.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gary Grossman, Edelman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DuoBook: Generate bilingual stories to learn any language]]></title>
        <id>https://duobook.co/</id>
        <link href="https://duobook.co/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-04T12:40:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Old Timey Code and Old Timey Mono Fonts]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/dse/old-timey-mono-font</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/dse/old-timey-mono-font"/>
        <updated>2025-05-04T04:10:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Not everything needs an LLM: A framework for evaluating when AI makes sense]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3006312</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/not-everything-needs-an-llm-a-framework-for-evaluating-when-ai-makes-sense/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-03T19:35:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The answer to 'What customer needs requires an AI solution?' isn’t always 'Yes.' LLMs are still expensive and not always accurate.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sharanya Rao</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[RSAC 2025: Why the AI agent era means more demand for CISOs]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3006066</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/security/rsac-2025-why-the-ai-agent-era-means-more-demand-for-cisos/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-02T23:02:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[RSAC 2025 made one thing clear: AI agents are entering security workflows, but boards want proof they work.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Louis Columbus</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Write Good API Documentation]]></title>
        <id>68151f0be5850fcb8543375a</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-write-good-api-docs/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-02T19:37:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Imagine purchasing a standing fan straight out of the box, all parts dismantled, and you have no manual or guide to put them together. Did you imagine that just now? Cool. Here is another scenario: imagine purchasing an LG product, such as a smart TV...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Okoro Emmanuel Nzube</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OpenAI overrode concerns of expert testers to release sycophantic GPT-4o]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3006276</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/openai-overrode-concerns-of-expert-testers-to-release-sycophantic-gpt-4o/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-02T17:57:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Once again, it shows the importance of incorporating more domains beyond the traditional math and computer science into AI development.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carl Franzen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use SonarQube to Improve Your Code Quality]]></title>
        <id>6815023dec2e34790eeb71a8</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-improve-your-code-quality-with-sonarqube/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-02T17:34:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SonarQube is a powerful open-source tool that helps you maintain code quality and security by analyzing your codebase for bugs and vulnerabilities. And it can play a major role when integrated into your CI/CD pipeline. In this tutorial, we will cover...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Divya Valsala Saratchandran</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn Kubernetes – Full Handbook for Developers, Startups, and Businesses]]></title>
        <id>68150214fd424d0874293171</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-kubernetes-handbook-devs-startups-businesses/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-02T17:34:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You’ve probably heard the word Kubernetes floating around, or it’s cooler nickname k8s (pronounced “kates“). Maybe in a job post, a tech podcast, or from that one DevOps friend who always brings it up like it’s the secret sauce to everything 😅. It s...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Prince Onukwili</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Roblox breaks ground on data center in Brazil for early 2026]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3006251</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/games/roblox-breaks-ground-on-data-center-in-brazil-for-early-2026/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-02T16:55:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At Gamescom Latam, Roblox announced it has broken ground on a new data center in Brazil -- slated to go live in early 2026.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dean Takahashi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[From Art School Drop-out to Microsoft Engineer with Shashi Lo [Podcast #170]]]></title>
        <id>6814f2ab33857abe499038b0</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/from-art-school-drop-out-to-microsoft-engineer-with-shashi-lo-podcast-170/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-02T16:28:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On this week's episode of the podcast, I interview Shashi Lo. He's a software engineer at Microsoft. He grew up the child of refugees. He wanted to start earning money and build his family so he abandoned his art school degree and taught himself how ...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Quincy Larson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Download: foreign disinformation intel, and gene-edited pork]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1116079</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/05/02/1116079/the-download-foreign-disinformation-intel-and-gene-edited-pork/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-02T12:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is today’s edition of The Download, our weekday newsletter that provides a daily dose of what’s going on in the world of technology. A senior State Department official demanded records of communications with journalists, European officials, and Trump critics A previously unreported document distributed by senior US State Department official Darren Beattie reveals a sweeping effort…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rhiannon Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The US has approved CRISPR pigs for food]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1116059</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/05/02/1116059/the-us-approves-crispr-pigs-for-food/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-02T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Most pigs in the US are confined to factory farms where they can be afflicted by a nasty respiratory virus that kills piglets. The illness is called porcine reproductive and respiratory syndrome, or PRRS. A few years ago, a British company called Genus set out to design pigs immune to this germ using CRISPR gene…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Antonio Regalado</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hidden costs in AI deployment: Why Claude models may be 20-30% more expensive than GPT in enterprise settings]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3006096</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/hidden-costs-in-ai-deployment-why-claude-models-may-be-20-30-more-expensive-than-gpt-in-enterprise-settings/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-01T20:14:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It is a well-known fact that different model families can use different tokenizers. However, there has been limited analysis on how the process of “tokenization” itself varies across these tokenizers. Do all tokenizers result in the same number of tokens for a given input text? If not, how different are the generated tokens? How significant […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lavanya Gupta</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Senior State Department official sought internal communications with journalists, European officials, and Trump critics]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1115988</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/05/01/1115988/senior-state-department-official-sought-internal-communications-with-journalists-european-officials-and-trump-critics/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-01T17:41:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A previously unreported document distributed by senior US State Department official Darren Beattie reveals a sweeping effort to uncover all communications between the staff of a small government office focused on online disinformation and a lengthy list of public and private figures—many of whom are longtime targets of the political right.  The document, originally shared…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eileen Guo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Astronomer’s $93M raise underscores a new reality: Orchestration is king in AI infrastructure]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3006195</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/astronomer-93m-raise-underscores-a-new-reality-orchestration-is-king-in-ai-infrastructure/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-01T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Astronomer secures $93 million in Series D funding to solve the AI implementation gap through data orchestration, helping enterprises streamline complex workflows and operationalize AI initiatives at scale.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Nuñez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft launches Phi-4-Reasoning-Plus, a small, powerful, open weights reasoning model!]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3006213</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/microsoft-launches-phi-4-reasoning-plus-a-small-powerful-open-weights-reasoning-model/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-01T12:41:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The release demonstrates that with carefully curated data and training techniques, small models can deliver strong reasoning performance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carl Franzen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Download: China’s energy throwback, and choosing between love and immortality]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1115999</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/05/01/1115999/the-download-chinas-energy-throwback-and-choosing-between-love-and-immortality/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-01T12:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is today’s edition of The Download, our weekday newsletter that provides a daily dose of what’s going on in the world of technology. A long-abandoned US nuclear technology is making a comeback in China China has once again beat everyone else to a clean energy milestone—its new nuclear reactor is reportedly one of the first to…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rhiannon Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Salesforce takes aim at ‘jagged intelligence’ in push for more reliable AI]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3006124</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/salesforce-tackles-jagged-intelligence-problem-with-new-ai-benchmarks-and-models/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-01T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Salesforce unveils groundbreaking AI research tackling "jagged intelligence," introducing new benchmarks, models, and guardrails to make enterprise AI agents more intelligent, trusted, and consistently reliable for business use.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Nuñez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A long-abandoned US nuclear technology is making a comeback in China]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1115957</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/05/01/1115957/old-new-nuclear-technology/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-01T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[China has once again beat everyone else to a clean energy milestone—its new nuclear reactor is reportedly one of the first to use thorium instead of uranium as a fuel and the first of its kind that can be refueled while it’s running. It’s an interesting (if decidedly experimental) development out of a country that’s…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Casey Crownhart</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[UiPath’s new orchestrator guides AI agents to follow your enterprise’s rules]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3006059</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/uipaths-new-orchestrator-guides-ai-agents-to-follow-your-enterprises-rules/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T21:20:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[UiPath's agent orchestration layer Maestro moves prompts through three layers: the agent, a human and the robotic process automation system.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Emilia David</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The ‘era of experience’ will unleash self-learning AI agents across the web—here’s how to prepare]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3005579</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/the-era-of-experience-will-unleash-self-learning-ai-agents-across-the-web-heres-how-to-prepare/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T20:38:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AI visionaries predict an 'Era of Experience' where AI learns autonomously, and it will have important implications for application design.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ben Dickson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Qwen swings for a double with 2.5-Omni-3B model that runs on consumer PCs, laptops]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3006114</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/qwen-swings-for-a-double-with-2-5-omni-3b-model-that-runs-on-consumer-pcs-laptops/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T20:31:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Qwen2.5-Omni-3B model is licensed for non-commercial use only under Alibaba Cloud’s Qwen Research License Agreement.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carl Franzen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Breaking the ‘intellectual bottleneck’: How AI is computing the previously uncomputable in healthcare]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3005667</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/breaking-the-intellectual-bottleneck-how-ai-is-computing-the-previously-uncomputible-in-healthcare/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T19:03:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How University of Texas Medical Branch is using AI to identify patients at high cardiovascular risk, flag for stroke and catch 'basic stuff.']]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Taryn Plumb</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OpenAI rolls back ChatGPT’s sycophancy and explains what went wrong]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3006053</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/openai-rolls-back-chatgpts-sycophancy-and-explains-what-went-wrong/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T15:14:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Many organizations may also begin shifting toward open-source alternatives that they can host and tune themselves.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carl Franzen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Structify raises $4.1M seed to turn unstructured web data into enterprise-ready datasets]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3006010</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/structify-raises-4-1m-seed-to-turn-unstructured-web-data-into-enterprise-ready-datasets/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Brooklyn-based Structify emerges from stealth with $4.1 million in seed funding to transform how businesses prepare data for AI, promising to save data scientists from the task that consumes 80% of their time.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Nuñez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Download: stereotypes in AI models, and the new age of coding]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1115952</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/04/30/1115952/the-download-stereotypes-in-ai-models-and-the-new-age-of-coding/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T12:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is today’s edition of The Download, our weekday newsletter that provides a daily dose of what’s going on in the world of technology. This data set helps researchers spot harmful stereotypes in LLMs What’s new? AI models are riddled with culturally specific biases. A new data set, called SHADES, is designed to help developers combat the…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rhiannon Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This data set helps researchers spot harmful stereotypes in LLMs]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1115946</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/04/30/1115946/this-data-set-helps-researchers-spot-harmful-stereotypes-in-llms/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T09:41:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AI models are riddled with culturally specific biases. A new data set, called SHADES, is designed to help developers combat the problem by spotting harmful stereotypes and other kinds of discrimination that emerge in AI chatbot responses across a wide range of languages. Margaret Mitchell, chief ethics scientist at AI startup Hugging Face, led the…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rhiannon Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[No more window switching: Mastercard’s Agent Pay transforms how enterprises use AI search]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3005997</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/no-more-window-switching-mastercards-agent-pay-transforms-how-enterprises-use-ai-search/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T22:24:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mastercard is working with AI companies and banks to allow AI platforms and agents to facilitate transactions.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Emilia David</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Web3j Six Month Project Update]]></title>
        <id>68109495670a1300013504c2</id>
        <link href="https://blog.web3labs.com/web3j-six-month-project-update/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T09:10:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[November 2024 - April 2025
This report summarizes the activities and accomplishments of Web3j, an LF Decentralized Trust project, from November 2024 to April 2025. During this period, the project made significant strides in improving the framework’s functionality, enhancing user engagement, and bolstering overall community interaction. 
Key]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>George Tebrean</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[QuickNode: Building the Infrastructure for the Next Generation of Blockchain]]></title>
        <id>6807d5787fb8500001c39b99</id>
        <link href="https://blog.quicknode.com/quicknode-building-the-infrastructure-for-the-next-generation-of-blockchain/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-28T16:02:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Join QuickNode co-founder Dmitry Shklovsky as he discusses blockchain infrastructure, building decentralized applications, and the future of Web3 development on TheCube's Crypto Trailblazer Series.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>QuickNode</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>