<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2025-05-28T13:09:07.914Z</id>
    <title>AngJianming RSS Feed</title>
    <updated>2025-05-28T13:09:07.914Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elon Musk’s xAI inks $300M deal with Telegram for Grok integration]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/elon-musk-xai-300-million-telegram-deal-grok-integration</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/elon-musk-xai-300-million-telegram-deal-grok-integration?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss%3FREFRESH1635339232122&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T13:06:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Elon Musk’s artificial intelligence company xAI has partnered with Telegram to integrate its AI chatbot Grok across the messaging platform, according to Telegram CEO Pavel Durov.
Telegram and xAI have agreed to a one-year partnership to distribute Grok to a billion Telegram users and integrate it into its apps, Durov announced on X on May 28.
As part of the agreement, Telegram will receive $300 million in cash and equity from Musk’s AI company, in addition to 50% of revenue from xAI subscriptions sold via Telegram, the CEO noted.
“Together, we win,” Durov said in the statement on X.
Grok integration begins with Telegram
According to a promo video accompanying Durov’s announcement, the partnership is expected to bring a wide rollout of Grok features within the messenger.
Accessible via the …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Helen Partz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Akool Live Camera can translate video calls in real time, swap faces, and get live virtual avatars to mimic human movements]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008843</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/games/akool-live-camera-can-translate-video-calls-in-real-time-swap-faces-and-get-virtual-avatars-to-mimic-human-movements/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Akool Live Camera uses AI to capture human movement and mimic that movement with a generated virtual avatar in real time.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dean Takahashi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Former Chainlink, Two Sigma execs build ‘Moirai’ to uncover crypto gems]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/former-chainlink-two-sigma-execs-moirai-uncover-crypto-gems</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/former-chainlink-two-sigma-execs-moirai-uncover-crypto-gems?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss%3FREFRESH1635339232122&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Metalayer Ventures, a crypto-focused venture capital firm led by former executives from Chainlink and Two Sigma, has launched a $25 million fund to invest in early-stage blockchain projects with a focus on stablecoins, tokenization and cryptocurrency infrastructure. 
Metalayer’s fund has already backed seven companies, the company disclosed to Cointelegraph on May 28. These include AnchorZero, a platform helping crypto founders use Roth IRAs for tax advantages, and Spark Capital, a new venture focused on stablecoin infrastructure.
Other portfolio companies include Ethena, ClearToken, Crossover Markets, Station70 and Theo — an onchain trading infrastructure project that recently raised $20 million from 17 different VC firms.
The company plans to eventually back up to 30 companies with early…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Sam Bourgi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Resources for Project Managers: Essential Tools, Websites, and Communities]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/isabella_harry_e56dfaa53c/resources-for-project-managers-essential-tools-websites-and-communities-4oo4</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/isabella_harry_e56dfaa53c/resources-for-project-managers-essential-tools-websites-and-communities-4oo4"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T12:59:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Project management is a dynamic field requiring a mix of technical skills, strategic thinking, and effective communication. Fortunately, project managers have access to a wide range of tools, websites, and communities to help them stay organized, improve their processes, and stay current in their profession. Here’s a short guide to some of the most valuable resources available.
Trello – A visual project management tool that uses boards, lists, and cards to help teams track tasks and collaborate.
*Asana *– Great for tracking projects, assigning tasks, and setting deadlines. It’s ideal for teams that need clear visibility and accountability.
Microsoft Project – A more robust solution for enterprise-level project planning, scheduling, and resource management.
Monday.com – Offers customizable …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Isabella harry</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Stochastic Momentum Index (SMI) with RSI and MACD for Confirmation]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/johnwilson1/stochastic-momentum-index-smi-with-rsi-and-macd-for-confirmation-4hjp</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/johnwilson1/stochastic-momentum-index-smi-with-rsi-and-macd-for-confirmation-4hjp"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T12:59:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discovering the Stochastic Momentum Index (SMI): A Fresh Take on Momentum Trading


When it comes to technical analysis, certain tools always seem to come up—RSI, moving averages, Bollinger Bands, and classic oscillators. These indicators have earned their place in almost every trader’s arsenal. At one point or another, most traders have used them to guide their decisions.

But if you’re searching for a different perspective—something that goes beyond the usual—then it might be time to explore the Stochastic Momentum Index, or SMI. While not as well-known, this indicator offers a fresh angle on market momentum and can help refine your trading approach.
The Stochastic Momentum Index is a momentum-focused tool designed to track both the strength and direction of an asset's price movement. It…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>member_4fb06303</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Show HN: Voiden – a free, offline, Git-native API Client]]></title>
        <id>https://voiden.md/</id>
        <link href="https://voiden.md/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T12:48:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cybersecurity Certification: Your Gateway to a Secure and Rewarding Career]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/aakruthi_singh_ef9a32b0ab/cybersecurity-certification-your-gateway-to-a-secure-and-rewarding-career-7o3</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/aakruthi_singh_ef9a32b0ab/cybersecurity-certification-your-gateway-to-a-secure-and-rewarding-career-7o3"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T12:46:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A cybersecurity certification is a formal recognition that demonstrates your knowledge, skills, and expertise in protecting computer systems, networks, and data from cyber threats. These certifications are issued by accredited organizations and are often required by employers to validate your credibility in the cybersecurity domain.
Here are a few compelling reasons to pursue a cybersecurity certification:
Career Advancement: Certifications help you stand out in a competitive job market and qualify for better roles.
Higher Salaries: Certified professionals often earn significantly more than non-certified peers.
Skill Validation: Proves your ability to address modern security challenges.
Industry Recognition: Establishes you as a trusted expert in the cybersecurity field.
Continuous Learnin…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Aakruthi Singh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Subtle Art of Trust: Syncing Auth Between Frontend, Backend, and Database]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/ackermannq/the-subtle-art-of-trust-syncing-auth-between-frontend-backend-and-database-4b8p</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/ackermannq/the-subtle-art-of-trust-syncing-auth-between-frontend-backend-and-database-4b8p"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T12:45:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How to architect a fullstack authentication system where your frontend, backend, and database all trust each other without leaking security or breaking developer flow.
Authentication in a modern fullstack app isn't just about logging in-it's about establishing a durable trust contract between all parts of your system: the frontend, the backend API, and the data layer (often managed via a service like Supabase or a custom DB). And while frameworks like NextAuth, Firebase, or Supabase Auth promise convenience, the reality is often messier.
This article explores how to design a seamless, secure, and maintainable authentication pipeline where each layer communicates just enough to stay in sync-without coupling too tightly or leaking user data.
In a typical React+Node stack, you’ll often run in…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ackermannQ</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[2025 OT Cybersecurity Trends: Safeguarding Industrial Systems in a Connected World]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/shieldworkz_fcbf9eaa30bfe/2025-ot-cybersecurity-trends-safeguarding-industrial-systems-in-a-connected-world-2eo1</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/shieldworkz_fcbf9eaa30bfe/2025-ot-cybersecurity-trends-safeguarding-industrial-systems-in-a-connected-world-2eo1"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T12:42:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In 2025, the convergence of Operational Technology (OT), Industrial Control Systems (ICS), and the Internet of Things (IoT) has transformed industries like manufacturing, oil & gas, and energy. While this interconnectedness drives efficiency, it also exposes critical infrastructure to sophisticated cyber threats. At Shieldworkz, we are committed to helping organizations navigate this evolving landscape with proactive cybersecurity strategies tailored for OT environments.
Why This Matters


The integration of OT and IT systems has blurred traditional security boundaries, making it challenging to protect critical infrastructure. Cyberattacks targeting OT systems can lead to operational disruptions, financial losses, and reputational damage. In 2025, the threat landscape has become more compl…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shieldworkz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Building Resilient Microservices with C# and .NET: A Complete Guide]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/chakewitz/building-resilient-microservices-with-c-and-net-a-complete-guide-2dea</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/chakewitz/building-resilient-microservices-with-c-and-net-a-complete-guide-2dea"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T12:39:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Building Resilient Microservices with C# and .NET: A Complete Guide


Microservices are the backbone of modern software architectures. Their modularity, scalability, and ability to enable agile development have made them a favored choice for building distributed systems. But with great power comes great responsibility—especially when it comes to designing resilient microservices. In this guide, you'll learn how to build microservices with C# and .NET that can withstand failures, scale efficiently, and remain maintainable over time.
Imagine a busy restaurant kitchen where each chef specializes in a specific dish. If one chef calls in sick, the kitchen may struggle to deliver orders. Similarly, in microservices, each service is specialized and works independently. But when one service fails,…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maria</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Do You Really Need ROS for Robotics? (Spoiler : No)]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/mandip_sapkota_2a737707b7/do-you-really-need-ros-for-robotics-spoiler-no-30e5</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/mandip_sapkota_2a737707b7/do-you-really-need-ros-for-robotics-spoiler-no-30e5"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T12:35:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction to ROS (Robot Operating System)



  
  
  Introduction


If you follow robotics, or are even just a little curious about robotics software, you’ve probably heard of ROS.
ROS stands for Robot Operating System, and it was built by Willow Garage in 2007, coincidentally the same year I was born.
Contrary to what the name suggests, it's not actually an operating system. Instead, ROS is a framework and a collection of tools that make it easier to build robotic applications.
ROS operates at the middleware level, meaning it sits on top of an actual OS, most commonly Ubuntu Linux and helps with tasks like communication, control, and coordination between different robot components.
And before knowing whether to use ROS or not, you need to know the main point of ROS:
“Don’t reinvent the…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mandip Sapkota</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Telegram Signs $300M Deal With Elon Musk's xAI to Integrate Grok Into Its Messaging App, TON up 16%]]></title>
        <id>bb67b222-2a8d-4beb-ad54-115b5de06914</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2025/05/28/telegram-signs-usd300m-deal-to-integrate-grok-ai-into-app-ton-token-up-16"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T12:32:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Telegram will also receive 50% of revenue from xAI subscriptions sold via the app.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Oliver Knight</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is Bun? The Node.js Alternative Explained]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/klimenko/what-is-bun-the-nodejs-alternative-explained-56dl</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/klimenko/what-is-bun-the-nodejs-alternative-explained-56dl"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T12:32:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[JavaScript tooling in 2025 feels kind of broken. Starting a new project usually means pulling in five different tools, waiting 30 seconds for a hot reload, and watching your laptop heat up like it’s mining crypto. Everything feels bloated, fragmented, and honestly, slow.
The way we build apps has changed. Microservices, serverless functions, edge deployments. These are all standard now. Performance and developer experience matter more than ever. But instead of getting easier, things feel more complicated.
This is where Bun comes in. It’s a new JavaScript runtime, built from scratch in Zig. It includes a package manager, bundler, test runner, and transpiler. All of it packed into a single binary.
So is Bun the future of JavaScript tooling, or just another fast tool with a short hype cycle? …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maksim Klimenko</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[I love writing useless tools... but I also believe that infrastructure-as-code deserves some more spice and flair, so I created Neofetch for Terraform! https://github.com/RoseSecurity/terrafetch]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/rosesecurity/i-love-writing-useless-tools-but-i-also-believe-that-infrastructure-as-code-deserves-some-more-19m7</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/rosesecurity/i-love-writing-useless-tools-but-i-also-believe-that-infrastructure-as-code-deserves-some-more-19m7"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T12:30:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A post by RoseSecurity]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>RoseSecurity</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Building a Chatbot With Symfony and MongoDB]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/mongodb/building-a-chatbot-with-symfony-and-mongodb-5c8g</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/mongodb/building-a-chatbot-with-symfony-and-mongodb-5c8g"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T12:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We are living in the age of AI. Almost every modern application or website offers some level of AI integration. Whether it is Google Docs, WhatsApp chat, or Zoom, you will come across an AI integration, especially chatbots, which have become essential tools for enhancing user engagement and support. So why not build one tailored for your own application?
A well-designed chatbot doesn't just answer questions—it creates interactions that enhance user experience and build loyalty. The convergence of advanced AI technologies with robust web frameworks has opened new possibilities for businesses to deploy intelligent conversational agents that truly understand user intent.
In this tutorial, we will walk through the steps to build a chatbot application for the Symfony Documentation along with Do…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Aasawari Sahasrabuddhe</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Python Descriptors Simplified Our PageObjects (And Still Do)]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/sshukalovich/how-python-descriptors-simplified-our-pageobjects-and-still-do-29od</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/sshukalovich/how-python-descriptors-simplified-our-pageobjects-and-still-do-29od"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T12:27:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Not long ago I ran a small poll: who's still using Selenium in 2025?

Surprisingly most respondents said they are.  
These days, I mostly work on backend tests, with just a bit of UI covered using Playwright.

But that poll brought back a technique we used with Selenium around seven years ago.
It's about using descriptors in PageObjects - a rare but elegant approach that still holds up today.  
I'm not presenting this as the only right way, but rather as a small practice that once helped — and might be worth revisiting.
A quick refresher: what are descriptors in Python?
In simple terms, a descriptor is any object that implements one of the methods: __get__, __set__, or __delete__.

They’re the mechanism behind things like @property, but you can use them directly to control attribute access…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Siarhei Shukalovich</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JavaScript]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/swetha_c8c2e8547316457985/javascript-122h</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/swetha_c8c2e8547316457985/javascript-122h"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T12:25:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[JavaScript is a high-level, interpreted programming language primarily used to create interactive and dynamic content on websites. It is one of the core technologies of the web, along with HTML (for structure) and CSS (for styling).
Internal = script is inside HTML file.
External = script is in separate .js file and linked.
Inline = script is inside element attribute.
Primitive Data Types :
String    => Text data
Reference (Non-Primitive) Data Types :
Object   => Collection of key-value pairs
Variable Declarations:
var   => Can be redeclared and reassigned
let   => Can be reassigned, but not redeclared in the same scope
const => Cannot be reassigned or redeclared]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Swetha</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Download: the story of OpenAI, and making magnesium]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1117492</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/05/28/1117492/the-download-the-story-of-openai-and-making-magnesium/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T12:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is today’s edition of The Download, our weekday newsletter that provides a daily dose of what’s going on in the world of technology. OpenAI: The power and the pride OpenAI’s release of ChatGPT 3.5 set in motion an AI arms race that has changed the world. How that turns out for humanity is something we are…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rhiannon Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Good Ideas Die Quietly and Bad Ideas Go Viral]]></title>
        <id>https://www.newyorker.com/books/under-review/why-good-ideas-die-quietly-and-bad-ideas-go-viral</id>
        <link href="https://www.newyorker.com/books/under-review/why-good-ideas-die-quietly-and-bad-ideas-go-viral"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T12:03:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Telegram to Raise $1.5B Through Bond Sale Backed by BlackRock and Citadel: WSJ]]></title>
        <id>69d6fcd6-1ed7-4524-9802-92366c43e96a</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/28/telegram-to-raise-15b-through-bond-sale-backed-by-blackrock-and-citadel-wsj"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T12:00:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The funds will be used to repurchase debt and are convertible into equity if Telegram goes public.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Francisco Rodrigues</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[XRP price set for 48% jump as spot ETF reality draws closer]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/xrp-price-48-jump-spot-etf-reality-draws-closer</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/xrp-price-48-jump-spot-etf-reality-draws-closer?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss%3FREFRESH1635339232122&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T11:50:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Key takeaways:

XRP’s falling wedge pattern signals a bullish reversal; 48% price surge potential.

SEC’s review of WisdomTree’s XRP ETF may spark investor interest as approval odds jump to 84% on Polymarket. 

XRP price is forming a falling wedge pattern on the daily chart, a technical chart formation associated with strong bullish momentum following an upward breakout. Could this technical setup, coupled with the SEC’s review of a spot XRP ETF application by WisdomTree, signal the start of a rally to $3.40 and higher?
XRP falling wedge pattern targets $3.40
From a technical perspective, XRP (XRP) price could gain significant momentum if it breaks out of this falling wedge pattern.
In technical analysis, a falling wedge is a bullish reversal chart pattern that comprises two converging tre…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Nancy Lubale</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ether Favored Over Bitcoin by Big Money, Here Are 3 Clues That Point to ETH Bias in Crypto Market]]></title>
        <id>79f6034e-b020-4ec2-8fc8-96dcc4e17b41</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/28/ether-favored-over-bitcoin-by-big-money-here-are-3-clues-that-point-to-eth-bias-in-crypto-market"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T11:47:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Key indicators suggests traders are becoming more bullish on ether relative to bitcoin.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Omkar Godbole</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TnG Introduces Limited Edition NFC Card With LED Light]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=354227</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/354227/tng-introduces-limited-edition-nfc-card-with-led-light/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T11:36:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Touch ‘n Go (TnG) has introduced a new limited edition NFC card which is much different than its usual offerings. Apart from featuring a unique graphic, this version is the first to include a built-in light-up function. Befitting its “You light up my life” theme, this limited edition release features an LED-equipped lightbulb which activates […]
The post TnG Introduces Limited Edition NFC Card With LED Light appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Heirul Kamel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GameStop officially confirms first Bitcoin purchase of 4,710 BTC]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/gamestop-buys-bitcoin-4710-btc</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/gamestop-buys-bitcoin-4710-btc?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss%3FREFRESH1635339232122&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T11:27:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[GameStop, the US video game and consumer electronics retailer, has confirmed its first Bitcoin investment, acquiring 4,710 Bitcoin, according to a statement posted May 28 on the company’s X account.
The company did not specify how much it paid for the Bitcoin (BTC) or when the purchases were made. The amount purchased was worth around $513 million at the time of writing.
The announcement is GameStop's first publicly acknowledged Bitcoin purchase since the company disclosed plans to move into Bitcoin investment in March.
At the time, GameStop said it would fund the Bitcoin purchase through debt financing and launched a $1.3 billion convertible notes offering.
Source: GameStop
The news comes after months of speculation that GameStop was exploring alternative assets, including cryptocurrencies.
GameStop (GME) stock shares have climbed amid the speculation, jumping 12% in March. February rumors helped fuel an 18% spike in GME stock prices.
According to TradingView, GameStop shares closed at $35 on May 27 and were trading at $36.30 in the pre-market at the time of publication. The stock is up around 30% in the past 30 days, with year-to-date gains of about 10%.
Cointelegraph contacted GameStop for comment regarding its Bitcoin purchase but did not receive a response by the time of publication.
This is a developing story, and further information will be added as it becomes available.
Magazine: Bitcoin vs. the quantum computer threat: Timeline and solutions (2025–2035)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Helen Partz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GameStop Purchases Over $500M Worth of Bitcoin]]></title>
        <id>54ccdbd6-adac-4863-adab-241fb08dbf67</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2025/05/28/gamestop-purchases-over-usd500m-worth-of-bitcoin"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T11:25:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[GameStop announced the purchase on X on Wednesday but did not offer further details about when the BTC were acquired or the price paid.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Crawley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Daybook Americas: Bitcoin Dominance Tops 64% While Options Indicate Bullish Tilt]]></title>
        <id>e4441cf1-cf04-44b4-9d90-b65964f01777</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/daybook-us/2025/05/28/crypto-daybook-americas-bitcoin-dominance-tops-64-while-options-indicate-bullish-tilt"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T11:15:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Your day-ahead look for May 28, 2025]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>James Van Straten</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mazda 6e BEV Set To Launch In Indonesia Following Thailand Debut]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=354212</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/354212/mazda-6e-bev-set-to-launch-in-indonesia-following-thailand-debut/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T10:58:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mazda 6e (also known as EZ-6 in China) will be launching in the Indonesian market soon after it was confirmed for the Thailand market. This information was confirmed by PT Eurokars Motor Indonesia Chief Operating Officer Ricky Thio. He also added that the pure electric variant of the 6e will be the model that will […]
The post Mazda 6e BEV Set To Launch In Indonesia Following Thailand Debut appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Keran</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hollyland Launches Lark A1 And Lark Max 2 Microphones]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=354193</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/354193/hollyland-launches-lark-a1-and-lark-max-2-microphones/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T10:53:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hollyland has announced two new wireless microphones, the Lark A1 and the Lark Max 2. To start off, the Lark A1 is designed with vloggers, streamers, and other content creators in mind. The mics can deliver 24-bit high-fidelity audio quality and have a sound pressure level of 120dB. They also come with three levels of noise […]
The post Hollyland Launches Lark A1 And Lark Max 2 Microphones appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nurul Kamil</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TON Foundation hires former Visa executive to lead payments strategy]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/ton-foundation-hires-visa-executive-nikola-plecas</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/ton-foundation-hires-visa-executive-nikola-plecas?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss%3FREFRESH1635339232122&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T10:52:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Open Network Foundation (TON Foundation) appointed former Visa executive Nikola Plecas as its new vice president of payments.
Plecas will be responsible for shaping and executing TON’s payment infrastructure strategy, the company said in a May 28 blog post.
He is tasked with expanding the network’s capabilities, managing financial partnerships and ensuring compliance across jurisdictions as the foundation scales services for over 1 billion Telegram users.
“Joining TON Foundation represents an incredible opportunity to shape the future of payments on a truly global scale,” Plecas said.
Related: How to use tsUSDe on TON for yield-generating dollar savings
Plecas to lead TON’s new payment strategy
Plecas will lead the push to build a payments architecture that is both globally interoperab…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Amin Haqshanas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Synology Introduces New BeeStation Plus NAS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=354195</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/354195/synology-introduces-new-beestation-plus-nas/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T10:49:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Synology has introduced its latest consumer Network-Attached Storage (NAS) product, the BeeStation Plus. A tier above its existing BeeStation model, which offered up to 4TB of storage, the Plus brings to the table a higher capacity support of up to 8TB. Design-wise, the BeeStation Plus’ overall look and connectivity layout resembles that of its sibling. […]
The post Synology Introduces New BeeStation Plus NAS appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Heirul Kamel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why is Bitcoin price stuck?]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/why-is-bitcoin-price-stuck</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/why-is-bitcoin-price-stuck?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss%3FREFRESH1635339232122&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T10:46:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Key points:

Bitcoin price is stuck in a range, with overhead resistance at $110,000 continuing to obstruct a rally to new all-time highs.

Traders are in a wait-and-see mood due to uncertainty surrounding macroeconomic events.

Bitcoin’s (BTC) bull run has stalled, with the price consolidating within a roughly $3,500 range since May 23. The $110,000 level proves to be a stubborn barrier.
BTC/USD four-hour chart. Cointelegraph/TradingView
Let’s look at some of the reasons why Bitcoin price remains stuck.
Bitcoin runs into resistance at $110,000
Data from Cointelegraph Markets Pro and Bitstamp shows that BTC price oscillates within a tight range between $106,600 and $110,700, with no clear directional bias.
BTC price has “broken out of the triangle pattern and is moving upward,” but a key r…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Nancy Lubale</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amina Bank hits $40M revenue in 2024 as crypto AUM doubles]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/amina-bank-2024-crypto-revenue-aum-growth</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/amina-bank-2024-crypto-revenue-aum-growth?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss%3FREFRESH1635339232122&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T10:32:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Swiss crypto bank Amina Bank, formerly Seba Bank, reported record financial results for 2024, with revenue climbing 69% year-over-year to $40.4 million.
The bank also saw its assets under management (AUM) rise by 136% to $4.2 billion, driven by institutional demand and strategic expansion, according to a May 28 news release.
The Zurich-based bank credited the growth to its multi-jurisdictional footprint, 24/7 trading capabilities and a lending book that has maintained zero defaults over five years.
“I’m incredibly proud of our team’s tenacity and focus, which led to quarterly profitability in Q4 2024, a pivotal milestone that confirms the value of our approach,” CEO Franz Bergmueller said.
Related: Bitcoin Suisse eyes UAE expansion with regulatory nod in Abu Dhabi
Amina adds $801 million i…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Amin Haqshanas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Razer Iskur V2 X Lightning Review: Comfortable And Well-Rounded For Its Price]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=350725</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/350725/razer-iskur-v2-x-lightning-review-comfortable-and-well-rounded-for-its-price/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T10:20:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Back during CES 2025 earlier this year, I had the chance to literally have a brief seat on Razer’s Iskur V2 X gaming chair. It felt comfortable at the time but as it is with demo booths, I couldn’t draw any conclusive points until I had a right and proper sit-down with it. Fast forward […]
The post Razer Iskur V2 X Lightning Review: Comfortable And Well-Rounded For Its Price appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John Law</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BlackRock to join Telegram’s $1.5B bond sale: WSJ]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/blackrock-telegram-bond-sale-1-5b-ipo-discount</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/blackrock-telegram-bond-sale-1-5b-ipo-discount?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss%3FREFRESH1635339232122&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T10:10:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BlackRock, one of the world’s largest Bitcoin holders, is reportedly participating in a bond raise by crypto-friendly messenger Telegram.
Telegram is expected to raise at least $1.5 billion in a bond issue on May 28, with support from existing backers like BlackRock and Abu Dhabi’s investment firm Mubadala, The Wall Street Journal reported.
As part of the sale, Telegram is offering investors five-year bonds at a 9% yield, the report said, citing sources familiar with the matter.
Telegram plans to use the proceeds to buy back remaining debt from bonds issued in 2021, which are due to mature in March 2026.
Discounts for potential Telegram IPO
Apart from existing Telegram bondholders like BlackRock and Mubadala, the sale is also expected to bring new investors, including the US hedge fund fir…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Helen Partz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OpenAI: The power and the pride]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1117486</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/05/28/1117486/openai-the-power-and-the-pride/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T10:07:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In April, Paul Graham, the founder of the tech startup accelerator Y Combinator, sent a tweet in response to former YC president and current OpenAI CEO Sam Altman. Altman had just bid a public goodbye to GPT-4 on X, and Graham had a follow-up question.  “If you had [GPT-4’s model weights] etched on a piece…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mat Honan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This startup wants to make more climate-friendly metal in the US]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1117481</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/05/28/1117481/metal-magrathea/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A California-based company called Magrathea just turned on a new electrolyzer that can make magnesium metal from seawater. The technology has the potential to produce the material, which is used in vehicles and defense applications, with net-zero greenhouse-gas emissions. Magnesium is an incredibly light metal, and it’s used for parts in cars and planes, as…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Casey Crownhart</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fungible cryptos in secondary sales are not securities, Ripple tells SEC]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/ripple-sec-letter-crypto-not-securities</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/ripple-sec-letter-crypto-not-securities?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss%3FREFRESH1635339232122&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T09:59:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ripple, the blockchain company behind XRP, argued that fungible cryptocurrencies are not securities when transferred in secondary transactions in a recent letter sent to the US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC).
In its May 27 letter, Ripple cited US attorney and crypto law thought leader Lewis Cohen to support its claim. In his widely cited 2022 paper, “The Ineluctable Modality of Securities Law: Why Fungible Crypto Assets Are Not Securities,” he wrote:
“[T]here is no current basis in the law relating to ‘investment contracts’ to classify most fungible crypto assets as ‘securities’ when transferred in secondary transactions.”
In his paper, Cohen explained that in secondary transactions, an investment contract transaction is generally not present. He further claimed that fungible cry…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Adrian Zmudzinski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Ordinals Can Now Be Bridged to Cardano Through BitVMX]]></title>
        <id>b447c47b-7de1-4781-be62-2c7d9b55fb08</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/tech/2025/05/23/bitcoin-ordinals-can-now-be-bridged-to-cardano-through-bitvmx"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T09:48:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The on-chain transaction between Bitcoin and Cardano was facilitated by BitVMX, an interoperability protocol built using the BitVM programming language]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Crawley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Apple May Launch A Gaming App To Replace Game Center]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=354187</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/354187/apple-gaming-app-to-replace-game-center/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T09:38:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Apple will reportedly launch a dedicated gaming app to replace its current Game Center, as per Bloomberg via Android Authority. The purported app may come pre-installed on iPhones, iPads, Macs, and Apple TVs sometime later this year, corresponding with the expected launch of iOS 19. The report states that the new gaming app will launch […]
The post Apple May Launch A Gaming App To Replace Game Center appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Newsdesk</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin whales keep buying as BTC price dip targets include $94K]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-whales-keep-buying-btc-price-dip-targets-include-94k</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-whales-keep-buying-btc-price-dip-targets-include-94k?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss%3FREFRESH1635339232122&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T09:32:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Key points:

Bitcoin whales are adding to their BTC positions while price ranges below all-time highs.

If a new market correction comes, one potential bounce level lies in the mid-$90,000 zone.

Hyperliquid trader James Wynn hints at large-volume traders shaping low-timeframe price performance.

Bitcoin (BTC) may see support only at $94,000 if a fresh BTC price correction ensues, new analysis says.
In its latest X commentary, Keith Alan, co-founder of trading resource Material Indicators, pointed to a Bitcoin bounce zone at the 21-week moving average.
Bitcoin whales jump in amid “consolidating” price
Bitcoin continues to track sideways within a $5,000 range after hitting all-time highs of $112,000, data from Cointelegraph Markets Pro and TradingView shows.
For Alan, the market is giving o…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by William Suberg</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ether Likely Building Energy To Smash Through $3K]]></title>
        <id>ad059040-85de-42af-aaee-8c8fbd3fb602</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/28/ether-likely-building-energy-to-smash-through-usd3k"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T09:01:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ether is forming an ascending triangle pattern, suggesting a potential rise above $3,000.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Omkar Godbole</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Surges Ahead as Strategy Lags]]></title>
        <id>6435de2c-c974-4be6-b38d-d84fe54d2733</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/28/bitcoin-surges-ahead-as-strategy-stock-lags"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T08:48:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Divergence grows amid mNAV compression and a shift in Strategy's funding approach for bitcoin accumulation]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>James Van Straten</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Toyota And Lexus To Streamline Its Line-Ups With Unified Vehicle Architecture]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=354177</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/354177/toyota-lexus-to-streamline-with-unified-vehicle-architecture/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T08:33:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Toyota and Lexus have been developing standalone EVs and ICE vehicles on separate platforms since the introduction of its first electrified models. However, both the companies, have announced plans to streamline their electric vehicle (EV) and internal combustion engine (ICE) lineups. Instead of producing separate models for each powertrain type, the automakers will offer multiple […]
The post Toyota And Lexus To Streamline Its Line-Ups With Unified Vehicle Architecture appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Keran</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sui validators vote on $162M Cetus recovery plan to restore user funds]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/cetus-protocol-vote-recover-frozen-funds</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/cetus-protocol-vote-recover-frozen-funds?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss%3FREFRESH1635339232122&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T08:30:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sui-based decentralized exchange Cetus may be one step closer to recovering funds lost in a recent exploit, pending the outcome of a community governance vote scheduled to end June 3.
Cetus was exploited for over $220 million worth of digital assets on May 22. Shortly after the incident, Cetus managed to freeze $162 million of the funds.
In a May 27 post on X, Sui said Cetus had requested a community vote to approve the recovery of the frozen funds. 
“If the community vote is approved, the funds will be recovered from the attacker and held in a multisig trust account until they can be returned to accounts that had positions in Cetus,” the post said.
The vote is part of a broader recovery plan that includes using Cetus’s treasury and securing an emergency loan from the Sui Foundation.  
Sou…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Zoltan Vardai</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[XRP Spot ETF in the U.S. Moves Closer to Reality]]></title>
        <id>80550bef-bd55-4271-8043-f119034bf2fb</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/28/xrp-spot-etf-in-the-us-moves-closer-to-reality"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T08:06:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The SEC is evaluating whether a proposed XRP ETF by WisdomTree offers enough investor protection and safeguards against manipulation.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shaurya Malwa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OnePlus 13s To Fully Embrace AI; Will Feature New Plus Key]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=354150</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/354150/oneplus-13s-to-fully-embrace-ai-will-feature-new-plus-key/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T08:02:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[OnePlus recently announced that it will be going all-in on AI, with the launch of the OnePlus 13s. As part of the embrace, one major change to the phone will be the introduction of the Plus Key, which also serves as the replacement for the long-used Alert Slider.  In essence, the Plus Key is a […]
The post OnePlus 13s To Fully Embrace AI; Will Feature New Plus Key appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Newsdesk</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Metaplanet issues $50M in new debt to buy more Bitcoin]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/metaplanet-raises-50m-zero-interest-bonds-bitcoin-purchase</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/metaplanet-raises-50m-zero-interest-bonds-bitcoin-purchase?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss%3FREFRESH1635339232122&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T07:55:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Japanese investment company Metaplanet is raising $50 million through a private placement of zero-interest bonds as part of its strategy to increase its Bitcoin exposure. 
In a May 28 announcement, the company said it was raising $50 million through bonds. The bonds are issued in $1.25 million denominations and carry no interest. Investors will not receive regular payments, with any potential profit expected to come from the bonds’ redemption value.
Evo Fund, a Cayman Islands-based investment firm, will be the sole bondholder. The investment company has been Metaplanet’s primary backer for its Bitcoin acquisition strategy, subscribing to multiple rounds of Metaplanet’s zero-interest bonds, providing capital for its Bitcoin (BTC) buys.
The bonds are unsecured and not guaranteed, with neithe…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Ezra Reguerra</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Spot ETFs Pull in $5.77B in May, Their Best Performance Since November]]></title>
        <id>06b5d5e2-ab27-4183-bea5-80fdadb01349</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/28/bitcoin-spot-etfs-pull-in-usd5-77b-in-may-their-best-performance-since-november"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T07:45:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin's spot price recently reached record highs above $110,000.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Omkar Godbole</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sony WF-C710N Lightning Review: Bass For Your Buck]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=353657</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/353657/sony-wf-c710n-lightning-review-bass-for-your-buck/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T07:42:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Sony WF-C710N TWS earbuds launched a few months ago and are the successor to the WF-C700N. Designed as a budget-friendly option, the WF-C710N features a few upgrades from its older counterpart, namely improved ANC and longer battery life. Given that these aren’t Sony’s top-of-the-line offering, one should not expect them to be particularly mindblowing. […]
The post Sony WF-C710N Lightning Review: Bass For Your Buck appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nurul Kamil</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[vivo X Fold5 Gets Certified By SIRIM On Its Way To Launch]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=354162</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/354162/vivo-x-fold5-sirim/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T07:28:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[vivo is said to introduce its next flagship foldable, the X Fold5, some time in the next few months, with a tentative launch window in July. While the company has not announced anything concrete yet, the upcoming foldable has made an appearance on the SIRIM database, indicating that it will be coming here soon after […]
The post vivo X Fold5 Gets Certified By SIRIM On Its Way To Launch appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ikmal Rozlan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Are Monero Traders Buying The Dip? XMR Futures Open Interest Surges as Price Falls By Nearly $100 in 3 Days]]></title>
        <id>b9147f16-dc3e-4f8f-9a10-a1b19b807b2b</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/28/are-xmr-traders-buying-the-dip-monero-futures-open-interest-surges-as-price-falls-by-nearly-usd100-in-3-days"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T07:12:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The price drop follows a meteoric rally from $165 to $420.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Omkar Godbole</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why are 2025/05/28 and 2025-05-28 different days in JavaScript?]]></title>
        <id>https://brandondong.github.io/blog/javascript_dates/</id>
        <link href="https://brandondong.github.io/blog/javascript_dates/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T07:09:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto czar Sacks says US could possibly ‘acquire more Bitcoin’]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/david-sacks-us-potentially-acquire-more-bitcoin</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/david-sacks-us-potentially-acquire-more-bitcoin?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss%3FREFRESH1635339232122&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T06:21:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[White House AI and crypto czar David Sacks says the US could buy more Bitcoin if the government can fund the purchase in a “budget-neutral” way without a tax or adding to the growing national debt.
Sacks told Gemini co-founders Cameron and Tyler Winklevoss during a May 27 fireside chat at the Bitcoin 2025 conference that while he “can’t promise anything,” a pathway does exist for the government to buy more Bitcoin (BTC).
However, it would require convincing Commerce Secretary Howard Lutnick or Treasury Secretary Scott Besson to OK the buy and fund it “without a new tax or adding to the debt,” Sacks said, adding that “maybe by finding the money from some other program that’s not using it — then we could potentially acquire more Bitcoin.”
David Sacks said the US could buy more Bitcoin, but h…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Stephen Katte</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Australian regulator takes former Blockchain Global director to court]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/australian-regulator-legal-action-former-blockchain-global-director</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/australian-regulator-legal-action-former-blockchain-global-director?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss%3FREFRESH1635339232122&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T06:16:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Australia’s markets regulator has filed civil proceedings against Liang “Allan” Guo, the former director of Blockchain Global. 
Guo will face the court on “allegations relating to multiple breaches of his directors’ duties,” the Australian Securities and Investments Commission said in a May 28 press release.
ASIC alleged Guo made multiple breaches of directors’ duties relating to his dealings with ACX Exchange customer funds, and claimed he made false and misleading statements about those dealings and failed to maintain proper books and records. 
The now-liquidated Blockchain Global operated the ACX Exchange from mid-2016 until December 2019, when it collapsed as customers could no longer withdraw their assets. 
During liquidator’s examinations in 2022, the courts were told that ACX exchan…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Martin Young</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Altcoin ‘wildfire’ inbound as trader shuts down bear market fears]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/altcoin-season-sparks-crypto-trader-shuts-down-bear-market-fears</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/altcoin-season-sparks-crypto-trader-shuts-down-bear-market-fears?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss%3FREFRESH1635339232122&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T06:08:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A crypto trader has pushed back against claims that altcoin season is already over, arguing that it hasn’t even started yet, as many tokens are still near their local price bottoms.
“I don’t understand why people start claiming that a bear market is around the corner,” MN Trading Capital founder Michaël van de Poppe said in a May 28 X post.
Calls for altcoin season mount
“They are literally on the bottom,” van de Poppe added before stating that the “final easy 12-24 months are coming.” While many altcoins have posted gains over the past 30 days, they remain below their levels from the market uptrend until US President Donald Trump’s inauguration in January.
Solana (SOL) posted 17.84% gains over the past 30 days, trading at $175.17, but is still down 32% since Jan. 19, according to CoinMark…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Ciaran Lyons</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sui Network Steps in to Compensate Cetus Losses in Full After $223M Exploit]]></title>
        <id>30ac7fbc-8a4a-491e-b202-fa2fbcd85c68</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/28/sui-network-steps-in-to-compensate-cetus-losses-in-full-after-223m-exploit"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T06:04:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Sui Foundation has extended a loan to Cetus to fully reimburse affected users, with repayment contingent on an upcoming on-chain community vote.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shaurya Malwa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[IMF says El Salvador to make ‘efforts’ to stop Bitcoin buys with $120M payments deal]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/imf-el-salvador-efforts-stop-bitcoin-buys-120m-payments-deal</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/imf-el-salvador-efforts-stop-bitcoin-buys-120m-payments-deal?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss%3FREFRESH1635339232122&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T06:01:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The International Monetary Fund said it has reached an agreement with El Salvador to pay the country $120 million following an initial review of its $1.4 billion loan agreement struck last year.
The IMF said on May 27 that as part of the deal, El Salvador will need to fulfill its prior obligations around limiting further government involvement in Bitcoin (BTC), and it will have to cease its involvement in the Chivo wallet by the end of July.
“On Bitcoin, efforts will continue to ensure that the total amount of Bitcoin held across all government-owned wallets remains unchanged,” the global lender said.
The planned payout, subject to IMF executive board approval, is part of a larger $1.4 billion, 40-month loan deal struck in December, which saw El Salvador agree to confine its Bitcoin ambiti…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Tarang Khaitan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Traders Eye New Highs by End of Summer; Ether Rises 3% on Treasury Optimism]]></title>
        <id>6e04b4fe-7b4e-4dfa-adcc-e2cd2140bafd</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/28/bitcoin-traders-eye-new-highs-by-end-of-summer-ether-rises-3-on-treasury-optimism"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T05:58:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With volatility elevated ahead of an upcoming Bitcoin conference, investors eye a summer breakout as ETH rises and BTC consolidates near $110,000.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shaurya Malwa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Uptrend at Risk of Breakdown Ahead of Nvidia Earnings, Fed Minutes]]></title>
        <id>46d2bfbb-d26c-403c-a39d-e0b23568e2da</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/28/bitcoin-uptrend-at-risk-ahead-of-nvda-earnings-fed-minutes-xrp-holds-key-support-amid-xrpfi-narrative"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T05:35:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Federal Reserve's minutes and Nvidia's earnings are key events that could influence market movements.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Omkar Godbole</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DWARF as a Shared Reverse Engineering Format]]></title>
        <id>https://lief.re/blog/2025-05-27-dwarf-editor/</id>
        <link href="https://lief.re/blog/2025-05-27-dwarf-editor/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T05:34:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CFTC’s Goldsmith Romero says commissioner exodus ‘not a great situation’]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/goldsmith-romero-cf-exodus-not-a-great-situation</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/goldsmith-romero-cf-exodus-not-a-great-situation?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss%3FREFRESH1635339232122&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T05:10:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Outgoing US Commodity Futures Trading Commission commissioner Christy Goldsmith Romero says the exodus of the agency’s top brass is “not a great situation” for crypto regulations.
The CFTC could be headed by just one commissioner once the other four depart later this year, which Goldsmith Romero said in a May 27 interview at the Brookings Institution will make creating regulations harder because it leaves a less diverse pool of opinions. 
“I think it’s not a great situation if you have one person who’s determining what the rules should be; you lose the benefit of this back-and-forth, this push-and-pull as to what’s the right thing to do,” she said.
“I’ve always wanted to hear from my fellow commissioners about what makes sense to them, and there are many things that they’ve convinced me of…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Stephen Katte</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trump’s CFTC pick Quintenz discloses crypto links, $3.4M assets]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/trump-cftc-pick-quintenz-discloses-crypto-links-assets</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/trump-cftc-pick-quintenz-discloses-crypto-links-assets?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss%3FREFRESH1635339232122&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T05:01:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[US President Donald Trump’s pick to chair the Commodity Futures Trading Commission has disclosed millions of dollars worth of assets, along with his various ties to crypto-related organizations.
In paperwork released by the US Office of Government Ethics on May 25, Brian Quintenz disclosed his key positions in crypto and market firms that would directly relate to the CFTC’s regulatory priorities and disclosed assets worth at least $3.4 million, according to a May 27 Bloomberg report. 
Quintenz was a CFTC commissioner from 2017 to 2021 and is currently the global head of crypto policy at Andreessen Horowitz, a position he said he will step down from if the Senate confirms him as CFTC chair. 
He holds an interest in three AH Capital Management investment funds, CNK Fund III, CNK Seed 1 Fund,…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Martin Young</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rep. Steil urges restraint on adding ‘non-germane items’ to crypto bills]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/steil-wants-lawmakers-restrain-adding-non-relevant-items-crypto-bills</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/steil-wants-lawmakers-restrain-adding-non-relevant-items-crypto-bills?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss%3FREFRESH1635339232122&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T04:46:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[US Representative Bryan Steil wants lawmakers to stop adding “non-germane items” into two key crypto bills, claiming that doing so is slowing the implementation of a regulatory framework for the industry.
“Individuals, when they see legislation that’s going to move forward, want to attach non-germane items to any bill that’s going to move through and be signed into law,” Steil, a Republican from Wisconsin who chairs the House Financial Services Subcommittee on crypto, told Cointelegraph at the Bitcoin 2025 conference in Las Vegas on May 27.
“We have to restrain ourselves from that instinct and attempt by our colleagues — both sides of the aisle,” he added.
Congress’s biggest crypto backers hope to pass the stablecoin-regulating Guiding and Establishing National Innovation for US Stablecoin…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Brayden Lindrea</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Jack Dorsey’s Block to bring Bitcoin payments to Square by 2026]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/block-inc-bitcoin-payments-square-2026</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/block-inc-bitcoin-payments-square-2026?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss%3FREFRESH1635339232122&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T03:21:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jack Dorsey’s financial services firm Block, Inc. will launch Bitcoin payments on Square, its payments processing arm, with a rollout to begin later this year before a full launch in 2026.
The company announced the plan at the Bitcoin 2025 conference in Las Vegas on May 27, where Block demonstrated the feature at the BTC Inc. merchandise store.
Merchants will be able to accept Bitcoin (BTC) payments through existing Square hardware using the Lightning Network, Bitcoin’s faster, lower-cost layer-2 scaling network. 
“Merchants can choose to hold the Bitcoin, or auto-convert it to fiat in real-time,” Dorsey said on X. 
The company said it expects to start rolling out in the second half of 2025, reaching all eligible Square sellers by 2026, subject to regulatory approvals. 
The move builds on …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Martin Young</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin’s ‘aggressive leg higher’ in Q3 still up in the air: Analyst]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-price-aggressive-leg-q3-uncertain-bitfinex-analysts</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-price-aggressive-leg-q3-uncertain-bitfinex-analysts?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss%3FREFRESH1635339232122&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T03:04:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin’s recent all-time high of $111,970 has sparked optimism among crypto market participants, but whether that carries through into the third quarter of this year remains uncertain, analysts say.
“The coming weeks will likely determine whether Bitcoinʼs latest breakout was a local high or the prelude to a more aggressive leg higher in Q3,” Bitfinex analysts said in a May 28 markets note.
Consolidation or mild retracement may “be healthy”
Bitcoin (BTC) reached new all-time highs of $111,970 on May 22; however, Bitfinex analysts say a continued price increase alone won’t necessarily confirm the uptrend heading into the next quarter. 
“A period of consolidation or mild retracement would not only be healthy but also provide a more sustainable foundation for the next leg higher,” the analys…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Ciaran Lyons</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Show HN: AutoThink – Boosts local LLM performance with adaptive reasoning]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=44112326</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=44112326"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T02:39:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Using Postgres pg_test_fsync tool for testing low latency writes]]></title>
        <id>https://tanelpoder.com/posts/using-pg-test-fsync-for-testing-low-latency-writes/</id>
        <link href="https://tanelpoder.com/posts/using-pg-test-fsync-for-testing-low-latency-writes/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T02:15:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Real-world assets could revitalize dying NFT lending market: DappRadar]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/real-world-assets-revitalize-dying-nft-lending-dappradar</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/real-world-assets-revitalize-dying-nft-lending-dappradar?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss%3FREFRESH1635339232122&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T02:11:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Real-world assets linking up with non-fungible tokens (NFTs) is one of a few key catalysts that could reignite the waning NFT lending sector, which is suffering from a collapse in volumes and user activity, says blockchain analytics platform DappRadar.
Volumes in the NFT lending market, which allows NFT holders to take out a loan against their token, have dropped 97% from a peak of around $1 billion in January 2024 to $50 million in May, DappRadar analyst Sara Gherghelas said in a May 27 report.
Gherghelas said for NFT lending to “move beyond survival mode,” it needs “new catalysts” to reignite the sector, such as real-world asset NFTs, like tokenized real estate or yield-bearing assets that could unlock more stable, trusted collateral sources.
“So far, 2025 has not delivered a compelling …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Stephen Katte</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Asia Morning Briefing: Bitcoin Becomes ‘Generational Asset’ as Speculators Ditch Rolexes]]></title>
        <id>3bdfdfa2-66d8-46b4-b7c7-362d6d9a1206</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/27/asia-morning-briefing-bitcoin-becomes-generational-asset-as-speculators-ditch-rolexes"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T01:33:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[PLUS: ETH's rally might be in its early stages, but there are a few headwinds holding it back]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>AI Boost</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Donald Trump Jr. Says Getting ‘Debanked, De-Insured, De-Everything’ Orange-Pilled Him]]></title>
        <id>af40f189-a0b6-47f0-a70a-10e1d3d04350</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2025/05/27/donald-trump-jr-says-getting-debanked-de-insured-de-everything-orange-pilled-him"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T01:08:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The eldest son of U.S. President Donald Trump said his family’s interest in crypto was, at least at first, “a product of necessity.”]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cheyenne Ligon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nasdaq files for 21Shares Sui ETF, kicking off SEC review]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/nasdaq-files-21-shares-sui-etf-sec-review</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/nasdaq-files-21-shares-sui-etf-sec-review?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss%3FREFRESH1635339232122&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T01:05:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nasdaq has filed for crypto asset manager 21Shares to list a spot Sui exchange-traded fund (ETF) in the US, initiating the Securities and Exchange Commission’s review process.
The stock market’s May 23 19b-4 filing, which asks the SEC to list the 21Shares SUI ETF, follows 21Shares’ April 30 submission of its S-1 registration statement to the SEC, which asked the regulator to approve trading of the proposed fund.
Both regulatory filings are needed for the Sui (SUI) tracking fund to go live, with the 19b-4 filing kicking off the SEC’s review process. The agency must decide whether to accept, reject or delay the application within 45 days and it can delay its decision multiple times, for a maximum review period of 240 days.
The SEC must decide on 21Shares’ application by Jan. 18, 2026, at the…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Brayden Lindrea</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Everyone’s looking to get in on vibe coding — and Google is no different with Stitch, its follow-up to Jules]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3009114</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/everyones-looking-to-get-in-on-vibe-coding-and-google-is-no-different-with-stitch-its-follow-up-to-jules/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T00:49:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google is looking to compete in vibe coding with Stitch, which designs user interfaces (UIs) with one prompt.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Taryn Plumb</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A privilege escalation from Chrome extensions (2023)]]></title>
        <id>https://0x44.xyz/blog/cve-2023-4369/</id>
        <link href="https://0x44.xyz/blog/cve-2023-4369/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T00:48:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spott’s AI-native recruiting platform scores $3.2M to end hiring software chaos]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3009108</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/spotts-ai-native-recruiting-platform-scores-3-2m-to-end-hiring-software-chaos/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T00:07:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Spott secures $3.2 million in funding to build an all-in-one AI-native recruitment platform that automates workflows and eliminates tech fragmentation for recruitment agencies seeking to focus on high-value activities.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Nuñez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Look Ma, No Bubbles: Designing a Low-Latency Megakernel for Llama-1B]]></title>
        <id>https://hazyresearch.stanford.edu/blog/2025-05-27-no-bubbles</id>
        <link href="https://hazyresearch.stanford.edu/blog/2025-05-27-no-bubbles"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T00:01:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Negotiating PoE+ Power in the Pre‑Boot Environment]]></title>
        <id>https://roderickkhan.com/posts/2025-05-16-poe-uefi-solution</id>
        <link href="https://roderickkhan.com/posts/2025-05-16-poe-uefi-solution"/>
        <updated>2025-05-27T23:45:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Anthropic debuts Claude conversational voice mode on mobile that searches your Google Docs, Drive, Calendar]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3009105</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/anthropic-debuts-conversational-voice-mode-for-claude-mobile-apps/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-27T23:23:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With the rollout of voice mode, Anthropic continues to broaden Claude's functionality and accessibility to all users.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carl Franzen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sen. Lummis on Push for Stablecoin Bill: ‘I Had No Idea How Hard This Was Going to Be’]]></title>
        <id>4e014c49-2796-42b1-ab27-e9fbd45be515</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2025/05/27/sen-lummis-on-push-for-stablecoin-bill-i-had-no-idea-how-hard-this-was-going-to-be"/>
        <updated>2025-05-27T23:18:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Wyoming Republican said she’s concerned the Senate Banking Committee has lost the “muscle memory” needed to actually legislate.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cheyenne Ligon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OpenTPU: Open-Source Reimplementation of Google Tensor Processing Unit (TPU)]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/UCSBarchlab/OpenTPU</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/UCSBarchlab/OpenTPU"/>
        <updated>2025-05-27T23:10:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ether price target shifts to $3K after SharpLink adopts ETH ‘treasury strategy’]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/ethereum-price-target-shifts-to-3k-after-sharplink-adopts-eth-treasury-strategy</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/ethereum-price-target-shifts-to-3k-after-sharplink-adopts-eth-treasury-strategy?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss%3FREFRESH1635339232122&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-27T22:34:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Key takeaways:

SharpLink Gaming establishes the first ETH treasury, backed by Ethereum co-founder Joe Lubin. SharpLink will invest $425 million to acquire 120,000 ETH. 

Ethereum futures open interest hits an all-time high of $36.1 billion, with ETH price climbing 4.5% on the daily chart. 

Nasdaq-listed SharpLink Gaming (SBET) announced a $425 million private investment in public equity (PIPE), acquiring approximately 69.1 million shares at $6.15 each to establish the first Nasdaq-listed Ethereum treasury company.
Spearheaded by Ethereum co-founder Joe Lubin, this move mirrors Strategy’s (MSTR) successful Bitcoin treasury strategy, which has yielded over $8.2 billion in gains in 2025, by leveraging stock and bond sales to acquire Bitcoin (BTC).
Former Ethereum core developer and contribu…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Biraajmaan Tamuly</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Best AWS Services to Deploy Front-End Applications in 2025]]></title>
        <id>68363d68d27e47d637cc580b</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/best-aws-services-for-frontend-deployment/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-27T22:32:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As front-end development evolves, finding the right deployment service is more important than ever. Amazon Web Services (AWS), a cloud-based service, offers a number of helpful tools and platforms for hosting modern front-end applications. Although i...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ijeoma Igboagu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Third individual arrested in NYC crypto torture and kidnapping case]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/third-suspect-arrested-in-nyc-crypto-torture-case</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/third-suspect-arrested-in-nyc-crypto-torture-case?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss%3FREFRESH1635339232122&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-27T22:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A third individual, suspected of being connected to the recent kidnapping, torture and attempted extortion of an Italian tourist in New York City, surrendered to law enforcement on May 27.
33-year-old William Duplessie was taken into custody by the New York Police Department (NYPD) and will be charged with “kidnapping and false imprisonment of an associate,” NYPD Commissioner Jessica Tisch said.
The incident comes amid a string of kidnappings and ransom attempts targeting crypto investors and their loved ones, prompting additional security measures from investors and industry executives.
According to reporting from The New York Times, Duplessie and crypto investor John Woeltz, who was previously arrested by police in connection with the case, both had connections to an NYC-based crypto hed…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Vince Quill</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security leaders lose visibility as consultants deploy shadow AI copilots to stay employed]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008925</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/security/shadow-ai-is-consultings-survival-strategy-in-the-genai-era/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-27T22:15:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fearing sweeping layoffs driven by AI and automation, elite consultants and high performers are turning to shadow AI for a competitive edge.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Louis Columbus</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Here’s what happened in crypto today]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/what-happened-in-crypto-today</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/what-happened-in-crypto-today?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss%3FREFRESH1635339232122&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-27T22:04:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today in crypto, Representative Bryan Steil tells Cointelegraph he wants lawmakers to stop adding non-relevant clauses into crypto bills, Trump Media confirmed a capital raise to buy Bitcoin after initially denying reports it would, and Circle announced its initial public offering on the New York Stock Exchange.
Rep. Steil wants restraint on crypto bill additions
Republican Representative Bryan Steil told Cointelegraph on May 27 that he wants lawmakers to stop adding what he considers are non-relevant clauses into two key crypto bills, claiming that doing so is slowing the implementation of a regulatory framework for the industry.
“Individuals, when they see legislation that’s going to move forward, want to attach non-germane items to any bill that’s going to move through and be signed int…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Cointelegraph</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Growing BTC reserve requires Congressional legislation — VanEck exec]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/btc-reserve-requires-congressional-legislation</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/btc-reserve-requires-congressional-legislation?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss%3FREFRESH1635339232122&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-27T21:52:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Building a permanent US strategic Bitcoin reserve would likely require targeted legislation rather than executive action, according to VanEck’s head of digital assets, Matthew Sigel. Speaking at Bitcoin 2025 in Las Vegas, Sigel said the most viable path forward may involve inserting Bitcoin mining incentives into the congressional budget reconciliation process.
According to Sigel, the most effective path to growing a US strategic Bitcoin reserve would be through targeted amendments to congressional budget legislation. These could include tax credits for mining companies that use methane gas and other incentives aimed at encouraging miners to share a portion of their mined BTC with the federal government. 
He argued that such an approach would allow the reserve to grow organically over time…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Vince Quill</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mustard Watches (1990)]]></title>
        <id>https://girard.perso.math.cnrs.fr/mustard/article.html</id>
        <link href="https://girard.perso.math.cnrs.fr/mustard/article.html"/>
        <updated>2025-05-27T21:48:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trump supports bill to buy 1 million BTC — Senator Lummis]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/president-trump-supports-bitcoin-bill-senator-lummis</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/president-trump-supports-bitcoin-bill-senator-lummis?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss%3FREFRESH1635339232122&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-27T21:38:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[US President Donald Trump supports the BITCOIN Act and has a team of experts in the White House working to roll out landmark digital asset legislation in the coming weeks, according to Wyoming Senator Cynthia Lummis. 
Speaking at the Bitcoin 2025 conference in Las Vegas, Nevada, Lummis said she is bringing the BITCOIN ACT to the “attention of the American people and the world,” adding that, “President Trump supports the bill.”
In March, Lummis reintroduced the BITCOIN Act — landmark legislation that directs the US government to acquire 1 million Bitcoin (BTC) over five years. The acquisitions would be financed using existing funds within the Federal Reserve System and the Treasury Department. 
As Cointelegraph reported, the Trump administration has reiterated the need to use “budget-neutra…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Sam Bourgi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[IMF Says 'Efforts Will Continue' to Ensure El Salvador Doesn't Accumulate More BTC]]></title>
        <id>8d143099-8963-43dd-8726-4c9137d7092d</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2025/05/27/imf-says-efforts-will-continue-to-ensure-el-salvador-doesn-t-accumulate-more-btc"/>
        <updated>2025-05-27T21:36:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[El Salvador has kept purchasing bitcoin, but the IMF seems unfazed.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tom Carreras</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Solana Network Is Now Live on MetaMask]]></title>
        <id>877b0eae-e56b-4a47-827c-511acb4f3b8f</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/tech/2025/05/27/the-solana-network-is-now-live-on-metamask"/>
        <updated>2025-05-27T21:30:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It's the first time that MetaMask integrates a non-EVM network.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tom Carreras</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Selling Bitcoin is like playing in a ‘bad house-rate casino’ — Adam Back]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/selling-bitcoin-like-playing-bad-house-rate-casino-adam-back</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/selling-bitcoin-like-playing-bad-house-rate-casino-adam-back?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss%3FREFRESH1635339232122&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-27T21:24:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Selling Bitcoin is like “playing in a really bad house-rate casino,” according to Adam Back, CEO of Blockstream and one of Bitcoin’s earliest adopters. In a recent interview with Bitcoin financial services firm Unchained, Back said the odds are stacked against traders trying to time the market.
Back came to this conclusion in the early days of Bitcoin, he said, when the price “was going up basically exponentially but it [was] extremely volatile.”
“So [...] if you see something that’s going up exponentially but with volatility, if you sell it to time the market a bit falling, the odds are against you,” Back said, adding:
“The trend line is up and to the right, exponential, and so there’s extremely bad trading odds attached to selling because you’re really hoping that it falls.”
Adam Back du…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Christopher Tepedino</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OKX Global General Counsel Is Latest Legal Exec to Leave the Exchange]]></title>
        <id>633a6f62-6d22-4b53-9232-7492f2bf883d</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2025/05/27/okx-global-general-counsel-gone-as-exchange-s-legal-compliance-purge-continues"/>
        <updated>2025-05-27T20:53:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The new chief legal officer, Linda Lacewell, is said to be restructuring the firm's legal and compliance divisions, according to a source familiar with the situation.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ian Allison</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Show HN: My LLM CLI tool can run tools now, from Python code or plugins]]></title>
        <id>https://simonwillison.net/2025/May/27/llm-tools/</id>
        <link href="https://simonwillison.net/2025/May/27/llm-tools/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-27T20:53:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Maple Finance, FalconX secure Bitcoin-backed loans from Cantor Fitzgerald — Report]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/maple-finance-falconx-secure-bitcoin-backed-loans-from-cantor-fitzgerald-report</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/maple-finance-falconx-secure-bitcoin-backed-loans-from-cantor-fitzgerald-report?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss%3FREFRESH1635339232122&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-27T20:30:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Wall Street financial firm Cantor Fitzgerald has closed its first Bitcoin lending deal nearly a year after announcing its crypto lending services.
According to a May 27 Bloomberg report, Cantor provided Bitcoin-backed loans to FalconX and Maple Finance. FalconX, a digital asset broker, said it secured a facility worth over $100 million as part of a “broader credit framework,” while Maple Finance reportedly closed the first tranche of an agreement with Cantor.
The service allows companies holding Bitcoin to borrow funds and use the cryptocurrency as collateral, providing a way to unlock liquidity without selling their BTC holdings. Cantor announced its Bitcoin financing business with an initial capital of $2 billion in July 2024, targeting institutional investors seeking to leverage their B…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Ana Paula Pereira</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[In Vietnam, an unlikely outpost for Chicano culture]]></title>
        <id>https://www.latimes.com/world-nation/story/2025-05-27/chicano-culture-vietnam</id>
        <link href="https://www.latimes.com/world-nation/story/2025-05-27/chicano-culture-vietnam"/>
        <updated>2025-05-27T20:09:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Square Pilots Real-Time Bitcoin Payments in Vegas, Plans Full Availability to Customers in 2026]]></title>
        <id>e8e1111b-4022-4d8e-8b3f-054d29702ccf</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/tech/2025/05/27/square-pilots-real-time-bitcoin-payments-in-vegas-plans-full-availability-to-customers-in-2026"/>
        <updated>2025-05-27T20:05:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The feature would still need regulatory approval in order to be made available to all customers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Helene Braun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Third Arrest Made in Manhattan Bitcoin Kidnapping, Torture Case]]></title>
        <id>3a087997-0aca-4f4d-8637-34c5ac7bbab5</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2025/05/27/third-arrest-made-in-manhattan-bitcoin-kidnapping-torture-case"/>
        <updated>2025-05-27T19:33:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The incident, involving alleged abduction and abuse for nearly three weeks, comes amid a growing trend of physical attacks on cryptocurrency users.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Francisco Rodrigues</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mistral launches API for building AI agents that run Python, generate images, perform RAG and more]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3009083</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/mistral-launches-api-for-building-ai-agents-that-run-python-generate-images-perform-rag-and-more/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-27T18:52:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For professionals like the Lead AI Engineer or Senior AI Engineer, the Mistral Agents API represents a powerful addition to their AI toolkit.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carl Franzen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Steak n’ Shake COO Says Bitcoin Payments Cut Processing Fees in Half]]></title>
        <id>a8c010d3-3217-42a6-93e7-d1f067a9b224</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/27/steak-n-shake-coo-says-bitcoin-payments-cut-processing-fees-in-half"/>
        <updated>2025-05-27T18:38:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The American fast-food chain started accepting bitcoin payments earlier this month. Next step: robo taxies, cyber chefs, and drones.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cheyenne Ligon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Build a Rocket Boy drops trailer detailing MindsEye’s blend of Grand Theft Auto and AI robot combat]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3009068</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/games/build-a-rocket-boy-drops-trailer-detailing-mindseyes-blend-of-grand-theft-auto-and-ai-robot-combat/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-27T18:21:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[IOI Partners and Build a Rocket Boy dropped a new trailer on MindsEye, a new title coming on June 10 from the co-creator of Grand Theft Auto V.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dean Takahashi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MARA’s Fred Thiel Says U.S. Should Start Mining Bitcoin to Fill Strategic Reserve]]></title>
        <id>bd4ed8d7-8332-46b7-8194-2dee8c8b1697</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/27/maras-fred-thiel-says-us-should-start-mining-bitcoin-to-fill-strategic-reserve"/>
        <updated>2025-05-27T18:08:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“I think it’s critical, the U.S. making a statement that we’re going to have a strategic reserve is an empty statement unless you start putting stuff into it," he said.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cheyenne Ligon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Running GPT-2 in WebGL: Rediscovering the Lost Art of GPU Shader Programming]]></title>
        <id>https://nathan.rs/posts/gpu-shader-programming/</id>
        <link href="https://nathan.rs/posts/gpu-shader-programming/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-27T18:02:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Salesforce’s $8B acquisition of Informatica means for enterprise data and AI]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3009056</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/data-infrastructure/what-salesforces-8b-acquisition-of-informatica-means-for-enterprise-data-and-ai/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-27T17:20:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Industry analysts explain how Salesforce's $8 billion Informatica acquisition will transform enterprise data management and accelerate agentic AI adoption .]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sean Michael Kerner</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[XRP Bounces Back as Bulls Defend Key Technical Support]]></title>
        <id>5046f1f3-a5d2-4aa0-9ec8-77f339ad8147</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/27/xrp-bounces-back-as-bulls-defend-key-technical-support"/>
        <updated>2025-05-27T17:16:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Market cap swings nearly $4B as XRP weathers capital outflows, holding firm above 50-day SMA despite global economic headwinds.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>AI Boost</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Launch HN: Relace (YC W23) – Models for fast and reliable codegen]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=44108206</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=44108206"/>
        <updated>2025-05-27T15:59:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Square Theory]]></title>
        <id>https://aaronson.org/blog/square-theory</id>
        <link href="https://aaronson.org/blog/square-theory"/>
        <updated>2025-05-27T15:33:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pyrefly vs. Ty: Comparing Python's two new Rust-based type checkers]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.edward-li.com/tech/comparing-pyrefly-vs-ty/</id>
        <link href="https://blog.edward-li.com/tech/comparing-pyrefly-vs-ty/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-27T15:01:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A new sodium metal fuel cell could help clean up transportation]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1117456</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/05/27/1117456/sodium-fuel-cell/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-27T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new type of fuel cell that runs on sodium metal could one day help clean up sectors where it’s difficult to replace fossil fuels, like rail, regional aviation, and short-distance shipping. The device represents a departure from technologies like lithium-based batteries and is more similar conceptually to hydrogen fuel cell systems.  The sodium-air fuel…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Casey Crownhart</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use Your Raspberry Pi Headlessly with VS Code and SSH (No Monitor Needed)]]></title>
        <id>6835cf3101fd0876c3c66de0</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-your-raspberry-pi-headlessly-with-vs-code-and-ssh/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-27T14:41:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Raspberry Pi is a portable computer with an onboard processor that fits comfortably in the palm of your hand. Compared with general purpose computers, it’s an affordable option developed by the Raspberry Pi Foundation. The Raspberry Pi Model B wa...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Josiah Adesola</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Building customer-centric convenience]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1116819</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/05/27/1116819/building-customer-centric-convenience/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-27T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the U.S., two-thirds of the country’s 150,000 convenience stores are run by independent operators. Mom-and-pop shops, powered by personal relationships and local knowledge, are the backbone of the convenience sector. These neighborhood operators have long lacked the resources needed to compete with larger chains when it comes to technology, operations, and customer loyalty programs. …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>MIT Technology Review Insights</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Download: nuclear-powered AI, and a short history of creativity]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1117453</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/05/27/1117453/the-download-nuclear-powered-ai-and-a-short-history-of-creativity/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-27T12:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is today’s edition of The Download, our weekday newsletter that provides a daily dose of what’s going on in the world of technology. Can nuclear power really fuel the rise of AI? In the AI arms race, all the major players say they want to go nuclear. Over the past year, the likes of Meta, Amazon,…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rhiannon Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How a hawk learned to use traffic signals to hunt more successfully]]></title>
        <id>https://www.frontiersin.org/news/2025/05/23/street-smarts-hawk-use-traffic-signals-hunting</id>
        <link href="https://www.frontiersin.org/news/2025/05/23/street-smarts-hawk-use-traffic-signals-hunting"/>
        <updated>2025-05-27T11:46:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BGP handling bug causes widespread internet routing instability]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.benjojo.co.uk/post/bgp-attr-40-junos-arista-session-reset-incident</id>
        <link href="https://blog.benjojo.co.uk/post/bgp-attr-40-junos-arista-session-reset-incident"/>
        <updated>2025-05-27T11:15:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[LumoSQL]]></title>
        <id>https://lumosql.org/src/lumosql/doc/trunk/README.md</id>
        <link href="https://lumosql.org/src/lumosql/doc/trunk/README.md"/>
        <updated>2025-05-27T10:39:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Show HN: Lazy Tetris]]></title>
        <id>https://lazytetris.com/</id>
        <link href="https://lazytetris.com/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-27T03:58:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[From disruption to reinvention: How knowledge workers can thrive after AI]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008969</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/from-disruption-to-reinvention-how-knowledge-workers-can-thrive-after-ai/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-26T19:05:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We are beginning a cognitive migration: Away from what AI now does well, and toward a redefinition of what humans are now made for.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gary Grossman, Edelman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Looking for Keys Under the Lamppost]]></title>
        <id>https://www.johndcook.com/blog/2025/05/25/lamppost/</id>
        <link href="https://www.johndcook.com/blog/2025/05/25/lamppost/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-25T21:25:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Windows Registry Adventure #7: Attack surface analysis]]></title>
        <id>https://googleprojectzero.blogspot.com/2025/05/the-windows-registry-adventure-7-attack-surface.html</id>
        <link href="https://googleprojectzero.blogspot.com/2025/05/the-windows-registry-adventure-7-attack-surface.html"/>
        <updated>2025-05-25T20:24:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google’s ‘world-model’ bet: building the AI operating layer before Microsoft captures the UI]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008900</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/googles-world-model-bet-building-the-ai-operating-layer-before-microsoft-captures-the-ui/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-25T17:42:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google doubles down on its ‘world-model’ vision, racing to build an AI operating layer to drive a universal personal assistant with Gemini. Even as Microsoft moves to capture the enterprise UI. Here's what's at stake.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matt Marshall</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Level Design Book]]></title>
        <id>https://book.leveldesignbook.com/</id>
        <link href="https://book.leveldesignbook.com/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-25T11:03:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Ingredients of a Productive Monorepo]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.swgillespie.me/posts/monorepo-ingredients/</id>
        <link href="https://blog.swgillespie.me/posts/monorepo-ingredients/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-25T10:49:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The length of file names in early Unix]]></title>
        <id>https://utcc.utoronto.ca/~cks/space/blog/unix/UnixEarlyFilenameLenghts</id>
        <link href="https://utcc.utoronto.ca/~cks/space/blog/unix/UnixEarlyFilenameLenghts"/>
        <updated>2025-05-25T07:37:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Space Selfie]]></title>
        <id>https://space.crunchlabs.com/</id>
        <link href="https://space.crunchlabs.com/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-25T01:36:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Beyond single-model AI: How architectural design drives reliable multi-agent orchestration]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008888</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/beyond-single-model-ai-how-architectural-design-drives-reliable-multi-agent-orchestration/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-24T22:35:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Successful AI agents require enterprises to orchestrate interactions, manage shared knowledge and plan for failure.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nikhil Gupta, Atlassian</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[There Is No Diffie-Hellman but Elliptic Curve Diffie-Hellman]]></title>
        <id>https://keymaterial.net/2025/05/23/there-is-no-diffie-hellman-but-elliptic-curve-diffie-hellman/</id>
        <link href="https://keymaterial.net/2025/05/23/there-is-no-diffie-hellman-but-elliptic-curve-diffie-hellman/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-24T20:53:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Show HN: Terminal Flower Garden]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/bdavidzhang/flower-garden-cli</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/bdavidzhang/flower-garden-cli"/>
        <updated>2025-05-24T17:25:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Hobby Computer Culture]]></title>
        <id>https://technicshistory.com/2025/05/24/the-hobby-computer-culture/</id>
        <link href="https://technicshistory.com/2025/05/24/the-hobby-computer-culture/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-24T14:33:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OpenAI updates Operator to o3, making its $200 monthly ChatGPT Pro subscription more enticing]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008828</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/openai-updates-operator-to-o3-making-its-200-monthly-chatgpt-subscription-more-enticing/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-23T21:51:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Operator remains a research preview and is accessible only to ChatGPT Pro users. The Responses API version will continue to use GPT-4o.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carl Franzen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The battle to AI-enable the web: NLweb and what enterprises need to know]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008795</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/the-battle-to-ai-enable-the-web-nlweb-and-what-enterprises-need-to-know/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-23T21:05:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft's NLWeb protocol transforms websites into AI-powered apps with conversational interfaces.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sean Michael Kerner</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The 3 biggest bombshells from this week’s AI extravaganza]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008808</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/the-3-biggest-bombshells-from-this-weeks-ai-extravaganza/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-23T20:29:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Enterprises looking to build with AI should find plenty to look forward to with the announcements from Microsoft, Google & Anthropic this week.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nick Mokey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build a Testing Framework for E-Commerce Checkout and Payments]]></title>
        <id>68308f32f4205e3b843cfb37</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-build-a-testing-framework-for-e-commerce-checkout-and-payments/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-23T15:07:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When I first started working on E-commerce applications, I assumed testing checkout flows and payments would be straightforward. My expectation was simple: users select items, provide an address, pay, and receive confirmation. But I quickly learned t...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Venkata Sai Sandeep</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Architecture of Mathematics – And How Developers Can Use it in Code]]></title>
        <id>68308ee8ccde6bc325c82393</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/the-architecture-of-mathematics-and-how-developers-can-use-it-in-code/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-23T15:06:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA["To understand is to perceive patterns." - Isaiah Berlin Math is not just numbers. It is the science of finding complex patterns that shape our world. This means that to truly understand it, we need to see beyond numbers, formulas, and theorems and ...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tiago Capelo Monteiro</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Feature Fridays: dTelecom]]></title>
        <id>682f3eb8646f7c0001399182</id>
        <link href="https://blog.quicknode.com/feature-fridays-dtelecom/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-23T13:37:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[dTelecom is reshaping digital communication with decentralized, AI-powered infrastructure for Web3 developers and businesses.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>QuickNode</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use React 19 in Power Apps PCF Components]]></title>
        <id>6830767c62d9a28c0de11007</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-react-19-in-pcf-components/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-23T13:22:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Power Apps Component Framework – PCF for short – lets you create complex custom components using traditional web development tools like HTML, CSS, and JavaScript. When creating a new PCF project, you can choose from two types of controls: standar...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brandon Wozniewicz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why enterprise RAG systems fail: Google study introduces ‘sufficient context’ solution]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008684</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/why-enterprise-rag-systems-fail-google-study-introduces-sufficient-context-solution/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-23T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google's "sufficient context" helps refine RAG systems, reduce LLM hallucinations, and boost AI reliability for business applications.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ben Dickson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Download: meet Cathy Tie, and Anthropic’s new AI models]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1117399</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/05/23/1117399/the-download-meet-cathy-tie-and-anthropics-new-ai-models/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-23T12:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is today’s edition of The Download, our weekday newsletter that provides a daily dose of what’s going on in the world of technology. Meet Cathy Tie, Bride of “China’s Frankenstein” Since the Chinese biophysicist He Jiankui was released from prison in 2022, he has sought to make a scientific comeback and to repair his reputation after…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rhiannon Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Laid off but not afraid with X-senior Microsoft Dev MacKevin Fey [Podcast #173]]]></title>
        <id>68304756ecdb03ab557f3974</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/laid-off-but-not-afraid-with-x-senior-microsoft-dev-mackevin-fey-podcast-173/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-23T10:00:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On this week's episode of the podcast, freeCodeCamp founder Quincy Larson interviews MacKevin Fey. He just got laid off last week from his senior engineering role at Microsoft. We talk about: How Mack's approaching the job search after being laid of...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The FDA plans to limit access to covid vaccines. Here’s why that’s not all bad.]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1117329</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/05/23/1117329/fda-limit-access-covid-vaccines/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-23T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This week, two new leaders at the US Food and Drug Administration announced plans to limit access to covid vaccines, arguing that there is not much evidence to support the value of annual shots in healthy people. New vaccines will be made available only to the people who are most vulnerable—namely, those over 65 and…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jessica Hamzelou</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meet Cathy Tie, Bride of “China’s Frankenstein”]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1117373</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/05/23/1117373/cathy-tie-he-jiankui-china-crispr-x-twitter-feed/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-23T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Since the Chinese biophysicist He Jiankui was released from prison in 2022, he has sought to make a scientific comeback and to repair his reputation after a three-year incarceration for illegally creating the world’s first gene-edited children.  While he has bounced between cities, jobs, and meetings with investors, one area of visible success on his…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Caiwei Chen, Antonio Regalado</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[After GPT-4o backlash, researchers benchmark models on moral endorsement—find sycophancy persists across the board]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008691</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/after-gpt-4o-backlash-researchers-benchmark-models-on-moral-endorsement-find-sycophancy-persists-across-the-board/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-22T23:46:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new benchmark can test how much LLMs become sycophants, and found that GPT-4o was the most sycophantic of the models tested.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Emilia David</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn Vue.js in This Beginner's Course]]></title>
        <id>682f84537a13a40bfa336307</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-vuejs-in-this-beginners-course/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-22T20:08:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you’ve been meaning to add Vue.js to your front-end toolbelt, today’s your day. We just published a full, 6-hour Vue 3 course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel. Instructor Bhrugen Patel walks you through everything you need to build modern, ...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Anthropic faces backlash to Claude 4 Opus behavior that contacts authorities, press if it thinks you’re doing something ‘egregiously immoral’]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008672</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/anthropic-faces-backlash-to-claude-4-opus-behavior-that-contacts-authorities-press-if-it-thinks-youre-doing-something-immoral/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-22T19:12:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bowman later edited his tweet and the following one in a thread to read as follows, but it still didn't convince the naysayers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carl Franzen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Anthropic’s new hybrid AI model can work on tasks autonomously for hours at a time]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1117338</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/05/22/1117338/anthropics-new-hybrid-ai-model-can-work-on-tasks-autonomously-for-hours-at-a-time/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-22T16:51:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Anthropic has announced two new AI models that it claims represent a major step toward making AI agents truly useful. AI agents trained on Claude Opus 4, the company’s most powerful model to date, raise the bar for what such systems are capable of by tackling difficult tasks over extended periods of time and responding…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rhiannon Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Anthropic overtakes OpenAI: Claude Opus 4 codes seven hours nonstop, sets record SWE-Bench score and reshapes enterprise AI]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008575</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/anthropic-claude-opus-4-can-code-for-7-hours-straight-and-its-about-to-change-how-we-work-with-ai/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-22T16:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Anthropic's Claude Opus 4 outperforms OpenAI's GPT-4.1 with unprecedented seven-hour autonomous coding sessions and record-breaking 72.5% SWE-bench score, transforming AI from quick-response tool to day-long collaborator.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Nuñez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Deploy Your FastAPI + PostgreSQL App on Render: A Beginner's Guide]]></title>
        <id>682f4900bcc94cb9bccbf905</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/deploy-fastapi-postgresql-app-on-render/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-22T15:55:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This guide is a comprehensive roadmap for deploying a FastAPI backend connected to a PostgreSQL database using Render, a cloud platform that supports hosting Python web apps and managed PostgreSQL databases.   You can find the complete source code he...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Preston Osoro</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[An Animated Introduction to Elixir]]></title>
        <id>682f44e3dcb21c615cf1a12d</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/an-animated-introduction-to-elixir/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-22T15:38:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Elixir is a dynamic, functional programming language designed for building scalable and maintainable applications. It leverages the battle-tested Erlang VM, known for running low-latency, distributed, and fault-tolerant systems. Elixir is based on an...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mark Mahoney</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Time Magazine appears to accidentally publish embargoed story confirming new Anthropic model]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008649</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/time-magazine-appears-to-accidentally-publish-embargoed-story-confirming-anthropic-claude-4-opus/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-22T15:26:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Someone also appears to have published a full scrape of the Time article online on the news aggregator app Newsbreak.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carl Franzen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Enchant launches zero-equity accelerator for gaming and AI startups]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008571</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/games/enchant-launches-zero-equity-accelerator-for-gaming-and-ai-startups/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-22T12:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Enchant is launching a new zero-equity accelerator for gaming and AI startups, with applications now open for its three-month program.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dean Takahashi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[At Google I/O, Sergey Brin makes surprise appearance — and declares Google will build the first AGI]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008490</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/at-google-i-o-sergey-brin-makes-surprise-appearance-and-declares-google-will-build-the-first-agi/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-21T22:20:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google co-founder Sergey Brin makes surprise appearance at Google I/O, declaring "Gemini will be the very first AGI," revealing philosophical tensions with DeepMind CEO Hassabis who urges scientific caution in the high-stakes AI race.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Nuñez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Master Database Management Systems]]></title>
        <id>682e3c04117e792e5f46edc3</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/master-database-management-systems/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-21T20:48:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Understanding how to manage data effectively is a critical skill for anyone pursuing a career in tech. And we just published a course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will teach you all about Database Management Systems (DBMS). This in-de...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OpenAI updates its new Responses API rapidly with MCP support, GPT-4o native image gen, and more enterprise features]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008465</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/programming-development/openai-updates-its-new-responses-api-rapidly-with-mcp-support-gpt-4o-native-image-gen-and-more-enterprise-features/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-21T15:30:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Support for remote Model Context Protocol servers, integration of image generation and Code Interpreter tools, and upgrades to file search...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carl Franzen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mistral AI launches Devstral, powerful new open source SWE agent model that runs on laptops]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008458</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/mistral-ai-launches-devstral-powerful-new-open-source-swe-agent-model-that-runs-on-laptops/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-21T14:57:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Beyond performance and portability, its Apache 2.0 license offers a compelling proposition for commercial applications.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carl Franzen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AMD unveils new Threadripper CPUs and Radeon GPUs for gamers at Computex 2025]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008206</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/games/amd-unveils-new-threadripper-cpus-and-radeon-gpus-for-gamers-at-computex-2025/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-21T03:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AMD held a Computex press event to introduce its Radeon RX 9060 XT graphics cards and Threadripper CPUs for next-gen gaming and workstations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dean Takahashi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google finally launches NotebookLM mobile app at I/O: hands-on, first impressions]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008400</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/google-finally-launches-notebooklm-mobile-app-at-i-o-hands-on-first-impressions/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T19:29:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As NotebookLM matures, its emerging business-tier capabilities suggest growing alignment with the productivity and compliance...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carl Franzen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google just leapfrogged every competitor with mind-blowing AI that can think deeper, shop smarter, and create videos with dialogue]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008346</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/google-just-leapfrogged-every-competitor-with-mind-blowing-ai-that-can-think-deeper-shop-smarter-and-create-videos-with-dialogue/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T17:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google unveiled major AI advancements at I/O 2025, including Gemini 2.5 with Deep Think, AI Mode in Search, Veo 3 for video with audio, and a $249 Ultra plan aimed at power users and enterprises.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Nuñez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google’s Jules aims to out-code Codex in battle for the AI developer stack]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008361</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/googles-jules-aims-to-out-code-codex-in-battle-for-the-ai-developer-stack/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T17:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google released Jules, its coding agent, into beta as autonomous coding agents are quickly gaining market share.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Emilia David</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Inside Google’s AI leap: Gemini 2.5 thinks deeper, speaks smarter and codes faster]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008366</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/inside-google-ai-leap-gemini-2-5-thinks-deeper-speaks-smarter-codes-faster/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T17:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google is moving closer to its goal of autonomous agentic AI with a series of enhancements to Gemini 2.5 Pro and Flash.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Taryn Plumb</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blazing-fast Solana data via gRPC: access the freshest Solana data from Shredstream leaders]]></title>
        <id>68273f14bf73460001094b35</id>
        <link href="https://blog.quicknode.com/yellowstone-grpc/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T15:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Access the fastest Solana data with the Yellowstone Geyser gRPC self-serve add-on or with the premium hybrid dedicated gRPC node.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>QuickNode</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is Sui: A Comprehensive Guide to Web3 Scalability]]></title>
        <id>6823533984101f00013a5ca4</id>
        <link href="https://blog.quicknode.com/what-is-sui-a-comprehensive-guide-to-web3-scalability/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-15T23:34:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Explore how Sui Network achieves 300,000 TPS through parallel processing, and its applications in gaming, DeFi, and supply chain management.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>QuickNode</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AI Meets Blockchain: Transforming Technology for the Next Era]]></title>
        <id>682354c584101f00013a5cb9</id>
        <link href="https://blog.quicknode.com/ai-and-blockchain-transforming-technology-together/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-15T23:34:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discover how AI and blockchain integration enhances security, efficiency, and innovation in healthcare, supply chains, and financial services.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>QuickNode</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Adventure Layer: AI Native Onchain Games, Unleashed]]></title>
        <id>6824c55abf73460001094973</id>
        <link href="https://blog.quicknode.com/adventure-layer-launches-on-quicknode-raas/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-15T12:04:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Adventure Layer launches layer-2 chain leveraging QuickNode's Rollup-as-a-Service (RaaS) product.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>QuickNode</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[QuickLee V2: An Improved Transparent Look into RPC Provider Latency]]></title>
        <id>680fc8e1f8ae810001969b47</id>
        <link href="https://blog.quicknode.com/quicklee-v2/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-14T13:57:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[View public and real-time dashboards to better understand latency and speed when evaluating RPC providers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>QuickNode</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>