<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2025-06-12T18:51:48.530Z</id>
    <title>AngJianming RSS Feed</title>
    <updated>2025-06-12T18:51:48.530Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bridging the Quantum Gap: A Guide to Hybrid Quantum-Classical Algorithms]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/vaib/bridging-the-quantum-gap-a-guide-to-hybrid-quantum-classical-algorithms-343g</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/vaib/bridging-the-quantum-gap-a-guide-to-hybrid-quantum-classical-algorithms-343g"/>
        <updated>2025-06-12T18:49:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bridging the Quantum Gap: A Practical Guide to Hybrid Quantum-Classical Algorithms for NISQ Devices


The promise of quantum computing to revolutionize fields from medicine to finance is immense. However, the path to fully fault-tolerant quantum computers, capable of running complex algorithms with perfect accuracy, is still a long one. We are currently in the era of Noisy Intermediate-Scale Quantum (NISQ) devices.
The NISQ Era Explained
NISQ refers to quantum computers that possess a limited number of qubits (typically 50-100+) and are susceptible to noise. This noise causes errors in quantum computations, and without robust error correction mechanisms (which require a significantly higher number of qubits than currently available), long, deep quantum circuits are not feasible. This limit…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Coder</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[React Router Data Mode: Parte 6 – Actions, formularios y mutaciones]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/kevinccbsg/react-router-data-mode-parte-6-actions-formularios-y-mutaciones-5354</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/kevinccbsg/react-router-data-mode-parte-6-actions-formularios-y-mutaciones-5354"/>
        <updated>2025-06-12T18:48:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Continuamos con la sexta entrega de esta serie sobre React Router Data Mode. En esta ocasión hablaremos sobre las actions: una de las piezas clave para el manejo de datos que nos ofrece React Router.
Si vienes del post anterior, puedes continuar con tu proyecto tal cual. Pero si prefieres empezar limpio o asegurarte de estar en el punto exacto, ejecuta los siguientes comandos:
# Enlace del repositorio https://github.com/kevinccbsg/react-router-tutorial-devto
git reset --hard
git clean -d -f
git checkout 05-action-create-contact

Una action es una función que podemos asociar a una ruta, y que se encarga de realizar mutaciones de datos. Lo interesante es que, al completarse, React Router revalida automáticamente los datos de la interfaz sin que tengamos que manejar ese proceso manualmente.
E…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Julián Martínez Escobar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Here’s what happened in crypto today]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/what-happened-in-crypto-today</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/what-happened-in-crypto-today?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-06-12T18:38:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Need to know what happened in crypto today? Here is the latest news on daily trends and events impacting Bitcoin price, blockchain, DeFi, NFTs, Web3 and crypto regulation.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Cointelegraph</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[So You Want to Be a Senior Engineer...]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/goldennoodles/so-you-want-to-be-a-senior-engineer-2jl3</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/goldennoodles/so-you-want-to-be-a-senior-engineer-2jl3"/>
        <updated>2025-06-12T18:33:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ah yes, the elusive title: Senior Software Engineer. Sounds fancy, doesn’t it? Makes your CV look impressive, probably gets you a bit more attention on LinkedIn, and maybe even lets you escape the odd stand up meeting unscathed. But let’s get one thing straight... being “senior” isn’t just about how many years you’ve been bashing keys or the number of PR's you approve.
No, it’s a whole different game.
You’ve heard the legend the “10x engineer” who does the work of ten mere mortals, drinks black coffee by the litre (me haha), and churns out production ready code faster than the rest of us can open our laptops. Sounds cool, right? Shame it’s mostly nonsense.
Being senior isn’t about typing faster or writing smarter one liners. It’s about thinking first. It’s about building things that make s…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rus Kuzmin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hey watch this Maybe you will like this idea 💡]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/vidakhoshpey22/hey-watch-this-maybe-you-will-like-this-idea-5dah</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/vidakhoshpey22/hey-watch-this-maybe-you-will-like-this-idea-5dah"/>
        <updated>2025-06-12T18:31:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Your AI-Powered Dream & Mood Analyst with Runner H 🧠💤
Vida Khoshpey  ・ Jun 11
#devchallenge
        #runnerhchallenge
        #ai
        #mentalhealth]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Vida Khoshpey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TensorWave deploys AMD Instinct MI355X GPUs in its cloud platform]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3011697</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/games/tensorwave-deploys-amd-instinct-mi355x-gpus-in-its-cloud-platform/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-12T18:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[TensorWave, a leader in AMD-powered AI infrastructure solutions, today announced the deployment of AMD Instinct MI355X GPUs in its high-performance cloud platform.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dean Takahashi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AMD debuts AMD Instinct MI350 Series accelerator chips with 35X better inferencing]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3011704</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/games/amd-debuts-amd-instinct-mi350-series-accelerator-chips-with-35x-better-inferencing/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-12T18:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AMD announced its new AMD Instinct MI350 Series accelerators, which are four times faster on AI compute and 35 times faster on inferencing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dean Takahashi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kafka MQ]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/nanditha_vuppunuthula_d09/kafka-mq-304d</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/nanditha_vuppunuthula_d09/kafka-mq-304d"/>
        <updated>2025-06-12T18:28:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What is Kafka?


Kafka is a publish/subscribe (pub/sub) messaging system that provides data streaming capabilities while also taking advantage of distributed computing.
A pub/sub messaging system contains two components that relay some form of data or information between each other. One component publishes data while the other component subscribes to the publisher to receive the published data.
Kafka follows this pattern with its own set of components and features.
The first component in a pub/sub messaging system is the publisher which is referred to as a Producer in Kafka. The producer is a data source that publishes or produces a message into Kafka. One of the great features of Kafka is that it is data type independent. This means that Kafka does not care about what type of data is bein…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nanditha Vuppunuthula</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AI-Powered Rock Paper Scissors Game with Amazon Q CLI: A Journey in AI-Assisted Game Development]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/gagan_nadiger_3cf2b4d9615/ai-powered-rock-paper-scissors-game-with-amazon-q-cli-a-journey-in-ai-assisted-game-development-3p84</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/gagan_nadiger_3cf2b4d9615/ai-powered-rock-paper-scissors-game-with-amazon-q-cli-a-journey-in-ai-assisted-game-development-3p84"/>
        <updated>2025-06-12T18:24:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction
Why Rock Paper Scissors?
Simple core mechanics with room for complexity
Opportunity to implement various AI strategies
Potential for interesting player-AI interactions
Scope for adding engaging features
Key Features
Multiple AI Personalities
Predictive AI that learns player patterns
Random AI for unpredictable gameplay
Aggressive AI that counters player strategies
Innovative Gameplay Elements
Deception Rounds: Every 6th round, AI declares its move (but might be lying!)
Time-Limited Gameplay: 5-second decision window
Achievement System tracking player statistics
Global Leaderboard using JSON persistence
Effective Prompting Techniques
Breaking down complex features into smaller, manageable prompts
Using clear, specific requests for AI behavior implementation
Iterative refinement…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gagan Nadiger</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DeadLock - dead.lock file]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/gamecoder/deadlock-deadlock-file-5cam</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/gamecoder/deadlock-deadlock-file-5cam"/>
        <updated>2025-06-12T18:24:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello guys, I am excited to share that today I achieved another major milestone regarding my project "deadlock". Now the project is able to generate custom lock file that keeps track record of all the dependencies installed on the system. Though I am not sure how it will manage the versions. But, for the most part, if a user wants to run a project that it created earlier on a different computer, it can now easily manage the dependencies.
I am working on a function that will read the lock file and then install all the packages. Just like pip does with requirements.txt file.
That's all the update I had for today.
Thank you! 🫡]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chitransh Soral</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cloudflare Investigating Authentication Incident]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cloudflarestatus.com/incidents/25r9t0vz99rp</id>
        <link href="https://www.cloudflarestatus.com/incidents/25r9t0vz99rp"/>
        <updated>2025-06-12T18:24:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Simplicity Paradox: Why Your Startup's Technical Strategy Should Be Boring 🎯]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/jetthoughts/the-simplicity-paradox-why-your-startups-technical-strategy-should-be-boring-1ie8</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/jetthoughts/the-simplicity-paradox-why-your-startups-technical-strategy-should-be-boring-1ie8"/>
        <updated>2025-06-12T18:23:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Navigating the counterintuitive relationship between technical complexity and business velocity in resource-constrained environments
The most fascinating paradox in startup ecosystems isn't about funding or market timing—it's about technology. The companies generating millions from elegant Ruby on Rails applications, while venture-backed startups burn through cash on sophisticated architectures, reveal something profound about the relationship between technical elegance and business outcomes.
Let's explore this complexity-performance inversion and unpack why radical simplicity often creates the most sustainable competitive advantages.
Technical sophistication and business velocity operate as inverse functions in early-stage environments
Decision paralysis emerges from misaligned evaluation…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paul Keen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[🚀 Germany’s AI Autobahn: Accelerating a Nation’s Digital Future with NVIDIA 🤖]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/hemant_007/germanys-ai-autobahn-accelerating-a-nations-digital-future-with-nvidia-3oii</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/hemant_007/germanys-ai-autobahn-accelerating-a-nations-digital-future-with-nvidia-3oii"/>
        <updated>2025-06-12T18:23:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello Dev Community! 👋
This is ❤️‍🔥 Hemant Katta ⚔️
Germany is fast-tracking its 🤖 digital transformation 🤖 by integrating 🤖 artificial intelligence 🤖 deeply across industry 🏭, research 👨‍🏫, and startups 📈 — all powered by NVIDIA’s state-of-the-art GPUs and AI platforms.
It isn't just adopting AI 🤖 — it's racing to lead the global 🌏 AI 🤖arms race, and NVIDIA GPUs are the engines behind that push. Let’s dive into how deep this transformation really goes. 👇
Germany’s industrial 🏭 backbone, especially its Mittelstand (small and medium enterprises), is embracing AI 🤖 at scale through thousands of NVIDIA GPUs powering AI data centers 🏢.
A flagship initiative is an industrial AI 🤖 cloud platform, based on NVIDIA technology 👨‍💻, designed to make 🛠️ AI tools ⚙️ accessible and …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hemant</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin price fractal points to bull trap that could send BTC below $100K]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-price-fractal-points-to-bull-trap-that-could-send-btc-below-100k</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-price-fractal-points-to-bull-trap-that-could-send-btc-below-100k?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-06-12T18:19:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Escalating tensions in the Middle East and an ominous Bitcoin chart fractal could play a role in sending BTC price back under $100,000.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Biraajmaan Tamuly</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spaceballs 2 Will See Rick Moranis Return as Dark Helmet]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ign.com/articles/spaceballs-2-plots-a-course-for-2027-with-mel-brooks-in-first-teaser-trailer</id>
        <link href="https://www.ign.com/articles/spaceballs-2-plots-a-course-for-2027-with-mel-brooks-in-first-teaser-trailer"/>
        <updated>2025-06-12T18:16:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NPM: Issues with package install, package publish, and login]]></title>
        <id>https://status.npmjs.org/incidents/dn5mcp85737y</id>
        <link href="https://status.npmjs.org/incidents/dn5mcp85737y"/>
        <updated>2025-06-12T18:16:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing Turbo Transition: create smoother Turbo Streams]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/railsdesigner/introducing-turbo-transition-create-smoother-turbo-streams-3i4n</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/railsdesigner/introducing-turbo-transition-create-smoother-turbo-streams-3i4n"/>
        <updated>2025-06-12T18:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This article was originally published on Rails Designer
Ever wondered how to add more joy to components and partials injected or removed from the DOM? Something like this:

see original article for the actual gif)
Previously I used a solution that relied on event callbacks from turbo. It did its job, but I was never really happy with the solution nor with its usage.
So I am introducing: Turbo Transition: A “minion” for Turbo-Frames and Streams that transitions elements as they enter or leave the DOM. ✨ A way simpler, but equally powerful solution than what I had before.
Since I've been working actively on Rails Designers I have been exploring all kinds of interesting techniques. Turbo Transition, just like turbo-frame and turbo-stream is nothing more than a custom element that adds and rem…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rails Designer</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GCP Outage]]></title>
        <id>https://status.cloud.google.com/</id>
        <link href="https://status.cloud.google.com/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-12T18:11:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Shoring up global supply chains with generative AI]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1118533</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/06/12/1118533/shoring-up-global-supply-chains-with-generative-ai/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-12T18:10:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The outbreak of covid-19 laid bare the vulnerabilities of global, interconnected supply chains. National lockdowns triggered months-long manufacturing shutdowns. Mass disruption across international trade routes sparked widespread supply shortages. Costs spiralled. And wild fluctuations in demand rendered tried-and-tested inventory planning and forecasting tools useless. “It was the black swan event that nobody had accounted for,…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>MIT Technology Review Insights</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[🔥 Master JavaScript Objects: The Ultimate Guide with Real-World Examples!]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/techsolver94/master-javascript-objects-the-ultimate-guide-with-real-world-examples-25c4</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/techsolver94/master-javascript-objects-the-ultimate-guide-with-real-world-examples-25c4"/>
        <updated>2025-06-12T18:07:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[JavaScript objects are the backbone of the language, allowing you to store and organize data efficiently. This guide will explain key object methods and features step-by-step with practical examples to help you master JavaScript objects.
Read Article]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>TechSolve Central</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[¡Blazor y .NET 9: Desbloqueando la Velocidad Extrema con Server-Side Rendering (SSR) Estático para tu Web!]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/exavier_jaguileradev/blazor-y-net-9-desbloqueando-la-velocidad-extrema-con-server-side-rendering-ssr-estatico-para-5d4b</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/exavier_jaguileradev/blazor-y-net-9-desbloqueando-la-velocidad-extrema-con-server-side-rendering-ssr-estatico-para-5d4b"/>
        <updated>2025-06-12T18:07:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[: ¿Por qué la Velocidad y el SEO son Clave en 2025?
Explicación: El navegador no tiene que descargar JavaScript/WebAssembly, parsearlo, y luego construir el DOM. Simplemente recibe el HTML pre-generado y lo muestra de inmediato.
Explicación: Los motores de búsqueda (rastreadores) reciben un HTML completamente formado y listo para indexar, incluyendo todo el contenido, metadatos y enlaces. No tienen que ejecutar JavaScript.
, , og:image dinámicas generadas en el servidor.
Explicación: Menos datos para descargar, menos procesamiento del lado del cliente.
Explicación: El navegador del usuario hace menos trabajo.
Explicación: Como no hay conexión persistente con el servidor (como en Blazor Server interactivo), puedes escalar horizontalmente más fácilmente sin preocuparte por la afinidad de ses…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Exavier J Aguilera V</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NASA Is Worth Saving]]></title>
        <id>https://caseyhandmer.wordpress.com/2025/06/12/nasa-is-worth-saving/</id>
        <link href="https://caseyhandmer.wordpress.com/2025/06/12/nasa-is-worth-saving/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-12T17:59:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Show HN: ChatToSTL – AI text-to-CAD for 3D printing]]></title>
        <id>https://huggingface.co/spaces/flowfulai/ChatToSTL</id>
        <link href="https://huggingface.co/spaces/flowfulai/ChatToSTL"/>
        <updated>2025-06-12T17:58:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[USDC stablecoin launches on XRP Ledger]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/usdc-stablecoin-launches-xrp-ledger</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/usdc-stablecoin-launches-xrp-ledger?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-06-12T17:56:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Circle's USDC has a market capitalization of over $61 billion, making it the second-largest stablecoin, second to Tether's USDt.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Vince Quill</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trident Digital to create XRP treasury of up to $500M]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/trident-xrp-treasury-announcement</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/trident-xrp-treasury-announcement?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-06-12T17:31:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The reserve will be funded through stock issuance and other financial instruments, according to the announcement.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Christopher Tepedino</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trump addresses Coinbase summit to discuss crypto plans]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/donald-trump-coinbase-conference-crypto-plans</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/donald-trump-coinbase-conference-crypto-plans?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-06-12T17:17:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The US president has spoken in person at the Bitcoin 2024 conference in Nashville and released a video message for the Digital Asset Summit in New York City.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Turner Wright</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Will Rally as U.S. Growth Improves, Crypto Bills Progress: Coinbase Research]]></title>
        <id>ce7317a6-f34a-4aa0-910d-7673aed6db44</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/06/12/bitcoin-will-rally-as-us-growth-improves-crypto-bills-progress-coinbase-research"/>
        <updated>2025-06-12T17:16:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[U.S. economic resilience and stablecoin legislation will drive optimism for BTC, with the fate of altcoins being less certain.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tom Carreras</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Roame (YC S23) Is Hiring]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ycombinator.com/companies/roame/jobs/9QhTM31-founding-product-ai-engineer</id>
        <link href="https://www.ycombinator.com/companies/roame/jobs/9QhTM31-founding-product-ai-engineer"/>
        <updated>2025-06-12T17:01:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google Pixels are no longer the AOSP reference device]]></title>
        <id>https://9to5google.com/2025/06/12/android-open-source-project-pixel-change/</id>
        <link href="https://9to5google.com/2025/06/12/android-open-source-project-pixel-change/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-12T16:53:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Y Combinator startup Sorcerer raises $3.9M to launch more weather balloons]]></title>
        <id>https://www.axios.com/pro/climate-deals/2025/06/12/sorcerer-seed-weather-balloons</id>
        <link href="https://www.axios.com/pro/climate-deals/2025/06/12/sorcerer-seed-weather-balloons"/>
        <updated>2025-06-12T16:46:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Deutsche Telekom, Alibaba Cloud, Vodafone are running nodes on Nillion]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/nillion-enterprise-cluster-blockchain-privacy</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/nillion-enterprise-cluster-blockchain-privacy?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-06-12T16:40:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Enterprise Cluster initiative enables decentralized use cases for privacy-sensitive operations across healthcare and finance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Sam Bourgi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Solving LinkedIn Queens with SMT]]></title>
        <id>https://buttondown.com/hillelwayne/archive/solving-linkedin-queens-with-smt/</id>
        <link href="https://buttondown.com/hillelwayne/archive/solving-linkedin-queens-with-smt/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-12T16:18:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[US-backed Israeli company's spyware used to target European journalists]]></title>
        <id>https://apnews.com/article/spyware-italy-paragon-meloni-pegasus-f36dd32106f44398ee24001317ccf2bb</id>
        <link href="https://apnews.com/article/spyware-italy-paragon-meloni-pegasus-f36dd32106f44398ee24001317ccf2bb"/>
        <updated>2025-06-12T16:12:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DeFi Adding $5B of Solana Buying Power With New Line of Credit]]></title>
        <id>d9389ee6-52cc-4069-b37c-ce378169df95</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2025/06/12/defi-adding-5b-of-solana-buying-power-with-new-line-of-credit"/>
        <updated>2025-06-12T15:52:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The move will allow the Nasdaq-listed firm to add to its 609,000 SOL stack as of May 16.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Krisztian Sandor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[macOS Tahoe brings a new disk image format]]></title>
        <id>https://eclecticlight.co/2025/06/12/macos-tahoe-brings-a-new-disk-image-format/</id>
        <link href="https://eclecticlight.co/2025/06/12/macos-tahoe-brings-a-new-disk-image-format/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-12T15:49:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Researchers confirm two journalists were hacked with Paragon spyware]]></title>
        <id>https://techcrunch.com/2025/06/12/researchers-confirm-two-journalists-were-hacked-with-paragon-spyware/</id>
        <link href="https://techcrunch.com/2025/06/12/researchers-confirm-two-journalists-were-hacked-with-paragon-spyware/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-12T15:39:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Donald Trump: Administration Will Work Toward 'Clear and Simple' Crypto Frameworks]]></title>
        <id>f0052a2b-5df0-41cf-818b-61d445769331</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2025/06/12/donald-trump-administration-will-work-toward-clear-and-simple-crypto-frameworks"/>
        <updated>2025-06-12T15:19:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The U.S. president addressed an annual Coinbase event.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nikhilesh De</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Protocol: Polygon, Once a Scaling Leader, Eyes a Revamp]]></title>
        <id>8e5edc9c-ed09-4d37-802e-0b6a35662a4a</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/tech/2025/06/12/the-protocol-polygon-once-a-scaling-leader-eyes-a-revamp"/>
        <updated>2025-06-12T15:18:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Also: EF Treasury Policy, Increase of OP_CAT Data Limit, and Plume Genesis Goes Live.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Margaux Nijkerk</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[USDT issuer Tether buys 32% stake in Canada’s gold royalty firm]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/tether-buys-32-percent-stake-canada-elemental-altus</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/tether-buys-32-percent-stake-canada-elemental-altus?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-06-12T15:11:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tether’s investment in Canada’s Elemental Altus Royalties follows the company’s strategy to “integrate long-term, stable assets such as gold and Bitcoin in its ecosystem.”]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Helen Partz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AVAX Rebounds From Key Support After 6% Plunge]]></title>
        <id>0880bc09-4d1c-4912-a66f-83afe78e044a</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/06/12/avax-rebounds-from-key-support-after-6-plunge"/>
        <updated>2025-06-12T15:07:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Avalanche's token’s recovery from oversold conditions suggests potential for continued upward momentum if newly established support holds.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CD Analytics</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[iPhone 11 emulation done in QEMU]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/ChefKissInc/QEMUAppleSilicon</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/ChefKissInc/QEMUAppleSilicon"/>
        <updated>2025-06-12T15:04:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Does My Ripped CD Have Messed Up Track Names? and Why Is One Track Missing?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.akpain.net/blog/inside-a-cd/</id>
        <link href="https://www.akpain.net/blog/inside-a-cd/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-12T15:03:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NEAR Protocol Plunges 9% as Volatility Spikes Despite User Growth]]></title>
        <id>3ec4e2ff-0383-45d9-9aa7-74552fbc30fa</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/06/12/near-protocol-plunges-9-as-volatility-spikes-despite-user-growth"/>
        <updated>2025-06-12T15:03:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Network becomes second most popular L1 blockchain with 46 million monthly active users, yet price struggles amid inflation concerns.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Oliver Knight</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google DeepMind just changed hurricane forecasting forever with new AI model]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3011661</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/google-deepmind-just-changed-hurricane-forecasting-forever-with-new-ai-model/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-12T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google DeepMind launches Weather Lab platform for AI hurricane forecasting, showing improved accuracy in early tests with U.S. National Hurricane Center partnership.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Nuñez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto for Advisors: The Relationship Between Bitcoin and Altcoins]]></title>
        <id>cda2f7f6-e1a1-4e37-9062-6823809b832d</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/coindesk-indices/2025/06/11/crypto-for-advisors-the-relationship-between-bitcoin-and-altcoins"/>
        <updated>2025-06-12T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin’s new all-time high is both a milestone and potential signal: the next phase may belong to the broader crypto asset universe.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gregory Mall</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AI can’t do it alone: Blockchain is the missing piece in next-gen gaming]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/blockchain-is-the-missing-link</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/blockchain-is-the-missing-link?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-06-12T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AI is reshaping gaming, but blockchain is the missing link for next-gen, AI-powered social gaming experiences. Centralized systems limit progress, ownership and creativity.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Kin Wai Lau</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TON Slips as Selling Pressure Mounts Despite Recovery Attempts]]></title>
        <id>56ca4ee2-9b49-4e8c-b8e1-4e975fb014e8</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/06/12/ton-slips-as-selling-pressure-mounts-despite-recovery-attempts"/>
        <updated>2025-06-12T14:55:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Telegram’s token faces headwinds despite showing signs of potential support formation on the short-term.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CD Analytics</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin bulls halt $4K BTC price dip as US dollar hits new 3-year lows]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-bulls-halt-4k-btc-price-dip-us-dollar-hits-new-3-year-lows</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-bulls-halt-4k-btc-price-dip-us-dollar-hits-new-3-year-lows?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-06-12T14:53:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BTC price strength returns as US inflation cools beyond expectations, hitting dollar strength again — and new BTC price all-time highs are on the table.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by William Suberg</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Singapore's Trident Digital Targets Mammoth $500M Raise to Establish XRP Treasury]]></title>
        <id>feda3e96-3e0d-4ff4-851d-d881aea69d4e</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/06/12/singapores-trident-digital-targets-mammoth-500m-raise-to-establish-xrp-treasury"/>
        <updated>2025-06-12T14:49:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Trident Digital’s plan would make it among the first public companies to hold XRP as a core treasury asset.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shaurya Malwa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Seedance 1.0]]></title>
        <id>https://seed.bytedance.com/en/seedance</id>
        <link href="https://seed.bytedance.com/en/seedance"/>
        <updated>2025-06-12T14:26:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Japan’s fiscal debt crisis means for global crypto markets]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/explained/what-japans-fiscal-debt-crisis-means-for-global-crypto-markets</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/explained/what-japans-fiscal-debt-crisis-means-for-global-crypto-markets?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-06-12T14:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Japan’s debt crisis jolts crypto markets, testing their resilience and reviving Bitcoin’s role as a system hedge against fragile fiat systems.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Arunkumar Krishnakumar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto ownership isn’t just lambos and bros anymore]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/crypto-ownership-lambos-and-bros-anymore</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/crypto-ownership-lambos-and-bros-anymore?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-06-12T14:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The National Cryptocurrency Association’s 2025 report reveals a surprising normalcy to crypto ownership, spanning construction sites to art studios and challenging long-held stereotypes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Michael Tabone</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin adoption fueled by ‘deglobalization,’ Trump’s ‘big, beautiful bill’]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-adoption-driven-by-tariff-deglobalization-trump-s-big-beautiful-bill</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-adoption-driven-by-tariff-deglobalization-trump-s-big-beautiful-bill?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-06-12T14:12:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin adoption may benefit from continued global uncertainty until a trade agreement between the world’s two largest economies is finalized.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Zoltan Vardai</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Lending Platform Morpho V2 Brings DeFi Closer to Traditional Finance]]></title>
        <id>66aae448-e2dd-4c89-b33e-5070be77284b</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2025/06/12/crypto-lending-platform-morpho-v2-brings-defi-closer-to-traditional-finance"/>
        <updated>2025-06-12T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Morpho V2 delivers market-driven fixed-rate, fixed-term loans with customizable terms to meet the demands of institutions and enterprises.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ian Allison</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hong Kong to develop crypto tracking tool for money laundering]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/hong-kong-customs-university-crypto-tracking-tool</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/hong-kong-customs-university-crypto-tracking-tool?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-06-12T13:55:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hong Kong Customs and Excise Department teams up with the University of Hong Kong to build a crypto tracking tool amid a rise in money laundering cases involving digital assets.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Amin Haqshanas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bittrue Hacker Funnels $30M Through Tornado Cash, Made $9.3M by Trading Ether]]></title>
        <id>8a80ba60-a273-4530-855e-a5b1c7889610</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2025/06/12/bittrue-hacker-funnels-usd30m-through-tornado-cash-made-usd9-3m-by-trading-ether"/>
        <updated>2025-06-12T13:55:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The hacker laundered the ETH after the asset nearly doubled in the past two months.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Oliver Knight</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Lender Maple Partners with Liquid Staking Specialist Lido Finance]]></title>
        <id>4495203d-3ae2-40dd-b5cd-3ad38e41b5de</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2025/06/12/crypto-lender-maple-partners-with-liquid-staking-specialist-lido-finance"/>
        <updated>2025-06-12T13:37:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Maple will offer stablecoin credit lines backed by Lido’s staking token stETH.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ian Allison</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CoinDesk 20 Performance Update: Chainlink (LINK) Drops 6.2%, Leading Index Lower]]></title>
        <id>a34ce635-735c-44e4-a3c7-402c36de0e51</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/coindesk-indices/2025/06/12/coindesk-20-performance-update-chainlink-link-drops-62-leading-index-lower"/>
        <updated>2025-06-12T13:15:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[NEAR Protocol (NEAR) was also among the underperformers, declining 5.9% from Wednesday.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CoinDesk Indices</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chainlink, JPMorgan, Ondo Finance complete crosschain treasury settlement]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/chainlink-jp-morgan-ondo-crosschain-dvp-settlement</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/chainlink-jp-morgan-ondo-crosschain-dvp-settlement?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-06-12T13:14:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Chainlink, JPMorgan’s Kinexys, and Ondo Finance completed a crosschain DvP settlement between a permissioned payment network and a public RWA blockchain.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Amin Haqshanas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CP/M 2.2, CP/M 3.0, CP/M-86, Concurrent CP/M-86 listings by Digital Research]]></title>
        <id>http://www.bitsavers.org/pdf/digitalResearch/CPM_Listings/</id>
        <link href="http://www.bitsavers.org/pdf/digitalResearch/CPM_Listings/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-12T13:11:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Conduit, Braza Group Debut Stablecoin Forex Swaps for Cross-Border Payments in Brazil]]></title>
        <id>3147f753-d3d1-4e64-a49e-4e88f60a1352</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2025/06/12/conduit-braza-group-debut-stablecoin-forex-swaps-for-cross-border-payments-in-brazil"/>
        <updated>2025-06-12T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Stablecoin rails cut payment processing time to minutes from a few days on traditional SWIFT rails, the companies said.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Krisztian Sandor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tether Buys $82M Stake in Gold-Focused Investment Company Elemental Altus]]></title>
        <id>01325f70-bd18-4abb-a61d-a8cd5edc8779</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2025/06/12/tether-takes-minority-stake-in-gold-focused-investment-company-elemental-altus"/>
        <updated>2025-06-12T12:46:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tether referred to increasing its exposure to gold as a "dual pillar strategy", alongside its holdings of over 100,000 BTC]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Crawley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fujifilm X-E5 Now Official; Starts From RM6,998 In Malaysia]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=355755</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/355755/fujifilm-x-e5-now-official-starts-from-rm6998-in-malaysia/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-12T12:24:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fujifilm has officially launched the X-E5, its latest APS-C mirrorless camera that blends the classic rangefinder aesthetic with updated internals. Announced during its X Summit 2025 event in Shanghai, the new shooter introduces significant upgrades over its predecessor while maintaining its signature compact form. The camera is built around Fujifilm’s 40.2MP X-Trans CMOS 5 HR […]
The post Fujifilm X-E5 Now Official; Starts From RM6,998 In Malaysia appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Heirul Kamel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Download: AI agents’ autonomy, and sodium-based batteries]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1118609</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/06/12/1118609/the-download-ai-agents-autonomy-and-sodium-based-batteries/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-12T12:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is today’s edition of The Download, our weekday newsletter that provides a daily dose of what’s going on in the world of technology. Are we ready to hand AI agents the keys? In recent months, a new class of agents has arrived on the scene: ones built using large language models. Any action that can be…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rhiannon Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tried automating crypto trades with Grok 3? Here’s what happens]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/automated-crypto-trades-with-grok-3</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/automated-crypto-trades-with-grok-3?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-06-12T12:08:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Automating crypto trades with Grok 3 might seem promising, but issues like data loss and inaccurate signals can hurt your performance in a fast-paced market.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Callum Reid</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FBI Crypto Veteran Chris Wong Joins TRM Labs to Bolster Fight Against Illicit Finance]]></title>
        <id>95a13e13-f84e-457e-b78e-343d33f83d2d</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2025/06/12/fbi-crypto-veteran-chris-wong-joins-trm-labs-to-bolster-fight-against-illicit-finance"/>
        <updated>2025-06-12T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An ex-FBI agent who led landmark crypto investigations is joining TRM Labs’ team.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tom Carreras</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A receipt printer cured my procrastination]]></title>
        <id>https://www.laurieherault.com/articles/a-thermal-receipt-printer-cured-my-procrastination</id>
        <link href="https://www.laurieherault.com/articles/a-thermal-receipt-printer-cured-my-procrastination"/>
        <updated>2025-06-12T11:41:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nasdaq-listed Mercurity Fintech to raise $800M for Bitcoin treasury]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/mercurity-800m-bitcoin-treasury-plan</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/mercurity-800m-bitcoin-treasury-plan?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-06-12T11:36:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mercurity’s $800 million Bitcoin treasury financing plan would make the firm the 11th-largest corporate Bitcoin holder after Galaxy Digital.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Zoltan Vardai</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ether futures open interest hits $20B all-time high: Will ETH price follow?]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/ethereum-futures-open-interest-hits-20b-all-time-high-will-eth-price-follow</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/ethereum-futures-open-interest-hits-20b-all-time-high-will-eth-price-follow?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-06-12T11:27:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ether futures data shows momentum, with ETH price more than doubling since April lows, increasing the chance of a rally to $4,000 in the coming weeks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Nancy Lubale</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Daybook Americas: Bitcoin Drops as Mideast Tensions Rise, but $200K Still In Play]]></title>
        <id>479e77b6-ed06-4486-b5b8-cfee8d86d1df</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/daybook-us/2025/06/12/crypto-daybook-americas-bitcoin-drops-as-mideast-tensions-rise-but-200k-still-in-play"/>
        <updated>2025-06-12T11:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Your day-ahead look for June 12, 2025]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Francisco Rodrigues</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dollar Index Falls Below 98 for First Time in Three Years, Gives Room for Crypto Run]]></title>
        <id>ffabe7e3-4ff1-4a7a-870a-75e1882af863</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/06/12/dollar-index-falls-below-98-for-first-time-in-three-years-gives-room-for-crypto-run"/>
        <updated>2025-06-12T11:08:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Weaker dollar sparks optimism for risk assets as inflation eases.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>James Van Straten</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FSB warns crypto nearing ‘tipping point’ as ties to TradFi deepen]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/fsb-warns-crypto-tipping-point-tradfi</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/fsb-warns-crypto-tipping-point-tradfi?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-06-12T10:59:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Outgoing FSB Chair Klaas Knot says stablecoins and ETFs are accelerating crypto’s integration into traditional finance, raising systemic risk concerns.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Amin Haqshanas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Strategy Launches STRD, Its Third 'Bitcoin-Backed' Preferred Stock on Nasdaq]]></title>
        <id>d7a8ad4f-1f19-4609-8ab2-daa63c093980</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/06/12/strategy-launches-strd-its-third-bitcoin-backed-preferred-stock-on-nasdaq"/>
        <updated>2025-06-12T10:51:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New 10% yield offering aims to raise nearly $1 billion to support Strategy’s continued bitcoin accumulation. 
New 10% yield offering aims to raise nearly $1 billion to support Strategy’s continued bitcoin accumulation.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>James Van Straten</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Nintendo Products Spotted On SIRIM, But…]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=355749</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/355749/new-nintendo-products-spotted-on-sirim/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-12T10:47:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While consumers in other Southeast Asian countries – including Singapore, Thailand, and the Philippines – eagerly anticipate the arrival of the Switch 2 on 26 June, those of us in Malaysia are still left in suspense. As we’ve reported previously, sources familiar with the matter have informed us that Nintendo’s next-gen handheld console is still […]
The post New Nintendo Products Spotted On SIRIM, But… appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Heirul Kamel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto exchange Binance launches in Syria after Trump lifts sanctions]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/binance-welcomes-syria-trump-lifts-sanctions</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/binance-welcomes-syria-trump-lifts-sanctions?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-06-12T10:42:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Binance’s rollout in Syria features a full access launch, allowing Syrians to trade at least 300 tokens, including Bitcoin, XRP, Toncoin and more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Helen Partz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[93% of all Bitcoin is already mined. Here’s what that means]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/explained/93-of-all-bitcoin-is-already-mined-heres-what-that-means</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/explained/93-of-all-bitcoin-is-already-mined-heres-what-that-means?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-06-12T10:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With 93% of all Bitcoin already mined, the race for the remaining coins is intensifying. Here’s how it impacts scarcity, mining rewards and the future of the network.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Bradley Peak</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ETH Bulls Tighten Grip as $393M Exits Exchanges and ETF Inflows Outpace Bitcoin]]></title>
        <id>18d6d0d9-10c2-489a-bd3e-61241ef1d185</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/06/12/eth-bulls-tighten-grip-as-usd393m-exits-exchanges-and-etf-inflows-outpace-bitcoin"/>
        <updated>2025-06-12T10:36:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Despite a 0.15% pullback, ETH options skew, exchange outflows and ETF flows all point to growing upside interest among traders and institutions.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Siamak Masnavi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Leapmotor C10 Now Priced At RM125,000; Comes With Updated Features]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=355726</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/355726/leapmotor-c10-update-gets-price-cut/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-12T10:24:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Leapmotor C10, which was launched last October by Stellantis Malaysia, has now gained some updates for the 2025 model year. The major update is the price drop from RM159,000 to RM125,000, which is RM34,000 less. This price drop puts the SUV EV right in the lanes of BYD Atto 3 and Proton eMAS further […]
The post Leapmotor C10 Now Priced At RM125,000; Comes With Updated Features appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Keran</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Micron Begins Shipping HBM4 Memory To Key Customers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=355731</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/355731/micron-hbm4-shipping/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-12T10:07:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[MIcron recently announced that it has begun shipping out its HBM4 memory modules to key customers. These include the 36GB modules, built on its 1-beta, 12-high advanced packaging technology. “Micron Technology, Inc. (Nasdaq: MU), today announced the shipment of HBM4 36GB 12-high samples to multiple key customers. This milestone extends Micron’s leadership in memory performance […]
The post Micron Begins Shipping HBM4 Memory To Key Customers appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John Law</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Are we ready to hand AI agents the keys?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1118189</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/06/12/1118189/ai-agents-manus-control-autonomy-operator-openai/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-12T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On May 6, 2010, at 2:32 p.m. Eastern time, nearly a trillion dollars evaporated from the US stock market within 20 minutes—at the time, the fastest decline in history. Then, almost as suddenly, the market rebounded. After months of investigation, regulators attributed much of the responsibility for this “flash crash” to high-frequency trading algorithms, which…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Grace Huckins</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[These new batteries are finding a niche]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1118556</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/06/12/1118556/sodium-batteries-niche/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-12T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Lithium-ion batteries have some emerging competition: Sodium-based alternatives are starting to make inroads. Sodium is more abundant on Earth than lithium, and batteries that use the material could be cheaper in the future. Building a new battery chemistry is difficult, mostly because lithium is so entrenched. But, as I’ve noted before, this new technology has…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Casey Crownhart</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Wikipedia Pauses AI Summaries Due To Backlash]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=355734</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/355734/wikipedia-pauses-ai-summaries-due-to-backlash/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-12T09:49:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It is no secret that the Wikimedia Foundation has been dabbling in generative AI as of late. One of its recent endeavours involves introducing AI-generated article summaries to Wikipedia. However, due to the overwhelmingly negative response from the encyclopedia’s volunteer editors, the organisation has put the project on hold. Wikimedia initially intended to launch an […]
The post Wikipedia Pauses AI Summaries Due To Backlash appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nurul Kamil</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Maximizing Battery Storage Profits via High-Frequency Intraday Trading]]></title>
        <id>https://arxiv.org/abs/2504.06932</id>
        <link href="https://arxiv.org/abs/2504.06932"/>
        <updated>2025-06-12T09:43:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Jack Ma’s Ant International eyes stablecoin licenses in Singapore, Hong Kong]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/jack-ma-ant-group-stablecoin-license-for-singapore-hong-kong</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/jack-ma-ant-group-stablecoin-license-for-singapore-hong-kong?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-06-12T09:21:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ant International plans to apply for stablecoin licenses in Hong Kong and Singapore, signaling growing fintech interest in regulated crypto payment systems, Bloomberg reported.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Zoltan Vardai</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Can Bitcoin fix Pakistan’s energy problem? The 2,000 megawatt mining strategy explained]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/explained/can-bitcoin-fix-pakistans-energy-problem-the-2-000-megawatt-mining-strategy-explained</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/explained/can-bitcoin-fix-pakistans-energy-problem-the-2-000-megawatt-mining-strategy-explained?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-06-12T09:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Can Bitcoin solve the energy crisis in Pakistan? 2,000 MW Mining Plan]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Bradley Peak</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Jack Ma's Ant International Seeks Stablecoin Licenses in Hong Kong, Singapore: Bloomberg]]></title>
        <id>7b62ebd3-0185-429d-a694-027d6b5ca6b3</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2025/06/12/jack-mas-ant-international-seeks-stablecoin-licenses-in-hong-kong-singapore-bloomberg"/>
        <updated>2025-06-12T08:55:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hong Kong has been establishing a stablecoin regime since 2023, with the legislation expected to go into effect in August]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Crawley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Qualcomm Snapdragon 8 Elite 3 May Come In Two Variants]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=355689</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/355689/qualcomm-snapdragon-8-elite-3-two-variants/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-12T08:37:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’ve only just seen references to the sequel to the Qualcomm Snapdragon 8 Elite late last month, and now we are hearing rumours of the chip that would come after said sequel. And it’s not all good either, as while one part of it is that it will be made using TSMC’s 2nm process, the […]
The post Qualcomm Snapdragon 8 Elite 3 May Come In Two Variants appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ian Chee</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto has killed the weekend: Hedge funds quietly scramble to adapt]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/hedge-funds-hire-weekend-crypto-traders</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/hedge-funds-hire-weekend-crypto-traders?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-06-12T08:31:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hedge funds like Qube, Virtu and Jump are hiring weekend crypto traders as traditional finance adapts to nonstop digital asset markets.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Amin Haqshanas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why is Bitcoin price down today?]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/why-is-bitcoin-price-down-today</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/why-is-bitcoin-price-down-today?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-06-12T08:30:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin is down 1.7% over the last 24 hours after running into resistance above the $108,000 level, among other drivers that are weakening bullish momentum.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Nancy Lubale</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin must avoid sub-$100K wick as traders digest 55% China tariffs]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-must-avoid-sub-100k-wick-traders-55-china-tariffs</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-must-avoid-sub-100k-wick-traders-55-china-tariffs?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-06-12T08:19:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BTC price requirements are clear as consolidation below all-time highs continues. Can Bitcoin bulls stick to the plan and avoid falling back below $100,000?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by William Suberg</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Redditor Fix NVIDIA RTX 50 Series Incompatibility Issue With EVGA Z690 Board By Taping Pins]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=355719</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/355719/redditor-rtx-50-series-evga-z690-board/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-12T08:19:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Remember when EVGA decided to leave the GPU market in 2022? Beyond its once thriving GPU business, the company has since been forced to downsize itself by staff reductions, which has led to being large unable to provide support for other PC components and, in this case, to its Intel 600 Series motherboards. Recently, a […]
The post Redditor Fix NVIDIA RTX 50 Series Incompatibility Issue With EVGA Z690 Board By Taping Pins appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John Law</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mercurity Fintech Plans $800M Bitcoin Treasury, Eyes Russell 2000 Inclusion]]></title>
        <id>18ce4b9c-f1ef-4a53-b84a-a701f61888e1</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/06/12/mercurity-fintech-plans-800m-bitcoin-treasury-eyes-russell-2000-inclusion"/>
        <updated>2025-06-12T08:18:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The company, which operates cryptocurrency mining facilities and offers financial services, did not disclose how ti plans on raising the funds.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Francisco Rodrigues</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Strong Uptake at 10-Year U.S. Debt Sale Eases Demand Concerns, 30-Year Sale's Up Next]]></title>
        <id>1bb6590a-4635-4da4-b852-35df1785c6aa</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/06/12/strong-uptake-at-10-year-u-s-debt-sale-eases-demand-concerns-30-year-sale-s-up-next"/>
        <updated>2025-06-12T08:07:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The U.S. national debt exceeds $36 trillion, with analysts suggesting bitcoin and gold as hedges against potential fiscal crises.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Omkar Godbole</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Alchemy Pay taps Backed to expand access to tokenized ETFs, stocks]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/alchemy-pay-tokenized-etf-rwa-launch</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/alchemy-pay-tokenized-etf-rwa-launch?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-06-12T08:01:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Alchemy Pay is preparing to launch 55 US tokenized ETFs and stocks on multiple networks, including Solana, via Backed’s xStocks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Helen Partz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin-Based Stablecoin Network Plasma Raises Deposit Cap to $1B, Gets Filled in 30 Minutes]]></title>
        <id>5a52e1d3-835e-45f5-9f99-c006a8856758</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/06/12/bitcoin-based-stablecoin-network-plasma-raises-deposit-cap-to-1b-gets-filled-in-30-minutes"/>
        <updated>2025-06-12T07:26:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Depositors earn the right to participate in the sale based on their final units at the time of the lock-up.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shaurya Malwa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[XRP Slides 4% After Failing to Break $2.33 Resistance Level Thrice]]></title>
        <id>ee885288-48a2-4a59-8d86-484bab011ca2</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/06/12/xrp-slides-4-after-failing-to-break-233-resistance-level-thrice"/>
        <updated>2025-06-12T07:14:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Market sentiment shifts as XRP faces significant technical barriers despite recovery attempts.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shaurya Malwa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nubia Z70S Ultra Photographer Edition, Pad Pro Arrive In Malaysia; Starts From RM2,399]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=355694</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/355694/nubia-z70s-ultra-pad-pro/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-12T07:00:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nubia has officially launched its latest lineup of flagship devices, namely the Z70S Ultra Photographer Edition and the Pad Pro. The former is the same device as the smartphone released in China earlier this year, but the new edition includes a professional retro kit that includes a phone case, a Neo Bar smart camera control […]
The post Nubia Z70S Ultra Photographer Edition, Pad Pro Arrive In Malaysia; Starts From RM2,399 appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ikmal Rozlan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BMW Malaysia Launches New M5 G90 Hybrid For RM1,188,800]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=355667</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/355667/bmw-m5-g90-hybrid-launch-malaysia/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-12T06:52:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today at the My BMW World event, the German automaker has launched the all-new 7th generation M5 (G90). This performance sedan features a plug-in hybrid electric powertrain (PHEV) and comes with a hefty price tag of RM1,188,800. The BMW M5 G90, other than for its performance, is also known for its aggressive look, and the […]
The post BMW Malaysia Launches New M5 G90 Hybrid For RM1,188,800 appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Keran</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ASUS Malaysia Launches New TUF Gaming Laptops With NVIDIA RTX 50 Series]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=355661</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/355661/asus-tuf-gaming-laptops-rtx-50-series/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-12T06:48:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ASUS Malaysia announced the availability of its new TUF Gaming laptops. These laptops are refreshes of the existing range, with the main refreshed component being the NVIDIA GeForce RTX 50 Series laptop GPUs. In total, The new TUF Gaming series comprises three SKUs: the F16, A16, and A14. Starting with the F16, this model is […]
The post ASUS Malaysia Launches New TUF Gaming Laptops With NVIDIA RTX 50 Series appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John Law</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DeFi Development to refile $1B Solana plan after SEC filing snag]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/defi-development-corp-sec-solana-fundraise-setback</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/defi-development-corp-sec-solana-fundraise-setback?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-06-12T06:14:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Formerly only a real estate financing company, DeFi Development Corp started buying Solana to become a Solana treasury company as well, currently holding over 609,000 tokens.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Stephen Katte</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Michael Saylor shares how COVID-19 chaos drove him to Bitcoin]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/michael-saylor-war-currency-spurred-invest-in-bitcoin</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/michael-saylor-war-currency-spurred-invest-in-bitcoin?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-06-12T06:10:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Michael Saylor says pandemic-era lockdowns and unabated money printing pushed him to convert his company’s massive cash reserves into Bitcoin.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Martin Young</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[US Bancorp studying stablecoins as crypto custody arm sees revival]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/us-bancorp-studying-stablecoins-crypto-custody-sees-revival</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/us-bancorp-studying-stablecoins-crypto-custody-sees-revival?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-06-12T06:07:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[U.S. Bancorp CEO Gunjan Kedia says her bank is looking into stablecoins as its crypto custody business bounces back after struggling under Biden.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Jesse Coghlan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Peter Brandt’s 75% Bitcoin crash scenario ‘very unlikely’: Analyst]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-trader-peter-brandt-speculation-btc-crash-analysts-disagree</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-trader-peter-brandt-speculation-btc-crash-analysts-disagree?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-06-12T05:57:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto analysts say the current environment is entirely different from 2021, when Bitcoin experienced a 76% price drop over 12 months.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Ciaran Lyons</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Show HN: Eyesite – Experimental website combining computer vision and web design]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.andykhau.com/blog/eyesite</id>
        <link href="https://blog.andykhau.com/blog/eyesite"/>
        <updated>2025-06-12T00:37:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft Office migration from Source Depot to Git]]></title>
        <id>https://danielsada.tech/blog/carreer-part-7-how-office-moved-to-git-and-i-loved-devex/</id>
        <link href="https://danielsada.tech/blog/carreer-part-7-how-office-moved-to-git-and-i-loved-devex/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-12T00:15:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chatterbox TTS]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/resemble-ai/chatterbox</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/resemble-ai/chatterbox"/>
        <updated>2025-06-11T20:23:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Attackers Steal Data from Websites (And How to Stop Them)]]></title>
        <id>6849e4d1a3aec42347669919</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-attackers-steal-data-from-websites-and-how-to-stop-them/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-11T20:19:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Across platforms, behind every app, and on your own website, hackers may patiently wait.  These days, everyone should have identity theft protections, and be informed about data threats lurking in the trenches of the world-wide-web’s war on privacy a...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alex Tray</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Research suggests Big Bang may have taken place inside a black hole]]></title>
        <id>https://www.port.ac.uk/news-events-and-blogs/blogs/space-cosmology-and-the-universe/what-if-the-big-bang-wasnt-the-beginning-our-research-suggests-it-may-have-taken-place-inside-a-black-hole</id>
        <link href="https://www.port.ac.uk/news-events-and-blogs/blogs/space-cosmology-and-the-universe/what-if-the-big-bang-wasnt-the-beginning-our-research-suggests-it-may-have-taken-place-inside-a-black-hole"/>
        <updated>2025-06-11T19:44:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft-backed Mistral launches European AI cloud to compete with AWS and Azure]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3011628</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/microsoft-backed-mistral-launches-european-ai-cloud-to-compete-with-aws-and-azure/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-11T17:51:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mistral AI partners with Nvidia to launch European AI infrastructure platform, challenging US cloud giants while unveiling breakthrough reasoning models that rival OpenAI.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Nuñez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Databricks open-sources declarative ETL framework powering 90% faster pipeline builds]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3011579</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/data-infrastructure/databricks-open-sources-declarative-etl-framework-powering-90-faster-pipeline-builds/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-11T17:29:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With Apache Spark Declarative Pipelines, engineers describe what their pipeline should do using SQL or Python, and Apache Spark handles the execution.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shubham Sharma</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Show HN: Spark, An advanced 3D Gaussian Splatting renderer for Three.js]]></title>
        <id>https://sparkjs.dev/</id>
        <link href="https://sparkjs.dev/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-11T17:02:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘Generative AI helps us bend time’: CrowdStrike, Nvidia embed real-time LLM defense, changing how enterprises secure AI]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3011386</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/security/crowdstrike-falcon-now-powers-runtime-defense-in-nvidias-llms/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-11T16:39:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Falcon is now built into Nvidia’s LLMs, delivering native runtime threat defense and eliminating blind spots across AI pipelines.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Louis Columbus</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Asset sprawl, siloed data and CloudQuery’s search for unified cloud governance]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3011440</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/data-infrastructure/asset-sprawl-siloed-data-and-cloudquerys-search-for-unified-cloud-governance/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-11T13:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CloudQuery's developer-first approach to cloud governance pulls data from 60-plus sources into a single, queryable data warehouse.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Taryn Plumb</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why most enterprise AI agents never reach production and how Databricks plans to fix it]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3011290</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/why-most-enterprise-ai-agents-never-reach-production-and-how-databricks-plans-to-fix-it/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-11T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Databricks Agent Bricks automates enterprise AI agent optimization and evaluation, eliminating manual processes that block production deployments.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sean Michael Kerner</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Outset raises $17M to replace human interviewers with AI agents for enterprise research]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3011482</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/outset-raises-17m-to-replace-human-interviewers-with-ai-agents-for-enterprise-research/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-11T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Outset raises $17M Series A to scale its AI-moderated research platform used by Nestlé, Microsoft, and WeightWatchers that's 8x faster and 81% cheaper than traditional market research.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Nuñez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lemony is a plug-and-play device for secure on-premise AI]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3011497</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/games/lemony-is-a-plug-and-play-device-for-secure-on-premise-ai/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-11T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Lemony launched a simple-looking device to deliver on-premise artificial intelligence to redefine how organizations deploy generative AI.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dean Takahashi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Wandercraft raises $75M for acceleration of AI-powered humanoid robotics and exoskeletons]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3011520</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/games/wandercraft-raises-75m-for-acceleration-of-ai-powered-humanoid-robotics-and-exoskeletons/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-11T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Wandercraft, a maker of self-balancing robotic mobility systems, has secured $75 million in funding to accelerate AI-powered robotics.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dean Takahashi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Quantum Art integrates Nvidia for its scalable quantum computers]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3011543</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/games/quantum-art-integrates-nvidia-for-its-scalable-quantum-computers/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-11T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Quantum Art a developer of full-stack quantum computers, has integrated Nvidia's CUDA-Q hybrid quantum-classical platform into its "qubits."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dean Takahashi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Download: Amsterdam’s welfare AI experiment, and making humanoid robots safer]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1118528</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/06/11/1118528/the-download-amsterdams-welfare-ai-experiment-and-making-humanoid-robots-safer/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-11T12:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is today’s edition of The Download, our weekday newsletter that provides a daily dose of what’s going on in the world of technology. Inside Amsterdam’s high-stakes experiment to create fair welfare AI Amsterdam thought it was on the right track. City officials in the welfare department believed they could build technology that would prevent fraud while…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rhiannon Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nvidia believes physical AI systems are a $50 trillion market opportunity]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3011509</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/games/nvidia-believes-physical-ai-systems-are-a-50-trillion-market-opportunity/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-11T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jensen Huang, CEO of Nvidia, said Nvidia's physical AI systems are poised to revolutionize industries, with a $50 trillion market opportunity.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dean Takahashi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Get Information About Your Linux System Through the Command Line]]></title>
        <id>68495738cb7b75f7a33a73c4</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/get-linux-system-info-through-cli/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-11T10:15:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Whether you’ve just gained access to a new Linux system, ethically hacked into one as part of a security test, or you’re just curious to know more about your current machine, this article will guide you through the process. You’ll learn how you can g...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Zaira Hira</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why humanoid robots need their own safety rules]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1118519</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/06/11/1118519/humanoids-safety-rules/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-11T10:11:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Last year, a humanoid warehouse robot named Digit set to work handling boxes of Spanx. Digit can lift boxes up to 16 kilograms between trolleys and conveyor belts, taking over some of the heavier work for its human colleagues. It works in a restricted, defined area, separated from human workers by physical panels or laser…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Victoria Turk</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Inside Amsterdam’s high-stakes experiment to create fair welfare AI]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1118233</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/06/11/1118233/amsterdam-fair-welfare-ai-discriminatory-algorithms-failure/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-11T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This story is a partnership between MIT Technology Review, Lighthouse Reports, and Trouw, and was supported by the Pulitzer Center.  Two futures Hans de Zwart, a gym teacher turned digital rights advocate, says that when he saw Amsterdam’s plan to have an algorithm evaluate every welfare applicant in the city for potential fraud, he nearly…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eileen Guo, Gabriel Geiger, Justin-Casimir Braun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AlphaSense launches its own Deep Research for the web AND your enterprise files — here’s why it matters]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3011457</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/alphasense-launches-its-own-deep-research-for-the-web-and-your-enterprise-files-heres-why-it-matters/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-11T00:49:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Every report generated by Deep Research includes clickable citations to underlying content, enabling both verification and deeper follow-up.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carl Franzen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Helion: A modern fast paced Doom FPS engine in C#]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/Helion-Engine/Helion</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/Helion-Engine/Helion"/>
        <updated>2025-06-10T22:56:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OpenAI launches o3-pro AI model, offering increased reliability and tool use for enterprises — while sacrificing speed]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3011390</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/openai-launches-o3-pro-ai-model-offering-increased-reliability-and-tool-use-for-enterprises-while-sacrificing-speed/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-10T22:19:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[OpenAI released the latest in its o-series of reasoning model that promises more reliable and accurate responses for enterprises.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Emilia David</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The five security principles driving open source security apps at scale]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3010821</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/security/top-five-security-principles-driving-open-source-cyber-apps-at-scale/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-10T20:52:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Open-source AI is shaping the future of cybersecurity innovation, consistently breaking down barriers and delivering results.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Louis Columbus</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[First thoughts on o3 pro]]></title>
        <id>https://www.latent.space/p/o3-pro</id>
        <link href="https://www.latent.space/p/o3-pro"/>
        <updated>2025-06-10T20:42:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AlphaOne gives AI developers a new dial to control LLM ‘thinking’ and boost performance]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3011239</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/alphaone-gives-ai-developers-a-new-dial-to-control-llm-thinking-and-boost-performance/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-10T20:34:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new framework called AlphaOne is a novel way to modulate LLM thinking, improving model accuracy and efficiency without costly retraining.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ben Dickson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Apple Code Signing Handbook]]></title>
        <id>68489084490c709f6b3070ed</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/apple-code-signing-handbook/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-10T20:07:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this handbook, I’ll demystify the Apple app code signing process. Apple's ecosystem is powerful, but its distribution mechanisms – with various identifiers, certificates, and profiles – can appear complex. This guide attempts to make that journey ...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sravan Karuturi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hyperliquid in 2025: A High-Performance DEX Building the Future of Onchain Finance]]></title>
        <id>6846e8f8529c590001648fa0</id>
        <link href="https://blog.quicknode.com/hyperliquid-protocol-analysis-2025/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-10T19:47:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Explore how hyperliquid became the leading perp DEX: A deep dive of architecture, metrics, tokenomics, and vision for onchain finance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Unhashed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mistral’s first reasoning model, Magistral, launches with large and small Apache 2.0 version]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3011320</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/mistrals-first-reasoning-model-magistral-launches-with-large-and-small-apache-2-0-version/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-10T18:55:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The company is signaling that the future of reasoning AI will be both powerful and, in a meaningful way, open to all.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carl Franzen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OpenAI announces 80% price drop for o3, it’s most powerful reasoning model]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3011288</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/openai-announces-80-price-drop-for-o3-its-most-powerful-reasoning-model/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-10T18:08:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It could benefit startups, research teams, and individual developers who previously found higher-tier model access cost-prohibitive.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carl Franzen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Deploy a Next.js App To Vercel With GitHub Actions]]></title>
        <id>684871b16bc1898625c952fd</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/deploy-to-vercel-with-github-actions/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-10T17:56:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Vercel is a cloud platform or Platform-as-a-Service (PaaS) designed to help frontend developers create, preview, and deploy web applications swiftly and efficiently. In this tutorial, we’ll focus on deploying a Next.js application to Vercel using Git...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chidiadi Anyanwu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Qualcomm shares its vision for the future of smart glasses with on-glass Gen AI]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3011107</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/games/qualcomm-shares-its-vision-for-the-future-of-smart-glasses-with-on-glass-gen-ai/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-10T16:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Qualcomm has enabled what one of its executives said was a strange and "most interesting" conversations with generative AI-powered smart glasses.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dean Takahashi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn the MERN Stack in 2025]]></title>
        <id>68483a699e226a329abe4dee</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-the-mern-stack-in-2025/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-10T14:00:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you’ve been meaning to learn full-stack web development but don’t know where to start, this new course is a solid way in. Whether you're aiming to get a job in web dev or just want to build your own projects, understanding how the pieces fit toget...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vanta’s AI agent wants to run your compliance program — and it just might]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3011165</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/vantas-ai-agent-wants-to-run-your-compliance-program-and-it-just-might/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-10T13:01:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Vanta launches autonomous AI agent that automates security compliance workflows, helping enterprises save 12+ hours weekly on policy management and audit preparation.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Nuñez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Zip debuts 50 AI agents to kill procurement inefficiencies—OpenAI is already on board]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3010781</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/zip-debuts-50-ai-agents-to-kill-procurement-inefficiencies-openai-is-already-on-board/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-10T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Zip launches 50 AI agents to automate enterprise procurement for OpenAI, Canva, targeting $4.4B in savings through automated contract reviews and compliance checks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Nuñez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Zencoder just launched an AI that can replace days of QA work in two hours]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3011083</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/zencoder-just-launched-an-ai-that-can-replace-days-of-qa-work-in-two-hours/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-10T12:59:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Zencoder launches Zentester, an AI-powered testing agent that automates end-to-end software testing, as the startup competes with GitHub Copilot and other AI coding tools in the rapidly consolidating market.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Nuñez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Your AI and Data Future is Sovereign]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1118376</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/06/10/1118376/your-ai-and-data-future-is-sovereign/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-10T12:14:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[EDB CEO, Kevin Dallas, takes the stage at MIT Technology Review's EmTech AI event.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Courtney Dobson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Download: IBM’s quantum computer, and cuts to military AI testing]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1118372</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/06/10/1118372/the-download-ibms-quantum-computer-and-cuts-to-military-ai-testing/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-10T12:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is today’s edition of The Download, our weekday newsletter that provides a daily dose of what’s going on in the world of technology. IBM aims to build the world’s first large-scale, error-corrected quantum computer by 2028 The news: IBM announced detailed plans today to build an error-corrected quantum computer with significantly more computational capability than existing…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rhiannon Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[IBM aims to build the world’s first large-scale, error-corrected quantum computer by 2028]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1118297</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/06/10/1118297/ibm-large-scale-error-corrected-quantum-computer-by-2028/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-10T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[IBM announced detailed plans today to build an error-corrected quantum computer with significantly more computational capability than existing machines by 2028. It hopes to make the computer available to users via the cloud by 2029.  The proposed machine, named Starling, will consist of a network of modules, each of which contains a set of chips,…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sophia Chen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rust compiler performance]]></title>
        <id>https://kobzol.github.io/rust/rustc/2025/06/09/why-doesnt-rust-care-more-about-compiler-performance.html</id>
        <link href="https://kobzol.github.io/rust/rustc/2025/06/09/why-doesnt-rust-care-more-about-compiler-performance.html"/>
        <updated>2025-06-10T08:24:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Archaeological evidence of intensive indigenous farming in MI's Upper Peninsula]]></title>
        <id>https://www.science.org/doi/10.1126/science.ads1643</id>
        <link href="https://www.science.org/doi/10.1126/science.ads1643"/>
        <updated>2025-06-09T22:17:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Apple makes major AI advance with image generation technology rivaling DALL-E and Midjourney]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3011035</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/apple-makes-major-ai-advance-with-image-generation-technology-rivaling-dall-e-and-midjourney/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-09T18:50:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Apple researchers develop STARFlow, a breakthrough AI image generation system that challenges diffusion models used by DALL-E and Midjourney with competitive performance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Nuñez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What are Onchain Agents: An Introduction to Autonomous, Agent-Driven Web]]></title>
        <id>6840a302a1fc8e00012e657d</id>
        <link href="https://blog.quicknode.com/introduction-to-onchain-agents/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-09T15:37:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An introduction to onchain AI agents: autonomous programs that combine blockchain trustlessness with AI intelligence. Learn how they work.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Unhashed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Top Blockchain Data Tools: How to be Informed Onchain?]]></title>
        <id>6840a419a1fc8e00012e658d</id>
        <link href="https://blog.quicknode.com/top-blockchain-data-tools/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-09T15:32:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Web3 in 2025 runs on data. This guide covers the best onchain data tools and analytics platforms and how QuickNode Streams powers them.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Unhashed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Common Solana RPC Errors & Fixes Using QuickNode Logs]]></title>
        <id>6840a20da1fc8e00012e6573</id>
        <link href="https://blog.quicknode.com/solana-rpc-errors-quicknode-logs/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-09T15:28:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn how to identify and fix common Solana RPC errors using QuickNode Logs that provide real-time insights into every request and response.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Unhashed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Developer's Guide to Monad: EVM-Compatible L1 Architecture and Implementation]]></title>
        <id>6840a4c8a1fc8e00012e6598</id>
        <link href="https://blog.quicknode.com/monad-developer-guide/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-09T15:09:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Build faster, cheaper, and better on Monad: A deep dive into Monad’s architecture, performance features, and developer workflows.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Unhashed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Quantum Computation Lecture Notes (2022)]]></title>
        <id>https://math.mit.edu/~shor/435-LN/</id>
        <link href="https://math.mit.edu/~shor/435-LN/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-09T07:54:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Like humans, AI is forcing institutions to rethink their purpose]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3010794</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/like-humans-ai-is-forcing-institutions-to-rethink-their-purpose/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-08T20:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Like people undergoing cognitive migration, institutions must reassess what they were made for in this age of AI.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gary Grossman, Edelman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dancing brainwaves: How sound reshapes your brain networks in real time]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2025/06/250602155001.htm</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2025/06/250602155001.htm"/>
        <updated>2025-06-08T11:47:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Agent-based computing is outgrowing the web as we know it]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3010786</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/agent-based-computing-is-outgrowing-the-web-as-we-know-it/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-07T22:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AI agents are moving from passive assistants to active participants. Today, we ask them to do. Tomorrow, we’ll authorize them to act.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Justin Westcott, Edelman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sam Altman calls for ‘AI privilege’ as OpenAI clarifies court order to retain temporary and deleted ChatGPT sessions]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3010670</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/sam-altman-calls-for-ai-privilege-as-openai-clarifies-court-order-to-retain-temporary-and-deleted-chatgpt-sessions/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-06T17:48:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Should talking to an AI chatbot be protected and privileged information, like talking to a doctor or lawyer? A new court order raises the idea]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carl Franzen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Voice AI that actually converts: New TTS model boosts sales 15% for major brands]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3010147</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/voice-ai-that-actually-converts-new-tts-model-boosts-sales-15-for-major-brands/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-06T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new spoken language model can quickly generate “infinite” new voices of varying genders, ages, demographics, based on a simple text prompt.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Taryn Plumb</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[From electrical engineering student to CTO with Hitesh Choudhary [Podcast #175]]]></title>
        <id>6842e00169a5099a551058ce</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/from-electrical-engineering-student-to-cto-with-hitesh-choudhary-podcast-175/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-06T12:33:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On this week's episode of the podcast, freeCodeCamp founder Quincy Larson interviews former CTO and prolific programming teacher Hitesh Choudhary.   We talk about: The limits of AI in building a robust codebase Time management Higher Education in ...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Protect Your Remote Workforce from Cyber Attacks]]></title>
        <id>6842cf8a6fcd9b03c19d04ea</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/protect-remote-workforce-from-cyber-attacks/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-06T11:22:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Working remotely gives your team flexibility, but it also opens the door to cyber threats. Remote workers are more exposed without the protection of office firewalls and on-site IT teams.  Hackers know that people often use weak passwords, forget to ...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Manish Shivanandhan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Reduce Technical Debt in the Power Platform]]></title>
        <id>6842c4f3e7fdc9878ba5dadd</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-reduce-technical-debt-in-the-power-platform/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-06T10:37:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Technical debt refers to the future cost – measured in terms of time, money, effort, or opportunity – of choosing expedient solutions today instead of more deliberate and scalable ones. And it's not just a pro-code concept. It might be easier to unde...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brandon Wozniewicz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Micro-Frontend Architecture Handbook]]></title>
        <id>6842c120a3469a9ca728862b</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/complete-micro-frontends-guide/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-06T10:21:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Over the years, in my role as a lead full-stack developer, solutions architect, and mentor, I’ve been immersed in the world of micro frontend architecture, working across different large-scale frontend projects where multiple teams, stacks, and deplo...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Maksimchenko</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OpenFeign vs WebClient: How to Choose a REST Client for Your Spring Boot Project]]></title>
        <id>6841f2c63a801418642db429</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/best-choice-openfeign-or-webclient/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-05T19:40:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When building microservices with Spring Boot, you’ll have to decide how the services will communicate with one another. The basic choices in terms of protocols are Messaging and REST. In this article we’ll discuss tools based on REST, which is a comm...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mario Casari</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Powering High-Performance Web3 Experiences: Gravity (by Galxe) Launches on QuickNode]]></title>
        <id>683622d561c46d0001eed5d9</id>
        <link href="https://blog.quicknode.com/gravity-alpha-launch/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-29T13:54:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Explore Galxe Gravity’s omnichain power on QuickNode. Build scalable, identity-centric dApps effortlessly with dedicated endpoints and developer tools.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>QuickNode</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>