<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2025-05-02T20:15:24.879Z</id>
    <title>AngJianming RSS Feed</title>
    <updated>2025-05-02T20:15:24.879Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction to Data Engineering Concepts |17| Apache Iceberg, Arrow, and Polaris]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/alexmercedcoder/introduction-to-data-engineering-concepts-17-apache-iceberg-arrow-and-polaris-2ei1</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/alexmercedcoder/introduction-to-data-engineering-concepts-17-apache-iceberg-arrow-and-polaris-2ei1"/>
        <updated>2025-05-02T19:59:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Free Resources




Free Apache Iceberg Course


Free Copy of “Apache Iceberg: The Definitive Guide”


Free Copy of “Apache Polaris: The Definitive Guide”


2025 Apache Iceberg Architecture Guide


How to Join the Iceberg Community


Iceberg Lakehouse Engineering Video Playlist


Ultimate Apache Iceberg Resource Guide 
As the data lakehouse ecosystem matures, new technologies are emerging to close the gap between raw, scalable storage and the structured, governed world of traditional analytics. Apache Iceberg, Apache Arrow, and Apache Polaris are three such technologies—each playing a distinct role in enabling high-performance, cloud-native data platforms that prioritize openness, flexibility, and consistency.
In this post, we’ll explore what each of these technologies brings to the table a…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alex Merced</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gamepad API for Game Controller Integration]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/omriluz1/gamepad-api-for-game-controller-integration-62n</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/omriluz1/gamepad-api-for-game-controller-integration-62n"/>
        <updated>2025-05-02T19:59:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Gamepad API for Game Controller Integration: A Comprehensive Guide



  
  
  Historical Context


The Gamepad API represents a significant leap in web technology, providing developers with the ability to access gamepad inputs natively within a web browser. Before this API, developers often relied on browser support for other technologies, such as Flash or native applications, to create engaging gaming experiences on the web. The introduction of the Gamepad API in the late 2010s marked a paradigm shift; it allowed developers to create immersive gaming experiences that can fully leverage console-style gamepad controls within HTML5 applications.
The specification for the Gamepad API was drafted in the W3C Gamepad Community Group and has seen constant evolution since its inception. As of late…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Omri Luz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction to Data Engineering Concepts |16| Data Lakehouse Architecture Explained]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/alexmercedcoder/introduction-to-data-engineering-concepts-16-data-lakehouse-architecture-explained-2l5k</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/alexmercedcoder/introduction-to-data-engineering-concepts-16-data-lakehouse-architecture-explained-2l5k"/>
        <updated>2025-05-02T19:58:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Free Resources




Free Apache Iceberg Course


Free Copy of “Apache Iceberg: The Definitive Guide”


Free Copy of “Apache Polaris: The Definitive Guide”


2025 Apache Iceberg Architecture Guide


How to Join the Iceberg Community


Iceberg Lakehouse Engineering Video Playlist


Ultimate Apache Iceberg Resource Guide 
Data lakes and data warehouses each brought strengths and limitations to the way organizations manage analytics. Lakes offered flexibility and scale, but lacked consistency and performance. Warehouses delivered speed and structure, but often at the cost of rigidity and duplication. The data lakehouse aims to unify the best of both worlds.
In this post, we’ll explore what a data lakehouse is, how it differs from its predecessors, and why it represents a fundamental shift in mo…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alex Merced</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Setting up and customizing an Apache web server on Linux]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/ivofonga25/setting-up-and-customizing-an-apache-web-server-on-linux-4ae1</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/ivofonga25/setting-up-and-customizing-an-apache-web-server-on-linux-4ae1"/>
        <updated>2025-05-02T19:58:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction


In this blog post, i will walk you through the proces of installing and customizing an Apache web server on linux system (Ubuntu). this project has helped me understand the practical steps of web server setup and give me hands on experience with customizing a live webpage.
step1: Chosing the Web Server


For this project, i decided to chose Apache due to its long-standing popularity, extensive documentation and ease of usage.
step2: Installing Apache


First of all, i had to update my package list to make sure the latest software version is available.
sudo apt update

Next, i installed Apache with the command
sudo apt install Apache2

step3: verifying the installation


To verify that Apache is runing, i use the command 
sudo systemctl status apache2

The output confirmed th…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ajocha ivo fonga</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction to Data Engineering Concepts |15| Cloud Data Platforms and the Modern Stack]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/alexmercedcoder/introduction-to-data-engineering-concepts-cloud-data-platforms-and-the-modern-stack-4g96</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/alexmercedcoder/introduction-to-data-engineering-concepts-cloud-data-platforms-and-the-modern-stack-4g96"/>
        <updated>2025-05-02T19:56:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Free Resources




Free Apache Iceberg Course


Free Copy of “Apache Iceberg: The Definitive Guide”


Free Copy of “Apache Polaris: The Definitive Guide”


2025 Apache Iceberg Architecture Guide


How to Join the Iceberg Community


Iceberg Lakehouse Engineering Video Playlist


Ultimate Apache Iceberg Resource Guide 
The cloud has transformed how organizations approach data engineering. What once required physical servers, manual provisioning, and heavyweight infrastructure can now be spun up in minutes with managed, scalable services. But with this convenience comes complexity—deciding how to compose the right mix of tools and platforms for your data workflows.
In this post, we’ll explore what defines the modern data stack, how cloud platforms like AWS, GCP, and Azure fit into the pictur…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alex Merced</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Future of Fragment Telegram: Anticipated Updates and Innovations in Digital Communication]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/ashucommits/the-future-of-fragment-telegram-anticipated-updates-and-innovations-in-digital-communication-2fmh</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/ashucommits/the-future-of-fragment-telegram-anticipated-updates-and-innovations-in-digital-communication-2fmh"/>
        <updated>2025-05-02T19:56:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Abstract:

This article explores the upcoming updates and innovations promised by Fragment Telegram. We dive deep into its enhanced privacy, multimedia capabilities, group and channel upgrades, artificial intelligence integrations, and blockchain interoperability. From detailed background context to practical use cases, challenges, and future outlooks, this post lights the way for both end users and businesses eager to understand how Fragment Telegram is set to reshape digital communication. For more details, check out the Original Article.
Fragment Telegram is emerging as a cutting-edge digital communication tool. Designed to blend the best of privacy, user interaction, and blockchain technology, Fragment Telegram has been rapidly gaining traction. This post provides an engaging and techn…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ashu-commits</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction to Data Engineering Concepts |14| DevOps for Data Engineering]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/alexmercedcoder/introduction-to-data-engineering-concepts-14-devops-for-data-engineering-1l72</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/alexmercedcoder/introduction-to-data-engineering-concepts-14-devops-for-data-engineering-1l72"/>
        <updated>2025-05-02T19:53:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Free Resources




Free Apache Iceberg Course


Free Copy of “Apache Iceberg: The Definitive Guide”


Free Copy of “Apache Polaris: The Definitive Guide”


2025 Apache Iceberg Architecture Guide


How to Join the Iceberg Community


Iceberg Lakehouse Engineering Video Playlist


Ultimate Apache Iceberg Resource Guide 
As data systems grow more complex and interconnected, the principles of DevOps—long applied to software engineering—have become increasingly relevant to data engineering. Continuous integration, infrastructure as code, testing, and automation aren’t just for deploying apps anymore. They’re essential for delivering reliable, maintainable, and scalable data pipelines.
In this post, we’ll explore how DevOps practices translate into the world of data engineering, why they matter,…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alex Merced</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Building a YouTube Analytics Dashboard]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/amin12905/building-a-youtube-analytics-dashboard-3i77</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/amin12905/building-a-youtube-analytics-dashboard-3i77"/>
        <updated>2025-05-02T19:52:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction


In the growing creator economy, YouTube channels pump out tons of videos every week. and Creators need a simple dashboard that answers the following questions:
How has my channel grown over time?
What is the best day and time to post a video?
What are the most engaging videos in my channel?
To tackle this, I built an end-to-end data pipeline that automatically pulls, processes, and visualizes YouTube data.
In this article goes over the steps I took to archieve this.
Instead of using Docker,I installed everything natively because it gave me more control, better performance tuning, and more flexibility compared to containerized environments.
Apache Airflow schedules and manages all the ETL jobs automatically.
First, it’s good practice to create a separate user to run Airflow (…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mohamed Amin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction to Data Engineering Concepts |13| Building Scalable Pipelines]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/alexmercedcoder/introduction-to-data-engineering-concepts-13-building-scalable-pipelines-37gf</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/alexmercedcoder/introduction-to-data-engineering-concepts-13-building-scalable-pipelines-37gf"/>
        <updated>2025-05-02T19:51:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Free Resources




Free Apache Iceberg Course


Free Copy of “Apache Iceberg: The Definitive Guide”


Free Copy of “Apache Polaris: The Definitive Guide”


2025 Apache Iceberg Architecture Guide


How to Join the Iceberg Community


Iceberg Lakehouse Engineering Video Playlist


Ultimate Apache Iceberg Resource Guide 
As data volumes increase and workflows grow more interconnected, the ability to build scalable data pipelines becomes essential. It's not enough for a pipeline to work—it needs to keep working as data grows from gigabytes to terabytes, as new sources are added, and as more users rely on the output for decision-making.
In this post, we’ll explore what makes a pipeline scalable, the principles behind designing for growth, and the tools and patterns that data engineers use to ma…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alex Merced</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto skeptic to release SBF, Mashinsky interviews in documentary]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/ben-mckenzie-documentary-bankman-fried-mashinsky</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/ben-mckenzie-documentary-bankman-fried-mashinsky?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss%3FREFRESH1635337282334&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-02T19:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ben McKenzie, an actor known for his roles on television shows including Gotham and The OC, will make his directorial debut in a scathing documentary about cryptocurrency.
According to an April 29 Deadline report, McKenzie wrote, directed, and produced the documentary Everyone Is Lying To You For Money, set to premiere at SXSW London in June. The film features footage from 2022 of former FTX CEO Sam “SBF” Bankman-Fried and former Celsius CEO Alex Mashinsky before their respective companies folded. 
“Why is the false story of crypto still spreading?” said McKenzie, according to Deadline. “That’s the question I set out to answer with this film.”
Sam Bankman-Fried (left) with Ben McKenzie (right). Source: Instagram
Working with The New Republic staff writer Jacob Silverman, McKenzie pivoted f…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Turner Wright</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction to Data Engineering Concepts |12| Scheduling and Workflow Orchestration]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/alexmercedcoder/introduction-to-data-engineering-concepts-12-scheduling-and-workflow-orchestration-6j2</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/alexmercedcoder/introduction-to-data-engineering-concepts-12-scheduling-and-workflow-orchestration-6j2"/>
        <updated>2025-05-02T19:41:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Free Resources




Free Apache Iceberg Course


Free Copy of “Apache Iceberg: The Definitive Guide”


Free Copy of “Apache Polaris: The Definitive Guide”


2025 Apache Iceberg Architecture Guide


How to Join the Iceberg Community


Iceberg Lakehouse Engineering Video Playlist


Ultimate Apache Iceberg Resource Guide 
As data pipelines grow in complexity, managing them manually becomes unsustainable. Whether you're running daily ETL jobs, refreshing dashboards, or processing streaming data in micro-batches, you need a way to coordinate and monitor these tasks reliably. That’s where workflow orchestration comes in.
In this post, we'll explore what orchestration means in the context of data engineering, how it differs from simple job scheduling, and what tools and design patterns help keep d…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alex Merced</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Economics of Fragment Telegram Fees: A Comprehensive Analysis]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/kallileiser/the-economics-of-fragment-telegram-fees-a-comprehensive-analysis-4g2n</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/kallileiser/the-economics-of-fragment-telegram-fees-a-comprehensive-analysis-4g2n"/>
        <updated>2025-05-02T19:40:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Abstract:

This post delivers a deep-dive into the fee structure powering Fragment Telegram—a decentralized messaging platform built on blockchain technology. We discuss the background, core fee components like transaction fees, service fees, and conversion fees, and explain the economic impacts these fees bring to user adoption, market competition, and revenue stability. Alongside a technical yet accessible analysis, we explore use cases, challenges, and the future of dynamic pricing models and regulatory compliance. This comprehensive guide is enhanced with tables, bullet lists, and authoritative links to provide both human readers and search engine crawlers with valuable insights.
Modern digital communications have gradually evolved from traditional messaging platforms to decentralized …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>kallileiser</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction to Data Engineering Concepts |11| Metadata, Lineage, and Governance]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/alexmercedcoder/introduction-to-data-engineering-concepts-11-metadata-lineage-and-governance-1p66</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/alexmercedcoder/introduction-to-data-engineering-concepts-11-metadata-lineage-and-governance-1p66"/>
        <updated>2025-05-02T19:38:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Free Resources




Free Apache Iceberg Course


Free Copy of “Apache Iceberg: The Definitive Guide”


Free Copy of “Apache Polaris: The Definitive Guide”


2025 Apache Iceberg Architecture Guide


How to Join the Iceberg Community


Iceberg Lakehouse Engineering Video Playlist


Ultimate Apache Iceberg Resource Guide 
As data systems grow more complex, understanding where your data came from, how it has changed, and who is responsible for it becomes just as critical as the data itself. It’s not enough to know that a dataset exists—you need to know how it was created, whether it’s trustworthy, and how it fits into the broader system.
In this post, we’ll break down three interconnected concepts—metadata, data lineage, and governance—and explore why they’re essential to building transparent, …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alex Merced</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin data, macroeconomic charts point to new BTC all-time high ‘in 100 days’ — Analysts]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-data-macroeconomic-charts-point-to-new-btc-all-time-high-in-100-days-analysts</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-data-macroeconomic-charts-point-to-new-btc-all-time-high-in-100-days-analysts?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss%3FREFRESH1635337282334&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-02T19:35:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Key Takeaways:

Analyst predicts a low VIX (

Bitcoin network economist Timothy Peterson raised Bitcoin’s (BTC) chances of hitting a new high in 100 days, and he maintains an optimistic outlook in 2025. 
In an analysis shared on X that ties BTC’s price action to the CBOE Volatility Index (VIX) —an indicator that measures 30-day market volatility expectations — the analyst pointed out that the VIX index has dropped from 55 to 25 over the past 50 trading days. A VIX score below 18 implied a “risk-on” environment, favoring assets like Bitcoin. 
Peterson’s model, which had a 95% tracking accuracy, predicted a $135,000 target within the next 100 days if the VIX remains low. This aligns with Bitcoin’s sensitivity to market sentiment, as a low VIX reduces uncertainty, encouraging investment in ri…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Biraajmaan Tamuly</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[VR Design Unpacked: The Secret to Beat Saber's Fun Isn't What You Think]]></title>
        <id>https://www.roadtovr.com/beat-saber-instructed-motion-until-you-fall-inside-xr-design/</id>
        <link href="https://www.roadtovr.com/beat-saber-instructed-motion-until-you-fall-inside-xr-design/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-02T19:16:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A proof of concept tool to verify estimates]]></title>
        <id>https://terrytao.wordpress.com/2025/05/01/a-proof-of-concept-tool-to-verify-estimates/</id>
        <link href="https://terrytao.wordpress.com/2025/05/01/a-proof-of-concept-tool-to-verify-estimates/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-02T19:09:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Images of Soviet Venus lander falling to Earth suggest its parachute may be out]]></title>
        <id>https://www.leonarddavid.com/old-soviet-venus-descent-craft-nearing-earth-reentry/</id>
        <link href="https://www.leonarddavid.com/old-soviet-venus-descent-craft-nearing-earth-reentry/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-02T19:02:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Impossible Contradictions of Mark Twain]]></title>
        <id>https://www.newyorker.com/magazine/2025/05/05/mark-twain-ron-chernow-book-review</id>
        <link href="https://www.newyorker.com/magazine/2025/05/05/mark-twain-ron-chernow-book-review"/>
        <updated>2025-05-02T18:55:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[XYO Network tops 10M DePIN nodes — Co-founder]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/xyo-network-tops-10-m-de-pin-nodes-co-founder</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/xyo-network-tops-10-m-de-pin-nodes-co-founder?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss%3FREFRESH1635337282334&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-02T18:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[XYO Network has onboarded more than 10 million nodes to its decentralized physical infrastructure network (DePIN), co-founder Markus Levin told Cointelegraph in an interview.
The nodes mostly comprise human users who provide data in exchange for rewards via the network’s mobile application, COIN. “The vast majority of our 10 million nodes are mobile users, but some are IoT devices like smart speakers,” Levin told Cointelegraph. 
Approximately 80% of XYO’s users are non-crypto natives who are participating in Web3 for the first time, he added.
They include truckers, rideshare drivers, delivery people, and nurses among others, Levin said, adding that “95% convert after onboarding through the COIN app.”
XYO launched a layer-1 blockchain network in January. Source: XYO 
Related: DePIN XYO laun…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Alex O’Donnell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Show HN: I built a synthesizer based on 3D physics]]></title>
        <id>https://anukari.com/</id>
        <link href="https://anukari.com/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-02T18:12:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin ETFs, gov’t adoption to drive BTC to $1M by 2029: Finance Redefined]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-etfs-gov-t-adoption-btc-1-m-by-2029-finance-redefined</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-etfs-gov-t-adoption-btc-1-m-by-2029-finance-redefined?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss%3FREFRESH1635337282334&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-02T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The cryptocurrency market continued its recovery in the past week as the total crypto market capitalization breached the $3 trillion mark for the first time since the beginning of March.
Bitcoin (BTC) rose to an over two-month high of $97,300 last seen at the end of February, before the “Liberation Day” tariffs announcement in the US, bolstering analyst predictions for a rally driven by “structural” institutional and exchange-traded fund (ETF) inflows into the world’s first cryptocurrency.
Risk appetite continued rising among crypto investors, as Chinese state-linked news outlets indicated that the Trump administration has quietly contacted Beijing to discuss tariff reductions.
Total crypto market cap, 1-year chart. Source: CoinMarketCap
In the wider crypto space, Ethereum developers propo…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Zoltan Vardai</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rams is a documentary portrait of Dieter Rams (2018)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hustwit.com/rams</id>
        <link href="https://www.hustwit.com/rams"/>
        <updated>2025-05-02T17:59:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OpenAI overrode concerns of expert testers to release sycophantic GPT-4o]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3006276</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/openai-overrode-concerns-of-expert-testers-to-release-sycophantic-gpt-4o/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-02T17:57:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Once again, it shows the importance of incorporating more domains beyond the traditional math and computer science into AI development.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carl Franzen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Price predictions 5/2: BTC, ETH, XRP, BNB, SOL, DOGE, ADA, SUI, LINK, AVAX]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/price-predictions-5-2-btc-eth-xrp-bnb-sol-doge-ada-sui-link-avax</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/price-predictions-5-2-btc-eth-xrp-bnb-sol-doge-ada-sui-link-avax?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss%3FREFRESH1635337282334&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-02T17:54:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Key points:

Bitcoin trends toward $100,000. Will bears sell at this level?

Altcoins are trading above their respective support levels, suggesting that an altcoin rally is brewing.

Bitcoin’s (BTC) tight consolidation resolved in favor of the bulls with a break above the $95,000 barrier on May 1. The bulls are trying to push the price to the psychologically crucial level at $100,000, which may again witness a tough battle between the bulls and the bears. 
Veteran trader Peter Brandt sounded positive when he said in a post on X that Bitcoin could rally to the $125,000 to $150,000 range by August or September 2025 if it manages to regain its broken parabolic slope. However, Brandt cautioned that the rally could be followed by a sharp correction of more than 50%.
Crypto market data daily vie…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Rakesh Upadhyay</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Show HN: Blast – Fast, multi-threaded serving engine for web browsing AI agents]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/stanford-mast/blast</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/stanford-mast/blast"/>
        <updated>2025-05-02T17:42:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The History of Album Art]]></title>
        <id>https://matthewstrom.com/writing/album-art/</id>
        <link href="https://matthewstrom.com/writing/album-art/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-02T17:30:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The SEC Can Learn From the IRS in Making Regulation Simpler for Crypto]]></title>
        <id>78bdc336-22b5-4c24-908f-f66947f9e820</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/opinion/2025/05/02/the-sec-can-learn-from-the-irs-in-making-regulation-simpler-for-crypto"/>
        <updated>2025-05-02T17:17:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The IRS has relied on voluntary disclosure programs to bring taxpayers into compliance rather than imposing punitive actions upfront. A similar model should be applied to crypto regulation as well, says Miles Fuller, Director of Government Solutions, TaxBit.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Miles Fuller</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CoinDesk Recap: Movement’s Very Bad Week]]></title>
        <id>01956a2f-bd75-40e4-9784-ab38707d3d2c</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/news-analysis/2025/05/02/coindesk-recap-movements-very-bad-week"/>
        <updated>2025-05-02T17:06:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Plus: Mastercard, World, Strategy, Kraken, and Trump]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Benjamin Schiller</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Toma (YC W24) Is Hiring Engs #3-4 (AI for Automotive)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ycombinator.com/companies/toma/jobs</id>
        <link href="https://www.ycombinator.com/companies/toma/jobs"/>
        <updated>2025-05-02T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Grayscale’s Bitcoin Trust still dominates ETF revenue in 2025]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/why-grayscales-bitcoin-trust-still-dominates-etf-revenue-2025</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/why-grayscales-bitcoin-trust-still-dominates-etf-revenue-2025?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss%3FREFRESH1635337282334&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-02T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the annals of financial history, few institutions have faced the tempests of competition with the steadfast resolve of Grayscale Bitcoin Trust (GBTC). Born in 2013 as a private placement, GBTC pioneered regulated Bitcoin investment, granting investors access to Bitcoin’s (BTC) meteoric rise without the perils of digital wallets or unregulated exchanges.
On Jan. 11, 2024, it transitioned into a spot Bitcoin ETF following a landmark victory against the SEC. This marked a pivotal moment with the SEC’s view that ETFs can offer lower expense ratios and enhanced tax efficiency compared to traditional funds. 
Even still, GBTC’s financial resilience shines, generating $268.5 million in annual revenue, surpassing the $211.8 million of all other US spot Bitcoin ETFs combined, despite losing over …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Michael Tabone</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Roblox breaks ground on data center in Brazil for early 2026]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3006251</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/games/roblox-breaks-ground-on-data-center-in-brazil-for-early-2026/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-02T16:55:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At Gamescom Latam, Roblox announced it has broken ground on a new data center in Brazil -- slated to go live in early 2026.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dean Takahashi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin is a matter of national security — Deputy CIA director]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-matter-national-security-deputy-cia-director</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-matter-national-security-deputy-cia-director?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss%3FREFRESH1635337282334&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-02T16:52:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The US Central Intelligence Agency is increasingly incorporating Bitcoin (BTC) as a tool in its operations, and working with the cryptocurrency is a matter of national security, Michael Ellis, the agency’s deputy director, told podcast host Anthony Pompliano.
In an appearance on the market analyst and investor’s show, Ellis told Pompliano that the intelligence agency works with law enforcement to track BTC, and it is a point of data collection in counter-intelligence operations. Ellis added:
"Bitcoin is here to stay — cryptocurrency is here to stay. As you know, more and more institutions are adopting it, and I think that is a great trend. One that this administration has obviously been leaning forward into."
"It's another area of competition where we need to ensure the United States is we…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Vince Quill</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Building Burstables: CPU slicing with cgroups]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ubicloud.com/blog/building-burstables-cpu-slicing-with-cgroups</id>
        <link href="https://www.ubicloud.com/blog/building-burstables-cpu-slicing-with-cgroups"/>
        <updated>2025-05-02T16:45:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Show HN: Exhibit and Site on Mechanisms for Students]]></title>
        <id>https://mechanical-library.org/</id>
        <link href="https://mechanical-library.org/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-02T16:37:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Franklin Templeton Backs Bitcoin DeFi Push, Citing ‘New Utility’ for Investors]]></title>
        <id>a8a2a3e7-0dc5-43bd-ac1b-139bb8b38afb</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2025/05/02/bitcoin-defi-shows-infrastructure-progress-versus-store-of-value-franklin-templeton-s-kevin-farrelly"/>
        <updated>2025-05-02T16:35:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA["I don’t think focusing on Bitcoin DeFi will dilute or complicate Bitcoin’s core narrative." Farrelly said.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Omkar Godbole</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin hits new 10-week high as Trump demands rate cut on US jobs beat]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-hits-10-week-high-trump-demands-rate-cut-on-us-jobs-beat</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-hits-10-week-high-trump-demands-rate-cut-on-us-jobs-beat?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss%3FREFRESH1635337282334&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-02T16:30:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Key points:

The US labor market is “still holding up” as nonfarm payrolls data comes in higher than expected.

Bitcoin and stocks head higher as US President Donald Trump repeats calls for the Fed to lower interest rates.

BTC price action may spark a “liquidity grab” above $97,000, a trader warns.

Bitcoin (BTC) hit new multimonth highs after the May 2 Wall Street open as US nonfarm payrolls data beat expectations.
BTC/USD 1-hour chart. Source: Cointelegraph/TradingView
Bitcoin meanders after nonfarm payrolls beat
Data from Cointelegraph Markets Pro and TradingView showed BTC/USD building on $97,000 as markets digested the latest in a bumper week of macro data.
Nonfarm payrolls indicated 177,000 jobs added in April, considerably more than the roughly 140,000 forecast.
“The labor market i…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by William Suberg</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cambodian Huione Group Received $98B in Crypto Leading to U.S. Crackdown: Elliptic]]></title>
        <id>02505ce6-423f-4a8e-a0bf-663db3a1c932</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2025/05/02/cambodian-huione-group-received-usd98b-in-crypto-leading-to-u-s-crackdown-elliptic"/>
        <updated>2025-05-02T15:50:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The group rolled out its own stablecoin in January to avoid traditional currency restrictions.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Oliver Knight</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kevin O’Leary: ‘Crypto Will Be the 12th Sector of the Economy’]]></title>
        <id>bccd1491-f322-4da3-bbbb-d9ede5c9a6ac</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/consensus-toronto-2025-coverage/2025/05/02/kevin-oleary-crypto-will-be-the-12th-sector-of-the-economy"/>
        <updated>2025-05-02T15:36:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ahead of Consensus 2025, the investor and TV personality shares his crypto portfolio strategy, why he won’t touch bitcoin ETFs, and what could unleash trillions into digital assets.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jennifer Sanasie</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Show HN: GPT-2 implemented using graphics shaders]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/nathan-barry/gpt2-webgl</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/nathan-barry/gpt2-webgl"/>
        <updated>2025-05-02T15:21:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The language brain matters more for programming than the math brain? (2020)]]></title>
        <id>https://massivesci.com/articles/programming-math-language-python-women-in-science/</id>
        <link href="https://massivesci.com/articles/programming-math-language-python-women-in-science/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-02T15:19:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Expanding on what we missed with sycophancy]]></title>
        <id>https://openai.com/index/expanding-on-sycophancy/</id>
        <link href="https://openai.com/index/expanding-on-sycophancy/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-02T15:07:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Free speech is at risk without decentralized, open-source technology]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/free-speech-is-at-risk</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/free-speech-is-at-risk?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss%3FREFRESH1635337282334&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-02T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Opinion by: Chris Jenkins, adviser to Pocket Network
Tim Berners-Lee’s vision of the World Wide Web is dead. Instead of an open and accessible global information system, the web is controlled by centralized global data conglomerates, which don’t just restrict free speech but also monetize your data as a price of entry. Web2 firms have built walled gardens with massive information asymmetry between companies and users.
Blockchain-based decentralized tech challenges the status quo, offering an alternative to Web2’s closed-source infrastructure. 
It enables developers and engineers to build a censorship-resistant and accessible open-data web to champion the cause of free speech. Open-source technology creates a paradigmatic shift in a fair and inclusive internet where centralized web companie…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Chris Jenkins</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Strategy’s $84B Bitcoin Expansion Plan Backed by Wall Street Analysts]]></title>
        <id>948ec075-9ba8-47be-b191-c8726a971c72</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/02/strategy-s-usd84b-bitcoin-expansion-plan-backed-by-wall-street-analysts"/>
        <updated>2025-05-02T14:34:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sell-side bulls from Benchmark and TD Cowen viewed Michael Saylor and team's plan as a bold yet realistic escalation of its bitcoin-focused strategy amid rising institutional interest.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Helene Braun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ether more ‘like a memecoin,’ says trading firm as ETH drops 45% YTD]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/ether-more-like-memecoin-two-prime-bitcoin-only</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/ether-more-like-memecoin-two-prime-bitcoin-only?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss%3FREFRESH1635337282334&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-02T14:30:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As Ether’s price has struggled in the first quarter of 2025, a US-based investment adviser firm, Two Prime, has dropped support for ETH and adopted a Bitcoin-only strategy.
After lending $1.5 billion in loans both in Bitcoin (BTC) and Ether (ETH) over the past 15 months, Two Prime decided to ditch ETH to focus solely on BTC asset management and lending, the firm announced on May 1.
“ETH’s statistical trading behavior, value proposition, and community culture have failed beyond a point that is worth engaging,” Two Primes stated.
The firm’s shift to a Bitcoin-only approach comes as ETH has lost 45% of its value year-to-date, with some optimists speculating that ETH is potentially close to the bottom and reversing its negative trend soon.
“Ether no longer trades predictably”
“As an algorithmi…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Helen Partz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Moon soon? XRP&#039;s strongest spot premium aligns with 70% rally setup]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/xrp-moon-soon-strongest-spot-premium-aligns-with-70-rally-setup</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/xrp-moon-soon-strongest-spot-premium-aligns-with-70-rally-setup?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss%3FREFRESH1635337282334&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-02T14:25:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Key takeaways:

XRP’s strongest spot premium phase suggests real buying demand, not just speculative futures trading. 

The number of XRP addresses holding ≥10,000 tokens has steadily climbed, even during recent price pullbacks. 

A falling wedge pattern points to a possible breakout toward $3 to $3.78, with up to 70% upside if confirmed.

XRP (XRP) is experiencing its strongest sustained phase of spot premium in history, a period where the spot market has been consistently trading at stronger levels compared to perpetual futures.
XRP’s 350% rally is backed by real demand  
Since 2020, most major XRP price peaks happened when the perpetual futures market was leading, noted market analyst Dom in his May 2 post on X. 
XRP’s futures prices being higher than spot signaled excessive speculation…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Yashu Gola</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Here’s what happened in crypto today]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/what-happened-in-crypto-today</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/what-happened-in-crypto-today?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss%3FREFRESH1635337282334&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-02T13:56:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today in crypto, the European Union is set to ban anonymous crypto accounts and privacy coins starting in 2027 under sweeping new Anti-Money Laundering (AML) regulations, the US Treasury moved to cut the Huione Group off from the financial system over its crypto crime ties, and Coinbase is set to halt trading for the MOVE token.
European Union to ban anonymous crypto and privacy tokens by 2027
The European Union is set to impose sweeping AML rules that will ban privacy-preserving tokens and anonymous cryptocurrency accounts from 2027.
Under the new Anti-Money Laundering Regulation (AMLR), credit institutions, financial institutions and crypto asset service providers (CASPs) will be prohibited from maintaining anonymous accounts or handling privacy-preserving cryptocurrencies, such as Moner…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Cointelegraph</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google is hurting new apps that have less users than competitors]]></title>
        <id>https://support.google.com/googleplay/android-developer/thread/330114530/fewer-users-warning-hurting-specialized-and-new-apps-need-answers?hl=en</id>
        <link href="https://support.google.com/googleplay/android-developer/thread/330114530/fewer-users-warning-hurting-specialized-and-new-apps-need-answers?hl=en"/>
        <updated>2025-05-02T13:54:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin unsure as recession looms, US-China tariff talks kick off]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-uncertainty-recession-us-china-trade-talks</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-uncertainty-recession-us-china-trade-talks?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss%3FREFRESH1635337282334&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-02T13:49:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin’s recovery to its all-time high may be threatened by rising recession fears, which could ease if the United States and China begin tariff negotiations this month, research analysts told Cointelegraph.
Appetite for global risk assets such as Bitcoin (BTC) may take another hit, with analysts from Apollo Global Management predicting a recession by the summer.
“Apollo predicting Summer Recession: Sharpest decline in earnings outlook since 2020,” cross-asset analyst Samantha LaDuc wrote in an April 26 X post.
The progress on the tariff negotiations may be the most significant factor impacting a potential recession and Bitcoin’s price trajectory, according to Aurelie Barthere, principal research analyst at crypto intelligence platform Nansen.
Source: Samantha LaDuc

“May is seen as pivot…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Zoltan Vardai</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Suno v4.5]]></title>
        <id>https://suno.com/explore/</id>
        <link href="https://suno.com/explore/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-02T13:18:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Cannae Problem]]></title>
        <id>https://www.joanwestenberg.com/the-cannae-problem/</id>
        <link href="https://www.joanwestenberg.com/the-cannae-problem/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-02T13:11:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[UK regulator moves to restrict borrowing for crypto investments]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/uk-fca-crypto-credit-investment-ban</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/uk-fca-crypto-credit-investment-ban?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss%3FREFRESH1635337282334&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-02T13:11:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The United Kingdom’s financial regulator, the Financial Conduct Authority (FCA), plans to stop retail investors from borrowing money to fund their crypto investments.
According to a May 2 Financial Times report, the ban on borrowing to fund crypto purchases is one of the upcoming crypto rules by the FCA. David Geale, FCA executive director of payments and digital finance, told the FT that “crypto is an area of potential growth for the UK, but it has to be done right.” He added:
“To do that we have to provide an appropriate level of protection.”
Geale denied claims that the FCA is hostile to the crypto industry. Instead, he explained that he views the industry as offering high-risk investments with less consumer protection. “We are open for business,“ he said.
The interview follows the FCA …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Adrian Zmudzinski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CoinDesk 20 Performance Update: SUI Drops 5.9% as Index Trades Lower]]></title>
        <id>80df5460-4087-47aa-8242-c866619082ba</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/coindesk-indices/2025/05/02/coindesk-20-performance-update-sui-drops-5-9-as-index-trades-lower"/>
        <updated>2025-05-02T13:10:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Avalanche (AVAX) was also among the underperformers, falling 2.4% from Thursday.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CoinDesk Indices</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Are Donald Trump’s tariffs a legal house of cards?]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/are-donald-trumps-tariffs-legal-house-of-cards</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/are-donald-trumps-tariffs-legal-house-of-cards?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss%3FREFRESH1635337282334&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-02T12:54:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On Wednesday, speaking from the White House, US President Donald Trump suggested that families scale back on gifts this year.
Asked about his tariff program, the president remarked, “Somebody said, ‘Oh, the shelves are gonna be open. Well, maybe the children will have two dolls instead of 30 dolls, and maybe the two dolls will cost a couple of bucks more.’”
But the toy stores where those dolls are sold might have something to say about it. 
Earlier in the week, Mischief Toy Store in St. Paul, Minnesota joined a growing number of American small businesses suing the president over his emergency tariff plan.
Throughout April, a groundswell of lawsuits led by 13 states further challenged Trump’s ambitious tariff program. Their success or failure rests on hundreds of years of judicial policy an…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Aaron Brogan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tether’s U.S.-Focused Stablecoin Could Launch Later This Year, CEO Paolo Ardoino Says]]></title>
        <id>139fe562-bf9d-4889-9dc5-68ce9698a2ed</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2025/05/02/tether-s-u-s-focussed-stablecoin-may-launch-later-this-year-ceo-ardoino-says"/>
        <updated>2025-05-02T12:46:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The company's U.S. plans depend on the final stablecoin legislation, and is aiming to create a "payment product" that institutions can use, Paolo Ardoino said in a CNBC interview.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Krisztian Sandor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[U.S. Added Stronger Than Expected 177K Jobs in April]]></title>
        <id>b0accd14-95e9-4d1e-89c6-dc819628417f</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/02/us-added-stronger-than-expected-177k-jobs-in-april"/>
        <updated>2025-05-02T12:35:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The price of bitcoin was modestly lower at $96,700 in the moments following the news.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephen Alpher</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Common Lisp jq replacement]]></title>
        <id>https://world-playground-deceit.net/blog/2025/03/a-common-lisp-jq-replacement.html</id>
        <link href="https://world-playground-deceit.net/blog/2025/03/a-common-lisp-jq-replacement.html"/>
        <updated>2025-05-02T12:15:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Download: foreign disinformation intel, and gene-edited pork]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1116079</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/05/02/1116079/the-download-foreign-disinformation-intel-and-gene-edited-pork/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-02T12:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is today’s edition of The Download, our weekday newsletter that provides a daily dose of what’s going on in the world of technology. A senior State Department official demanded records of communications with journalists, European officials, and Trump critics A previously unreported document distributed by senior US State Department official Darren Beattie reveals a sweeping effort…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rhiannon Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Traders Brace for ‘Sell in May and Go Away’ as Seasonality Favors Bears]]></title>
        <id>7b93f9f5-ff5f-4582-a4e6-710a7cae724d</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/02/bitcoin-traders-brace-for-sell-in-may-and-go-away-as-seasonality-favours-bears"/>
        <updated>2025-05-02T12:05:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Could a centuries-old seasonal market pattern be a sign of further losses? Bitcoin’s five-year performance leans toward “yes.”]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shaurya Malwa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[KuCoin to reenter South Korea after securing key markets: CEO]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/kucoin-ceo-south-korea-plans-compliance-challenges-token2049</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/kucoin-ceo-south-korea-plans-compliance-challenges-token2049?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss%3FREFRESH1635337282334&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-02T11:56:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto exchange KuCoin said that it may reenter South Korea after its platform was blocked in the country. 
On March 21, South Korean regulators ordered Google Play to block access to exchanges that were not compliant with the requirements needed to operate in the country. On April 11, South Korea’s Financial Services Commission (FSC) ordered the Apple Store to block unregistered crypto exchanges. 
KuCoin was among those affected by the country’s crackdown on unregistered platforms that were previously available. While the platform is now unavailable to South Koreans, it has not fully abandoned the jurisdiction. 
In an exclusive interview with Cointelegraph, KuCoin’s newly appointed CEO, BC Wong, said that the crypto exchange has plans to reenter the country. 
Wong (left), KuCoin EU CEO Ol…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Ezra Reguerra</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kraken's Quarterly Revenue Jumps 19% to $472M in Q1, Trading Volume Rises by 29%]]></title>
        <id>fa65ddca-2ac1-4c2c-bcc6-febe23fbd47a</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/02/krakens-quarterly-revenue-jumps-19-to-472m-in-q1-trading-volume-rises-by-29"/>
        <updated>2025-05-02T11:53:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The exchange posted adjusted EBITDA of $187 million, a 1% increase from the previous quarter and a 17% rise year-over-year.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Francisco Rodrigues</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[EU to ban anonymous crypto accounts and privacy coins by 2027]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/eu-crypto-ban-anonymous-privacy-tokens-2027</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/eu-crypto-ban-anonymous-privacy-tokens-2027?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss%3FREFRESH1635337282334&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-02T11:32:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The European Union is set to impose sweeping Anti-Money Laundering (AML) rules that will ban privacy-preserving tokens and anonymous cryptocurrency accounts from 2027.
Under the new Anti-Money Laundering Regulation (AMLR), credit institutions, financial institutions and crypto asset service providers (CASPs) will be prohibited from maintaining anonymous accounts or handling privacy-preserving cryptocurrencies, such as Monero (XMR) and Zcash (ZEC).
“Article 79 of the AMLR establishes strict prohibitions on anonymous accounts [...]. Credit institutions, financial institutions, and crypto-asset service providers are prohibited from maintaining anonymous accounts,” according to the AML Handbook, published by European Crypto Initiative (EUCI).
The AML Handbook. Source: EUCI
The regulation is pa…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Zoltan Vardai</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google Adds Blockchain Tech to Wallet to Let Users Prove Age Without Sharing Data]]></title>
        <id>88ddd081-0c2b-4cdb-81d4-745436f70a70</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/02/google-adds-zero-knowledge-proofs-to-wallet-for-age-verification"/>
        <updated>2025-05-02T11:20:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The new cryptographic system lets users prove they’re old enough to use restricted applications without giving more information than required.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shaurya Malwa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Daybook Americas: All Eyes on Jobs, Fed as Bitcoin Prepares for Breakout Rally]]></title>
        <id>a74cd382-8207-47f1-ae66-9502332e8671</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/daybook-us/2025/05/02/crypto-daybook-americas-all-eyes-on-jobs-fed-as-bitcoin-prepares-for-breakout-rally"/>
        <updated>2025-05-02T11:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Your day-ahead look for May 2, 2025]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Francisco Rodrigues</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[US Court To Apple: No More Collecting Fees From Non-App Store Purchases]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=350337</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/350337/us-court-to-apple-no-more-collecting-fees-from-non-app-store-purchases/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-02T11:11:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[US District Court Judge Yvonne Gonzalez Rogers recently ruled that Apple had violated her 2021 ruling of a lawsuit filed against the fruit company by Epic Games. “For the reasons set forth herein, the Court finds Apple in willful violation of this Court’s 2021 Injunction which issued to restrain and prohibit Apple’s anticompetitive conduct and […]
The post US Court To Apple: No More Collecting Fees From Non-App Store Purchases appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John Law</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Webflow makes GSAP 100% free – plus more updates]]></title>
        <id>https://webflow.com/blog/gsap-becomes-free</id>
        <link href="https://webflow.com/blog/gsap-becomes-free"/>
        <updated>2025-05-02T11:09:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Altair at 50: Remembering the first Personal Computer]]></title>
        <id>https://www.goto10retro.com/p/altair-at-50-remembering-the-first</id>
        <link href="https://www.goto10retro.com/p/altair-at-50-remembering-the-first"/>
        <updated>2025-05-02T11:03:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to live an intellectually rich life]]></title>
        <id>https://utsavmamoria.substack.com/p/how-to-live-an-intellectually-rich</id>
        <link href="https://utsavmamoria.substack.com/p/how-to-live-an-intellectually-rich"/>
        <updated>2025-05-02T10:58:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google To Release NotebookLM App For Mobile Devices Later This Month]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=350348</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/350348/google-to-release-notebooklm-app-for-mobile-devices-later-this-month/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-02T10:54:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google is preparing to launch a mobile version of its NotebookLM platform, set to arrive on both Android and iOS on 20 May 2025. While the app listings are already live on the Play Store and Apple App Store, downloads won’t be available until the release date. In the meantime, you can register your interest […]
The post Google To Release NotebookLM App For Mobile Devices Later This Month appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Heirul Kamel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Totalitarian Buddhist Who Beat SIM City (2010)]]></title>
        <id>https://web.archive.org/web/20211117094441/https://www.vice.com/en/article/4w4kg3/the-totalitarian-buddhist-who-beat-sim-city</id>
        <link href="https://web.archive.org/web/20211117094441/https://www.vice.com/en/article/4w4kg3/the-totalitarian-buddhist-who-beat-sim-city"/>
        <updated>2025-05-02T10:46:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Circle’s Refund Protocol, explained: Bringing refunds to stablecoin payments]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/explained/circles-refund-protocol-explained-bringing-refunds-to-stablecoin-payments</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/explained/circles-refund-protocol-explained-bringing-refunds-to-stablecoin-payments?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss%3FREFRESH1635337282334&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-02T10:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Why are refunds important in stablecoin payments?            
            
                
Anyone who has used traditional payment systems will likely be familiar with refunds and chargebacks. If a purchase goes wrong, like receiving damaged items or not receiving the product at all, the payer can file a complaint with the seller to recover their funds. This process of refunds builds trust between payers and sellers, ensuring secure transactions for both sides.
However, stablecoin transactions differ significantly. Unlike credit cards or PayPal, stablecoin payments are generally irreversible. Once sent, the payment is final, with no standard way to dispute or reverse it if issues arise, which can make payers wary of using stablecoins for daily purchases.
This highlights the importance of …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Dilip Kumar Patairya</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin hodler unrealized profits near 350% as $100K risks sell-off]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-hodler-unrealized-profits-near-350-100k-risks-sell-off</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-hodler-unrealized-profits-near-350-100k-risks-sell-off?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss%3FREFRESH1635337282334&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-02T10:38:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Key points:

Bitcoin long-term holders are about to hit a level of unrealized profit, which has traditionally caused them to sell.

That level coincides with the return to a six-figure BTC price.

Order book data suggests that bulls may not succeed in keeping the upside going.

Bitcoin (BTC) risks a “notable increase” in selling from its older investors if price rises further, warns onchain analytics firm Glassnode.
In the latest edition of its regular newsletter, “The Week Onchain,” researchers calculated that long-term holders (LTHs) are sitting on almost 350% unrealized profits.
Bitcoin sell-side odds in line for crucial test
Bitcoin at multimonth highs will tempt an increasing number of hodlers to take profits — including so-called “diamond hands.”
Using a variety of metrics to track i…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by William Suberg</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Movement Labs suspends co-founder following MOVE market turmoil]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/movement-labs-cofounder-suspended-over-market-maker-controversy</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/movement-labs-cofounder-suspended-over-market-maker-controversy?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss%3FREFRESH1635337282334&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-02T09:53:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Movement Labs confirmed the suspension of its co-founder, Rushi Manche, following controversies over a market maker deal that he brokered.
Movement announced the suspension of Manche in a May 2 X post, explaining that the “decision was made in light of ongoing events.” The decision follows Coinbase's recent decision to suspend the Movement Network (MOVE) trading, citing the token’s failure to meet its listing standards.
Source: Movement
The suspension came after a recently announced third-party review requested by the Movement Network Foundation into an agreement orchestrated by Manche with Rentech — the latter helped broker an agreement with market maker Web3Port. Private intelligence firm Groom Lake is conducting the investigation.
This was followed by Web3Port reportedly selling the 66 …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Adrian Zmudzinski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Samsung Galaxy Z Flip7 Reportedly Getting Exynos 2500 Chip]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=350319</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/350319/samsung-galaxy-z-flip7-reportedly-getting-exynos-2500-chip/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-02T09:45:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Another day brings in yet another leak surrounding the upcoming Samsung Galaxy Z Flip7 and Fold7 phones. We’ve previously heard rumours about their purported specs, slimness, and cameras. Now, a new report, courtesy of The Chosun Daily, alleges that the Z Flip7 will feature Samsung’s in-house Exynos 2500 chipset. This decision was apparently made with […]
The post Samsung Galaxy Z Flip7 Reportedly Getting Exynos 2500 Chip appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Newsdesk</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GWM Reportedly Launching The Tank 500 Hybrid SUV In Malaysia During MAS 2025]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=350313</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/350313/gwm-reportedly-launching-the-tank-500-hybrid-suv-in-malaysia-during-mas-2025/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-02T09:40:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The GWM Tank 500 will be launched on 8 May during this year’s Malaysia Autoshow (MAS 2025), Paultan.org reports. As you may recall, the hybrid SUV was initially unveiled at the Kuala Lumpur International Mobility Show (KLIMS) last December, alongside the brand’s Wey 80 MPV. To recap, the GWM Tank 500 is a seven-seater vehicle […]
The post GWM Reportedly Launching The Tank 500 Hybrid SUV In Malaysia During MAS 2025 appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Keran</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Janet Jackson’s Rhythm Nation Was Once The Cause Of Laptop Crashes]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=350298</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/350298/janet-jacksons-rhythm-nation-was-once-the-cause-of-laptop-crashes/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-02T09:27:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Janet Jackson’s Rhythm Nation is best remembered as one of the many anthems of the 80s. But for some technicians and laptop vendors, this song was the bane, a scourge to laptops everywhere, causing them to crash without any warning, and for nearly a decade. Now, to understand this weird phenomenon, we need to take […]
The post Janet Jackson’s Rhythm Nation Was Once The Cause Of Laptop Crashes appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John Law</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[UK’s FCA Seeks Public and Industry Views on Crypto Regulation]]></title>
        <id>aa514eb9-f086-4076-bd79-cdf33344f63b</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2025/05/02/uks-fca-seeks-public-and-industry-views-on-crypto-regulation"/>
        <updated>2025-05-02T09:23:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Financial Conduct Authority is seeking views on intermediaries, staking, lending and borrowing, and decentralised finance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Camomile Shumba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[From digital identity to outer space: Projects push crypto use cases]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/blockchain-digital-identity-outer-space-ai-connectivity-use-cases</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/blockchain-digital-identity-outer-space-ai-connectivity-use-cases?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss%3FREFRESH1635337282334&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-02T09:04:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As the crypto space developed, blockchain use cases expanded from simple digital currencies and non-fungible tokens (NFTs) to more complex areas such as digital identity verification and telecommunications. 
Ahead of the Token2049 event in Dubai, Cointelegraph spoke with Spacecoin CEO Stuart Gardner, Spacecoin founder Tae Oh, and Humanity Protocol founder Terrence Kwok to explore how they use blockchain to improve certain industries. 
From addressing challenges like verification in the artificial intelligence era to bringing internet connectivity to developing countries, projects are integrating blockchain to solve problems in different industries.  

Digital identity verification to combat the AI threat 
As artificial intelligence developed, the technology brought improvements that people…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Ezra Reguerra</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Stablecoins: Depegging, fraudsters and decentralization]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/stablecoins-depegging-fraudsters-decentralization</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/stablecoins-depegging-fraudsters-decentralization?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss%3FREFRESH1635337282334&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-02T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Opinion by: Merav Ozair, PhD
Lately, stablecoins are everywhere — this time around, headed by “traditional” financial institutions. Bank of America and Standard Chartered are considering launching their own stablecoin, joining JPMorgan, which launched its stablecoin, JPM Coin — rebranded as Kinexys Digital Payments — to facilitate transactions with their institutional clients on their blockchain platform, Kinexys (formerly Onyx). 
Mastercard plans to bring stablecoins to the mainstream, joining Bleap Finance, a crypto startup. The aim is to enable stablecoins to be spent directly onchain — without conversions or intermediaries — seamlessly integrating blockchain assets with Mastercard’s global payment rails. 
In early April 2025, Visa joined the Global Dollar Network (USDG) stablecoin cons…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Dr. Merav Ozair</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Metaplanet Issues $25M Bonds to Buy More Bitcoin]]></title>
        <id>c48f128f-cc7d-4f6f-b547-fd3d2947e370</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/02/metaplanet-issues-25m-bonds-to-buy-more-bitcoin"/>
        <updated>2025-05-02T08:54:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The bonds, redeemable in 2025, will be repaid through capital raised from stock acquisition rights.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Francisco Rodrigues</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lepas: Yet Another Sub-Brand From Chery]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=350275</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/350275/lepas-yet-another-sub-brand-from-chery/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-02T08:16:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Chery appears to be assembling an army of sub-brands in the automotive industry, with its latest addition is a brand called “Lepas”. Yes, it may sound like the Malay word for “letting go”, but we assure that it is not the case. According to Chery, the name is a fusion of “leap” and “passion”, and […]
The post Lepas: Yet Another Sub-Brand From Chery appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Keran</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The US has approved CRISPR pigs for food]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1116059</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/05/02/1116059/the-us-approves-crispr-pigs-for-food/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-02T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Most pigs in the US are confined to factory farms where they can be afflicted by a nasty respiratory virus that kills piglets. The illness is called porcine reproductive and respiratory syndrome, or PRRS. A few years ago, a British company called Genus set out to design pigs immune to this germ using CRISPR gene…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Antonio Regalado</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Unifi Mobile Offers 32,500 Free SIM Cards Via Tabung Haji Events]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=350283</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/350283/unifi-mobile-offers-32500-free-sim-cards-via-tabung-haji-events/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-02T07:48:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Unifi Mobile has announced that, in addition to its own roaming plans for Hajj pilgrims, it is giving out free prepaid SIM cards to pilgrims who attend select events organised by Tabung Haji. Via its Sahabat Korporate TH 2025 program, the company is giving away up to 32,500 prepaid SIM cards for free. The company […]
The post Unifi Mobile Offers 32,500 Free SIM Cards Via Tabung Haji Events appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ian Chee</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Just redesigned my personal site with a TTY-style interface]]></title>
        <id>https://www.abdisa.me/</id>
        <link href="https://www.abdisa.me/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-02T07:48:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Artificial general intelligence (AGI): Can it really think like a human?]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/explained/artificial-general-intelligence-agi-can-it-really-think-like-a-human</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/explained/artificial-general-intelligence-agi-can-it-really-think-like-a-human?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss%3FREFRESH1635337282334&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-02T07:33:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What is AGI?            
            
                
When the lines blur between man and machine, you’re looking at artificial general intelligence (AGI). Unlike its counterpart, artificial narrow intelligence (ANI), which is the use of AI for solving individual problem statements, AGI represents artificial intelligence that can understand, learn and apply knowledge in a way that is indistinguishable from human cognition.
AGI is still theoretical, but the prospect of artificial intelligence being able to holistically replace human input and judgment has naturally attracted plenty of interest, with researchers, technologists and academics alike seeking to bring the concept of AGI to reality. 
Yet another strand of prevailing research seeks to explore the feasibility and implications of AG…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Jules Winnfield</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pinterest Adds Labels To Identify AI-Generated Content]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=350263</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/350263/pinterest-adds-labels-to-identify-ai-generated-content/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-02T07:21:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Pinterest has introduced labels for identifying AI-generated content to its platform. In a blog post shared this week, the company explained that it had been testing the feature over the past few months, and that it is also working on tools to aid users in managing their experience with generative AI. This feature has been […]
The post Pinterest Adds Labels To Identify AI-Generated Content appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nurul Kamil</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dogecoin, XRP ETF Hopes Are Fuelling Bullish Sentiment, Social Data Shows]]></title>
        <id>bc24e3a5-5697-434c-9ae4-fd05f13803d6</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/02/dogecoin-xrp-etf-hopes-are-fuelling-bullish-sentiment-social-data-shows"/>
        <updated>2025-05-02T07:21:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Traders grow more optimistic on approval odds as social buzz rebounds across the two majors.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shaurya Malwa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Prasarana Releases New MyRapid Pulse App With New Features]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=350261</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/350261/prasarana-releases-new-myrapid-pulse-app-with-new-features/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-02T07:13:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In what it states is an effort to push forth our country’s national mobility agenda, Prasarana Malaysia Berhad (Prasarana) has introduced a new version of its MyRapid PULSE trip planner app. The original version, which was launched back in 2020, was discontinued on 1 May. Via a statement released from its official website, Prasarana states […]
The post Prasarana Releases New MyRapid Pulse App With New Features appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ian Chee</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Maxis Announces Fibre Network Infrastructure Expansion In Penang]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=350269</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/350269/maxis-announces-fibre-network-infrastructure-expansion-in-penang/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-02T07:07:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Maxis has announced a major expansion of its fibre broadband network in Penang, aiming to connect over 100,000 homes statewide by 2027. The initiative supports the Penang2030 plan, which targets the development of a digital and inclusive state. According to the telco, the deployment will cover all districts, with a focus on high-demand urban areas. […]
The post Maxis Announces Fibre Network Infrastructure Expansion In Penang appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Heirul Kamel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto in ‘gamble mindset’ as memecoin mentions hit YTD high: Santiment]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/crypto-gamble-mindset-memecoin-discussions-ytd-high-santiment</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/crypto-gamble-mindset-memecoin-discussions-ytd-high-santiment?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss%3FREFRESH1635337282334&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-02T05:57:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Online discussions about memecoins have hit a year-to-date high, gaining considerable attention after sentiment cooled earlier in the year, according to onchain analytics platform Santiment. 
Two weeks ago, discussions around Bitcoin (BTC) and layer-1 protocols peaked during the market volatility brought on by the Trump administration’s sweeping tariffs. However, that’s since shifted to high market cap memecoins, Santiment marketing director Brian Quinlivan said in a May 1 blog post.
“Online discussions about these high-risk tokens have proliferated as traders embrace a gamble mindset, rather than a calculated investment approach,” he said.
“This is a telltale sign that traders are increasingly investing based solely on speculation and short-term gains,” Quinlivan added.
Online discussions…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Stephen Katte</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Riot Platforms posts Q1 loss, beats revenue estimates]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/riot-platforms-bitcoin-miner-revenue-earnings-report-q1-2025</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/riot-platforms-bitcoin-miner-revenue-earnings-report-q1-2025?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss%3FREFRESH1635337282334&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-02T05:29:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin miner Riot Platforms reported its highest-ever quarterly revenue, but still posted a loss as mining costs have nearly doubled compared to the same period last year amid efforts to expand its facilities.
“We achieved a new record for quarterly revenue this quarter, at $161.4 million,” Riot CEO Jason Les said in a May 1 report for its first quarter 2025 earnings. The company just surpassed Wall Street estimates of $159.79 million by 1%.
Riot’s Q1 revenue was a 50% jump compared to the same quarter a year ago.
Riot blames “halving event” for expenses
The firm reported a net loss of $296,367 over Q1, a 240% decrease from the $211,777 net income it posted in the year-ago quarter.
Riot said that the average cost to mine Bitcoin (BTC) over the quarter was $43,808, almost 90% more than the…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Ciaran Lyons</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Jumps Above $97K as Traders Optimistic U.S.-China Trade Deal Possible]]></title>
        <id>95a1779c-8bab-46e8-ae67-bd8e09ea5e81</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/02/bitcoin-jumps-above-97k-as-traders-optimistic-us-china-trade-deal-possible"/>
        <updated>2025-05-02T05:04:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[But bettors are skeptical that a trade deal can be reached before June.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sam Reynolds</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Don't watermark your legal PDFs with purple dragons in suits]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2025/05/dont-watermark-your-legal-pdfs-with-purple-dragons-in-suits/</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2025/05/dont-watermark-your-legal-pdfs-with-purple-dragons-in-suits/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-02T04:49:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[US Treasury wants to cut off Huione over ties to crypto crime]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/us-treasury-cutting-huione-banking-system-crypto-laundering-ties</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/us-treasury-cutting-huione-banking-system-crypto-laundering-ties?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss%3FREFRESH1635337282334&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-02T04:39:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The US Treasury Department is seeking to bar the Cambodia-based Huione Group from accessing the American banking system, accusing the company of helping North Korea’s state-sponsored Lazarus Group launder cryptocurrency.
The Treasury’s Financial Crimes Enforcement Network (FinCEN) proposed on May 1 to prohibit US financial institutions from opening or maintaining correspondent or payable-through accounts for or on behalf of the Huione Group.
Huione Group has established itself as the “marketplace of choice for malicious cyber actors” like the Lazarus Group, who have “stolen billions of dollars from everyday Americans,” US Treasury Secretary Scott Bessent said in a May 1 statement.
“Today’s proposed action will sever Huione Group’s access to correspondent banking, degrading these groups’ ab…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Brayden Lindrea</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SEC files to drop crypto promo case against YouTuber Ian Balina]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/sec-to-drop-crypto-promo-case-against-youtuber-ian-balina</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/sec-to-drop-crypto-promo-case-against-youtuber-ian-balina?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss%3FREFRESH1635337282334&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-02T04:18:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The US Securities and Exchange Commission has filed to drop another of its crypto lawsuits, this time its unregistered securities sales case against crypto influencer and YouTuber Ian Balina. 
The SEC said in a May 1 joint stipulation with Balina to an Austin federal court that it “believes the dismissal of this case is appropriate,” citing the work of the agency’s Crypto Task Force.
The agency didn’t give a reason for wanting to dismiss its case, but said its decision “does not necessarily reflect the Commission’s position on any other case.”
Balina told Cointelegraph in March that the SEC had informed him it would recommend the court dismiss the case and claimed the agency’s actions were based on a shift in the agency’s priorities.
“Obviously, the new administration is pro-crypto,” Balin…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Martin Young</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Movement Labs Suspends Rushi Manche Amid Coinbase Delisting, Token-Dumping Scandal]]></title>
        <id>cee6719f-5828-45ef-96c9-d68109d7a8df</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/02/movement-labs-suspends-rushi-manche-after-coinbase-delists-move-token"/>
        <updated>2025-05-02T03:16:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Movement Labs cites 'ongoing events' as the reason for suspension.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sam Reynolds</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sky pitches ousting Maker token to complete upgrade]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/sky-pitches-ousting-maker-token-completing-upgrade</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/sky-pitches-ousting-maker-token-completing-upgrade?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss%3FREFRESH1635337282334&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-02T03:01:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decentralized finance (DeFi) lending platform Sky has pitched a proposal to finalize its upgrade from Maker by replacing its governance token and enabling staking.
The proposal, posted on May 1 to Sky’s decentralized autonomous organization (DAO) forum, would see the Sky (SKY) token take over the Maker (MKR) token as the protocol’s governance token.
If the DAO accepts, the change would be slated to take place around May 15 to May 19 and downgrading from SKY to MKR would also be disabled.
Sky co-founder Rune Christensen said in response to the proposal that it was a “huge milestone,” which he “fully supports,” and laments that allowing users to downgrade from SKY back to MKR has been a “key limiting factor preventing exchanges from adopting SKY.”
“With this change, exchanges are likely to m…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Stephen Katte</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kraken tells how it spotted North Korean hacker in job interview]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/kraken-details-how-it-spotted-north-korean-hacker-in-job-interview</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/kraken-details-how-it-spotted-north-korean-hacker-in-job-interview?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss%3FREFRESH1635337282334&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-02T02:38:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[US crypto exchange Kraken has detailed a North Korean hacker’s attempt to infiltrate the organization by applying for a job interview.
“What started as a routine hiring process for an engineering role quickly turned into an intelligence-gathering operation,” the company wrote in a May 1 blog post.
Kraken said the applicant’s red flags appeared early on in the process when they joined an interview under a name different from what they applied with and “occasionally switched between voices,” apparently being guided through the interview.
Rather than immediately rejecting the applicant, Kraken decided to advance them through its hiring process to gather information about the tactics used.
International sanctions have effectively cut North Korea off from the rest of the world, and the country’…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Martin Young</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kraken finalizes NinjaTrader buy as Q1 revenue jumps 19%]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/kraken-confirms-ninjatrader-aquisition-q1-revenue-rises</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/kraken-confirms-ninjatrader-aquisition-q1-revenue-rises?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss%3FREFRESH1635337282334&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-02T00:54:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto exchange Kraken has completed its acquisition of the futures trading platform NinjaTrader and reported its first quarter revenues jumped 19% year-on-year to $471.7 million.
Kraken said in a May 1 report that its NinjaTrader acquisition would give its US customers access to the traditional derivatives market, aligning with its plans to expand its offerings and be the go-to platform for all types of trading.
NinjaTrader is a registered Futures Commission Merchant with the Commodity Futures Trading Commission. Last month, it rolled out trading for over 11,000 stocks and exchange-traded funds to certain US clients.
The deal, which Kraken dubbed the largest ever between a crypto and traditional finance firm, allows NinjaTrader to expand to the UK, continental Europe and Australian market…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Brayden Lindrea</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[When Americana doesn't mean American]]></title>
        <id>https://deeprootsmag.org/2017/09/18/over-there-when-americana-doesnt-mean-american/</id>
        <link href="https://deeprootsmag.org/2017/09/18/over-there-when-americana-doesnt-mean-american/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-02T00:13:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fast(er) regular expression engines in Ruby]]></title>
        <id>https://serpapi.com/blog/faster-regular-expression-engines-in-ruby/</id>
        <link href="https://serpapi.com/blog/faster-regular-expression-engines-in-ruby/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-02T00:00:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[U.S. Senate Moves Toward Action on Stablecoin Bill]]></title>
        <id>c0194c8e-984d-4cbf-89cf-7851ccf13bc2</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2025/05/01/us-senate-moves-toward-action-on-stablecoin-bill"/>
        <updated>2025-05-01T23:32:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[U.S. Senate Majority Leader John Thune has started the process toward a vote on the legislation to establish rules for stablecoin issuers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jesse Hamilton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[U.S. Government Begins to Sever Cambodia's Huione Group from Financial System]]></title>
        <id>a66c958f-d47c-4d7e-a38e-cceb38b4e476</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2025/05/01/us-government-begins-to-sever-cambodias-huione-group-from-financial-system"/>
        <updated>2025-05-01T22:26:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Treasury Department's financial-crimes arm used its most potent safeguard to propose cutting off the organization as a money-laundering danger.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jesse Hamilton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mango Markets Exploiter Gets 4+ Years for Child Porn; Fraud Retrial Looms]]></title>
        <id>94b44575-7184-4d56-9ef0-bd0d3a473eb7</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2025/05/01/mango-markets-exploiter-avi-eisenberg-sentenced-to-4-years-in-prison-for-child-porn"/>
        <updated>2025-05-01T20:53:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The judge overseeing Eisenberg's case said he was considering approving a retrial on fraud charges for the Mango Markets theft.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cheyenne Ligon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Strategy Raising Another $21B to Buy Bitcoin, Posts Large Q1 Loss on BTC Price Decline]]></title>
        <id>b18ae745-5680-424c-bba9-732df77cc9c1</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/01/strategy-raising-another-21b-to-buy-bitcoin-posts-large-q1-loss-on-btc-price-decline"/>
        <updated>2025-05-01T20:27:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The company boosted its BTC Yield target to 25% from 15% and its BTC $ Gain Target to $15 billion from $10 billion.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>James Van Straten</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hidden costs in AI deployment: Why Claude models may be 20-30% more expensive than GPT in enterprise settings]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3006096</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/hidden-costs-in-ai-deployment-why-claude-models-may-be-20-30-more-expensive-than-gpt-in-enterprise-settings/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-01T20:14:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It is a well-known fact that different model families can use different tokenizers. However, there has been limited analysis on how the process of “tokenization” itself varies across these tokenizers. Do all tokenizers result in the same number of tokens for a given input text? If not, how different are the generated tokens? How significant […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lavanya Gupta</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gold Continues Correcting and That Might Be Good for Bitcoin]]></title>
        <id>005376e6-9980-448a-8c9f-0ca4ac718671</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/01/gold-continues-correcting-and-that-might-be-good-for-bitcoin"/>
        <updated>2025-05-01T19:52:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The two assets have had inverse-correlated ETF flows on four different days in the last week.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tom Carreras</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SEC Ditches PayPal's PYUSD Probe, Removing Key Regulatory Hurdle for Its Stablecoin]]></title>
        <id>d1829ae0-5c18-4b2a-8ec7-1916bf4a92e0</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2025/05/01/sec-ditches-paypal-usd-probe-helping-its-stablecoin-offering-grow-further"/>
        <updated>2025-05-01T19:47:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The SEC subpoenaed PayPal in late 2023 over its dollar-backed stablecoin.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Aoyon Ashraf</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Senior State Department official sought internal communications with journalists, European officials, and Trump critics]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1115988</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/05/01/1115988/senior-state-department-official-sought-internal-communications-with-journalists-european-officials-and-trump-critics/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-01T17:41:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A previously unreported document distributed by senior US State Department official Darren Beattie reveals a sweeping effort to uncover all communications between the staff of a small government office focused on online disinformation and a lengthy list of public and private figures—many of whom are longtime targets of the political right.  The document, originally shared…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eileen Guo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Litecoin Surges 7% as SEC Likely to Approve Spot ETF with 90% Odds: Analyst]]></title>
        <id>679b4e10-60a2-4034-8c70-cb250be04630</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/01/litecoin-surges-7-as-sec-likely-to-approve-spot-etf-with-90-odds-analyst"/>
        <updated>2025-05-01T17:28:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bullish reversal pattern forms as LTC reclaims critical $86 level amid increasing institutional interest.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>AI Boost</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Django Crash Course for Beginners]]></title>
        <id>6813a8237eaea66216eb6819</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/django-crash-course-for-beginners/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-01T16:58:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Django is a high-level web framework built with Python that encourages rapid development and clean, pragmatic design. Django handles much of the heavy lifting involved in web development, so you can focus more on writing your app and less on reinvent...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Incremental Static Regeneration (ISR) Works in Next.js]]></title>
        <id>68139db5555c3ab781a6e0a1</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-incremental-static-regeneration-isr-works-in-nextjs/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-01T16:13:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When you build a website, you often have two main choices for how pages are created: statically or dynamically. Static pages are created once when you build your project. They’re fast because the server doesn’t have to do any extra work when someone ...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joan Ayebola</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Brief Introduction to React]]></title>
        <id>681397cd1168f254478cd514</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/a-brief-introduction-to-react/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-01T15:48:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This tutorial introduces the basics of using React components in your web apps. React is a JavaScript library used to build user interfaces, especially for single-page applications where parts of the page need to update without a full page reload. It...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mark Mahoney</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Doom GPU Flame Graphs]]></title>
        <id>https://www.brendangregg.com/blog/2025-05-01/doom-gpu-flame-graphs.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.brendangregg.com/blog/2025-05-01/doom-gpu-flame-graphs.html"/>
        <updated>2025-05-01T14:30:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elm Test Distributions]]></title>
        <id>https://martin.janiczek.cz/2025/05/01/elm-test-distributions.html</id>
        <link href="https://martin.janiczek.cz/2025/05/01/elm-test-distributions.html"/>
        <updated>2025-05-01T13:19:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Astronomer’s $93M raise underscores a new reality: Orchestration is king in AI infrastructure]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3006195</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/astronomer-93m-raise-underscores-a-new-reality-orchestration-is-king-in-ai-infrastructure/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-01T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Astronomer secures $93 million in Series D funding to solve the AI implementation gap through data orchestration, helping enterprises streamline complex workflows and operationalize AI initiatives at scale.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Nuñez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft launches Phi-4-Reasoning-Plus, a small, powerful, open weights reasoning model!]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3006213</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/microsoft-launches-phi-4-reasoning-plus-a-small-powerful-open-weights-reasoning-model/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-01T12:41:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The release demonstrates that with carefully curated data and training techniques, small models can deliver strong reasoning performance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carl Franzen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Download: China’s energy throwback, and choosing between love and immortality]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1115999</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/05/01/1115999/the-download-chinas-energy-throwback-and-choosing-between-love-and-immortality/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-01T12:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is today’s edition of The Download, our weekday newsletter that provides a daily dose of what’s going on in the world of technology. A long-abandoned US nuclear technology is making a comeback in China China has once again beat everyone else to a clean energy milestone—its new nuclear reactor is reportedly one of the first to…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rhiannon Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Salesforce takes aim at ‘jagged intelligence’ in push for more reliable AI]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3006124</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/salesforce-tackles-jagged-intelligence-problem-with-new-ai-benchmarks-and-models/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-01T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Salesforce unveils groundbreaking AI research tackling "jagged intelligence," introducing new benchmarks, models, and guardrails to make enterprise AI agents more intelligent, trusted, and consistently reliable for business use.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Nuñez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A long-abandoned US nuclear technology is making a comeback in China]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1115957</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/05/01/1115957/old-new-nuclear-technology/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-01T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[China has once again beat everyone else to a clean energy milestone—its new nuclear reactor is reportedly one of the first to use thorium instead of uranium as a fuel and the first of its kind that can be refueled while it’s running. It’s an interesting (if decidedly experimental) development out of a country that’s…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Casey Crownhart</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Strings Just Got Faster]]></title>
        <id>https://inside.java/2025/05/01/strings-just-got-faster/</id>
        <link href="https://inside.java/2025/05/01/strings-just-got-faster/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-01T06:33:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[UiPath’s new orchestrator guides AI agents to follow your enterprise’s rules]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3006059</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/uipaths-new-orchestrator-guides-ai-agents-to-follow-your-enterprises-rules/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T21:20:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[UiPath's agent orchestration layer Maestro moves prompts through three layers: the agent, a human and the robotic process automation system.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Emilia David</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The ‘era of experience’ will unleash self-learning AI agents across the web—here’s how to prepare]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3005579</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/the-era-of-experience-will-unleash-self-learning-ai-agents-across-the-web-heres-how-to-prepare/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T20:38:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AI visionaries predict an 'Era of Experience' where AI learns autonomously, and it will have important implications for application design.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ben Dickson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Qwen swings for a double with 2.5-Omni-3B model that runs on consumer PCs, laptops]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3006114</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/qwen-swings-for-a-double-with-2-5-omni-3b-model-that-runs-on-consumer-pcs-laptops/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T20:31:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Qwen2.5-Omni-3B model is licensed for non-commercial use only under Alibaba Cloud’s Qwen Research License Agreement.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carl Franzen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Breaking the ‘intellectual bottleneck’: How AI is computing the previously uncomputable in healthcare]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3005667</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/breaking-the-intellectual-bottleneck-how-ai-is-computing-the-previously-uncomputible-in-healthcare/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T19:03:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How University of Texas Medical Branch is using AI to identify patients at high cardiovascular risk, flag for stroke and catch 'basic stuff.']]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Taryn Plumb</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Local cosmetics sector can be launchpad to position Malaysia as innovation-led economy: Sirim chief tech officer]]></title>
        <id>f3d9620891e0882d2a66ea582395ca3a</id>
        <link href="https://thesun.my/business-news/local-cosmetics-sector-can-be-launchpad-to-position-malaysia-as-innovation-led-economy-sirim-chief-tech-officer-AH14020110"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T17:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SHAH ALAM: The Malaysian cosmetics sector can serve as a launchpad to position the nation as an innovation-led economy, said Sirim Bhd chief technolog...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hayatun Razak</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How IPv4 Works – A Handbook for Developers]]></title>
        <id>68124752fa6fa6a9a91d9994</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-ipv4-works-a-handbook-for-developers/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T15:52:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Internet Protocol version 4 (IPv4) is one of the core protocols of standards-based internetworking methods in the Internet and other packet-switched networks. IPv4 is still the most widely deployed Internet protocol. Google’s IPv6 Statistics show...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Omer Rosenbaum</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Get Your First SaaS Customers]]></title>
        <id>681242328ca367c7e5d58873</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-get-your-first-saas-customers/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T15:30:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Starting a SaaS (Software as a Service) business is exciting. You’ve put in the long hours building something you believe people will love. But now comes the big question: How do you get your first customers? Getting those first few users can feel li...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Udemezue John</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Get the User Model in Django – A Simple Guide With Examples]]></title>
        <id>68123f859249b83d2215937d</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-get-user-model-in-django/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T15:19:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When I’m working with Django, one of the first things I often need to do is work with users – like getting the logged-in user, creating a new one, or extending the default user model to add more information. Now, Django has a built-in User model, but...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Udemezue John</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Oracle ERP Test Automation Guide – Examples and Best Practices]]></title>
        <id>68123ef3b70ffa1e4ce467ae</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/oracle-erp-test-automation-guide/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T15:17:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Oracle Enterprise Resource Planning helps businesses manage finance and supply chains. It also supports human resources and brings different functions together. Many growing businesses rely on it to handle complex tasks, as system failures or errors ...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nazneen Ahmad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OpenAI rolls back ChatGPT’s sycophancy and explains what went wrong]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3006053</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/openai-rolls-back-chatgpts-sycophancy-and-explains-what-went-wrong/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T15:14:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Many organizations may also begin shifting toward open-source alternatives that they can host and tune themselves.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carl Franzen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Three Omani innovators selected for ITEX 2025 in Malaysia]]></title>
        <id>57ab645df98f4874d208689be5dc65c4</id>
        <link href="https://www.muscatdaily.com/2025/04/30/three-omani-innovators-selected-fpr-itex-2025-in-malaysia/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T14:55:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Three Omani innovators selected to compete at ITEX 2025 in Malaysia. Projects include innovations in water filtration, dental materials, and remote control technology]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nisha Joshi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Structify raises $4.1M seed to turn unstructured web data into enterprise-ready datasets]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3006010</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/structify-raises-4-1m-seed-to-turn-unstructured-web-data-into-enterprise-ready-datasets/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Brooklyn-based Structify emerges from stealth with $4.1 million in seed funding to transform how businesses prepare data for AI, promising to save data scientists from the task that consumes 80% of their time.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Nuñez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Download: stereotypes in AI models, and the new age of coding]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1115952</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/04/30/1115952/the-download-stereotypes-in-ai-models-and-the-new-age-of-coding/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T12:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is today’s edition of The Download, our weekday newsletter that provides a daily dose of what’s going on in the world of technology. This data set helps researchers spot harmful stereotypes in LLMs What’s new? AI models are riddled with culturally specific biases. A new data set, called SHADES, is designed to help developers combat the…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rhiannon Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This data set helps researchers spot harmful stereotypes in LLMs]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1115946</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/04/30/1115946/this-data-set-helps-researchers-spot-harmful-stereotypes-in-llms/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T09:41:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AI models are riddled with culturally specific biases. A new data set, called SHADES, is designed to help developers combat the problem by spotting harmful stereotypes and other kinds of discrimination that emerge in AI chatbot responses across a wide range of languages. Margaret Mitchell, chief ethics scientist at AI startup Hugging Face, led the…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rhiannon Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Malaysia attracts US$3.7 billion in digital investments, solidifying]]></title>
        <id>b95e1bfb983c9cc102bc4266d362a8c2</id>
        <link href="https://www.digitalnewsasia.com/digital-economy/malaysia-attracts-us37-billion-digital-investments-solidifying-position-aseans-tech"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T02:31:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Malaysia’s digital economy continues to go from strength to strength, emerging as a strategic engine of growth that creates jobs, opens new opportunities, and fosters local innovation for businesses]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>@DigitalNewsAsia</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MDV powers Malaysia's tech innovation with over RM13bil financing]]></title>
        <id>d3f5fdc4ea236d719dc3a9d352d4620c</id>
        <link href="https://www.nst.com.my/business/corporate/2025/04/1209375/mdv-powers-malaysias-tech-innovation-over-rm13bil-financing"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T01:56:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[KUALA LUMPUR: Malaysia Debt Ventures Bhd (MDV) has emerged as a key enabler of the nation’s innovation and digital transformation agenda, with more than RM13 billion channelled into over 1,000 high-impact, technology-driven projects.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bernama</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[No more window switching: Mastercard’s Agent Pay transforms how enterprises use AI search]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3005997</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/no-more-window-switching-mastercards-agent-pay-transforms-how-enterprises-use-ai-search/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T22:24:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mastercard is working with AI companies and banks to allow AI platforms and agents to facilitate transactions.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Emilia David</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meta unleashes Llama API running 18x faster than OpenAI: Cerebras partnership delivers 2,600 tokens per second]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3005976</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/meta-unleashes-llama-api-running-18x-faster-than-openai-cerebras-partnership-delivers-2600-tokens-per-second/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T20:02:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Meta partners with Cerebras to launch its new Llama API, offering developers AI inference speeds up to 18 times faster than traditional GPU solutions, challenging OpenAI and Google in the fast-growing AI services market.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Nuñez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meta’s first dedicated AI app is here with Llama 4 — but it’s more consumer than productivity or business oriented]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3005961</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/metas-first-dedicated-ai-app-is-here-with-llama-4-but-its-more-consumer-than-productivity-or-business-oriented/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T18:19:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This mainstream exposure will likely accelerate a shift in what people expect not just from consumer apps, but from workplaces...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carl Franzen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Create Accessible and User-Friendly Forms in React]]></title>
        <id>6810f59e8deee87383c1bc46</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-create-accessible-and-user-friendly-forms-in-react/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T15:51:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When designing web applications, you’ll often be asked the age old question “How accessible is your website” and “Does it offer the best user experience?”. These are both very valid questions, but they are often overlooked in favour of rich or fancy ...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Grant Riordan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn Calculus by Coding in Python]]></title>
        <id>6810eebd43aa3d16a14700eb</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-calculus-by-coding-in-python/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T15:22:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Calculus is one of the cornerstones of higher mathematics and a powerful tool for understanding change, motion, and growth across countless disciplines. But for many students, Calculus can seem intimidating or abstract. What if you could learn it ste...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Register Models in Django Admin]]></title>
        <id>6810e5a2dc9845a2ab207f06</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-register-models-in-django-admin/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T14:43:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When you're building a website or an app with Django, one of the most exciting moments is when your database models finally come to life. But to manage your data easily – adding, editing, or deleting entries – you need Django’s Admin panel. Now, here...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Udemezue John</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tripp launches Kōkua AI as mental wellness coach across multiple platforms]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3005798</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/games/tripp-launches-kokua-ai-as-mental-wellness-coach-across-multiple-platforms/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T13:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tripp launched Kōkua AI, a mental wellness guide designed to deliver real-time, personalized emotional support across multiple platforms.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dean Takahashi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[xMEMS extends micro cooling fan-on-a-chip tech to AI data centers]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3005879</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/game-development/xmems-extends-micro-cooling-fan-on-a-chip-tech-to-ai-data-centers/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[xMEMS Labs, a pioneer of MEMS-based chips, announced that its innovative µCooling fan-on-a-chip tech will be expanded to AI data centers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dean Takahashi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Download: the AI Hype Index, and “normal” AI]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1115932</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/04/29/1115932/the-download-the-ai-hype-index-and-normal-ai/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T12:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is today’s edition of The Download, our weekday newsletter that provides a daily dose of what’s going on in the world of technology. The AI Hype Index: AI agent cyberattacks, racing robots, and musical models Separating AI reality from hyped-up fiction isn’t always easy. That’s why we’ve created the AI Hype Index—a simple, at-a-glance summary of…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rhiannon Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The AI Hype Index: AI agent cyberattacks, racing robots, and musical models]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1115918</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/04/29/1115918/the-ai-hype-index-ai-agent-cyberattacks-racing-robots-and-musical-models/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Separating AI reality from hyped-up fiction isn’t always easy. That’s why we’ve created the AI Hype Index—a simple, at-a-glance summary of everything you need to know about the state of the industry. AI agents are the AI industry’s hypiest new product—intelligent assistants capable of completing tasks without human supervision. But while they can be theoretically…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Editors</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Web3j Six Month Project Update]]></title>
        <id>68109495670a1300013504c2</id>
        <link href="https://blog.web3labs.com/web3j-six-month-project-update/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T09:10:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[November 2024 - April 2025
This report summarizes the activities and accomplishments of Web3j, an LF Decentralized Trust project, from November 2024 to April 2025. During this period, the project made significant strides in improving the framework’s functionality, enhancing user engagement, and bolstering overall community interaction. 
Key]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>George Tebrean</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[We need to start thinking of AI as “normal”]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1115928</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/04/29/1115928/is-ai-normal/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Right now, despite its ubiquity, AI is seen as anything but a normal technology. There is talk of AI systems that will soon merit the term “superintelligence,” and the former CEO of Google recently suggested we control AI models the way we control uranium and other nuclear weapons materials. Anthropic is dedicating time and money…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>James O'Donnell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Alibaba launches open source Qwen3 model that surpasses OpenAI o1 and DeepSeek R1]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3005880</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/alibaba-launches-open-source-qwen3-model-that-surpasses-openai-o1-and-deepseek-r1/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-28T23:56:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Qwen3’s open-weight release under an accessible license marks an important milestone, lowering barriers for developers and organizations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carl Franzen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ex-OpenAI CEO and power users sound alarm over AI sycophancy and flattery of users]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3005850</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/ex-openai-ceo-and-power-users-sound-alarm-over-ai-sycophancy-and-flattery-of-users/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-28T21:49:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crucially, the turbulence also nudges many organizations to explore open-source models they can host, monitor, and fine-tune themselves.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carl Franzen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Beyond A2A and MCP: How LOKA’s Universal Agent Identity Layer changes the game]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3005824</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/beyond-a2a-and-mcp-how-lokas-universal-agent-identity-layer-changes-the-game/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-28T20:35:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The LOKA protocol, a proposed standard for AI agents from Carnegie Mellon University researchers, will give identities and intentions to agents.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Emilia David</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[30 seconds vs. 3: The d1 reasoning framework that’s slashing AI response times]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3005393</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/30-seconds-vs-3-the-d1-reasoning-framework-thats-slashing-ai-response-times/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-28T19:31:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[d1 framework changes boosts diffusion LLMs with novel reinforcement learning, unlocking efficient, problem-solving AI possibilities.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ben Dickson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Relational Graph Transformers]]></title>
        <id>https://kumo.ai/research/relational-graph-transformers/</id>
        <link href="https://kumo.ai/research/relational-graph-transformers/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-28T18:13:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Writer releases Palmyra X5, delivers near GPT-4.1 performance at 75% lower cost]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3005734</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/writer-releases-palmyra-x5-delivers-near-gpt-4-performance-at-75-lower-cost/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-28T17:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Writer unveils Palmyra X5: The enterprise AI model that processes 1,500 pages at once, costs 75% less than GPT-4, and enables affordable autonomous agents for businesses seeking automation ROI.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Nuñez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[QuickNode: Building the Infrastructure for the Next Generation of Blockchain]]></title>
        <id>6807d5787fb8500001c39b99</id>
        <link href="https://blog.quicknode.com/quicknode-building-the-infrastructure-for-the-next-generation-of-blockchain/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-28T16:02:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Join QuickNode co-founder Dmitry Shklovsky as he discusses blockchain infrastructure, building decentralized applications, and the future of Web3 development on TheCube's Crypto Trailblazer Series.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>QuickNode</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Does RAG make LLMs less safe?  Bloomberg research reveals hidden dangers]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3005592</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/does-rag-make-llms-less-safe-bloomberg-research-reveals-hidden-dangers/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-28T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[RAG is supposed to make enterprise AI more accurate, but it could potentially also make it less safe according to new research.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sean Michael Kerner</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[UPDATED] Malaysia and Maldives explore new ties in solar, defence, and digital tech [WATCH]]]></title>
        <id>2ff00997f9c35cff9b55bf1c234d9fd9</id>
        <link href="https://www.nst.com.my/news/nation/2025/04/1208426/updated-malaysia-and-maldives-explore-new-ties-solar-defence-and-digital"/>
        <updated>2025-04-28T04:17:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[PUTRAJAYA: Malaysia is eager to explore new avenues of cooperation with the Maldives, including floating solar energy, defence, and digital technology, says Datuk Seri Anwar Ibrahim.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hakim Mahari</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Retail & E-Commerce Innovation Marketing & Tech Summit: Malaysia 2025]]></title>
        <id>cd2a0d19be53d9723fc0475f09d0da2d</id>
        <link href="https://marketech-apac.com/conference/retail-e-commerce-innovation-marketing-tech-summit-malaysia-2025/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-28T01:58:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Retail & E-Commerce Innovation Marketing & Tech Summit: Malaysia 2025]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Zyra Kate Capilastique</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Is your AI product actually working? How to develop the right metric system]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3005642</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/is-your-ai-product-actually-working-how-to-develop-the-right-metric-system/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-27T19:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Metrics are critical for determining AI product performance. But where to begin? Here's a framework to apply across various use cases.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sharanya Rao, Intuit</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bits + Bytes: A Miscellany Of Technology]]></title>
        <id>92c9e6ae0de9449f2a2cd9808d52c95a</id>
        <link href="https://theedgemalaysia.com/node/752832"/>
        <updated>2025-04-27T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[NEWS

Malaysia sees tech salary surge in 2025, led by system engineers

Tech salaries in Malaysia have risen significantly this year, with system engineers recording the highest increase at 8%, according to NodeFlair’s Tech Salary Report 2...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Edge Malaysia</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FORKLIFTACTION, B2B news service and business platform about forklifts and materials handling]]></title>
        <id>20065c212264065b824a3328d06be4fc</id>
        <link href="https://www.forkliftaction.com/pagenotfound.aspx"/>
        <updated>2025-04-27T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[FORKLIFTACTION, B2B news service and business platform about forklifts and materials handling]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Forkliftaction</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DeepSeek’s success shows why motivation is key to AI innovation]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3005636</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/deepseeks-success-shows-why-motivation-is-key-to-ai-innovation/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-26T19:55:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How did DeepSeek attain such cost-savings while American companies could not? Let's dive into the technical details.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Debasish Ray Chawdhuri, Talentica Software</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Malaysia remains 9th largest global exporter of high-tech products]]></title>
        <id>ec83e12fc9489689eba3a736f7c0fd4e</id>
        <link href="https://e.vnexpress.net/news/tech/tech-news/malaysia-remains-9th-largest-global-exporter-of-high-tech-products-4878750.html"/>
        <updated>2025-04-26T02:41:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Malaysia successfully maintained its position as the ninth-largest exporter of high-tech goods out of 143 economies in 2023, the highest recognition it has achieved in the past decade, Bernama has reported.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>VnExpress</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Liquid AI is revolutionizing LLMs to work on edge devices like smartphones with new ‘Hyena Edge’ model]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3005611</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/liquid-ai-is-revolutionizing-llms-to-work-on-edge-devices-like-smartphones-with-new-hyena-edge-model/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-25T22:02:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hyena Edge’s success positions Liquid AI as one of the emerging players to watch in the evolving AI model landscape.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carl Franzen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The new AI calculus: Google’s 80% cost edge vs. OpenAI’s ecosystem]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3005571</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/the-new-ai-calculus-googles-80-cost-edge-vs-openais-ecosystem/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-25T20:26:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Explore the Google vs OpenAI AI ecosystem battle post-o3. Deep dive into Google's huge cost advantage (TPU vs GPU), agent strategies & model risks for enterprise]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matt Marshall</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Malaysia remains 9th largest global exporter of high-tech products]]></title>
        <id>e1054193ac5220fd5f3cf3fb0ac3fcbd</id>
        <link href="https://en.vietnamplus.vn/malaysia-remains-9th-largest-global-exporter-of-high-tech-products-post318075.vnp"/>
        <updated>2025-04-25T18:11:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Malaysia’s high-tech exports increased by 2 billion USD to reach 127 billion USD in 2023. He said high-tech exports comprised 58.69% of total manufacturing exports in 2023, up from 52.48% recorded in 2022.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Vietnam+ (VietnamPlus)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[UK agrees to assist Malaysia in technology, new energy]]></title>
        <id>9bba1ab03b6cc59e6474a313d3bc9d9c</id>
        <link href="https://theedgemalaysia.com/node/753068"/>
        <updated>2025-04-25T15:31:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The UK has agreed to collaborate with Malaysia in various fields, including technology and new energy management, said Deputy Prime Minister Datuk Seri Fadillah Yusof.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Edge Malaysia</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Need to embrace technological advancements, sustainable practices discussed at country's premier real estate event]]></title>
        <id>13ba8e804fd9567fa951b4f7cc51bead</id>
        <link href="https://theedgemalaysia.com/node/753073"/>
        <updated>2025-04-25T12:00:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Industry leaders, policymakers, investors and experts explored the future of Malaysia's real estate landscape at the National Real Estate Convention (NREC) 2025 held here recently.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Edge Malaysia</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cooperations with China continue to drive Malaysia's tech ambitions: experts]]></title>
        <id>7cf31983f27357e33a7e7403d769042c</id>
        <link href="https://english.news.cn/20250423/23952d602d384abe9a3be2f40797fa2d/c.html"/>
        <updated>2025-04-23T09:33:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cooperations with China continue to drive Malaysia's tech ambitions: experts-]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>english.news.cn</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[IBM Tech Innovation Summit]]></title>
        <id>eb7b875c351e513c2d4750bb29a0ab40</id>
        <link href="https://www.malaysiakini.com/news/741130"/>
        <updated>2025-04-23T02:44:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Seats are limited. Register now!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Malaysiakini Team</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Alabama’s Pursell Agri-Tech teams with Wastech on fertilizer venture in Malaysia]]></title>
        <id>af0a46cec4f3cf8c521e3bd5a58cb6d6</id>
        <link href="https://www.madeinalabama.com/2025/04/alabamas-pursell-agri-tech-teams-with-wastech-on-fertilizer-venture-in-malaysia/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-21T18:21:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Pursell and Wastech Group are establishing a state-of-the-art facility in Malaysia to producte advanced controlled release fertilizers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jerry Underwood</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>