<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2025-04-30T12:26:44.860Z</id>
    <title>AngJianming RSS Feed</title>
    <updated>2025-04-30T12:26:44.860Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tokenized Apollo Credit Fund Makes DeFi Debut With Levered-Yield Strategy by Securitize, Gauntlet]]></title>
        <id>677307ee-e3e4-4cc2-bf42-97ffd9c4e6fd</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/04/30/tokenized-apollo-credit-fund-makes-defi-debut-with-levered-yield-strategy-by-securitize-gauntlet"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T12:17:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The offering aims to make real-world asset tokens competitive with stablecoins for DeFi yield strategies, Securitize's Reid Simon said.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Krisztian Sandor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Boost Your Dev Team's Efficiency with Oraculum]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/daniyar_art/boost-your-dev-teams-efficiency-with-oraculum-481f</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/daniyar_art/boost-your-dev-teams-efficiency-with-oraculum-481f"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T12:17:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I’d like to introduce Oraculum, a tool built to help engineering teams measure and improve productivity. It seamlessly integrates with Jira and GitLab, offering insights into key metrics like active days, code review times, and task lifecycles. Oraculum helps engineering managers make data-driven decisions to optimize team performance and streamline workflows.
After implementing Oraculum, we identified top performers, low performers, and even made some tough decisions, including letting go of a few developers based on data insights.
We’d love feedback from engineers and team leads on how this could benefit your teams. If you're interested in learning more or testing it out, feel free to reach out!
Here some screenshots]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniyar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[F2]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/david_bermenvliz/f2-19j5</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/david_bermenvliz/f2-19j5"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T12:16:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Check out this Pen I made!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Berúmen Véliz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Developers Should Care About Workplace Accessibility]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/corporateone/why-developers-should-care-about-workplace-accessibility-5e9d</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/corporateone/why-developers-should-care-about-workplace-accessibility-5e9d"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T12:15:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As developers, we often think of accessibility in the context of websites and applications—adding alt text, ensuring color contrast, enabling keyboard navigation. But there’s a broader arena where accessibility matters just as much: the workplace itself.
Whether you're working remotely, on-site, or in a hybrid model, building accessible digital environments is essential—not just for compliance, but for inclusion, productivity, and innovation.
At CorporateOne, we design workplace technology solutions that prioritize accessibility from the ground up. Here’s why developers should take workplace accessibility seriously—and how it shapes better code, teams, and culture.
🧠 Accessibility Is Not a Feature—It’s a Mindset
Think about:
Internal dashboards
Virtual meeting platforms
Knowledge bases an…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Aditi Khaskalam</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AI Classification models Performance Evaluation using Confusion Matrix -]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/lea_abraham_7a0232a6cd616/ai-classification-models-performance-evaluation-using-confusion-matrix--g80</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/lea_abraham_7a0232a6cd616/ai-classification-models-performance-evaluation-using-confusion-matrix--g80"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T12:15:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A confusion matrix is a table used to evaluate the performance of a classification model by showing the true and predicted classifications for a set of test data. It helps in visualizing and analyzing how well the model is performing, especially for multi-class classification problems. The confusion matrix provides a detailed breakdown of the correct and incorrect predictions, making it easier to understand the types of errors the model is making.

Accuracy: The proportion of correct predictions (both true positives and true negatives) out of all predictions.
Accuracy = (TP + TN) / (TP + TN + FP + FN)
Precision: The proportion of true positive predictions out of all positive predictions made by the model.
Precision (Positive Predictive Value) = TP / TP + FP
Recall (Sensitivity, True Positi…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lea Abraham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin macro indicator that predicted 2022 bottom flashes &#039;buy signal&#039;]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-macro-indicator-predicted-2022-bottom-flashes-buy</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-macro-indicator-predicted-2022-bottom-flashes-buy?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T12:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Key takeaways:

Macro Chain Index issues first buy signal since 2022, hinting at a new Bitcoin bull run.

RSI crossover on the MCI aligns with past cycle bottoms that preceded 500%+ BTC rallies.

Bitcoin price recovers from $74K to $95K amid rising open interest and positive funding rates.

A key Bitcoin (BTC) indicator that accurately signaled the 2022 market bottom has just flashed another buy signal, suggesting the cryptocurrency may be entering a new bull phase.
Bitcoin metric hints at “absolute bottom”
Dubbed the Macro Chain Index (MCI), the indicator is a composite of several long-term on-chain and macroeconomic metrics. 
It analyzes factors such as accumulation behavior, network activity, and supply trends, helping identify whether Bitcoin is undervalued or overvalued relative to it…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Yashu Gola</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nueva función]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/david_bermenvliz/nueva-funcion-14i4</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/david_bermenvliz/nueva-funcion-14i4"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T12:12:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Check out this Pen I made!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Berúmen Véliz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FIFA shifts NFT platform to new Ethereum-compatible blockchain]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/fifa-collect-nfts-move-to-evm-blockchain</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/fifa-collect-nfts-move-to-evm-blockchain?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T12:12:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Federation Internationale de Football Association (FIFA) plans to launch a new blockchain network to support its non-fungible token (NFT) collectibles, the organization announced on April 30.
FIFA will launch its “FIFA Blockchain,” with Ethereum Virtual Machine (EVM) compatibility and aims to provide “better performance, future features, and improved scalability.”
As part of the move, FIFA Collect — its official NFT collection — will migrate from the Algorand blockchain to the new FIFA Blockchain. The migration is scheduled to begin no earlier than May 20, FIFA said.  
FIFA announces new blockchain for FIFA collection migration. Source: collect.fifa.com

“At this stage, no immediate action is required. When the migration process begins, we will provide clear, step-by-step instructions on what (if anything) you need to do,” the announcement stated.
The collection’s migration will take place “not earlier than” May 20, FIFA said, adding that it will confirm the exact date and provide clear instructions for NFT holders.
Following the migration, external Algorand-based wallets such as Pera and Defly will no longer be supported. Instead, users will be able to connect to FIFA Collect via MetaMask or other EVM wallets that support WalletConnect.
Other listed collectibles will be automatically listed on the new platform, unless users delist them before the migration date.
This is a developing story, and further information will be added as it becomes available.
Related: Bitcoin volatility lowest in 563 days, Hayes predicts $1M BTC by 2028]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Zoltan Vardai</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blockchain Project Funding Through Yield Farming]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/kallileiser/blockchain-project-funding-through-yield-farming-1g31</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/kallileiser/blockchain-project-funding-through-yield-farming-1g31"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T12:11:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Abstract


This post explores the innovative funding mechanism of yield farming within the blockchain ecosystem. It discusses how blockchain projects leverage yield farming to gain funding outside traditional channels, the mechanics behind liquidity pools and smart contracts, and the broader implications for decentralized finance (DeFi). We provide background and context, detail core features and benefits, and examine both practical use cases and challenges. We also explore future trends such as cross-chain yield farming and derivative-based strategies, supported by useful tables, bullet lists, and curated links from authoritative sources such as what is blockchain, decentralized finance for project funding, and smart contracts on blockchain. Finally, we explore insights from industry expe…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>kallileiser</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[No Experience Remote Jobs: 9 Reasons to Consider]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/harsha_abegunasekara_0684/no-experience-remote-jobs-9-reasons-to-consider-2iai</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/harsha_abegunasekara_0684/no-experience-remote-jobs-9-reasons-to-consider-2iai"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T12:11:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[TL;DR




Remote-first companies want self-starters, not just anyone who can use Zoom.


Sending the same generic CV won’t work—tailor it for remote readiness.


Stop relying on LinkedIn; remote job boards are your new best friend.


Interviews happen online—treat them seriously and test your setup.


Soft skills, like communication and time management, are more important than ever.



Dreaming of working in your pyjamas, coffee in hand, tapping away from the comfort of your living room? You’re not alone. No experience remote jobs have exploded in popularity—and so has the competition. For every listing, there’s a sea of applications. So, why is your inbox still empty?
It’s not just about applying—it’s about how you apply. Let’s unpack the 9 most common reasons you’re not hearing back and …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Harsha Abegunasekara</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Install Qwen 3 Locally?]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/nodeshiftcloud/how-to-install-qwen-3-locally-4fme</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/nodeshiftcloud/how-to-install-qwen-3-locally-4fme"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T12:09:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Built across eight sizes (0.6B, 1.7B, 4B, 8B, 14B, 30B, 32B, and 235B), the Qwen 3 family delivers a major leap in understanding, reasoning, and communication. With both dense and MoE (Mixture of Experts) models, there’s something for every use case — from lightweight tasks to heavyweight thinking.
✅ Multilingual by default: Trained across 119 languages and dialects using a jaw-dropping 36 trillion words, it understands cultural nuance and translates like a native.
Hugging Face
Link : https://huggingface.co/collections/Qwen/qwen3-67dd247413f0e2e4f653967f


For the purpose of this tutorial, we will use a GPU-powered Virtual Machine offered by NodeShift; however, you can replicate the same steps with any other cloud provider of your choice. NodeShift provides the most affordable Virtual Mach…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ayush kumar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS SageMaker]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/lea_abraham_7a0232a6cd616/aws-sagemaker-l91</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/lea_abraham_7a0232a6cd616/aws-sagemaker-l91"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T12:08:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AWS SageMaker is a fully managed service that allows data scientists and developers to build, train, and deploy machine learning models at scale. It simplifies the process of developing and deploying machine learning models by offering tools and capabilities to perform each step of the machine learning workflow, from preparing data to monitoring deployed models.
1. Data Preparation and Labeling:
2. Model Building:
•SageMaker Studio: An integrated development environment (IDE) that offers tools to build, train, and deploy machine learning models. It’s a web-based interface that supports Jupyter notebooks and various integrations.
3. Model Training:
•Distributed Training: SageMaker allows training on large datasets by automatically distributing the training job across multiple instances.
4. …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lea Abraham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meet YouTubeThumbnailGrabber.app: Effortless HD Thumbnail Extraction]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/rutanshiraval200/meet-youtubethumbnailgrabberapp-effortless-hd-thumbnail-extraction-3nm5</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/rutanshiraval200/meet-youtubethumbnailgrabberapp-effortless-hd-thumbnail-extraction-3nm5"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T12:05:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hey Dev Community! 👋
Ever needed a crisp, high-resolution thumbnail from a YouTube video without wrestling through embed code or inspecting elements? That’s exactly why I built YouTubeThumbnailGrabber.app a tiny tool that does one job, and does it in under 3 seconds.

What It Does
Paste any YouTube URL, including Shorts or embedded links
Instantly fetch the highest-resolution thumbnail available
Download with a single click—no sign-up, no ads, no watermark
Whether you’re A/B testing thumbnails, repurposing art for social media, or just curious what that secret 4K cover looks like, this tool has you covered.
Under the Hood
Next.js for super-fast React pages and server-side functions
API route that parses the video ID and returns full-HD thumbnail URLs
Tailwind CSS for a clean, responsive interface on both desktop and mobile
Netlify for one-click deployment and a global CDN]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rutanshi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Top 10 AI Models Every Developer Should Know in 2025]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/nikl/top-10-ai-models-every-developer-should-know-in-2025-30f8</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/nikl/top-10-ai-models-every-developer-should-know-in-2025-30f8"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T12:04:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Before diving into specific models, let's clarify the distinct categories of AI models available today:



Category
What They Do
Example Use Cases




LLMs
Process and generate human-like text
Code generation, content creation, API documentation


Generative Models
Create content across multiple modalities
Custom UI assets, wireframes, mockups


Computer Vision
Process and understand visual data
OCR integration, document analysis, UI testing


Recommendation Systems
Predict user preferences
In-app content personalization, user engagement


Time Series Models
Analyze sequential data patterns
System monitoring, anomaly detection


Reinforcement Learning
Learn through trial and error
Training agents, optimization problems


Graph Neural Networks
Process node-edge relationships
Network analysi…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nik L.</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mastercard Introduces Agent Pay, A New System For AI-Led Commerce]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=350185</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/350185/mastercard-introduces-agent-pay/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T12:04:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mastercard has introduced a new technology called “Agent Pay”, aimed at powering secure and intelligent payments in a world increasingly shaped by artificial intelligence. Developed with companies including Microsoft and other leading AI platforms, the system is designed to allow AI agents – such as virtual assistants, chatbots, or autonomous shopping tools – to initiate […]
The post Mastercard Introduces Agent Pay, A New System For AI-Led Commerce appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Heirul Kamel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Using Python & WebSockets to Generate Live OHLC Forex Data]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/shridhargv/using-python-websockets-to-generate-live-ohlc-forex-data-1082</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/shridhargv/using-python-websockets-to-generate-live-ohlc-forex-data-1082"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T12:03:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This tutorial guides you through building a real-time Forex OHLC data generator using Python and WebSockets. Learn how to stream FX prices, convert them to OHLC format, and save the results with clean, efficient code.
Accessing real-time market data is essential for modern trading and financial analytics. WebSockets provide an efficient method for live, continuous data streaming. In this tutorial, we’ll walk through how to use Python to connect to a WebSocket stream, collect Forex pricing data, and convert it into OHLC (Open, High, Low, Close) bars.
Before we start, ensure you have:
Python installed on your machine.
Basic understanding of how to use Python.
To stream live Forex data, you’ll need a TraderMade API key. Sign up for a 14-day free trial and find your API key in your account das…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shridhar G Vatharkar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vanar Chain tackles AWS-style outages with AI-powered data storage]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/vanar-chain-launches-neutron-ai-onchain-compression</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/vanar-chain-launches-neutron-ai-onchain-compression?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T11:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Vanar Chain, a layer-1 blockchain network, has launched a new artificial intelligence-powered compression and data authentication layer designed to address the industry’s longstanding issue with onchain storage.
Vanar Chain is launching Neutron, an AI-native blockchain layer with data compression ratios of up to 500:1, which can reduce a standard 25 megabyte file to just 50 kilobytes, transforming it into a “Neutron Seed” that can be stored on the blockchain ledger.
The new blockchain compression layer aims to solve the industry’s data storage issue, with traditional blockchains lacking the capacity to store data, only to reference it.
This design introduces potential single points of failure. Vanar's Neutron aims to solve this by enabling fully onchain, verifiable data storage.
Neutron is…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Zoltan Vardai</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Secret Deals, Foreign Investments: The Rise of Trump’s Crypto Firm]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nytimes.com/2025/04/29/us/politics/trump-crypto-world-liberty-financial.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.nytimes.com/2025/04/29/us/politics/trump-crypto-world-liberty-financial.html"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T11:19:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Daybook Americas: Biggest Tokens Show Restraint for Now, but 'Damage Has Already Been Done']]></title>
        <id>0b8f55d6-8763-4cc6-9352-6bfcb3db8bab</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/daybook-us/2025/04/30/crypto-daybook-americas-biggest-tokens-show-restraint-for-now-but-damage-has-already-been-done"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T11:17:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Your day-ahead look for April 30, 2025]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Francisco Rodrigues</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin traders predict BTC price gains ahead of $96K liquidity clash]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-traders-predict-btc-price-gains-ahead-of-96k-liquidity-clash</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-traders-predict-btc-price-gains-ahead-of-96k-liquidity-clash?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T11:11:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Key points:

Bitcoin consolidates after upside momentum stalls, but traders are confident that upside breakout will result.

Major risk-asset volatility is expected as US macro data precedes the monthly candle close.

April BTC price performance is on track to be the best since 2020.

Bitcoin (BTC) spent another day around $95,000 on April 30 as volatility waited in the wings.
BTC/USD 1-hour chart. Source: Cointelegraph/TradingView
Bitcoin enjoys the calm before the storm
Data from Cointelegraph Markets Pro and TradingView showed calm trading conditions with hours to go until the monthly close and key US macro data.
The latter comes in the form of Q1 GDP and the March print of the Personal Consumption Expenditures (PCE) index, known as the Federal Reserve’s “preferred” inflation gauge.
The…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by William Suberg</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nasdaq Seeks SEC Approval to List 21Shares Dogecoin ETF]]></title>
        <id>11f6cfaa-74d7-43a5-b5cd-081a49c73d92</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/04/30/nasdaq-seeks-sec-approval-to-list-21shares-dogecoin-etf"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T11:06:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase Custody Trust will hold the fund’s tokens and serve as the official custodian for the ETF.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shaurya Malwa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Inside Movement’s Token-Dump Scandal: Secret Contracts, Shadow Advisors and Hidden Middlemen]]></title>
        <id>ca25f2fb-f887-4098-86ec-a0104210e64e</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/tech/2025/04/30/inside-movement-s-token-dump-scandal-backroom-deals-shadow-advisors-and-secret-middlemen"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Movement, backed by Trump's World Liberty Financial, says it was duped into an agreement that experts say incentivized price manipulation.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sam Kessler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Week In Gaming: EA Cancels Titanfall Game, Borderlands 4 Gets New Release Date, And More]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=350162</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/350162/this-week-in-gaming/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T10:53:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’re halfway through the week, and in the world of gaming, some things have happened but not in such a major fashion that it would make waves. That being said, their occurrence is still important enough to warrant a report and as such, here’s a quick list of them. EA Lays Off Hundreds Of Staff, […]
The post This Week In Gaming: EA Cancels Titanfall Game, Borderlands 4 Gets New Release Date, And More appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John Law</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[KuCoin Commits $2 Billion to “Trust Project” Focusing on Crypto Security and Transparency]]></title>
        <id>2a3c88da-cd66-4d75-8f07-1dbedc9e3cc9</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2025/04/30/kucoin-commits-usd2-billion-to-trust-project-focusing-on-crypto-security-and-transparency"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T10:08:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[KuCoin’s native token, KCS, will play a more pivotal role in the ecosystem.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Omkar Godbole</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin volatility lowest in 563 days, Hayes predicts $1M BTC by 2028]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-volatility-563-day-low-hayes-predicts-1-m-btc-2028</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-volatility-563-day-low-hayes-predicts-1-m-btc-2028?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T10:02:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin is showing signs of maturity as a global financial asset, with price volatility dropping to its lowest level in more than 500 days, according to new research.
Volatility refers to the degree of variation of a trading price over time, which indicates the uncertainty about the size of changes in an asset’s value.
Bitcoin (BTC) weekly volatility hit a 563-day low on April 30, said Vetle Lunde, the head of research at K33 Research.
Source: Vetle Lunde
Bitcoin’s decreasing volatility suggests BTC is maturing as a global financial asset, leading to a more stable price trajectory.
Bitcoin has become the seventh-largest asset globally by market capitalization, reaching $1.87 trillion. It now ranks above Silver, Meta and Saudi Aramco, according to Companiesmarketcap.
Top 10 global assets by…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Zoltan Vardai</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Samsung One UI 8 Might Bring AI Video Summarisation]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=350177</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/350177/samsung-one-ui-8-might-bring-ai-video-summarisation/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T09:50:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Samsung will reportedly bring an AI video summarisation tool in its One UI 8 based on Android 16. As reported by SammyGuru, the tool will be able to analyse a video, based on speech, visuals, and captions. A multi-modal AI model will then summarise the main points of the video. The feature will apparently be […]
The post Samsung One UI 8 Might Bring AI Video Summarisation appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Newsdesk</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This data set helps researchers spot harmful stereotypes in LLMs]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1115946</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/04/30/1115946/this-data-set-helps-researchers-spot-harmful-stereotypes-in-llms/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T09:41:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AI models are riddled with culturally specific biases. A new data set, called SHADES, is designed to help developers combat the problem by spotting harmful stereotypes and other kinds of discrimination that emerge in AI chatbot responses across a wide range of languages. Margaret Mitchell, chief ethics scientist at AI startup Hugging Face, led the…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rhiannon Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Finland Bans Smartphones in Schools]]></title>
        <id>https://yle.fi/a/74-20158886</id>
        <link href="https://yle.fi/a/74-20158886"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T09:17:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chery Tiggo Cross HEV To Get Malaysian Appearance In May]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=350155</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/350155/chery-tiggo-cross-hev-to-get-malaysian-appearance-in-may/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T09:04:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This year’s edition of the Malaysia Auto Show is scheduled to happen in May as it usually does, but it looks like Chery may have a hybrid car to showcase during the event. This may come in the form of the Tiggo Cross, which may be known instead as the Tiggo 4 elsewhere. Paul Tan […]
The post Chery Tiggo Cross HEV To Get Malaysian Appearance In May appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ian Chee</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Circle taps Onafriq to cut Africa’s cross-border payment costs with USDC]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/circle-onafriq-partner-to-cut-africa-payment-costs-with-usdc</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/circle-onafriq-partner-to-cut-africa-payment-costs-with-usdc?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Stablecoin issuer Circle has partnered with Onafriq, Africa’s largest payments gateway, to reduce the high cost of cross-border payments across the continent using USDC.
According to a press release shared with Cointelegraph, Circle aims to pilot USDC (USDC) settlements within Onafriq’s vast network, which connects over 500 wallets and 200 million bank accounts in more than 40 countries.
“By integrating USDC, we aim to simplify financial transactions for institutions and individuals, reduce costs and strengthen trust,” Onafriq founder and CEO Dare Okoudjou said.
He added that the integration of USDC will simplify transactions and boost trust in digital financial services.
Currently, over 80% of intra-African transactions are routed through correspondent banks outside the continent and sett…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Amin Haqshanas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Xiaomi Debuts Its Own AI Model]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=350157</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/350157/xiaomi-debuts-its-own-ai-model/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T08:57:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Xiaomi has recently unveiled MiMo, its in-house open source AI model with reasoning capabilities. With the release of the large language model, the company has joined the ranks of China’s tech firms, hoping to gain a foothold in the AI industry. According to Xiaomi, MiMo was developed by Core, a specialised AI task force. The […]
The post Xiaomi Debuts Its Own AI Model appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nurul Kamil</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Xiaomi MiMo Reasoning Model]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/XiaomiMiMo/MiMo</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/XiaomiMiMo/MiMo"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T08:48:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Debate on Looser Data Limits Brings to Mind the Divisive Ordinals Controversy]]></title>
        <id>6feae542-2b1a-4681-be27-d67fdf8e8d0f</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/tech/2025/04/30/bitcoin-debate-on-looser-data-limits-brings-to-mind-the-divisive-ordinals-controversy"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T08:44:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Removing the blockchain's OP_RETURN size controls would allow more data to be embedded in transactions. Critics say this will only be used for spam.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sam Reynolds</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin May Evolve Into Low-Beta Equity Play Reflexively, BlackRock's Mitchnik Says]]></title>
        <id>74f0300a-3daa-4fd9-a866-5e9ec9ac6149</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2025/04/30/bitcoin-may-evolve-into-low-beta-equity-play-blackrocks-mitchnik-says"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T08:39:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA["It makes no fundamental sense, and yet when it's repeated enough, it can actually become a little self-fulfilling,” Mitchnik said.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Omkar Godbole</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Is Bitcoin a hedge against inflation in 2025?]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/explained/is-bitcoin-a-hedge-against-inflation</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/explained/is-bitcoin-a-hedge-against-inflation?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T08:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Understanding inflation and the need for hedges            
            
                
Bitcoin’s supply-and-demand dynamics, in addition to growing institutional adoption, position it as a potential hedge against inflation in 2025. However, its high volatility and centralization concerns mean it remains a speculative asset rather than a guaranteed safeguard against inflation.
What is inflation? 
Inflation refers to the general increase in the prices of goods and services in an economy over time, leading to a decrease in the purchasing power of money. As prices rise, each unit of currency buys fewer goods and services. Inflation is typically measured by indexes such as the Consumer Price Index (CPI), which tracks the average change in the prices paid by consumers for a basket of goods an…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Dilip Kumar Patairya</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trump Administration Could Alter Biden-Era AI Chip Rule]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=350146</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/350146/trump-administration-could-alter-biden-era-ai-chip-rule/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T08:24:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[US President Trump and his administration could be looking to bring back a Biden-era rule regarding the export of AI chips to other countries. Supposedly, it’s planning on making a few tweaks to the rule and, in conjunction, do away with its current way of segregating recipient countries into three tiers. According to sources close […]
The post Trump Administration Could Alter Biden-Era AI Chip Rule appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John Law</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Where and how to sell Pi Coin: A step-by-step guide]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/where-and-how-to-sell-pi-coin</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/where-and-how-to-sell-pi-coin?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T08:21:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Key takeaways

Set up your Pi Wallet and secure it with a 24-word seed phrase before transferring your coins.

KYC is often required on both CEXs and P2P platforms to transfer and sell Pi Coins.

You can sell Pi through CEXs or P2P platforms, each offering different security, speed and control.

Always do your own research (DYOR) before selling or holding, as expert opinions on Pi’s future vary.

If you’re here, you probably already know what Pi Coin is and just want to figure out how to sell it. However, a recap awaits, in case you need one. 
While the project pitches itself as a way to democratize crypto access through mobile mining, there are some major concerns that have been hard to ignore:

Pi claims over 60 million users, but blockchain explorers show only about 9.11 million wallets…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Bradley Peak</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Apple Watch SE 3 Display Leaked, May Come In Two Sizes]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=350132</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/350132/apple-watch-se-3-display-leaked-two-sizes/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T08:13:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There is a chance that Apple might be releasing its Watch SE 3 soon, possibly this year, as reported by 9to5Mac. The original model of the watch was released back in 2020, with the 2nd generation being launched two years later in 2022. Like the two preceding models, the third generation may also come in […]
The post Apple Watch SE 3 Display Leaked, May Come In Two Sizes appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ian Chee</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Leaderboard Illusion]]></title>
        <id>https://arxiv.org/abs/2504.20879</id>
        <link href="https://arxiv.org/abs/2504.20879"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T07:58:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Is Bitcoin price going to crash again?]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/is-bitcoin-price-going-to-crash-again</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/is-bitcoin-price-going-to-crash-again?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T07:56:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Key takeaways:

Bitcoin's 28% rebound from $75,000 faces resistance at $95,000, risking a bull trap.

Strong spot price momentum and ETF inflows support a potential $100,000 push.

Bull flag pattern suggests a $108,300 target if BTC breaks the $95,000 resistance.

Bitcoin (BTC) price has rebounded by 28% from its five-month low below $75,000 reached on April 9. However, its failure to break above the $95,000 resistance level decisively has sparked concerns that the latest recovery may trap bulls.
BTC/USD daily price chart. Source: Cointelegraph/TradingView
Bitcoin ETF flows provide a “more solid foundation”
But another big crash may be averted as BTC price momentum is backed by elevated spot Bitcoin ETF inflows in recent days. 
This provides Bitcoin a “more solid foundation” to surge forwa…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Nancy Lubale</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Banks must adopt crypto or be extinct in 10 years, Eric Trump says]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/bank-must-adopt-crypto-or-be-extinct-eric-trump</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/bank-must-adopt-crypto-or-be-extinct-eric-trump?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T07:51:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Eric Trump, executive vice president of the Trump Organization and son of US President Donald Trump, has delivered a warning to global banks regarding cryptocurrency adoption.
“The modern financial system is broken, it’s slow, it’s expensive,” Trump said in a CNBC interview on April 30, adding that the existing banking system “favors the ultra-wealthy.”
“It forced me into the crypto world,” he continued, adding: “And I’m telling you, if the banks don’t watch what’s coming, they’re going to be extinct in 10 years.”
SWIFT is an “absolute disaster”
While emphasizing the need for banks to closely monitor developments in the crypto industry, Trump highlighted the benefits of cryptocurrency’s underlying blockchain technology for the financial system.
He slammed the existing cross-border transact…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Helen Partz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[realme 14T Set To Land In Malaysia On 16 May]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=350149</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/350149/realme-14t-16-may/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T07:51:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hot on the heels of its recent launch of the 14 series, realme has revealed that it will be launching the 14T next month. The upcoming device has been listed on the brand’s official Shopee page with an arrival date of 16 May 2025. Aside from the first sale date, the listing also reveals that […]
The post realme 14T Set To Land In Malaysia On 16 May appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ikmal Rozlan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[I created Perfect Wiki and reached $250k in annual revenue without investors]]></title>
        <id>https://habr.com/en/articles/905812/</id>
        <link href="https://habr.com/en/articles/905812/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T07:45:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TON’s Broxus launches blockchain app scalability platform TON Factory]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/telegram-ton-factory-scalability-launch</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/telegram-ton-factory-scalability-launch?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T06:16:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Open Network (TON) ecosystem participant Broxus has unveiled TON Factory, a new platform designed to accelerate the development and scalability of high-throughput applications like decentralized exchanges (DEXs) and blockchain-based games.
In an April 30 post on Telegram, the project said TON Factory aims to help developers rapidly build and scale projects with modular components, integration tools, and hands-on expert support.
“For OGs already building on TON, TON Factory helps you scale further,” the announcement stated.
The initiative is backed by a team of over 150 engineers with experience delivering production-ready infrastructure in the TON ecosystem, per the announcement. 
Source: TON
“TON Factory will help developers focusing on L2/appchains with TVM tech and ensuring connecti…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Amin Haqshanas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BlackRock Looking to Tokenize Shares of Its $150B Treasury Trust Fund, SEC Filing Shows]]></title>
        <id>c3e9da3d-b1ba-4d10-99bf-07ac25dd1351</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/04/30/sec-filing-shows-blackrock-preparing-150-billion-tokenized-treasury-trust-offering"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T06:15:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BlackRock will work with BNY Mellon in creating a new class of Distributed Ledger Technology shares for the fund.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sam Reynolds</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Samsung To Add Direct Access To Gemini For Galaxy A Series]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=350134</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/350134/samsung-adds-direct-access-gemini-for-galaxy-a-series/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T06:10:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Samsung has announced that it is adding a feature to select Galaxy A series devices that allows users to directly access Gemini using the side button. With this feature, which is already available on the company’s Galaxy S series, users can simply press and hold the side button to activate the AI assistant. The upcoming […]
The post Samsung To Add Direct Access To Gemini For Galaxy A Series appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nurul Kamil</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum ETF staking will have little impact without multimonth rally: Analyst]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/ether-etf-staking-impact-on-inflows-little-price-rally-eric-balchunas</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/ether-etf-staking-impact-on-inflows-little-price-rally-eric-balchunas?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T06:04:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Key takeaways

Approving staking for spot Ether exchange-traded funds (ETFs) in the US may have a minimal impact on inflows unless Ether sees a sustained rally, says Eric Balchunas

ETH dropped significantly in price after the launch of the ETFs last year, unlike spot Bitcoin ETFs, which saw new all-time highs just two months after launching.

Balchunas said that for inflows to increase again, ETH would need a multimonth run and a strong narrative.

Spot Ethereum ETFs being able to stake a portion of the tokens under their control may not help garner inflows without a more sustained rally in the token’s price, says Bloomberg ETF analyst Eric Balchunas.
Balchunas said on an April 29 episode of the New Era Finance Podcast that staking being approved for Ether (ETH) ETFs would have “a little”…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Ciaran Lyons</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Telegram’s TON Takes On Real World Assets With Libre’s $500M Tokenized Bond Fund]]></title>
        <id>ebe6875e-7c61-4b31-9f2e-03a0d9648aa6</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2025/04/30/telegram-s-ton-takes-on-real-world-assets-with-libre-s-usd500m-tokenized-bond-fund"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T06:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Libre’s Telegram Bond Fund ($TBF) will offer accredited investors institutional-grade yield products that will also be available as collateral for on-chain borrowing and product development on TON,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ian Allison</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google’s “Audio Overviews” Feature For NotebookLM Now Supports Bahasa Malaysia]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=350138</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/350138/google-audio-overviews-now-supports-bahasa-malaysia/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T05:59:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google has updated its AI-powered learning tool, NotebookLM, by introducing support for more than 50 languages in its Audio Overviews feature. With this update, users can now generate podcast-style summaries of their submitted content in languages beyond English — including Bahasa Malaysia. According to a recent blog post, Google says the expansion is part of […]
The post Google’s “Audio Overviews” Feature For NotebookLM Now Supports Bahasa Malaysia appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Heirul Kamel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SEC drops investigation into PayPal’s stablecoin]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/sec-drops-investigation-into-paypal-s-stablecoin</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/sec-drops-investigation-into-paypal-s-stablecoin?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T05:46:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[PayPal says the US Securities and Exchange Commission has abandoned its investigation into the payment giant’s US-dollar stablecoin.
PayPal said in an April 29 regulatory filing that the SEC concluded its investigation into PayPal USD (PYUSD) and wouldn’t be taking any action.
The company said it received a subpoena from the SEC’s Division of Enforcement over its stablecoin in November 2023. 
“The subpoena requests the production of documents. We are cooperating with the SEC in connection with this request,” PayPal stated at the time.
In its latest filing, the firm said the SEC notified it in February that the agency “was closing this inquiry without enforcement action.”
PayPal has said its stablecoin is 100% redeemable for US dollars and “fully backed” by dollar deposits, including short-…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Martin Young</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FTX sues NFT Stars and Kurosemi in push to recover tokens]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/ftx-sues-nft-stars-and-kurosemi-in-push-to-recover-tokens</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/ftx-sues-nft-stars-and-kurosemi-in-push-to-recover-tokens?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T05:31:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bankrupt crypto exchange FTX has filed lawsuits against the non-fungible token marketplace NFT Stars and the blockchain gaming firm Kurosemi, which operates as Delysium, accusing them of withholding tokens they owed.
The lawsuits, both filed in the Delaware bankruptcy court, alleged that NFT Stars and Delysium failed to deliver all the tokens paid for by FTX despite repeated attempts to resolve the matter.
FTX claimed in an April 28 statement that it made “numerous unanswered attempts” to engage with both firms, and it would be “contacting numerous other token and coin issuers regarding FTX assets and will be filing additional suits against non-responsive parties.”
Source: FTX
As part of the complaint against Delysium, FTX claimed its defunct trading arm, Alameda Research, paid $1 million …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Stephen Katte</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SEC Delays Dogecoin and XRP ETF Decisions]]></title>
        <id>6bb80abf-8034-42d9-991c-6a51ab9ce9a3</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/04/30/sec-delays-dogecoin-and-xrp-etf-decisions"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T05:25:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The delays are expected as most ETF filings have final deadlines in October or beyond, one analyst pointed out.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shaurya Malwa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BlackRock files to create digital shares tracking one of its money market funds]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/blackrock-files-digital-shares-money-market-fund</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/blackrock-files-digital-shares-money-market-fund?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T05:18:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Asset manager BlackRock has filed to create digital ledger technology shares from one of the firm’s money market funds, which will leverage blockchain technology to maintain a mirror record of share ownership for investors.
The DLT shares will track BlackRock’s BLF Treasury Trust Fund (TTTXX), which may only be purchased from BlackRock Advisors and The Bank of New York Mellon (BNY), the firm said in its April 29 Form N-1A filing with the Securities and Exchange Commission.
The money market fund holds over $150 million worth of assets, invested almost entirely in US Treasury bills and cash.
BlackRock said that the shares “are expected to be purchased and held through BNY, which intends to use blockchain technology to maintain a mirror record of share ownership for its customers.”
Unlike the…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Brayden Lindrea</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[US Treasury’s OFAC can’t restore Tornado Cash sanctions, judge rules]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/us-treasury-ofac-cant-restore-tornado-cash-sanctions</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/us-treasury-ofac-cant-restore-tornado-cash-sanctions?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T04:14:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The US Treasury Department’s Office of Foreign Assets Control can’t restore or reimpose sanctions against the crypto mixing service Tornado Cash, a US federal court has ruled.
Austin federal court judge Robert Pitman said in an April 28 judgment that OFAC’s sanctions on Tornado Cash were unlawful and that the agency was “permanently enjoined from enforcing” sanctions.
Tornado Cash users led by Joseph Van Loon had sued the Treasury, arguing that OFAC’s addition of the platform’s smart contract addresses to its Specially Designated Nationals and Blocked Persons (SDN) list was “not in accordance with law.” 
OFAC had sanctioned Tornado Cash in August 2022, accusing the protocol of helping launder crypto stolen by the North Korean hacking collective, the Lazarus Group.
The agency dropped the pl…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Martin Young</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Strategy’s Bitcoin buys should be ‘super careless’ to pump price — Exec]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/michael-saylor-strategy-bitcoin-buying-approach-super-careless-idea-richard-byworth</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/michael-saylor-strategy-bitcoin-buying-approach-super-careless-idea-richard-byworth?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T03:48:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Key takeaways:

Richard Byworth says Michael Saylor’s Strategy could ramp up its Bitcoin buys by acquiring cash-rich companies and converting their cash into Bitcoin.

He says that Strategy should consider accelerating purchases as the Bitcoin supply on exchanges continues to decline.

Byworth argues that aggressively increasing Bitcoin holdings would boost Strategy’s mNAV, benefiting shareholders.

Michael Saylor’s Strategy should take a more aggressive approach to buying Bitcoin by acquiring companies to use their cash holdings to fund purchases and do away with over-the-counter buys, a crypto executive says.
“Saylor’s strategy so far has been the right one,” Syz Capital partner and Jan3 adviser Richard Byworth said on an April 29 podcast.
Strategy should try “super aggressive” buying
Ho…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Ciaran Lyons</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dataframely: A polars-native data frame validation library]]></title>
        <id>https://tech.quantco.com/blog/dataframely</id>
        <link href="https://tech.quantco.com/blog/dataframely"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T03:14:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Linux in Excel]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/NSG650/LinuxInExcel</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/NSG650/LinuxInExcel"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T03:08:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sycophancy in GPT-4o]]></title>
        <id>https://openai.com/index/sycophancy-in-gpt-4o/</id>
        <link href="https://openai.com/index/sycophancy-in-gpt-4o/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T03:06:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What It Takes to Defend a Cybersecurity Company from Today's Adversaries]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sentinelone.com/labs/top-tier-target-what-it-takes-to-defend-a-cybersecurity-company-from-todays-adversaries/</id>
        <link href="https://www.sentinelone.com/labs/top-tier-target-what-it-takes-to-defend-a-cybersecurity-company-from-todays-adversaries/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T02:53:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Malaysia attracts US$3.7 billion in digital investments, solidifying]]></title>
        <id>b95e1bfb983c9cc102bc4266d362a8c2</id>
        <link href="https://www.digitalnewsasia.com/digital-economy/malaysia-attracts-us37-billion-digital-investments-solidifying-position-aseans-tech"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T02:31:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Malaysia’s digital economy continues to go from strength to strength, emerging as a strategic engine of growth that creates jobs, opens new opportunities, and fosters local innovation for businesses]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>@DigitalNewsAsia</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Australia’s finance watchdog to crack down on dormant crypto exchanges]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/australia-finance-agency-austrac-dormant-crypto-exchange-blitz</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/australia-finance-agency-austrac-dormant-crypto-exchange-blitz?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T02:24:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Australia’s financial intelligence agency has told inactive registered crypto exchanges to withdraw their registrations or risk having them canceled over fears that the dormant firms could be used for scams.
There are currently 427 crypto exchanges registered with the Australian Transaction Reports and Analysis Centre (AUSTRAC), but the agency said on April 29 that it suspects a significant number are inactive and possibly vulnerable to being bought and co-opted by criminals.
The agency is contacting any so-called digital currency exchanges (DCEs) that appear to no longer be trading, and AUSTRAC CEO Brendan Thomas said they’ll be told to “use it or lose it.”
“Businesses registered with AUSTRAC are required to keep their details up to date; this includes details about services that are no l…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Stephen Katte</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MDV powers Malaysia's tech innovation with over RM13bil financing]]></title>
        <id>d3f5fdc4ea236d719dc3a9d352d4620c</id>
        <link href="https://www.nst.com.my/business/corporate/2025/04/1209375/mdv-powers-malaysias-tech-innovation-over-rm13bil-financing"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T01:56:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[KUALA LUMPUR: Malaysia Debt Ventures Bhd (MDV) has emerged as a key enabler of the nation’s innovation and digital transformation agenda, with more than RM13 billion channelled into over 1,000 high-impact, technology-driven projects.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bernama</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ledger scammers are sending letters to steal seed phrases]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/ledger-scammers-send-letters-steal-recovery-seed-phrases</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/ledger-scammers-send-letters-steal-recovery-seed-phrases?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T01:50:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Scammers are mailing physical letters to the owners of Ledger crypto hardware wallets asking them to validate their private seed phrases in a bid to access the wallets to clean them out.
In an April 29 X post, tech commentator Jacob Canfield shared a scam letter sent to his home via post that appeared to be from Ledger claiming he needed to immediately perform a “critical security update” on his device. 
The letter, which uses Ledger’s logo, business address, and a reference number to feign legitimacy, asks to scan a QR code and enter the wallet’s private recovery phrase under the guise of validating the device.
The letter threatens that “failure to complete this mandatory validation process may result in restricted access to your wallet and funds.”
Source: Jacob Canfield
A seed phrase, or…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Brayden Lindrea</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[You Wouldn't Download a Hacker News]]></title>
        <id>https://www.jasonthorsness.com/25</id>
        <link href="https://www.jasonthorsness.com/25"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T01:26:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trump Media considers crypto token and wallet for streaming arm]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/trump-media-exploring-crypto-token-digital-wallet</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/trump-media-exploring-crypto-token-digital-wallet?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T23:56:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Trump Media and Technology Group, the social media conglomerate backed by US President Donald Trump, is considering integrating a crypto token and wallet into its video streaming site, Truth+.
"We're exploring the introduction of a utility token within a Truth digital wallet that can initially be used to pay for Truth+ subscription costs, and later be applied to other products and services in the Truth ecosphere," Trump Media CEO Devin Nunes wrote in an April 29 letter to shareholders.
He added that the crypto token and wallet would be part of a rewards program that Trump Media is exploring across its services, which include the social media platform Truth Social and the financial services platform Truth.Fi.
Trump Media first signaled plans for a potential crypto payments venture last Nove…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Brayden Lindrea</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Labor pain, crypto gain — How weak JOLTS data sets path for Bitcoin price to rally]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/labor-pain-crypto-gain-how-weak-jolts-data-sets-path-for-bitcoin-price-to-rally</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/labor-pain-crypto-gain-how-weak-jolts-data-sets-path-for-bitcoin-price-to-rally?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T23:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Key points:

Weak labor and consumer data often precede Bitcoin rallies, leading some analysts to anticipate future economic stimulus programs.

Job openings fell to 7.2 million in March versus the 7.5 million forecast and consumer confidence hit its lowest level since January 2021.

If past patterns hold, Bitcoin could rally by mid-July and possibly reach $140,000 by October 2025.

Macroeconomic conditions have long been seen as a major influence on cryptocurrency prices. Generally, Bitcoin (BTC) and altcoins perform poorly when investors fear that employment and consumer data are weakening. 
According to a US Labor Department JOLTS report released on April 29, job openings in March approached their lowest levels in four years. US employers posted 7.2 million vacancies in March, below the…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Marcel Pechman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Betting markets’ Q1 US GDP forecast flips negative amid tariff turmoil]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/betting-markets-q1-us-gdp-forecast-flips-negative-amid-tariff-turmoil</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/betting-markets-q1-us-gdp-forecast-flips-negative-amid-tariff-turmoil?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T22:58:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bettors on prediction platforms Polymarket and Kalshi are flipping bearish on the US economy. As of April 29, both platforms are predicting that the US will log an economic contraction during the first quarter of 2025 in an upcoming economic data release. 
The US has logged positive growth figures every quarter since 2022, and a reversal in that trend could mark the start of a recession.
The pessimistic outlook marks a stark sentiment shift for prediction markets, which had recently anticipated a positive US growth report. On April 29, consensus Q1 US growth estimates on Kalshi, a US derivatives exchange, plunged from around 0.5% to -0.4% in less than 24 hours. 
Meanwhile, Polymarket bettors are setting the odds of a US economic contraction in Q1 at around 70%. On April 28, they still had …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Alex O’Donnell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Author of Crypto Bills Now Being Rehashed Predicts 'Wicked Hot Summer' in Congress]]></title>
        <id>efd65f86-4255-4797-861a-23f03284b564</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2025/04/29/author-of-crypto-bills-now-being-rehashed-predicts-wicked-hot-summer-in-congress"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T22:49:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Patrick McHenry, the ex-lawmaker who championed last year's crypto legislation, also said he expects a role to be found for Tether in the U.S. stablecoin field.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jesse Hamilton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[US Senate majority leader expects stablecoin vote before May 26 — Report]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/senate-majority-leader-john-thune-stablecoin-bills</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/senate-majority-leader-john-thune-stablecoin-bills?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T22:32:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[US Senate Majority Leader John Thune reportedly told Republican lawmakers that the chamber would address a bill on stablecoin regulation before the May 26 Memorial Day holiday.
According to an April 29 Politico report, Thune made the comments in a closed-door meeting with Republican senators, who hold a slim majority in the chamber. The Guiding and Establishing National Innovation for US Stablecoins, or GENIUS Act, was introduced by Senator Bill Hagerty in February and passed the Senate Banking Committee in March.
Thune did not mention any crypto or blockchain-related bills in his public comments on US President Donald Trump’s first 100 days in office. Since his Jan. 20 inauguration, Trump has signed several executive orders with the potential to affect US crypto policy, including one affe…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Turner Wright</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[No more window switching: Mastercard’s Agent Pay transforms how enterprises use AI search]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3005997</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/no-more-window-switching-mastercards-agent-pay-transforms-how-enterprises-use-ai-search/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T22:24:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mastercard is working with AI companies and banks to allow AI platforms and agents to facilitate transactions.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Emilia David</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin price still in bargain zone as US jobs report sparks rate cut hopes]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-price-still-in-bargain-zone-as-us-jobs-report-sparks-rate-cut-hopes</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-price-still-in-bargain-zone-as-us-jobs-report-sparks-rate-cut-hopes?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T22:22:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Key Takeaways:

Fidelity Digital Assets says Bitcoin is undervalued and the firm holds an optimistic mid-term outlook.

The JOLTS report shows a sharp drop in open US jobs, raising investors’ hope for Fed interest rate cuts. 

According to Fidelity Digital Assets, Bitcoin’s (BTC) mid-term outlook dropped to an “optimism” zone, as the investment firm noted that BTC is trending toward “undervaluation.” 
As proof,  the firm cited the “Bitcoin Yardstick” metric, which measures BTC’s market cap divided by its hashrate. A lower ratio suggests that Bitcoin is “cheaper” relative to the energy security of its network. 
In Q1 2025, the metric stayed between -1 and 3 standard deviations, cooling from its Q4 2024 overheated levels. The number of days above 2-standard deviations dropped from 22 to 15, …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Biraajmaan Tamuly</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Growth of crypto poses risks to investors, financial stability — Bank of Italy]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/crypto-risks-investors-financial-stability-bank-of-italy</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/crypto-risks-investors-financial-stability-bank-of-italy?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T21:50:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Bank of Italy identified Bitcoin (BTC) and other digital assets as emerging risk factors in a recent report, citing concerns for both investors and the financial system.
In its April 2025 Financial Stability Report, the Bank of Italy flags crypto volatility and rising integration with the broader economy, singling out stablecoins and non-financial firms’ crypto exposure as key concerns.
"The strong growth of Bitcoin and of other crypto-assets with high price volatility means risks not only for investors but also potentially for financial stability, given the growing interconnections between the digital asset ecosystem, the traditional financial sector and the real economy,” the report notes. 
Excerpt from the Bank of Italy’s Financial Stability Report. Source: Bank of Italy
The Bank of…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Christopher Tepedino</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trump's Truth Social Mulls Launching Token for Subscriptions in Latest Crypto Push]]></title>
        <id>38806852-3f69-4584-a468-6c835ffce78f</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2025/04/29/trump-s-truth-social-mulls-launching-token-for-subscriptions-in-further-crypto-push"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T21:39:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The company also plans to forge ahead with its ETFs, which will include cryptocurrencies.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tom Carreras</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Indian high court orders steps to block Proton Mail]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/indian-high-court-blocks-proton-mail</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/indian-high-court-blocks-proton-mail?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T21:13:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A court in India has ordered the encrypted email service Proton Mail blocked in the country for refusing to share information with authorities.
In an April 29 hearing of the High Court of Karnataka, Justice M Nagaprasanna ordered the government to “block forthwith” domain names associated with Proton Mail, citing authority under the country’s Information Technology Act of 2008. 
The order stemmed from a complaint filed in January by a New Delhi-based design firm, alleging that some of its employees received offensive emails through the service.  
It’s unclear whether the ban will take effect or face other possible challenges in court. The Proton team reported in March 2024 that Indian authorities had similarly proposed ordering the service blocked in response to alleged “hoax bomb threats,…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Turner Wright</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Only Teslas exempt from new auto tariffs thanks to 85% domestic content rule]]></title>
        <id>https://fuelarc.com/cars/only-tesla-exempt-from-new-auto-tariffs-thanks-to-85-domestic-content-rule/</id>
        <link href="https://fuelarc.com/cars/only-tesla-exempt-from-new-auto-tariffs-thanks-to-85-domestic-content-rule/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T20:59:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SEC punts decisions on XRP, DOGE ETFs]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/sec-punts-decision-on-bitwise-xrp-doge-etfs</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/sec-punts-decision-on-bitwise-xrp-doge-etfs?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T20:51:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) has postponed deciding on whether to greenlight two proposed cryptocurrency exchange-traded funds (ETFs) holding Dogecoin and XRP, filings show. 
The US regulator has delayed its deadline for ruling on the proposed ETF listings until June, according to two filings reviewed by Cointelegraph. 
The filings were responses to March requests from US exchanges NYSE Arca and Cboe BZX Exchange to list Bitwise’s Dogecoin (DOGE) ETF and Franklin Templeton’s XRP (XRP) ETF, respectively. 
They came on the same day that Nasdaq, another US exchange, asked for permission to list a 21Shares Dogecoin ETF. 
Dogecoin is the world’s most heavily traded memecoin, with a market capitalization of around $26 billion as of April 29, according to data from CoinGecko. X…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Alex O’Donnell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Edges Above $95K, U.S. Stocks Remain Strong as Analyst Warns of 'Blind' Market]]></title>
        <id>0b77b062-fd9e-4a51-9e8c-b2f07d34ab15</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/04/29/bitcoin-edges-up-to-usd95k-u-s-stocks-remain-strong-as-analyst-warns-of-blind-market"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T20:11:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Secretary of Commerce Howard Lutnick announced that the White House was finalizing a trade deal with an unnamed country.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tom Carreras</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meta unleashes Llama API running 18x faster than OpenAI: Cerebras partnership delivers 2,600 tokens per second]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3005976</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/meta-unleashes-llama-api-running-18x-faster-than-openai-cerebras-partnership-delivers-2600-tokens-per-second/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T20:02:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Meta partners with Cerebras to launch its new Llama API, offering developers AI inference speeds up to 18 times faster than traditional GPU solutions, challenging OpenAI and Google in the fast-growing AI services market.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Nuñez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Researchers are studying how to minimize human impact on public lands]]></title>
        <id>https://undark.org/2025/04/28/keep-wild-places-wild/</id>
        <link href="https://undark.org/2025/04/28/keep-wild-places-wild/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T19:45:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitget, Avalanche form crypto partnership in India]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitget-avalanche-form-partnership-to-boost-crypto-in-india</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitget-avalanche-form-partnership-to-boost-crypto-in-india?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T19:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitget, a cryptocurrency exchange with 100 million users, has announced a partnership with Avalanche to support community initiatives across India, one of the fastest-growing areas for crypto and Web3 developers.
The partnership will see at least $10 million doled out in mini-grants, scholarships, hackathons, and workshops to the Web3 community in the country. The initial focus will be in Delhi and Bangalore. Delhi is the most populous city in India, and Bangalore is known as the local “Silicon Valley.”
Cryptocurrency activity in India has surged over the past two years. According to CoinSwitch, a local exchange, crypto investment across the country accelerated in 2024, with the highest concentrations in Delhi (20.1%), Bengaluru (9.6%), and Mumbai (6.5%). 
Young adults aged 18 to 35 now ac…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Christopher Tepedino</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin price always rallies at least 50% after these two patterns emerge]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-price-always-rallies-at-least-50-after-these-two-patterns-emerge</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-price-always-rallies-at-least-50-after-these-two-patterns-emerge?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T19:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Key takeaways:

Bitcoin tends to rally significantly when low leverage meets stronger-than-expected retail sales and hawkish Federal Reserve signals.

In three separate 7-week periods, Bitcoin rose 50% to 84%.

Upcoming speeches from Fed Chair Jerome Powell could benefit Bitcoin price.

Bitcoin (BTC) price rallies are frequently linked to investors’ inflation concerns or data that surpasses expectations for economic growth, yet clear signals of an impending rally are rare. However, a combination of three independent events has historically coincided with BTC price surges of 50% or more.
Bitcoin/USD, log scale. Source: TradingView / Cointelegraph
Significant Bitcoin rallies occur when US Federal Reserve policy expectations ease, crypto market leverage is low, and strong retail data supports…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Marcel Pechman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SoFi Plans Major Push Into Crypto Amid New Regulatory Environment]]></title>
        <id>2f3ada3b-e97d-4f16-8191-76362479c063</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2025/04/29/sofi-will-allow-clients-to-invest-in-crypto-again-after-suspending-service-in-2023-plans-major-push"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T19:11:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There's been a “fundamental shift” in the crypto landscape in the U.S., CEO Anthony Noto said on Wednesday.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Helene Braun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bunq, Europe’s second-largest neobank, expands into crypto]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/bunq-europe-second-largest-neobank-expands-crypto</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/bunq-europe-second-largest-neobank-expands-crypto?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T19:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Update (April 29 at 8:54 pm UTC): This article has been updated to include comments from Bunq’s CEO to Cointelegraph. 
Europe’s second-largest neobank, Bunq, is expanding into cryptocurrency, citing growing retail investor demand for digital assets worldwide.
The Amsterdam-based neobank announced the launch of Bunq Crypto on April 29, a new offering enabling its users to invest in over 300 cryptocurrencies, including Bitcoin (BTC), Ether (ETH) and Solana (SOL).
Starting April 29, Bunq users in the Netherlands, France, Spain, Ireland, Italy and Belgium will be able to access cryptocurrencies directly through the Bunq app, according to an announcement.
Bunq CEO Ali Niknam told Cointelegraph that the move was driven by growing client demand for digital assets. “We believe that now many, many …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Zoltan Vardai</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tornado Cash Can’t Be Sanctioned Again, Texas Judge Rules]]></title>
        <id>fc5b1370-af53-43a5-b5da-ec4d7b6197e9</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2025/04/29/tornado-cash-can-t-be-sanctioned-again-texas-judge-rules"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T18:43:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In December, a U.S. appeals court ruled that the U.S. Treasury’s Office of Foreign Asset Control (OFAC) exceeded its statutory authority in sanctioning Tornado Cash.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cheyenne Ligon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meta’s first dedicated AI app is here with Llama 4 — but it’s more consumer than productivity or business oriented]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3005961</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/metas-first-dedicated-ai-app-is-here-with-llama-4-but-its-more-consumer-than-productivity-or-business-oriented/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T18:19:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This mainstream exposure will likely accelerate a shift in what people expect not just from consumer apps, but from workplaces...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carl Franzen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Show HN: Beatsync – perfect audio sync across multiple devices]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/freeman-jiang/beatsync</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/freeman-jiang/beatsync"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T17:32:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bamba: An open-source LLM that crosses a transformer with an SSM]]></title>
        <id>https://research.ibm.com/blog/bamba-ssm-transformer-model</id>
        <link href="https://research.ibm.com/blog/bamba-ssm-transformer-model"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T17:24:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chain of Recursive Thoughts: Make AI think harder by making it argue with itself]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/PhialsBasement/Chain-of-Recursive-Thoughts</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/PhialsBasement/Chain-of-Recursive-Thoughts"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T17:19:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Everything we announced at our first LlamaCon]]></title>
        <id>https://ai.meta.com/blog/llamacon-llama-news/?_fb_noscript=1</id>
        <link href="https://ai.meta.com/blog/llamacon-llama-news/?_fb_noscript=1"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T17:17:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Samourai Wallet Prosecutors Are Considering Dropping Charges Under New DOJ Crypto Enforcement Priorities: Filing]]></title>
        <id>9b36b910-d4ee-462e-9886-3535208b8bf1</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2025/04/29/samourai-wallet-prosecutors-are-considering-dropping-charges-under-new-doj-crypto-enforcement-priorities-filing"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T16:46:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The co-founders are each facing up to 25 years in prison for alleged money laundering and unlicensed money transmitting.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cheyenne Ligon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WonderFi’s Dean Skurka on Bringing Users Onchain and Canada's Crypto Evolution]]></title>
        <id>a385b7d2-bf6b-439c-ac1f-788c4e93eea3</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/consensus-toronto-2025-coverage/2025/04/29/wonderfis-dean-skurka-on-bringing-users-onchain-and-canadas-crypto-evolution"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T16:26:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[WonderFi's CEO, a speaker at Consensus 2025, outlines the firm’s Layer-2 ambitions, Australia expansion, regulatory hopes for Canada, and how volatility impacts the industry.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Aoyon Ashraf</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Will Arizona Become the First State to Join Feds in Planning a Bitcoin Reserve?]]></title>
        <id>d9063668-1142-442c-8cc1-b523c9bc1b60</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2025/04/29/will-arizona-become-the-first-state-to-join-feds-in-planning-a-bitcoin-reserve"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T16:11:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new approval from Arizona lawmakers to form a digital assets stockpile must still survive a veto potential from the Democratic governor.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jesse Hamilton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase’s Base Network Achieves ‘Stage 1’ Status, Reducing Centralization Risk]]></title>
        <id>7d072d24-3f60-421a-a920-8e95c984d5c0</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/tech/2025/04/29/coinbases-base-network-achieves-stage-1-status-reducing-centralization-risk"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T16:00:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The move means that Base will now have a security council which will  help approve certain network upgrades if needed.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Margaux Nijkerk</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Create Accessible and User-Friendly Forms in React]]></title>
        <id>6810f59e8deee87383c1bc46</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-create-accessible-and-user-friendly-forms-in-react/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T15:51:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When designing web applications, you’ll often be asked the age old question “How accessible is your website” and “Does it offer the best user experience?”. These are both very valid questions, but they are often overlooked in favour of rich or fancy ...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Grant Riordan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn College Calculus and Implement with Python]]></title>
        <id>6810eebd43aa3d16a14700eb</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-college-calculus-and-implement-with-python/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T15:22:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Calculus is one of the cornerstones of higher mathematics and a powerful tool for understanding change, motion, and growth across countless disciplines. But for many students, Calculus can seem intimidating or abstract. What if you could learn it ste...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Robinhood Crypto Revenue Expected to Fall in Q1 After Record Late 2024 Gain: JPMorgan]]></title>
        <id>566c9f9c-b936-42b1-a04e-184afe5d0f85</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/04/29/robinhood-crypto-revenue-expected-to-fall-in-q1-after-record-late-2024-gain-jpmorgan"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T15:12:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After a 700% surge in Q4 crypto revenue, analysts now expect a pullback in Q1 as trading activity slows.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Helene Braun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Register Models in Django Admin]]></title>
        <id>6810e5a2dc9845a2ab207f06</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-register-models-in-django-admin/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T14:43:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When you're building a website or an app with Django, one of the most exciting moments is when your database models finally come to life. But to manage your data easily – adding, editing, or deleting entries – you need Django’s Admin panel. Now, here...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Udemezue John</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Jepsen: Amazon RDS for PostgreSQL 17.4]]></title>
        <id>https://jepsen.io/analyses/amazon-rds-for-postgresql-17.4</id>
        <link href="https://jepsen.io/analyses/amazon-rds-for-postgresql-17.4"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T14:30:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[UK Government Targets Exchanges and Stablecoins With New Draft Crypto Rules]]></title>
        <id>fcb85fd8-4f27-4591-b2f0-903dd0f5a661</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2025/04/29/uk-government-releases-draft-crypto-rules"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T14:00:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The statutory instruments will see the creation of new regulated activities such as operating a cryptoasset trading exchange and stablecoin issuance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Camomile Shumba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How $330M BTC Hacker May Have Doubled Down on Monero Derivatives]]></title>
        <id>c860b182-cbd2-4443-a40e-0c334598597a</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2025/04/29/did-the-usd330m-btc-hacker-deliberatley-pump-monero-to-make-even-more-money"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T13:56:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Monero rose by 45% after a flurry of spot buys, but open interest increased by 107%.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Oliver Knight</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mission Impossible: Managing AI Agents in the Real World]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/gitconnected/mission-impossible-managing-ai-agents-in-the-real-world-f8e7834833af</id>
        <link href="https://medium.com/gitconnected/mission-impossible-managing-ai-agents-in-the-real-world-f8e7834833af"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T13:54:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tripp launches Kōkua AI as mental wellness coach across multiple platforms]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3005798</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/games/tripp-launches-kokua-ai-as-mental-wellness-coach-across-multiple-platforms/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T13:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tripp launched Kōkua AI, a mental wellness guide designed to deliver real-time, personalized emotional support across multiple platforms.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dean Takahashi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CoinDesk 20 Performance Update: Bitcoin Cash (BCH) Gains 6.3% as Index Trades Higher]]></title>
        <id>80eb4f67-7086-4331-82c2-98a06bfb7f69</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/coindesk-indices/2025/04/29/coindesk-20-performance-update-bitcoin-cash-bch-gains-6-3-as-index-trades-higher"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T13:14:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum (ETH) joined Bitcoin Cash (BCH) as a top performer, rising 1.8% from Monday.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CoinDesk Indices</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Vanishing $212M Bitcoin Order Caused Chaos for Traders. Is Spoofing Back in Crypto?]]></title>
        <id>9adbeb31-30dc-42b0-b1c9-0d9fb663c71e</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2025/04/29/a-vanishing-usd212m-bitcoin-order-caused-chaos-for-traders-is-spoofing-back-in-crypto"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T13:06:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Despite increased scrutiny, spoofing remains a challenge in crypto, highlighting the need for better surveillance and stricter regulations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Oliver Knight</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[xMEMS extends micro cooling fan-on-a-chip tech to AI data centers]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3005879</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/game-development/xmems-extends-micro-cooling-fan-on-a-chip-tech-to-ai-data-centers/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[xMEMS Labs, a pioneer of MEMS-based chips, announced that its innovative µCooling fan-on-a-chip tech will be expanded to AI data centers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dean Takahashi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BONK Bets Gain Favor as New Token Issuance Platform Nets $800K in 3 Days]]></title>
        <id>a0f905dc-a43b-4370-839c-8fffa965effe</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/04/29/bonk-bets-gain-favor-as-new-token-issuance-platform-nets-800k-in-3-days"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T12:53:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“I expect the platform's success to surprise many,” well-followed X user @theunipcs “Bonk Guy” told CoinDesk in a Telegram message.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shaurya Malwa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New atomic fountain clock joins group that keeps the world on time]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nist.gov/news-events/news/2025/04/new-atomic-fountain-clock-joins-elite-group-keeps-world-time</id>
        <link href="https://www.nist.gov/news-events/news/2025/04/new-atomic-fountain-clock-joins-elite-group-keeps-world-time"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T12:39:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Performance optimization is hard because it's fundamentally a brute-force task]]></title>
        <id>https://purplesyringa.moe/blog/why-performance-optimization-is-hard-work/</id>
        <link href="https://purplesyringa.moe/blog/why-performance-optimization-is-hard-work/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T12:29:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Programming languages should have a tree traversal primitive]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.tylerglaiel.com/p/programming-languages-should-have</id>
        <link href="https://blog.tylerglaiel.com/p/programming-languages-should-have"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T12:23:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Download: the AI Hype Index, and “normal” AI]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1115932</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/04/29/1115932/the-download-the-ai-hype-index-and-normal-ai/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T12:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is today’s edition of The Download, our weekday newsletter that provides a daily dose of what’s going on in the world of technology. The AI Hype Index: AI agent cyberattacks, racing robots, and musical models Separating AI reality from hyped-up fiction isn’t always easy. That’s why we’ve created the AI Hype Index—a simple, at-a-glance summary of…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rhiannon Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Show HN: A Chrome extension that will auto-reject non-essential cookies]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.bymitch.com/posts/reject-cookies/</id>
        <link href="https://blog.bymitch.com/posts/reject-cookies/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T11:49:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The AI Hype Index: AI agent cyberattacks, racing robots, and musical models]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1115918</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/04/29/1115918/the-ai-hype-index-ai-agent-cyberattacks-racing-robots-and-musical-models/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Separating AI reality from hyped-up fiction isn’t always easy. That’s why we’ve created the AI Hype Index—a simple, at-a-glance summary of everything you need to know about the state of the industry. AI agents are the AI industry’s hypiest new product—intelligent assistants capable of completing tasks without human supervision. But while they can be theoretically…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Editors</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Web3j Six Month Project Update]]></title>
        <id>68109495670a1300013504c2</id>
        <link href="https://blog.web3labs.com/web3j-six-month-project-update/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T09:10:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[November 2024 - April 2025
This report summarizes the activities and accomplishments of Web3j, an LF Decentralized Trust project, from November 2024 to April 2025. During this period, the project made significant strides in improving the framework’s functionality, enhancing user engagement, and bolstering overall community interaction. 
Key]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>George Tebrean</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[We need to start thinking of AI as “normal”]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1115928</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/04/29/1115928/is-ai-normal/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Right now, despite its ubiquity, AI is seen as anything but a normal technology. There is talk of AI systems that will soon merit the term “superintelligence,” and the former CEO of Google recently suggested we control AI models the way we control uranium and other nuclear weapons materials. Anthropic is dedicating time and money…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>James O'Donnell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[My sourdough starter has twins]]></title>
        <id>https://brainbaking.com/post/2025/04/my-sourdough-starter-has-twins/</id>
        <link href="https://brainbaking.com/post/2025/04/my-sourdough-starter-has-twins/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T08:20:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[An illustrated guide to automatic sparse differentiation]]></title>
        <id>https://iclr-blogposts.github.io/2025/blog/sparse-autodiff/</id>
        <link href="https://iclr-blogposts.github.io/2025/blog/sparse-autodiff/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T03:18:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Alibaba launches open source Qwen3 model that surpasses OpenAI o1 and DeepSeek R1]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3005880</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/alibaba-launches-open-source-qwen3-model-that-surpasses-openai-o1-and-deepseek-r1/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-28T23:56:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Qwen3’s open-weight release under an accessible license marks an important milestone, lowering barriers for developers and organizations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carl Franzen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[I use zip bombs to protect my server]]></title>
        <id>https://idiallo.com/blog/zipbomb-protection</id>
        <link href="https://idiallo.com/blog/zipbomb-protection"/>
        <updated>2025-04-28T22:28:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ex-OpenAI CEO and power users sound alarm over AI sycophancy and flattery of users]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3005850</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/ex-openai-ceo-and-power-users-sound-alarm-over-ai-sycophancy-and-flattery-of-users/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-28T21:49:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crucially, the turbulence also nudges many organizations to explore open-source models they can host, monitor, and fine-tune themselves.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carl Franzen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Beyond A2A and MCP: How LOKA’s Universal Agent Identity Layer changes the game]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3005824</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/beyond-a2a-and-mcp-how-lokas-universal-agent-identity-layer-changes-the-game/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-28T20:35:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The LOKA protocol, a proposed standard for AI agents from Carnegie Mellon University researchers, will give identities and intentions to agents.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Emilia David</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build a Production-Ready DevOps Pipeline with Free Tools]]></title>
        <id>680fe1e69418a1165cb184a2</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-build-a-production-ready-devops-pipeline-with-free-tools/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-28T20:15:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A few months ago, I dove into DevOps, expecting it to be an expensive journey requiring costly tools and infrastructure. But I discovered you can build professional-grade pipelines using entirely free resources. If DevOps feels out of reach because y...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Opaluwa Emidowojo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[30 seconds vs. 3: The d1 reasoning framework that’s slashing AI response times]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3005393</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/30-seconds-vs-3-the-d1-reasoning-framework-thats-slashing-ai-response-times/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-28T19:31:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[d1 framework changes boosts diffusion LLMs with novel reinforcement learning, unlocking efficient, problem-solving AI possibilities.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ben Dickson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build a Website from Scratch – Start to Finish Walkthrough]]></title>
        <id>680fd51ef631538076304a73</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-build-a-website-from-scratch-start-to-finish-walkthrough/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-28T19:21:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, fellow developers! Building a website can feel overwhelming at first – especially when you're staring at a blank HTML file, wondering how it ever turns into a real website on the internet. If you're new to web development, you've probably asked y...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kunal Nalawade</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WorldGen: Open-source 3D scene generator for Game/VR/XR]]></title>
        <id>https://worldgen.github.io/</id>
        <link href="https://worldgen.github.io/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-28T18:39:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Can LLMs do randomness?]]></title>
        <id>https://rnikhil.com/2025/04/26/llm-coin-toss-odd-even</id>
        <link href="https://rnikhil.com/2025/04/26/llm-coin-toss-odd-even"/>
        <updated>2025-04-28T17:32:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Writer releases Palmyra X5, delivers near GPT-4.1 performance at 75% lower cost]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3005734</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/writer-releases-palmyra-x5-delivers-near-gpt-4-performance-at-75-lower-cost/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-28T17:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Writer unveils Palmyra X5: The enterprise AI model that processes 1,500 pages at once, costs 75% less than GPT-4, and enables affordable autonomous agents for businesses seeking automation ROI.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Nuñez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[QuickNode: Building the Infrastructure for the Next Generation of Blockchain]]></title>
        <id>6807d5787fb8500001c39b99</id>
        <link href="https://blog.quicknode.com/quicknode-building-the-infrastructure-for-the-next-generation-of-blockchain/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-28T16:02:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Join QuickNode co-founder Dmitry Shklovsky as he discusses blockchain infrastructure, building decentralized applications, and the future of Web3 development on TheCube's Crypto Trailblazer Series.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>QuickNode</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Enable CORS in Django]]></title>
        <id>680fa40e9096ceb5eeedd90e</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-enable-cors-in-django/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-28T15:51:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you've ever tried to connect your frontend app to your Django backend and suddenly hit an error that looks something like "has been blocked by CORS policy", you're not alone. It’s frustrating, especially when your code seems fine. So what’s going ...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Udemezue John</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Turn Ubuntu 24.04 into a KVM Hypervisor – Quick Setup with Web Management]]></title>
        <id>680fa285102a9fb019d4fa34</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/turn-ubuntu-2404-into-a-kvm-hypervisor/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-28T15:45:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Virtualization lets you run multiple operating systems on one machine. It’s perfect for testing apps, hosting servers, or learning DevOps. A hypervisor is the software that lets you run multiple virtual machines on a single physical machine, and the ...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shamsuddoha Ranju</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Automate Mobile Testing: Strategies for Reliable, Scalable Tests]]></title>
        <id>680fa2440e43e5b002c3c7f4</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-automate-mobile-testing-strategies/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-28T15:44:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mobile test automation uses tools and frameworks to test mobile applications automatically. It replicates user interactions to evaluate the app's functions and detect possible issues early on. This automated approach is helpful since it accelerates t...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nazneen Ahmad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[It's School time: Adventures in hacking an old Kindle]]></title>
        <id>https://samkhawase.com/blog/hacking-kindle/</id>
        <link href="https://samkhawase.com/blog/hacking-kindle/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-28T15:02:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Download: China’s manufacturers’ viral moment, and how AI is changing creativity]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1115909</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/04/28/1115909/the-download-chinas-manufacturers-viral-moment-and-how-ai-is-changing-creativity/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-28T12:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is today’s edition of The Download, our weekday newsletter that provides a daily dose of what’s going on in the world of technology. Why Chinese manufacturers are going viral on TikTok Since the video was posted earlier this month, millions of TikTok users have watched as a young Chinese man in a blue T-shirt sits beside…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rhiannon Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Does RAG make LLMs less safe?  Bloomberg research reveals hidden dangers]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3005592</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/does-rag-make-llms-less-safe-bloomberg-research-reveals-hidden-dangers/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-28T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[RAG is supposed to make enterprise AI more accurate, but it could potentially also make it less safe according to new research.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sean Michael Kerner</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Chinese manufacturers are going viral on TikTok]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1115876</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/04/28/1115876/why-chinese-manufacturers-are-going-viral-on-tiktok/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-28T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Since the video was posted earlier this month, millions of TikTok users have watched as a young Chinese man in a blue T-shirt sits beside a traditional tea set and speaks directly to the camera in accented English: “Let’s expose luxury’s biggest secret.”  He stands and lifts what looks like an Hermès Birkin bag, one…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Caiwei Chen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[UPDATED] Malaysia and Maldives explore new ties in solar, defence, and digital tech [WATCH]]]></title>
        <id>2ff00997f9c35cff9b55bf1c234d9fd9</id>
        <link href="https://www.nst.com.my/news/nation/2025/04/1208426/updated-malaysia-and-maldives-explore-new-ties-solar-defence-and-digital"/>
        <updated>2025-04-28T04:17:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[PUTRAJAYA: Malaysia is eager to explore new avenues of cooperation with the Maldives, including floating solar energy, defence, and digital technology, says Datuk Seri Anwar Ibrahim.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hakim Mahari</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Retail & E-Commerce Innovation Marketing & Tech Summit: Malaysia 2025]]></title>
        <id>cd2a0d19be53d9723fc0475f09d0da2d</id>
        <link href="https://marketech-apac.com/conference/retail-e-commerce-innovation-marketing-tech-summit-malaysia-2025/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-28T01:58:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Retail & E-Commerce Innovation Marketing & Tech Summit: Malaysia 2025]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Zyra Kate Capilastique</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Is your AI product actually working? How to develop the right metric system]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3005642</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/is-your-ai-product-actually-working-how-to-develop-the-right-metric-system/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-27T19:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Metrics are critical for determining AI product performance. But where to begin? Here's a framework to apply across various use cases.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sharanya Rao, Intuit</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bits + Bytes: A Miscellany Of Technology]]></title>
        <id>92c9e6ae0de9449f2a2cd9808d52c95a</id>
        <link href="https://theedgemalaysia.com/node/752832"/>
        <updated>2025-04-27T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[NEWS

Malaysia sees tech salary surge in 2025, led by system engineers

Tech salaries in Malaysia have risen significantly this year, with system engineers recording the highest increase at 8%, according to NodeFlair’s Tech Salary Report 2...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Edge Malaysia</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FORKLIFTACTION, B2B news service and business platform about forklifts and materials handling]]></title>
        <id>20065c212264065b824a3328d06be4fc</id>
        <link href="https://www.forkliftaction.com/pagenotfound.aspx"/>
        <updated>2025-04-27T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[FORKLIFTACTION, B2B news service and business platform about forklifts and materials handling]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Forkliftaction</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DeepSeek’s success shows why motivation is key to AI innovation]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3005636</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/deepseeks-success-shows-why-motivation-is-key-to-ai-innovation/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-26T19:55:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How did DeepSeek attain such cost-savings while American companies could not? Let's dive into the technical details.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Debasish Ray Chawdhuri, Talentica Software</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The True Size Of]]></title>
        <id>https://thetruesize.com/</id>
        <link href="https://thetruesize.com/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-26T15:41:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Malaysia remains 9th largest global exporter of high-tech products]]></title>
        <id>ec83e12fc9489689eba3a736f7c0fd4e</id>
        <link href="https://e.vnexpress.net/news/tech/tech-news/malaysia-remains-9th-largest-global-exporter-of-high-tech-products-4878750.html"/>
        <updated>2025-04-26T02:41:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Malaysia successfully maintained its position as the ninth-largest exporter of high-tech goods out of 143 economies in 2023, the highest recognition it has achieved in the past decade, Bernama has reported.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>VnExpress</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Liquid AI is revolutionizing LLMs to work on edge devices like smartphones with new ‘Hyena Edge’ model]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3005611</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/liquid-ai-is-revolutionizing-llms-to-work-on-edge-devices-like-smartphones-with-new-hyena-edge-model/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-25T22:02:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hyena Edge’s success positions Liquid AI as one of the emerging players to watch in the evolving AI model landscape.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carl Franzen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The new AI calculus: Google’s 80% cost edge vs. OpenAI’s ecosystem]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3005571</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/the-new-ai-calculus-googles-80-cost-edge-vs-openais-ecosystem/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-25T20:26:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Explore the Google vs OpenAI AI ecosystem battle post-o3. Deep dive into Google's huge cost advantage (TPU vs GPU), agent strategies & model risks for enterprise]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matt Marshall</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Create Models in Your Django Project]]></title>
        <id>680be6e3dfe4e9c64b6b0997</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-create-models-in-your-django-project/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-25T19:47:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you're building something with Django, there's one thing you can't skip: creating models. Models are the heart of any Django app. They define how your data is structured, how it's stored in the database, and how Django can interact with it. Now, i...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Udemezue John</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Malaysia remains 9th largest global exporter of high-tech products]]></title>
        <id>e1054193ac5220fd5f3cf3fb0ac3fcbd</id>
        <link href="https://en.vietnamplus.vn/malaysia-remains-9th-largest-global-exporter-of-high-tech-products-post318075.vnp"/>
        <updated>2025-04-25T18:11:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Malaysia’s high-tech exports increased by 2 billion USD to reach 127 billion USD in 2023. He said high-tech exports comprised 58.69% of total manufacturing exports in 2023, up from 52.48% recorded in 2022.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Vietnam+ (VietnamPlus)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Harden Your Node.js APIs – Security Best Practices]]></title>
        <id>680bb2b3917896a550779bcb</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-harden-your-nodejs-apis-security-best-practices/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-25T16:05:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you’ve built an API with Node.js, chances are you’ve thought about security – at least a little. Maybe you’ve heard about SQL injection, brute force attacks, or data leaks. But here’s the thing: it’s not just about big hacks. Even small gaps in yo...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Manish Shivanandhan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[UK agrees to assist Malaysia in technology, new energy]]></title>
        <id>9bba1ab03b6cc59e6474a313d3bc9d9c</id>
        <link href="https://theedgemalaysia.com/node/753068"/>
        <updated>2025-04-25T15:31:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The UK has agreed to collaborate with Malaysia in various fields, including technology and new energy management, said Deputy Prime Minister Datuk Seri Fadillah Yusof.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Edge Malaysia</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Show HN: An MCP server for understanding AWS costs]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=43794120</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=43794120"/>
        <updated>2025-04-25T14:43:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Download: how Trump’s tariffs will affect US manufacturing, and AI architecture]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1115868</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/04/25/1115868/the-download-how-trumps-tariffs-will-affect-us-manufacturing-and-ai-architecture/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-25T12:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is today’s edition of The Download, our weekday newsletter that provides a daily dose of what’s going on in the world of technology. Sweeping tariffs could threaten the US manufacturing rebound Despite the geopolitical chaos and market collapses triggered by President Trump’s announcement of broad tariffs on international goods, some supporters still hope the strategy will…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rhiannon Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Need to embrace technological advancements, sustainable practices discussed at country's premier real estate event]]></title>
        <id>13ba8e804fd9567fa951b4f7cc51bead</id>
        <link href="https://theedgemalaysia.com/node/753073"/>
        <updated>2025-04-25T12:00:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Industry leaders, policymakers, investors and experts explored the future of Malaysia's real estate landscape at the National Real Estate Convention (NREC) 2025 held here recently.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Edge Malaysia</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sweeping tariffs could threaten the US manufacturing rebound]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1115827</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/04/25/1115827/sweeping-tariffs-could-threaten-the-us-manufacturing-rebound/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-25T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Despite the geopolitical chaos and market collapses triggered by President Trump’s announcement of broad tariffs on international goods, some supporters still hope the strategy will produce a “golden age” of American industry. Trump himself insists, “Jobs and factories will come roaring back into our country.” While it’s possible that very targeted tariffs could help protect…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Rotman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Is that really your boss calling? Jericho Security raises $15M to stop deepfake fraud that’s cost businesses $200M in 2025 alone]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3005473</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/is-that-really-your-boss-calling-jericho-security-raises-15m-to-stop-deepfake-fraud-thats-cost-businesses-200m-in-2025-alone/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-24T22:18:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Pentagon-backed Jericho Security raises $15 million to combat deepfake fraud that has already cost North American businesses $200 million in 2025, using AI to detect increasingly convincing voice and video impersonations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Nuñez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Intel’s new CEO signals streamlining efforts but does not spell out exact layoff numbers]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3005456</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/games/intels-new-ceo-signals-streamlining-efforts-but-does-not-spell-out-exact-layoff-numbers/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-24T21:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Lip-Bu Tan, the new CEO of Intel, sent out a blunt message to employees saying the company has to reorganize to be more efficient.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dean Takahashi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Zencoder buys Machinet to challenge GitHub Copilot as AI coding assistant consolidation accelerates]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3005445</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/zencoder-buys-machinet-to-challenge-github-copilot-as-ai-coding-assistant-consolidation-accelerates/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-24T20:36:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Zencoder acquires Machinet to strengthen its position in the rapidly consolidating AI coding assistant market, expanding its JetBrains ecosystem integration while outperforming competitors like GitHub Copilot with innovative features such as Repo Grokking and Coffee Mode.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Nuñez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethically trained AI startup Pleias releases new small reasoning models optimized for RAG with built-in citations]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3005435</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/ethically-trained-ai-startup-pleias-releases-new-small-reasoning-models-optimized-for-rag-with-built-in-citations/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-24T17:03:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Pleias emphasizes the models’ suitability for integration into search-augmented assistants, educational tools, and user support systems.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carl Franzen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Evil Geniuses and Theta Labs launch AI chatbot based on esports mascot Meesh]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3005327</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/games/evil-geniuses-and-theta-labs-launch-ai-chatbot-based-on-esports-mascot-meesh/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-24T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Evil Geniuses, the well-known esports organization and brand, has launched its Meesh AI chatbot in a partnership with Theta Labs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dean Takahashi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Driving business value by optimizing the cloud]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1115716</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/04/24/1115716/driving-business-value-by-optimizing-the-cloud/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-24T13:56:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Organizations are deepening their cloud investments at an unprecedented pace, recognizing its fundamental role in driving business agility and innovation. Synergy Research Group reports that companies spent $84 billion worldwide on cloud infrastructure services in the third quarter of 2024, a 23% rise over the third quarter of 2023 and the fourth consecutive quarter in…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>MIT Technology Review Insights</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Download: Apple’s eucalyptus carbon bet, and climate tech’s bad vibes]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1115809</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/04/24/1115809/the-download-apples-eucalyptus-carbon-bet-and-climate-techs-bad-vibes/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-24T12:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is today’s edition of The Download, our weekday newsletter that provides a daily dose of what’s going on in the world of technology. Inside the controversial tree farms powering Apple’s carbon neutral goal “We were losing the light, and still about 20 kilometers from the main road, when the car shuddered and died at the edge…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rhiannon Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google adds more AI tools to its Workspace productivity apps]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3005313</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/google-adds-more-ai-tools-to-its-workspace-productivity-apps/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-23T22:43:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google expanded Gemini's features, adding the popular podcast-style feature Audio Overviews to the platform.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Emilia David</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Former DeepSeeker and collaborators release new method for training reliable AI agents: RAGEN]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3005302</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/former-deepseeker-and-collaborators-release-new-method-for-training-reliable-ai-agents-ragen/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-23T20:04:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[RAGEN stands out not just as a technical contribution but as a conceptual step toward more autonomous, reasoning-capable AI agents.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carl Franzen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon’s SWE-PolyBench just exposed the dirty secret about your AI coding assistant]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3005166</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/amazon-swe-polybench-just-exposed-the-dirty-secret-about-your-ai-coding-assistant/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-23T19:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon launches SWE-PolyBench, a groundbreaking multi-language benchmark that exposes critical limitations in AI coding assistants across Python, JavaScript, TypeScript, and Java while introducing new metrics beyond simple pass rates for real-world development tasks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Nuñez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OpenAI makes ChatGPT’s image generation available as API]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3005253</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/openai-makes-chatgpts-image-generation-available-as-api/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-23T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Enterprises can now make Studio Ghibli-inspired images through OpenAI's API.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Emilia David</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[From friction to flow: Why Swissport scrapped its VPN maze for Cato’s SASE platform]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3004830</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/security/from-friction-to-flow-why-swissport-scrapped-its-vpn-maze-for-catos-sase-platform/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-23T16:53:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Swissport ditches legacy tech, deploying a global SASE architecture with Cato Networks securing 26,000 users, unlocking real-time control.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Louis Columbus</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft just launched powerful AI ‘agents’ that could completely transform your workday — and challenge Google’s workplace dominance]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3005118</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/microsoft-just-launched-powerful-ai-agents-that-could-completely-transform-your-workday-and-challenge-googles-workplace-dominance/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-23T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft unveils new AI reasoning agents and Copilot features to transform workplace productivity, with Chief Product Officer Aparna Chennapragada sharing exclusive insights on the company's vision for human-agent collaboration.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Nuñez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cooperations with China continue to drive Malaysia's tech ambitions: experts]]></title>
        <id>7cf31983f27357e33a7e7403d769042c</id>
        <link href="https://english.news.cn/20250423/23952d602d384abe9a3be2f40797fa2d/c.html"/>
        <updated>2025-04-23T09:33:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cooperations with China continue to drive Malaysia's tech ambitions: experts-]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>english.news.cn</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[IBM Tech Innovation Summit]]></title>
        <id>eb7b875c351e513c2d4750bb29a0ab40</id>
        <link href="https://www.malaysiakini.com/news/741130"/>
        <updated>2025-04-23T02:44:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Seats are limited. Register now!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Malaysiakini Team</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[$42.1 million poured into startup offering energy-efficient solutions for costly and unwieldy operational data and AI workloads]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3005163</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/data-infrastructure/42-1-million-poured-into-startup-offering-energy-efficient-solutions-for-costly-and-unwieldy-operational-data-and-ai-workloads/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-23T02:28:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The funding infusion sharpens a mission to make hyperscale analytics radically cheaper and greener at the very moment enterprises fear ballooning data‑center power bills.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ujas Patel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[More accurate coding: Researchers adapt Sequential Monte Carlo for AI-generated code]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3005146</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/more-accurate-coding-researchers-adapt-sequential-monte-carlo-for-ai-generated-code/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-23T00:09:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Researchers from MIT, Yale, McGill University and others found that adapting the Sequential Monte Carlo algorithm can make AI-generated code better.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Emilia David</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SWiRL: The business case for AI that thinks like your best problem-solvers]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3004781</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/swirl-the-business-case-for-ai-that-thinks-like-your-best-problem-solvers/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-22T23:53:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Training LLMs on trajectories of reasoning and tool use makes them superior at multi-step reasoning tasks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ben Dickson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Batch data processing is too slow for real-time AI: How open-source Apache Airflow 3.0 solves the challenge with event-driven data orchestration]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3004953</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/data-infrastructure/open-source-airflow-3-0-set-to-accelerate-data-orchestration-for-enterprise-ai-inference/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-22T20:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Open-source data orchestration gets a major rewrite to help support inference and enterprise AI]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sean Michael Kerner</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Alabama’s Pursell Agri-Tech teams with Wastech on fertilizer venture in Malaysia]]></title>
        <id>af0a46cec4f3cf8c521e3bd5a58cb6d6</id>
        <link href="https://www.madeinalabama.com/2025/04/alabamas-pursell-agri-tech-teams-with-wastech-on-fertilizer-venture-in-malaysia/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-21T18:21:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Pursell and Wastech Group are establishing a state-of-the-art facility in Malaysia to producte advanced controlled release fertilizers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jerry Underwood</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>