<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2025-05-04T22:12:28.880Z</id>
    <title>AngJianming RSS Feed</title>
    <updated>2025-05-04T22:12:28.880Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mastering Git: Understanding `git init` and `git clone` for Effective Version Control]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/toluwanee/mastering-git-understanding-git-init-and-git-clone-for-effective-version-control-3k9l</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/toluwanee/mastering-git-understanding-git-init-and-git-clone-for-effective-version-control-3k9l"/>
        <updated>2025-05-04T21:59:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As a developer, you're likely no stranger to Git, the powerful version control system that helps you manage changes to your codebase. However, for those just starting out or looking to solidify their understanding, two fundamental commands can often cause confusion: git init and git clone. In this post, we'll dive into the differences between these commands, when to use each, and how they fit into your overall Git workflow.
git init: Starting a New Project from Scratch
When you're beginning a new project and want to put it under version control, git init is the command you'll use. This command creates a new Git repository in your project directory, initializing it with a hidden .git folder that tracks changes to your code.
Here's a step-by-step breakdown of what happens when you run git in…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Oni Toluwalope</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Enable Risk management with ML through Scalable Cloud-Native Data Management]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/prady1/enable-risk-management-with-ml-through-scalable-cloud-native-data-management-5eai</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/prady1/enable-risk-management-with-ml-through-scalable-cloud-native-data-management-5eai"/>
        <updated>2025-05-04T21:58:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Financial crimes are a persistent threat to financial institutions. Financial institutions have to build intelligent Risk management systems leveraging AI/ML which can defect and present malicious activities. Ability of computing power with the evolution of cloud computing has enabled leveraging machine learning(ML) for Risk management functions like anti money laundering.
Data is the foundation of any machine learning project. One of key consideration is availability of high quality data as data quality plays a vital role in identifying and mitigating financial crimes.
Why data quality is important => 
What are possible data quality challenges :-

Lack of data standardization across enterprise => 
Accuracy and completeness => 
Machine learning models may need data from past years which mi…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pradyumna</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Here’s what happened in crypto today]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/what-happened-in-crypto-today</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/what-happened-in-crypto-today?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-04T21:47:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today in crypto, the government of Maldives signs $9 billion deal to establish crypto hub, a group of pro-crypto US Senate Democrats have said they would oppose a stablecoin bill in its current form, and OKX founder and CEO has responded to Justin Sun’s criticism.
Maldives signs $9 billion deal to become international crypto hub
The government of the Maldives signed a $9 billion deal with Dubai-based family office MBS Global Investments to develop a crypto hub in the island nation's capital of Malé and to attract foreign investment opportunities.
Part of the development deal includes plans for an 830,000-square-meter facility used to house and host blockchain, crypto, and Web3 firms.
Maldives sits between Africa, Asia, and Australia. Source: Worldometer
According to the Financial Times, wh…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Cointelegraph</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use SAM in Scala for Discriminator Criteria Types]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/generatecodedev/how-to-use-sam-in-scala-for-discriminator-criteria-types-4b94</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/generatecodedev/how-to-use-sam-in-scala-for-discriminator-criteria-types-4b94"/>
        <updated>2025-05-04T21:45:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In Scala, using type members and type classes can lead to complex code, particularly when dealing with self-referential types. This article guides you through calling the getFor method from a SAM trait called DiscriminatorCriteria, utilizing Scala's powerful type system and quoted expressions.
Understanding DiscriminatorCriteria Trait
The DiscriminatorCriteria trait defines a method getFor that takes a type parameter <V <: A. Here's the trait's signature:
trait DiscriminatorCriteria[A] {
    def getFor[V <: A]: Int
}

The Issue at Hand
When working with mirrors and type reflections in Scala, particularly in macros or complex type derivation, it is common to encounter type mismatches. In your case, the issue arises when specifying headType as a type argument for the getFor method. This happ…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Generatecode</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Most Subtle Bug approved in a PR]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/gags88/the-most-subtle-bug-approved-in-a-pr-4ake</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/gags88/the-most-subtle-bug-approved-in-a-pr-4ake"/>
        <updated>2025-05-04T21:34:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[✅ Reviewed PR
The most subtle bugs aren't in the code you write - they're in the code you approve without enough context.
This is a short story about a seemingly harmless line in a PR that I reviewed - and how it taught me to slow down, even with small changes.
The line of code below,
if(!user.isVerified) return;

intention behind this was good not to allow unverified users to proceed into the app.
But this return statement wasn't part of larger flow. It was inside a route guard - and it exited silently, without a redirect, message or error.
User who signed up with Google or Github (OAuth) were marked isVerified=false
This line caused the app to fail to load the protected dashboard, but displayed no error
The app just failed silently with blank screen to user.
A fallback route with clear message was added and tested both social and email/password flows going forward.
if(!user.isVerified) {
    this.route.navigate(['/verify-email']);
    return;
}

🧠 Real world dev lesson from more than a decade of experience
💬 I'd love to hear your most unexpected regrets too]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gagandeep Sharma</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Timeline: My Career Shift from Mechanical Engineer to Cybersecurity]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/davebellen/timeline-my-career-shift-from-mechanical-engineer-to-cybersecurity-p25</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/davebellen/timeline-my-career-shift-from-mechanical-engineer-to-cybersecurity-p25"/>
        <updated>2025-05-04T21:31:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What This Blog Is About
In this second blog, I want to look back on my work journeyfrom my early days as a mechanical engineer to where I am now in cybersecurity. Ill walk you through the timeline of my roles, highlight the key skills and decisions that shaped my path, and share what I would do differently if I were just starting my transition today. My hope is that anyone looking to shift into tech or cybersecurity can take something useful from this.

Left: Just before kicking off a client project as an Identity & Access Management Engineeroutside their building in Sydney.

Right: Unwinding after workon a boat to Manly Beach in my One Piece costume, with the Sydney Opera House quietly in the background.
As you look at the diagram below, youll see a visual representation of the key milest…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dave Bellen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Disable Lightbox Behavior for Images in HTML?]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/generatecodedev/how-to-disable-lightbox-behavior-for-images-in-html-p02</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/generatecodedev/how-to-disable-lightbox-behavior-for-images-in-html-p02"/>
        <updated>2025-05-04T21:30:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When developing web pages that feature interactive elements, such as image galleries or portfolios, developers often implement lightbox functionality to enhance user experience. However, if you want to disable the lightbox feature for a specific image or set of images, you need to follow certain steps to ensure that the intended behavior is achieved.
This articles aims to explain why your images might still exhibit lightbox behavior even after removing the <a> tag and how you can effectively disable it using best practices in HTML, CSS, and JavaScript.
Understanding Lightbox Functionality
A lightbox is a script that allows images and other media to be displayed in an overlay on the current page. It’s typically invoked by wrapping your images in anchor (<a>) tags, which are then linked to t…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Generatecode</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Are AI Agents Simply LLM Wrappers?]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/distalx/are-ai-agents-simply-llm-wrappers-43lh</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/distalx/are-ai-agents-simply-llm-wrappers-43lh"/>
        <updated>2025-05-04T21:29:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Many AI Agents use Large Language Models (LLMs) for language.
But agents often do more:
Planning: They figure out how to do things step by step.
Memory: They remember what they've done.
Tool Use: They use other programs and tools.
Interaction: Some can see and act in the real world.
So, while LLMs are a key part, calling an AI Agent just an LLM wrapper misses the other important pieces that make them work.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>D</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kidnapped dad of crypto businessman freed from ransom attempt: Report]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/kidnapped-dad-crypto-entrepreneur-freed-ransom-attempt</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/kidnapped-dad-crypto-entrepreneur-freed-ransom-attempt?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-04T21:27:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The father of an unnamed crypto entrepreneur was freed by police in Paris, France, during a law enforcement raid of the property where the man was held captive for ransom over several days.
According to reporting from Le Monde, the May 3 raid resulted in five arrests. Local outlet Le Parisien also said the kidnappers demanded between 5 million and 7 million euros, or up to $7.9 million, to release the captive man.
Although the details on the identity of the victims remain scant, likely for security reasons, the crypto entrepreneur and his father co-owned a crypto marketing firm based in Malta, French media reports.
This incident features similarities to the kidnapping of Ledger co-founder David Balland in France in January 2025. Balland was also held for a crypto ransom until he was freed …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Vince Quill</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Build a No-Code Tech Newsletter Intelligence Agent with n8n and Vector Database]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/saintjamesfr/build-a-no-code-tech-newsletter-intelligence-agent-with-n8n-and-vector-database-19oi</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/saintjamesfr/build-a-no-code-tech-newsletter-intelligence-agent-with-n8n-and-vector-database-19oi"/>
        <updated>2025-05-04T21:26:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fighting mental fatigue...


Do you ever feel overwhelmed by tech newsletters? As a fullstack developer, you need to stay up to date across multiple areas — frontend, backend, databases, infrastructure, and more.
Personally, I’m subscribed to at least 15 newsletters, and I love them all — spoiler alert: I list most of them at the end of the article. But if I miss a day or two, my “DEV” folder starts overflowing. I often spend hours on the weekend catching up — reading inspiring articles, testing snippets, and discovering new tools. It’s one of the best ways to grow and stay sharp.
But let’s be honest — keeping up with everything is exhausting.
So last weekend, I gave myself a challenge: build a system to manage the overflow using as little code as possible, combining AI and automation. I’m…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>saint-james-fr</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub Actions + AWS: Effortless Zero-Downtime Deploys to S3, EC2 & Lambda]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/alex_aslam/github-actions-aws-effortless-zero-downtime-deploys-to-s3-ec2-lambda-45no</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/alex_aslam/github-actions-aws-effortless-zero-downtime-deploys-to-s3-ec2-lambda-45no"/>
        <updated>2025-05-04T21:22:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hey there, fellow developer! 👋 Let’s talk about a nightmare we’ve all had:

You’re deploying code to AWS, fingers crossed, praying it doesn’t take down your entire app. The loading spinner mocks you. Your Slack DMs blow up: “Is the site down??”  
But what if you could deploy updates with zero downtime while sipping coffee? Enter GitHub Actions + AWS—the dynamic duo that’ll turn you into the calmest dev in the room.  
Why GitHub Actions + AWS?




No More “It Works on My Machine”: Deploy from a clean, consistent environment every time.


Zero Downtime: Blue/green deployments, Lambda aliases, and S3 magic keep your site alive.


Free (Mostly): GitHub Actions gives you 2000 free minutes/month.



Let’s automate your AWS deploys like a pro.  
1. Deploy a Static Site to S3 (And Invalidate Clou…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alex Aslam</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Архитектура Масштабируемых PERN-Приложений: Уроки, Извлеченные Богданом Новотарским]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/bogdannovotarskij/arkhitiektura-masshtabiruiemykh-pern-prilozhienii-uroki-izvliechiennyie-boghdanom-novotarskim-47dn</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/bogdannovotarskij/arkhitiektura-masshtabiruiemykh-pern-prilozhienii-uroki-izvliechiennyie-boghdanom-novotarskim-47dn"/>
        <updated>2025-05-04T21:18:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Создать веб-приложение, которое решает конкретную задачу — это уже достижение. Но что происходит, когда ваше приложение становится популярным? Когда количество пользователей растет экспоненциально, объем данных увеличивается, а требования к функциональности усложняются? Именно здесь на первый план выходит масштабируемость — способность системы эффективно справляться с растущей нагрузкой.
PERN-стек (PostgreSQL, Express.js, React, Node.js) предоставляет мощный набор инструментов для создания современных веб-приложений. Но сам по себе стек не гарантирует масштабируемости. Ключ кроется в архитектуре — в том, как вы структурируете ваш код, проектируете базу данных и организуете взаимодействие компонентов.
Меня зовут Богдан Новотарский (bogdan-novotarskiy.com), я Fullstack разработчик, специализ…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Богдан Новотарский</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[🚀 Build a Trading Bot in 30 Minutes (Yes, Really!)]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/gokhanuck/build-a-trading-bot-in-30-minutes-yes-really-1mga</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/gokhanuck/build-a-trading-bot-in-30-minutes-yes-really-1mga"/>
        <updated>2025-05-04T21:16:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ever dreamed of launching your own automated trading bot that reacts to live market moves in milliseconds—without getting stuck on unreliable data or messy setup? 👀
This is exactly what developers are doing today with real-time stock, forex, and crypto APIs.
In this quick post, I’ll show you how to get your first trading bot prototype running in just 30 minutes. Perfect for anyone who wants to test ideas fast and see real data in action.
✅ Step 1: Get Your API Key
Head over to Finage and sign up for an account. You’ll receive your API key in just a few minutes—no long forms, no fuss.
✅ Step 2: Connect to the WebSocket
We’ll use Python and the websocket library to connect to real-time US stock data.
Here’s a simple example:
import websocket
import json

SOCKET_URL = "wss://abcd1234.finage.…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gokhan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Every Software Engineering Team Needs a QA Tester]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/peter_akojede/why-every-software-engineering-team-needs-a-qa-tester-3ef8</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/peter_akojede/why-every-software-engineering-team-needs-a-qa-tester-3ef8"/>
        <updated>2025-05-04T21:16:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the fast-paced world of software development, Quality Assurance (QA) Testers are the unsung heroes ensuring that what we build actually works — and works well. They test end to end to ensure the products meet its requirement and specification. They look for loopholes, and prevent bugs in production.
Here’s why QA is essential:
✅ Bug Prevention, Not Just Detection: QA testers help catch issues early, saving time and resources before bugs make it to production.
✅ Improved User Experience: They think like end users, helping to ensure a smooth, intuitive experience.
✅ Boosts Developer Efficiency: Engineers can focus on building, knowing QA has their back on quality.
✅ Confidence to Ship: With QA sign-off, teams can deploy with peace of mind.
✅ Maintains Brand Reputation: High-quality, reliable software keeps users happy and loyal.
A great QA Tester doesn’t just test — they collaborate, communicate, and elevate the whole team.
Let’s stop thinking of QA as the last step, and instead, an integral part of the process from Day One. 💡]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Peter Akojede</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Graceful Shutdown in Go: Practical Patterns]]></title>
        <id>https://victoriametrics.com/blog/go-graceful-shutdown/index.html</id>
        <link href="https://victoriametrics.com/blog/go-graceful-shutdown/index.html"/>
        <updated>2025-05-04T21:09:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[KaiPod Learning (YC S21) Is Hiring VP of Engineering]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ycombinator.com/companies/kaipod-learning/jobs/Bs3H9uB-vp-of-engineering</id>
        <link href="https://www.ycombinator.com/companies/kaipod-learning/jobs/Bs3H9uB-vp-of-engineering"/>
        <updated>2025-05-04T21:01:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ask HN: Hackathons feel fake now – anyone else noticing this?]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=43889502</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=43889502"/>
        <updated>2025-05-04T20:55:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The New Control Society]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thenewatlantis.com/publications/the-new-control-society</id>
        <link href="https://www.thenewatlantis.com/publications/the-new-control-society"/>
        <updated>2025-05-04T20:24:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Maldives to build $9 billion crypto hub to attract investment: Report]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/maldives-building-9-billion-crypto-hub</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/maldives-building-9-billion-crypto-hub?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-04T19:40:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The government of Maldives signed an agreement with MBS Global Investments, a Dubai-based family office, to develop a $9 billion crypto and blockchain hub in Malé, the capital of the South Pacific archipelago nation.
According to a report from the Financial Times, the agreement, which was signed on May 4, was done in the hopes of moving the Maldives away from reliance on tourism and fisheries by attracting foreign direct investment into blockchain and Web3 technologies.
The project outlines plans for the Maldives International Financial Centre, an 830,000-square-meter facility that will reportedly employ up to 16,000 individuals.
Completing the project will take an estimated five years and the capital requirements for the ambitious development are more than the $7 billion in annual gross d…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Vince Quill</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[I'd rather read the prompt]]></title>
        <id>https://claytonwramsey.com/blog/prompt/</id>
        <link href="https://claytonwramsey.com/blog/prompt/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-04T19:17:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The complicated business of electing a Doge]]></title>
        <id>https://www.theballotboy.com/electing-the-doge</id>
        <link href="https://www.theballotboy.com/electing-the-doge"/>
        <updated>2025-05-04T19:14:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[LLMs as Unbiased Oracles]]></title>
        <id>https://jazzberry.ai/blog/test-generation-as-the-foundation</id>
        <link href="https://jazzberry.ai/blog/test-generation-as-the-foundation"/>
        <updated>2025-05-04T18:45:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Traders’ Favorite Lottery Ticket for the First Half of the Year — The $300K BTC Call]]></title>
        <id>cc358427-d0a0-40fe-89d5-53fd74d3dc30</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/04/bitcoin-traders-favorite-lottery-ticket-for-the-first-half-of-the-year-the-usd300k-btc-call"/>
        <updated>2025-05-04T18:41:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA["There are always folks that want the hyperinflation hedge," one observer said, explaining the solid open interest build up in the $300K call option expiring on June 26.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Omkar Godbole</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Riot Games is fighting the war against video game hackers]]></title>
        <id>https://techcrunch.com/2025/05/03/how-riot-games-is-fighting-the-war-against-video-game-hackers/</id>
        <link href="https://techcrunch.com/2025/05/03/how-riot-games-is-fighting-the-war-against-video-game-hackers/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-04T18:35:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Orders of Infinity]]></title>
        <id>https://terrytao.wordpress.com/2025/05/04/orders-of-infinity/</id>
        <link href="https://terrytao.wordpress.com/2025/05/04/orders-of-infinity/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-04T17:55:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AI code is legacy code?]]></title>
        <id>https://text-incubation.com/AI+code+is+legacy+code+from+day+one</id>
        <link href="https://text-incubation.com/AI+code+is+legacy+code+from+day+one"/>
        <updated>2025-05-04T17:53:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Critical Program Reading (1975) [video]]]></title>
        <id>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=7hdJQkn8rtA</id>
        <link href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=7hdJQkn8rtA"/>
        <updated>2025-05-04T17:48:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Design for 3D-Printing]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.rahix.de/design-for-3d-printing/</id>
        <link href="https://blog.rahix.de/design-for-3d-printing/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-04T17:38:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Load-Store Conflicts]]></title>
        <id>https://zeux.io/2025/05/03/load-store-conflicts/</id>
        <link href="https://zeux.io/2025/05/03/load-store-conflicts/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-04T17:18:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Typed Lisp, a Primer]]></title>
        <id>https://alhassy.com/TypedLisp.html</id>
        <link href="https://alhassy.com/TypedLisp.html"/>
        <updated>2025-05-04T17:17:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Saylor signals impending Bitcoin purchase following Q1 earnings call]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/michael-saylor-signals-bitcoin-purchase-following-earnings-call</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/michael-saylor-signals-bitcoin-purchase-following-earnings-call?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-04T16:43:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Strategy co-founder Michael Saylor hinted at an impending Bitcoin (BTC) purchase, marking the fourth consecutive week of purchases by the BTC treasury company.
The company's most recent acquisition occurred on April 28 when Strategy purchased 15,355 BTC, valued at over $1.4 billion at the time, bringing the company's total holdings to 553,555 BTC.
According to data from SaylorTracker, Strategy is up approximately 39% on its investment, representing over $15 billion in unrealized gains.
Strategy’s history of Bitcoin acquisition. Source: SaylorTracker
Bitcoin investors continue closely monitoring the company, which has been a major driver of direct institutional exposure to BTC by popularizing the Bitcoin corporate treasury concept and indirectly through institutions holding Strategy's stock…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Vince Quill</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Minimal Linux Bootloader (2018)]]></title>
        <id>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/Stefan20162016/linux-insides-code/master/bootloader.asm</id>
        <link href="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/Stefan20162016/linux-insides-code/master/bootloader.asm"/>
        <updated>2025-05-04T16:36:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dummy's Guide to Modern LLM Sampling]]></title>
        <id>https://rentry.co/samplers</id>
        <link href="https://rentry.co/samplers"/>
        <updated>2025-05-04T16:26:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Show HN: EZ-TRAK Satellite Hand Tracking Suite]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/benb0jangles/EzTrak</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/benb0jangles/EzTrak"/>
        <updated>2025-05-04T16:10:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The great cognitive migration: How AI is reshaping human purpose, work and meaning]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3006326</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/the-great-cognitive-migration-ai-will-win-at-intelligence-but-only-we-can-make-it-matter/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-04T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Humans need to embrace domains where AI still falters, and where human creativity, ethics and emotion emain indispensable.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gary Grossman, Edelman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to set up stop-loss and take-profit orders]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/how-to-set-up-stop-loss-and-take-profit-orders</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/how-to-set-up-stop-loss-and-take-profit-orders?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-04T15:23:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Key takeaways

Bitcoin and crypto traders can rely on automated orders on their trading platform to limit losses and secure gains.

Stop-loss orders in Bitcoin trading started as manual risk management in the early 2010s. Now, they have become advanced, automated tools on today’s exchanges.


In the algorithm era and bot pestering, proper trading tools like stop-loss and take-profit orders will help you protect your trades.

Setting up advanced BTC trading strategies doesn’t guarantee a successful risk management plan. Monitoring the market regularly helps you understand current conditions. This way, you can avoid strategic mistakes.

Stop-loss and take-profit orders in trading were used long before Bitcoin. In traditional financial markets, they were already used as a risk management and …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Emi Lacapra</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Is this the end of Bitcoin DeFi?]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/is-this-the-end-of-bitcoin-de-fi</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/is-this-the-end-of-bitcoin-de-fi?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-04T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Opinion by: Markus Bopp, CEO of TAP Protocol
Not long ago, the idea of Bitcoin as a government-backed reserve asset seemed like a stretch. The US Federal Reserve’s move to establish a Strategic Bitcoin Reserve marks a clear turning point. Once dismissed as a speculative asset or niche investment, Bitcoin is increasingly being treated by some governments and financial institutions as a national store of value.
This evolution puts blockchain development at a crossroads. On one hand, memecoins, once dismissed as internet jokes, have dominated transaction volumes and social buzz on leading platforms. On the other hand, institutions and governments are taking the world’s most popular cryptocurrency — Bitcoin (BTC) — seriously and investing in infrastructure to secure it for the long term. 
If B…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Markus Bopp</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin eyes $95K retest as traders brace for Fed rate cut volatility]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-95k-retest-traders-brace-for-fed-rate-cut-volatility</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-95k-retest-traders-brace-for-fed-rate-cut-volatility?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-04T14:05:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Key points:

Bitcoin attacks liquidity clustered close to spot price into the weekly close.

Market commentators eye significant BTC price levels below $95,000. 

The Fed’s upcoming interest rate decision is the key macro event to watch next week.

Bitcoin (BTC) fell toward $95,000 into the May 4 weekly close as traders braced for more macro-induced downside.
BTC/USD 1-hour chart. Source: Cointelegraph/TradingView
BTC price liquidations mount after 10-week highs
Data from Cointelegraph Markets Pro and TradingView showed BTC/USD retreating from multimonth highs toward the May open.
Hitting liquidity clustered around spot price, Bitcoin created a recipe for volatility as market participants discussed key levels.
“Dense longs cluster 95.7k-96k, heavy shorts 96.5k-97k right around current pric…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by William Suberg</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chart of the Week: '10x Money Multiplier' for Bitcoin Could Take Wall Street by Storm]]></title>
        <id>cb8b2561-896a-4b39-9a17-7b5ec70ae1ac</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/04/chart-of-the-week-10x-money-multiplier-for-bitcoin-could-take-wall-street-by-storm"/>
        <updated>2025-05-04T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Publicly traded firms relentlessly buying bitcoin for their balance sheet could result in 'significant buy pressure.']]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Aoyon Ashraf</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TScale – distributed training on consumer GPUs]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/Foreseerr/TScale</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/Foreseerr/TScale"/>
        <updated>2025-05-04T13:29:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘Everything is lining up’ — Tokenization is having its breakout moment]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/tokenization-breakout-moment-blackrock-multibank-telegram</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/tokenization-breakout-moment-blackrock-multibank-telegram?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-04T12:30:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tokenization of real-world assets (RWAs) is evolving from an abstract concept to a practical financial tool as institutional players increasingly test and deploy blockchain-based infrastructure at scale.
This past week alone saw a flurry of announcements from both traditional financial institutions and blockchain-native firms advancing their RWA initiatives.
On April 30, BlackRock filed to create a digital ledger technology shares class for its $150 billion Treasury Trust fund. It will leverage blockchain technology to maintain a mirror record of share ownership for investors.
The DLT shares will track BlackRock’s BLF Treasury Trust Fund (TTTXX), which may only be purchased from BlackRock Advisors and The Bank of New York Mellon (BNY).
On the same day, Libre announced plans to tokenize $50…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Amin Haqshanas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[An Alabama landline that keeps ringing]]></title>
        <id>https://oxfordamerican.org/oa-now/the-alabama-landline-that-keeps-ringing</id>
        <link href="https://oxfordamerican.org/oa-now/the-alabama-landline-that-keeps-ringing"/>
        <updated>2025-05-04T12:02:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Binance to launch crypto payments in Kyrgyzstan with new partnership]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/binance-launches-crypto-payments-kyrgyzstan-partnership</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/binance-launches-crypto-payments-kyrgyzstan-partnership?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-04T09:46:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Binance has signed a memorandum of understanding (MOU) with Kyrgyzstan’s National Agency for Investments to introduce crypto payment infrastructure and blockchain education in the country.
The MoU was formalized during the inaugural meeting of the Council for the Development of Digital Assets, attended by Kyrgyz President Sadyr Japarov, the exchange said in a May 4 press release.
As part of the agreement, Binance will introduce Binance Pay to Kyrgyzstan, enabling crypto-based transactions for visitors and residents.
The partnership also focuses on educational collaboration. Binance Academy will work with Kyrgyz government agencies and financial institutions to develop blockchain-focused learning programs.
“Binance is excited to partner with the National Agency for Investments of the Kyrgyz…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Amin Haqshanas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Oberon Pi]]></title>
        <id>http://pascal.hansotten.com/niklaus-wirth/project-oberon/oberon-pi/</id>
        <link href="http://pascal.hansotten.com/niklaus-wirth/project-oberon/oberon-pi/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-04T08:54:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pro-crypto Democrats pull support for stablecoin bill in last minute]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/democrats-pull-support-gop-stablecoin-bill</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/democrats-pull-support-gop-stablecoin-bill?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-04T08:16:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A group of US Senate Democrats known for supporting the crypto industry have said they would oppose a Republican-led stablecoin bill if it moves forward in its current form.
The move threatens to stall legislation that could establish the first US regulatory framework for stablecoins, according to a May 3 report from Politico.
Per the report, nine Senate Democrats said in a joint statement that the bill “still has numerous issues that must be addressed.” They warned they would not support a procedural vote to advance the legislation unless changes are made.
Among the signatories were Senators Ruben Gallego, Mark Warner, Lisa Blunt Rochester and Andy Kim — all of whom had previously backed the bill when it passed through the Senate Banking Committee in March.
The bill, introduced by Senator…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Amin Haqshanas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Intel Confirms: Arc Celestial Xe3 GPUs Have Entered Pre-Validation]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=350379</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/350379/intel-confirms-arc-celestial-xe3-gpus-have-entered-pre-validation/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-04T07:01:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Intel has more or less confirmed that its third generation Arc Celestial GPUs are very much on the way, the relevant chips now in their pre-silicon validation phase. Despite the rumours that Intel was planning on killing off its Arc GPUs after Battlemage, a new leak by Haze on X serves as proof that the […]
The post Intel Confirms: Arc Celestial Xe3 GPUs Have Entered Pre-Validation appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John Law</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CMF Phone 2 Pro Hands On: Playfully Serious]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=350377</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/350377/cmf-phone-2-pro-hands-on-playfully-serious/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-04T06:21:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The recently launched CMF Phone 2 Pro delivers many of the features its predecessor lacked. It features a thinner body, an additional 50MP telephoto camera, and finally adds NFC support – a much-requested feature whose absence held back the Phone 1 from ranking among last year’s top midrange smartphones. All while retaining more or less […]
The post CMF Phone 2 Pro Hands On: Playfully Serious appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Heirul Kamel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoiners blast Arizona governor’s ‘ignorance’ after Bitcoin bill veto]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/arizona-governor-katie-hobbs-veto-bitcoin-bill-bitcoiners-react</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/arizona-governor-katie-hobbs-veto-bitcoin-bill-bitcoiners-react?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-04T06:04:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoiners and United States government officials have criticized Arizona Governor Katie Hobbs’ decision to veto a bill that would have allowed the state to hold Bitcoin as part of its official reserves.
“This will age poorly,” Casa co-founder and cypherpunk Jameson Lopp said in a May 3 X post. Bitcoin (BTC) entrepreneur Anthony Pompliano said, “Imagine the ignorance of a politician to believe they can make investment decisions.”
Call for government officials who understand Bitcoin is “the future”
“If she can’t outperform Bitcoin, she must buy it,” Pompliano said. Crypto lawyer Andrew Gordon said, “We need more elected officials who understand that Bitcoin and crypto are the future.”
Source: Julian Fahrer
Wendy Rogers, who co-sponsored the bill with State Representative Jeff Weninger, also…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Ciaran Lyons</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google Gemini May Get Two New Subscription Tiers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=350341</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/350341/google-gemini-may-get-two-new-subscription-tiers/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-04T04:00:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In its current form, you can do quite a lot with Google Gemini, and if the internet search giant keeps its promise, it will completely take over the role of the old Assistant by the end of the year. Those who need it to do more would obviously have to pay a subscription to get […]
The post Google Gemini May Get Two New Subscription Tiers appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ian Chee</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[vivo V50 Lite 5G Hands On: Classy Vibes]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=350310</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/350310/vivo-v50-lite-5g-hands-on/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-04T03:23:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[vivo has recently released the newest addition to its V series, the V50 Lite, in Malaysia. The company has also given us the opportunity to have a look at the phone, so here are my first impressions of the mid-range device. For starters, the V50 Lite comes in three colourways, which are Titanium Gold, Fantasy […]
The post vivo V50 Lite 5G Hands On: Classy Vibes appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nurul Kamil</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OKX fires back at Tron&#039;s Justin Sun over mysterious &#039;freeze notice&#039;]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/crypto-exchange-okx-star-xu-tron-justin-sun-freeze-notice</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/crypto-exchange-okx-star-xu-tron-justin-sun-freeze-notice?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-04T02:53:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[OKX founder and CEO Star Xu has publicly defended the crypto exchange after Tron founder Justin Sun accused it of failing to act on a law enforcement request to freeze stolen funds following a recent hack of Tron’s official X account.
“OKX also has consumers protection policy according to law, we can’t freeze a customer’s funds according to your personal X post or an oral communication. I think you should understand it as the CEO of HTX,” Xu said in an X post.
OKX says there is no communication in the spam box, either
Xu said that the crypto exchange had not received any related correspondence through OKX’s official channels. “Our LE cooperation team just checked the email, including the spam box; we haven’t received any request related with this case,”  Xu said.
Source: Star Xu
In what is…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Ciaran Lyons</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What went wrong with wireless USB]]></title>
        <id>http://oldvcr.blogspot.com/2025/05/what-went-wrong-with-wireless-usb.html</id>
        <link href="http://oldvcr.blogspot.com/2025/05/what-went-wrong-with-wireless-usb.html"/>
        <updated>2025-05-04T02:03:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tecno Camon 40 Pro 5G Review: AI Veneers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=349163</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/349163/tecno-camon-40-pro-5g-review/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-04T01:00:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hot on the heels of its new Camon series landing in Malaysia, Tecno followed up with the Camon 40 Pro 5G. It gets roughly the same specs as its 4G counterpart but with a more powerful chipset and a slightly upgraded display. The new Pro gets an affordable price tag and with it, the company […]
The post Tecno Camon 40 Pro 5G Review: AI Veneers appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ikmal Rozlan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gorgeous-GRUB: collection of decent community-made GRUB themes]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/Jacksaur/Gorgeous-GRUB</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/Jacksaur/Gorgeous-GRUB"/>
        <updated>2025-05-03T22:57:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Warren Buffett to step down as Berkshire Hathaway CEO by year&#039;s end]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/warren-buffett-step-down-berkshire-ceo-year-end</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/warren-buffett-step-down-berkshire-ceo-year-end?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-03T21:15:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Warren Buffett, the CEO of publicly traded investment company Berkshire Hathaway, announced at the company's annual shareholder meeting that he will step down by the end of 2025, and his chosen successor will take over as CEO, pending approval from Berkshire's board of directors.
According to CNBC, Buffett reiterated that Greg Abel, the company's vice chairman of non-insurance operations, who was previously named by Buffett as his successor, will take over. The Berkshire founder announced:
"The time has arrived when Greg should become the Chief executive officer of the company at year-end, and I want to spring that on the directors effectively and give that as my recommendation."
Buffett added that he would stay at the company in an advisory role "but the final word would be what Greg deci…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Vince Quill</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Local cosmetics sector can be launchpad to position Malaysia as innovation-led economy: Sirim chief tech officer]]></title>
        <id>f3d9620891e0882d2a66ea582395ca3a</id>
        <link href="https://thesun.my/business-news/local-cosmetics-sector-can-be-launchpad-to-position-malaysia-as-innovation-led-economy-sirim-chief-tech-officer-AH14020110"/>
        <updated>2025-05-03T20:35:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SHAH ALAM: The Malaysian cosmetics sector can serve as a launchpad to position the nation as an innovation-led economy, said Sirim Bhd chief technolog...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hayatun Razak</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Not everything needs an LLM: A framework for evaluating when AI makes sense]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3006312</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/not-everything-needs-an-llm-a-framework-for-evaluating-when-ai-makes-sense/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-03T19:35:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The answer to 'What customer needs requires an AI solution?' isn’t always 'Yes.' LLMs are still expensive and not always accurate.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sharanya Rao</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin miners should pay costs in depreciating currency — Ledn exec]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-miners-pay-costs-depreciating-currency-ledn</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-miners-pay-costs-depreciating-currency-ledn?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-03T19:30:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin (BTC) mining firms should hold their mined Bitcoin and use it as collateral for fiat-denominated loans to pay operating expenses instead of selling BTC and losing the upside of an asset that miners expect to surge in price, according to John Glover, chief investment officer at Bitcoin lending firm Ledn.
In an interview with Cointelegraph, Glover said that holding onto the BTC carries several benefits including, price appreciation, tax deferment, and the potential to make extra revenue by lending out BTC held in corporate treasuries. The executive added:
"If you are mining, you are generating all this Bitcoin. You understand the thesis behind Bitcoin and why it is likely going to continue to appreciate in the future. You do not want to sell any of your Bitcoin."
This debt-based appr…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Vince Quill</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gold-Backed Crypto Minting Volume Hits 3-Year High as Central Bank Buying Drops]]></title>
        <id>965a38b6-6be7-404a-a8ab-68148c671d6e</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/03/gold-backed-crypto-minting-volume-hits-3-year-high-as-central-bank-buying-drops"/>
        <updated>2025-05-03T19:15:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A surge in demand, particularly from ETFs, pushed the average quarterly gold price to a record high.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Francisco Rodrigues</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Show HN: Free, in-browser PDF editor]]></title>
        <id>https://breezepdf.com/</id>
        <link href="https://breezepdf.com/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-03T18:15:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum nears key Bitcoin price level that last time sparked 450% gains]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/ethereum-nears-key-bitcoin-price-level-last-time-450-gains</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/ethereum-nears-key-bitcoin-price-level-last-time-450-gains?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-03T17:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum’s Ether (ETH) token is approaching a critical price zone against Bitcoin (BTC), which historically marked the beginning of a massive rebound.
ETH price fractal from 2019 hints at bottom 
The ETH/BTC pair, currently trading near 0.019 BTC, is edging closer to 0.016 BTC — the exact level it reached in September 2019 before rallying nearly 450% over the following year.
ETH/BTC weekly performance chart. Source: TradingView
The current ETH/BTC setup resembles 2019, with both periods marked by oversold relative strength index (RSI), long stretches below key moving averages, and multiyear declines.
In 2019, ETH/BTC fell over 90% in the prior two years, driven by the ICO collapse. 
As of 2025, the pair is down over 80% from its 2021 peak, weighed by skepticism over Ethereum’s switch to pr…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Yashu Gola</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why tokenized gold beats other paper alternatives — Gold DAO]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/tokenized-gold-beats-paper-alternatives-gold-dao</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/tokenized-gold-beats-paper-alternatives-gold-dao?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-03T17:16:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tokenized gold carries several benefits over other forms of paper gold, including gold exchange-traded funds (ETFs), according to Melissa Song and Dustin Becker, representatives of Gold DAO, a decentralized autonomous organization that facilitates investor access to tokenized gold.
In an interview with Cointelegraph, the DAO representatives outlined three major benefits unique to tokenized gold, including 1:1 redeemability for a specific quantity of physical, serialized gold, usage as collateral in decentralized finance (DeFi) applications, and transactional efficiency through on-demand liquidity.
"When you buy an ETF, you are betting on the gold price going up, but you do not own any specific gold bar," Song told Cointelegraph.
The pair added that the price of gold surged in 2025 due to t…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Vince Quill</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Tiny Company Wants to Buy $20M TRUMP Token to Change U.S.-Mexico Trade Deals]]></title>
        <id>893602ea-e9cf-4e7d-aee8-d24977a98a69</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/03/a-tiny-company-wants-to-buy-usd20m-trump-token-to-change-u-s-mexico-trade-deals"/>
        <updated>2025-05-03T16:47:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Freight Technologies, which also invested in FET tokens, says it's aiming to strengthen its technology and geopolitical positioning.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Francisco Rodrigues</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Arizona Governor Calls Crypto an ‘Untested Investment,’ Vetoes Bitcoin Reserve Bill]]></title>
        <id>f4c091c5-cb7d-4741-8b59-d066c99d0c2a</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2025/05/03/arizona-governor-calls-crypto-an-untested-investment-vetoes-bitcoin-reserve-bill"/>
        <updated>2025-05-03T16:01:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The bill, Senate Bill 1025, aimed to create a digital assets reserve managed by the state.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Francisco Rodrigues</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘Like Spitting on a Fire’: Tether CEO Slams EU Deposit Protections Amid Bank Failure Warnings]]></title>
        <id>8fe34898-f626-4e9a-a14b-6435b54c6d95</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/03/like-spitting-on-a-fire-tether-ceo-slams-eu-deposit-protections-amid-bank-failure-warnings"/>
        <updated>2025-05-03T15:35:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Paolo Ardoino criticizes EU rules that could force stablecoin issuers to rely on fragile banks and warned about potential bank failures in the future.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Francisco Rodrigues</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin mining — Institutions boost investments amid favorable US climate]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-mining-institutions-boost-investments</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-mining-institutions-boost-investments?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-03T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Opinion by: Fakhul Miah, managing director of GoMining Institutional
The Bitcoin (BTC) mining industry has never been more attractive to institutional investors. Fintech giants are investing in Bitcoin mining rather than just accumulating the asset, all thanks to the favorable regulatory environment in the US and the profitability margin of BTC. 
Then, numerous companies are diversifying by allocating computing power to AI, further strengthening their economics and, thus, investment attractiveness. For now, it looks like the future of the foundational layer for the Bitcoin network could mark the new gusher age.
Is Bitcoin mining profitable?
Bitcoin mining is still profitable. CoinShares, a digital asset investment firm, shared that the average cost to mine 1 BTC for US-listed miners reache…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Fakhul Miah</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CME Group Crypto Derivatives Volume Soars 129% in April With ETH Leading the Charge]]></title>
        <id>0e1767d2-530f-48a3-b42b-4144a50565db</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/03/cme-group-crypto-derivatives-volume-soars-129-in-april-with-eth-leading-the-charge"/>
        <updated>2025-05-03T14:07:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The exchange saw its crypto derivatives volumes rise sharply to $8.9 billion in April, led by ether futures growth.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Francisco Rodrigues</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[After Zora airdrop goes awry, what’s next for Web3 creator economy?]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/zora-airdrop-whats-next-web3-creator-economy</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/zora-airdrop-whats-next-web3-creator-economy?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-03T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Onchain social network Zora has built a reputation as a popular tool for artists, musicians and other creatives to monetize their content onchain, but the recent launch of its eponymous ZORA token has left many users confused and dissatisfied.
The token’s price tanked shortly after launch, with users and observers complaining about everything from poor communication from the team to the token’s distribution and utility models. 
This comes amid an overall decline in interest in the onchain creator economy and a changing perspective on whether blockchain tools like non-fungible tokens (NFTs) are still useful for creatives who want to monetize their work on the blockchain.
With creators and builders shifting focus and NFTs no longer selling like they used to, does the ZORA token drop symboliz…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Jonathan DeYoung</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[State of Crypto: IRS Departures]]></title>
        <id>243d623c-f6d2-41f3-952d-c8dadc84112f</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2025/05/03/state-of-crypto-irs-departures"/>
        <updated>2025-05-03T13:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Seth Wilks and Raj Mukherjee, two IRS digital asset directors, are leaving the agency just over a year after joining it.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nikhilesh De</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is a sealed-bid token launch?]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/explained/what-is-a-sealed-bid-token-launch</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/explained/what-is-a-sealed-bid-token-launch?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-03T13:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What are the various methods for launching crypto tokens?            
            
                
Launching a new token is a critical step for any blockchain project. Token launches enable projects to offer their native assets to early users, investors or supporters while securing capital or encouraging community growth. 
From initial coin offerings (ICOs) to fair launches and airdrops, each approach carries different levels of transparency, accessibility and risk. Since projects differ in their goals and target communities, several token launch models have evolved over time. 
Some focus on decentralization and wide community offering, while others aim for optimized fundraising or targeted allocation. Elements such as market swings, bot interference and regulatory pressures influence how…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Dilip Kumar Patairya</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[iCaur Is Set To Launch Two Models At MAS 2025]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=350372</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/350372/icaur-is-set-to-launch-two-models-at-mas-2025/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-03T12:14:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It is a known fact that Chery’s sub-brand iCAUR (or iCAR in China) will be debuting its fully electric vehicle in Malaysia. Recently we reported that the 03 will be coming but it seems like it will be joined by the V23 as well. This was confirmed by the automaker through a social media announcement. […]
The post iCaur Is Set To Launch Two Models At MAS 2025 appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Keran</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Deribit eyes US expansion under crypto-friendly Trump admin: FT]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/deribit-us-expansion-trump-crypto-regulation</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/deribit-us-expansion-trump-crypto-regulation?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-03T10:44:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Deribit, the world’s largest crypto options exchange, is weighing an entry into the US market, encouraged by what it sees as a friendlier regulatory climate under President Donald Trump’s administration, according to a recent Financial Times report.
The Dubai-based exchange, which processed $1.3 trillion in notional volume last year, is “actively reassessing potential opportunities” in the United States, CEO Luuk Strijers told the FT.
He cited the “recent shift toward a more favorable regulatory stance on crypto in the US” as a key motivator behind the decision.
Deribit’s potential plan to expand into the US comes amid reports that Coinbase is in advanced negotiations to acquire the platform.
In a March 21 report, Bloomberg said both companies have notified regulators in Dubai, where Derib…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Amin Haqshanas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Over 70 crypto firms join forces to tackle big tech’s AI monopoly]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/crypto-firms-join-forces-tackle-big-tech-ai-monopoly</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/crypto-firms-join-forces-tackle-big-tech-ai-monopoly?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-03T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a move that hopes to challenge Big Tech’s grip on artificial intelligence, AI agent protocol Thinkagents.ai has launched a new open-source framework for building onchain agents that operate autonomously across decentralized networks.
While traditional systems aim to restrict data ownership and platform abilities for their users, Thinkagents.ai is creating an interoperable ecosystem owned and controlled by its users. For Mike Anderson, core contributor at THINK, the Think Agent Standard is the future of AI.
Anderson and his team developed the Think Agent Standard to enable millions of autonomous onchain AI agents to transact and communicate. The protocol now has over 70 companies, like Arbitrum and Yuga Labs, on board to help out. 
The platform is now live, allowing developers, enterpris…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Stephen Laddin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Arizona governor vetoes bill to make Bitcoin part of state reserves]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/arizona-bitcoin-reserve-bill-vetoed-by-governor</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/arizona-bitcoin-reserve-bill-vetoed-by-governor?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-03T09:23:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Arizona Governor Katie Hobbs has vetoed a bill that would have allowed the state to hold Bitcoin as part of its official reserves, effectively ending efforts to make Arizona the first US state to adopt such a policy.
The Digital Assets Strategic Reserve bill, which would have permitted Arizona to invest seized funds into Bitcoin (BTC) and create a reserve managed by state officials, was formally struck down on Friday, according to an update on the Arizona State Legislature’s website.
“Today, I vetoed Senate Bill 1025. The Arizona State Retirement System is one of the strongest in the nation because it makes sound and informed investments,” Hobbs wrote in a statement aimed at Warren Petersen, the President of the Arizona Senate.
“Arizonans’ retirement funds are not the place for the state t…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Amin Haqshanas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vitalik wants to make Ethereum ‘as simple as Bitcoin’ in 5 years]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/vitalikbuterin-ethereum-simplification-bitcoin-inspired-redesign</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/vitalikbuterin-ethereum-simplification-bitcoin-inspired-redesign?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-03T08:30:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum co-founder Vitalik Buterin called for simplifying Ethereum’s base protocol, aiming to make the network more efficient, secure and accessible, drawing inspiration from Bitcoin’s minimalist design.
In a blog post titled “Simplifying the L1,” published on May 3, Buterin laid out a vision to restructure Ethereum’s architecture across consensus, execution and shared components.
“This post will describe how Ethereum 5 years from now can become close to as simple as Bitcoin,” Buterin wrote, arguing that simplicity is key to Ethereum’s resilience and long-term scalability.
While recent upgrades like proof-of-stake (PoS) and Zero-Knowledge Succinct Non-Interactive Argument of Knowledge (zk-SNARK) integration have made Ethereum more robust, he said that technical complexity has led to bloat…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Amin Haqshanas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Archers Didn't Volley Fire]]></title>
        <id>https://acoup.blog/2025/05/02/collections-why-archers-didnt-volley-fire/</id>
        <link href="https://acoup.blog/2025/05/02/collections-why-archers-didnt-volley-fire/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-03T08:28:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Merovingians: 'Do-Nothing Kings'?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.historytoday.com/archive/feature/merovingians-do-nothing-kings</id>
        <link href="https://www.historytoday.com/archive/feature/merovingians-do-nothing-kings"/>
        <updated>2025-05-03T07:25:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Apple softens crypto-related app rules, &#039;hugely bullish&#039; for crypto industry]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/apple-app-store-epic-games-restrictions-ease-court-ruling-united-states</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/apple-app-store-epic-games-restrictions-ease-court-ruling-united-states?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-03T06:19:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto app developers are now free to direct users to payments outside of Apple’s ecosystem without restrictions or hefty fees, after a United States district judge ruled that Apple violated an injunction in its antitrust legal battle against Epic Games.
“The Court finds Apple in willful violation of this Court’s 2021 Injunction, which was issued to restrain and prohibit Apple’s anticompetitive conduct and anticompetitive pricing. Apple’s continued attempts to interfere with competition will not be tolerated,” US district judge Yvonne Gonzalez Rogers said in an April 30 court filing.
Apple must make changes “effective immediately”
“Effective immediately, Apple will no longer impede developers’ ability to communicate with users, nor will they levy or impose a new commission on off-app purch…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Ciaran Lyons</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[inDrive Receives Licence Revocation Notice In Malaysia; Talks With APAD Ongoing]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=350368</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/350368/indrive-receives-licence-revocation-notice-in-msia/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-03T04:58:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[inDrive has confirmed it is in active discussion with Malaysian regulators after receiving a notice of revocation from the Land Public Transport Agency (APAD). Reports indicate that the agency recently issued a three-month deadline for the e-hailing company to return its Intermediation Business Licence (IBL), citing alleged non-compliance with regulatory requirements introduced in 2019. In […]
The post inDrive Receives Licence Revocation Notice In Malaysia; Talks With APAD Ongoing appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Heirul Kamel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BBC Maestro Resurrects Agatha Christie For Online Writing Course]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=350288</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/350288/bbc-maestro-resurrects-agatha-christie-for-online-writing-course/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-03T04:23:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Almost half a century after her death, novelist Agatha Christie is teaching an online course on how to write mysteries. Naturally, this is made possible with the help of AI. The course, titled “Agatha Christie: Writing”, is offered by BBC Maestro and covers 11 video modules, along with 12 writing exercises. According to BBC Maestro, […]
The post BBC Maestro Resurrects Agatha Christie For Online Writing Course appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nurul Kamil</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Japanese Gamers Resort To Renting PS5s  Rather Than Buying]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=350292</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/350292/japanese-gamers-renting-ps5-rather-than-buying/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-03T04:00:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Even without the trade war going on, prices of gaming consoles are higher than they’ve ever been. This is especially true for the two most recent ones, the PS5 Pro and the Nintendo Switch 2. One way that Japanese gamers are dealing with this is by renting consoles rather than buying them. At least for […]
The post Japanese Gamers Resort To Renting PS5s  Rather Than Buying appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ian Chee</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin bros at &#039;the club&#039; may stop US gov’t from buying BTC — Arthur Hayes]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/arthur-hayes-bitmex-us-strategic-reseve-plans-doubts-bitcoin-bros</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/arthur-hayes-bitmex-us-strategic-reseve-plans-doubts-bitcoin-bros?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-03T03:25:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BitMEX co-founder Arthur Hayes says the United States is unlikely to add more Bitcoin to its reserves beyond what it has already seized due to the country’s high debt levels and the stereotype behind “Bitcoin bros.”
“I’m not really into the whole Strategic Reserve situation,” Hayes said in a May 1 interview.
Hayes doubts print money plans for Bitcoin
“The United States is a deficit country; the only way they can do a Strategic Reserve is not sell the Bitcoin they took from people, fine, that’s 200,000 Bitcoin,” he said.
Arthur Hayes spoke to Kyle Chasse on his crypto interview series. Source: Kyle Chasse
Hayes said it’s hard to imagine any “properly elected” politician openly announcing that the government plans to print money to buy Bitcoin (BTC).
“Especially when the popular narrative is…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Ciaran Lyons</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Grand Theft Auto VI Has Been Delayed To 26 May 2026]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=350363</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/350363/grand-theft-auto-vi-has-been-delayed-to-26-may-2026/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-03T02:00:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Rockstar Games has announced that its next major title, Grand Theft Auto VI (GTA VI) has officially been postponed to next year. The game’s new launch date is now 26 May 2026. “Grand Theft Auto VI is now set to release on May 26, 2026. We are very sorry that this is later than you […]
The post Grand Theft Auto VI Has Been Delayed To 26 May 2026 appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John Law</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Technical analysis of TM SGNL, the unofficial Signal app Trump officials used]]></title>
        <id>https://micahflee.com/tm-sgnl-the-obscure-unofficial-signal-app-mike-waltz-uses-to-text-with-trump-officials/</id>
        <link href="https://micahflee.com/tm-sgnl-the-obscure-unofficial-signal-app-mike-waltz-uses-to-text-with-trump-officials/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-02T23:20:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[RSAC 2025: Why the AI agent era means more demand for CISOS]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3006066</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/security/rsac-2025-why-the-ai-agent-era-means-more-demand-for-cisos/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-02T23:02:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[RSAC 2025 made one thing clear: AI agents are entering security workflows, but boards want proof they work.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Louis Columbus</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Stars align for Bitcoin rally to $100K, but futures traders exercise caution — Here’s why]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/stars-align-for-bitcoin-rally-to-100-k-but-futures-traders-exercise-caution-here-s-why</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/stars-align-for-bitcoin-rally-to-100-k-but-futures-traders-exercise-caution-here-s-why?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-02T22:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Key takeaways:

BTC hit $97,900 due to soaring institutional investor demand, but futures pricing shows traders aren't confident in a sustained rally.

Macroeconomic risks and global trade tensions cap bullish sentiment despite $3.6 billion in spot BTC ETF inflows.

BTC options lean bullish, suggesting big players expect upside, but their caution keeps leverage use low.

Bitcoin (BTC) broke out of a tight trading range between $93,000 and $95,600 on May 1, following six days of limited movement. Despite reaching its highest price in ten weeks at $97,930, sentiment remains neutral according to BTC derivatives indicators. This price action has occurred alongside significant net inflows into US spot exchange-traded Bitcoin funds (ETFs).
Some of the disappointment among traders can be attribut…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Marcel Pechman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pro-crypto senator pushes back on Trump&#039;s memecoin dinner — Report]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/senator-cynthia-lummis-critical-trump-memecoin-dinner</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/senator-cynthia-lummis-critical-trump-memecoin-dinner?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-02T22:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Senator Cynthia Lummis and at least one other Republican in Congress are reportedly critical of US President Donald Trump for offering the top holders of his memecoin a dinner and White House tour. 
According to a May 2 CNBC report, Lummis said the idea that the US president was offering exclusive access to himself and the White House for people willing to pay for it “gives [her] pause.” She wasn’t the only member of the Republican Party to be critical of Trump’s memecoin perks, announced on April 23, roughly three months after the then-president-elect launched the TRUMP token.  
“I don’t think it would be appropriate for me to charge people to come into the Capitol and take a tour,” said Republican Senator Lisa Murkowski, according to NBC News.

Despite Lummis’ reported “pause” over the p…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Turner Wright</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin data, macroeconomic charts point to new BTC all-time high ‘in 100 days’ — Analysts]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-data-macroeconomic-charts-point-to-new-btc-all-time-high-in-100-days-analysts</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-data-macroeconomic-charts-point-to-new-btc-all-time-high-in-100-days-analysts?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-02T21:38:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Key Takeaways:

Analyst predicts that a low VIX, specifically below 18, signals a risk-on market, which could potentially boost the Bitcoin price to $135,000 within the next 100 days.

The stablecoin market cap hits $220 billion, driving crypto liquidity and Bitcoin’s bullish price action.

A negative Bitcoin funding rate hints at a possible short-squeeze to $100,000.

Bitcoin network economist Timothy Peterson raised Bitcoin’s (BTC) chances of hitting a new high in 100 days, and he maintains an optimistic outlook in 2025. 
In an analysis shared on X that ties BTC’s price action to the CBOE Volatility Index (VIX) —an indicator that measures 30-day market volatility expectations — the analyst pointed out that the VIX index has dropped from 55 to 25 over the past 50 trading days. A VIX score…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Biraajmaan Tamuly</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Evidence of controversial Planet 9 uncovered in sky surveys taken 23 years apart]]></title>
        <id>https://www.space.com/astronomy/solar-system/evidence-of-controversial-planet-9-uncovered-in-sky-surveys-taken-23-years-apart</id>
        <link href="https://www.space.com/astronomy/solar-system/evidence-of-controversial-planet-9-uncovered-in-sky-surveys-taken-23-years-apart"/>
        <updated>2025-05-02T21:13:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum’s era of crypto dominance is over — LONGITUDE panel]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/ethereum-no-longer-on-track-to-dominate-crypto-nansen-ceo</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/ethereum-no-longer-on-track-to-dominate-crypto-nansen-ceo?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-02T20:39:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum’s relative dominance among layer-1 (L1) blockchain networks has declined, resulting in an “open race” to become the leading Web3 platform, according to Alex Svanevik, CEO of data service Nansen.
“If you’d asked me 3–4 years ago whether Ethereum would dominate crypto, I’d have said yes,” Svanevik said during a panel discussion at the LONGITUDE by Cointelegraph event. “But now, it’s clear that’s not what’s happening.”
Ethereum is still the most popular L1 network. According to data from DefiLlama, its roughly $52 billion in total value locked (TVL) represents 51% of cryptocurrency residing on blockchain networks.
However, Ethereum’s dominance has diminished sharply since 2021, when the L1 controlled as much as 96% of aggregate TVL, the data shows. 
Panelists at the LONGITUDE by Coin…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Alex O’Donnell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Most shops in Cannes to accept crypto by summer this year — Web3 exec]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/most-shops-cannes-accept-crypto-summer-2025</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/most-shops-cannes-accept-crypto-summer-2025?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-02T20:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Merchants in Cannes, France, the site of the international Cannes Film Festival, are set to begin accepting crypto payments by summer this year in an effort to attract clientele with high disposable income by modernizing the city's commercial payment ecosystem.
According to Artem Shaginyan, founder and head of strategy of Web3 payment company Lunu Pay, the Cannes municipal government is aiming for a 90% adoption rate among local merchants. The executive also told Cointelegraph:
"This is a big signal. When a city like Cannes, known globally for culture and commerce, starts integrating crypto at scale, it shows that Web3 payments aren’t just a niche thing anymore. It’s about proving that crypto can work in everyday settings, not just online or in theory."
In February, Cannes Mayor David Lisn…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Vince Quill</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[IRS' Crypto Leads Are Leaving the Agency After Accepting DOGE Deals]]></title>
        <id>66182685-6c87-4550-97ed-788ff310982a</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2025/05/02/irs-crypto-leads-are-leaving-the-agency-after-accepting-doge-deals"/>
        <updated>2025-05-02T20:10:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The pair took voluntary resignation offers and left their positions after only a little more than a year of government service, according to two people.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nikhilesh De</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[API Documentation: The Importance of Clear and Concise API Documentation]]></title>
        <id>68151f0be5850fcb8543375a</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-write-good-api-docs/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-02T19:37:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Imagine purchasing a standing fan straight out of the box, all parts dismantled, and you have no manual or guide to put them together. Did you imagine that just now? Cool. Here is another scenario: imagine purchasing an LG product, such as a smart TV...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Okoro Emmanuel Nzube</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OpenAI overrode concerns of expert testers to release sycophantic GPT-4o]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3006276</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/openai-overrode-concerns-of-expert-testers-to-release-sycophantic-gpt-4o/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-02T17:57:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Once again, it shows the importance of incorporating more domains beyond the traditional math and computer science into AI development.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carl Franzen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use SonarQube to Improve Your Code Quality]]></title>
        <id>6815023dec2e34790eeb71a8</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-improve-your-code-quality-with-sonarqube/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-02T17:34:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SonarQube is a powerful open-source tool that helps you maintain code quality and security by analyzing your codebase for bugs and vulnerabilities. And it can play a major role when integrated into your CI/CD pipeline. In this tutorial, we will cover...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Divya Valsala Saratchandran</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn Kubernetes – Full Handbook for Developers, Startups, and Businesses]]></title>
        <id>68150214fd424d0874293171</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-kubernetes-handbook-devs-startups-businesses/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-02T17:34:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You’ve probably heard the word Kubernetes floating around, or it’s cooler nickname k8s (pronounced “kates“). Maybe in a job post, a tech podcast, or from that one DevOps friend who always brings it up like it’s the secret sauce to everything 😅. It s...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Prince Onukwili</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The SEC Can Learn From the IRS in Making Regulation Simpler for Crypto]]></title>
        <id>78bdc336-22b5-4c24-908f-f66947f9e820</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/opinion/2025/05/02/the-sec-can-learn-from-the-irs-in-making-regulation-simpler-for-crypto"/>
        <updated>2025-05-02T17:17:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The IRS has relied on voluntary disclosure programs to bring taxpayers into compliance rather than imposing punitive actions upfront. A similar model should be applied to crypto regulation as well, says Miles Fuller, Director of Government Solutions, TaxBit.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Miles Fuller</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CoinDesk Recap: Movement’s Very Bad Week]]></title>
        <id>01956a2f-bd75-40e4-9784-ab38707d3d2c</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/news-analysis/2025/05/02/coindesk-recap-movements-very-bad-week"/>
        <updated>2025-05-02T17:06:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Plus: Mastercard, World, Strategy, Kraken, and Trump]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Benjamin Schiller</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Roblox breaks ground on data center in Brazil for early 2026]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3006251</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/games/roblox-breaks-ground-on-data-center-in-brazil-for-early-2026/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-02T16:55:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At Gamescom Latam, Roblox announced it has broken ground on a new data center in Brazil -- slated to go live in early 2026.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dean Takahashi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Franklin Templeton Backs Bitcoin DeFi Push, Citing ‘New Utility’ for Investors]]></title>
        <id>a8a2a3e7-0dc5-43bd-ac1b-139bb8b38afb</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2025/05/02/bitcoin-defi-shows-infrastructure-progress-versus-store-of-value-franklin-templeton-s-kevin-farrelly"/>
        <updated>2025-05-02T16:35:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA["I don’t think focusing on Bitcoin DeFi will dilute or complicate Bitcoin’s core narrative." Farrelly said.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Omkar Godbole</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[From Art School Drop-out to Microsoft Engineer with Shashi Lo [Podcast #170]]]></title>
        <id>6814f2ab33857abe499038b0</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/from-art-school-drop-out-to-microsoft-engineer-with-shashi-lo-podcast-170/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-02T16:28:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On this week's episode of the podcast, I interview Shashi Lo. He's a software engineer at Microsoft. He grew up the child of refugees. He wanted to start earning money and build his family so he abandoned his art school degree and taught himself how ...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Quincy Larson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cambodian Huione Group Received $98B in Crypto Leading to U.S. Crackdown: Elliptic]]></title>
        <id>02505ce6-423f-4a8e-a0bf-663db3a1c932</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2025/05/02/cambodian-huione-group-received-usd98b-in-crypto-leading-to-u-s-crackdown-elliptic"/>
        <updated>2025-05-02T15:50:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The group rolled out its own stablecoin in January to avoid traditional currency restrictions.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Oliver Knight</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kevin O’Leary: ‘Crypto Will Be the 12th Sector of the Economy’]]></title>
        <id>bccd1491-f322-4da3-bbbb-d9ede5c9a6ac</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/consensus-toronto-2025-coverage/2025/05/02/kevin-oleary-crypto-will-be-the-12th-sector-of-the-economy"/>
        <updated>2025-05-02T15:36:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ahead of Consensus 2025, the investor and TV personality shares his crypto portfolio strategy, why he won’t touch bitcoin ETFs, and what could unleash trillions into digital assets.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jennifer Sanasie</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Strategy’s $84B Bitcoin Expansion Plan Backed by Wall Street Analysts]]></title>
        <id>948ec075-9ba8-47be-b191-c8726a971c72</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/02/strategy-s-usd84b-bitcoin-expansion-plan-backed-by-wall-street-analysts"/>
        <updated>2025-05-02T14:34:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sell-side bulls from Benchmark and TD Cowen viewed Michael Saylor and team's plan as a bold yet realistic escalation of its bitcoin-focused strategy amid rising institutional interest.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Helene Braun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CoinDesk 20 Performance Update: SUI Drops 5.9% as Index Trades Lower]]></title>
        <id>80df5460-4087-47aa-8242-c866619082ba</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/coindesk-indices/2025/05/02/coindesk-20-performance-update-sui-drops-5-9-as-index-trades-lower"/>
        <updated>2025-05-02T13:10:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Avalanche (AVAX) was also among the underperformers, falling 2.4% from Thursday.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CoinDesk Indices</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tether’s U.S.-Focused Stablecoin Could Launch Later This Year, CEO Paolo Ardoino Says]]></title>
        <id>139fe562-bf9d-4889-9dc5-68ce9698a2ed</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2025/05/02/tether-s-u-s-focussed-stablecoin-may-launch-later-this-year-ceo-ardoino-says"/>
        <updated>2025-05-02T12:46:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The company's U.S. plans depend on the final stablecoin legislation, and is aiming to create a "payment product" that institutions can use, Paolo Ardoino said in a CNBC interview.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Krisztian Sandor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[U.S. Added Stronger Than Expected 177K Jobs in April]]></title>
        <id>b0accd14-95e9-4d1e-89c6-dc819628417f</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/02/us-added-stronger-than-expected-177k-jobs-in-april"/>
        <updated>2025-05-02T12:35:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The price of bitcoin was modestly lower at $96,700 in the moments following the news.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephen Alpher</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Download: foreign disinformation intel, and gene-edited pork]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1116079</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/05/02/1116079/the-download-foreign-disinformation-intel-and-gene-edited-pork/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-02T12:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is today’s edition of The Download, our weekday newsletter that provides a daily dose of what’s going on in the world of technology. A senior State Department official demanded records of communications with journalists, European officials, and Trump critics A previously unreported document distributed by senior US State Department official Darren Beattie reveals a sweeping effort…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rhiannon Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Traders Brace for ‘Sell in May and Go Away’ as Seasonality Favors Bears]]></title>
        <id>7b93f9f5-ff5f-4582-a4e6-710a7cae724d</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/02/bitcoin-traders-brace-for-sell-in-may-and-go-away-as-seasonality-favours-bears"/>
        <updated>2025-05-02T12:05:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Could a centuries-old seasonal market pattern be a sign of further losses? Bitcoin’s five-year performance leans toward “yes.”]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shaurya Malwa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kraken's Quarterly Revenue Jumps 19% to $472M in Q1, Trading Volume Rises by 29%]]></title>
        <id>fa65ddca-2ac1-4c2c-bcc6-febe23fbd47a</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/02/krakens-quarterly-revenue-jumps-19-to-472m-in-q1-trading-volume-rises-by-29"/>
        <updated>2025-05-02T11:53:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The exchange posted adjusted EBITDA of $187 million, a 1% increase from the previous quarter and a 17% rise year-over-year.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Francisco Rodrigues</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google Adds Blockchain Tech to Wallet to Let Users Prove Age Without Sharing Data]]></title>
        <id>88ddd081-0c2b-4cdb-81d4-745436f70a70</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/02/google-adds-zero-knowledge-proofs-to-wallet-for-age-verification"/>
        <updated>2025-05-02T11:20:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The new cryptographic system lets users prove they’re old enough to use restricted applications without giving more information than required.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shaurya Malwa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Daybook Americas: All Eyes on Jobs, Fed as Bitcoin Prepares for Breakout Rally]]></title>
        <id>a74cd382-8207-47f1-ae66-9502332e8671</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/daybook-us/2025/05/02/crypto-daybook-americas-all-eyes-on-jobs-fed-as-bitcoin-prepares-for-breakout-rally"/>
        <updated>2025-05-02T11:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Your day-ahead look for May 2, 2025]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Francisco Rodrigues</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[UK’s FCA Seeks Public and Industry Views on Crypto Regulation]]></title>
        <id>aa514eb9-f086-4076-bd79-cdf33344f63b</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2025/05/02/uks-fca-seeks-public-and-industry-views-on-crypto-regulation"/>
        <updated>2025-05-02T09:23:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Financial Conduct Authority is seeking views on intermediaries, staking, lending and borrowing, and decentralised finance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Camomile Shumba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Metaplanet Issues $25M Bonds to Buy More Bitcoin]]></title>
        <id>c48f128f-cc7d-4f6f-b547-fd3d2947e370</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/02/metaplanet-issues-25m-bonds-to-buy-more-bitcoin"/>
        <updated>2025-05-02T08:54:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The bonds, redeemable in 2025, will be repaid through capital raised from stock acquisition rights.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Francisco Rodrigues</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The US has approved CRISPR pigs for food]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1116059</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/05/02/1116059/the-us-approves-crispr-pigs-for-food/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-02T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Most pigs in the US are confined to factory farms where they can be afflicted by a nasty respiratory virus that kills piglets. The illness is called porcine reproductive and respiratory syndrome, or PRRS. A few years ago, a British company called Genus set out to design pigs immune to this germ using CRISPR gene…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Antonio Regalado</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dogecoin, XRP ETF Hopes Are Fuelling Bullish Sentiment, Social Data Shows]]></title>
        <id>bc24e3a5-5697-434c-9ae4-fd05f13803d6</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/02/dogecoin-xrp-etf-hopes-are-fuelling-bullish-sentiment-social-data-shows"/>
        <updated>2025-05-02T07:21:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Traders grow more optimistic on approval odds as social buzz rebounds across the two majors.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shaurya Malwa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Speed of VITs and CNNs]]></title>
        <id>https://lucasb.eyer.be/articles/vit_cnn_speed.html</id>
        <link href="https://lucasb.eyer.be/articles/vit_cnn_speed.html"/>
        <updated>2025-05-02T04:53:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hidden costs in AI deployment: Why Claude models may be 20-30% more expensive than GPT in enterprise settings]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3006096</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/hidden-costs-in-ai-deployment-why-claude-models-may-be-20-30-more-expensive-than-gpt-in-enterprise-settings/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-01T20:14:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It is a well-known fact that different model families can use different tokenizers. However, there has been limited analysis on how the process of “tokenization” itself varies across these tokenizers. Do all tokenizers result in the same number of tokens for a given input text? If not, how different are the generated tokens? How significant […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lavanya Gupta</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Senior State Department official sought internal communications with journalists, European officials, and Trump critics]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1115988</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/05/01/1115988/senior-state-department-official-sought-internal-communications-with-journalists-european-officials-and-trump-critics/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-01T17:41:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A previously unreported document distributed by senior US State Department official Darren Beattie reveals a sweeping effort to uncover all communications between the staff of a small government office focused on online disinformation and a lengthy list of public and private figures—many of whom are longtime targets of the political right.  The document, originally shared…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eileen Guo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Django Crash Course for Beginners]]></title>
        <id>6813a8237eaea66216eb6819</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/django-crash-course-for-beginners/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-01T16:58:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Django is a high-level web framework built with Python that encourages rapid development and clean, pragmatic design. Django handles much of the heavy lifting involved in web development, so you can focus more on writing your app and less on reinvent...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Incremental Static Regeneration (ISR) Works in Next.js]]></title>
        <id>68139db5555c3ab781a6e0a1</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-incremental-static-regeneration-isr-works-in-nextjs/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-01T16:13:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When you build a website, you often have two main choices for how pages are created: statically or dynamically. Static pages are created once when you build your project. They’re fast because the server doesn’t have to do any extra work when someone ...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joan Ayebola</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Brief Introduction to React]]></title>
        <id>681397cd1168f254478cd514</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/a-brief-introduction-to-react/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-01T15:48:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This tutorial introduces the basics of using React components in your web apps. React is a JavaScript library used to build user interfaces, especially for single-page applications where parts of the page need to update without a full page reload. It...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mark Mahoney</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Astronomer’s $93M raise underscores a new reality: Orchestration is king in AI infrastructure]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3006195</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/astronomer-93m-raise-underscores-a-new-reality-orchestration-is-king-in-ai-infrastructure/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-01T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Astronomer secures $93 million in Series D funding to solve the AI implementation gap through data orchestration, helping enterprises streamline complex workflows and operationalize AI initiatives at scale.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Nuñez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft launches Phi-4-Reasoning-Plus, a small, powerful, open weights reasoning model!]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3006213</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/microsoft-launches-phi-4-reasoning-plus-a-small-powerful-open-weights-reasoning-model/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-01T12:41:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The release demonstrates that with carefully curated data and training techniques, small models can deliver strong reasoning performance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carl Franzen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Download: China’s energy throwback, and choosing between love and immortality]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1115999</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/05/01/1115999/the-download-chinas-energy-throwback-and-choosing-between-love-and-immortality/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-01T12:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is today’s edition of The Download, our weekday newsletter that provides a daily dose of what’s going on in the world of technology. A long-abandoned US nuclear technology is making a comeback in China China has once again beat everyone else to a clean energy milestone—its new nuclear reactor is reportedly one of the first to…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rhiannon Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Salesforce takes aim at ‘jagged intelligence’ in push for more reliable AI]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3006124</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/salesforce-tackles-jagged-intelligence-problem-with-new-ai-benchmarks-and-models/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-01T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Salesforce unveils groundbreaking AI research tackling "jagged intelligence," introducing new benchmarks, models, and guardrails to make enterprise AI agents more intelligent, trusted, and consistently reliable for business use.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Nuñez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A long-abandoned US nuclear technology is making a comeback in China]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1115957</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/05/01/1115957/old-new-nuclear-technology/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-01T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[China has once again beat everyone else to a clean energy milestone—its new nuclear reactor is reportedly one of the first to use thorium instead of uranium as a fuel and the first of its kind that can be refueled while it’s running. It’s an interesting (if decidedly experimental) development out of a country that’s…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Casey Crownhart</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Thunderscope update: My take: Why open source is better]]></title>
        <id>https://www.crowdsupply.com/eevengers/thunderscope/updates/revving-up-for-production</id>
        <link href="https://www.crowdsupply.com/eevengers/thunderscope/updates/revving-up-for-production"/>
        <updated>2025-05-01T00:16:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[UiPath’s new orchestrator guides AI agents to follow your enterprise’s rules]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3006059</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/uipaths-new-orchestrator-guides-ai-agents-to-follow-your-enterprises-rules/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T21:20:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[UiPath's agent orchestration layer Maestro moves prompts through three layers: the agent, a human and the robotic process automation system.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Emilia David</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The ‘era of experience’ will unleash self-learning AI agents across the web—here’s how to prepare]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3005579</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/the-era-of-experience-will-unleash-self-learning-ai-agents-across-the-web-heres-how-to-prepare/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T20:38:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AI visionaries predict an 'Era of Experience' where AI learns autonomously, and it will have important implications for application design.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ben Dickson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Qwen swings for a double with 2.5-Omni-3B model that runs on consumer PCs, laptops]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3006114</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/qwen-swings-for-a-double-with-2-5-omni-3b-model-that-runs-on-consumer-pcs-laptops/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T20:31:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Qwen2.5-Omni-3B model is licensed for non-commercial use only under Alibaba Cloud’s Qwen Research License Agreement.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carl Franzen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Breaking the ‘intellectual bottleneck’: How AI is computing the previously uncomputable in healthcare]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3005667</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/breaking-the-intellectual-bottleneck-how-ai-is-computing-the-previously-uncomputible-in-healthcare/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T19:03:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How University of Texas Medical Branch is using AI to identify patients at high cardiovascular risk, flag for stroke and catch 'basic stuff.']]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Taryn Plumb</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How IPv4 Works – A Handbook for Developers]]></title>
        <id>68124752fa6fa6a9a91d9994</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-ipv4-works-a-handbook-for-developers/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T15:52:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Internet Protocol version 4 (IPv4) is one of the core protocols of standards-based internetworking methods in the Internet and other packet-switched networks. IPv4 is still the most widely deployed Internet protocol. Google’s IPv6 Statistics show...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Omer Rosenbaum</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Get Your First SaaS Customers]]></title>
        <id>681242328ca367c7e5d58873</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-get-your-first-saas-customers/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T15:30:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Starting a SaaS (Software as a Service) business is exciting. You’ve put in the long hours building something you believe people will love. But now comes the big question: How do you get your first customers? Getting those first few users can feel li...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Udemezue John</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Get the User Model in Django – A Simple Guide With Examples]]></title>
        <id>68123f859249b83d2215937d</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-get-user-model-in-django/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T15:19:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When I’m working with Django, one of the first things I often need to do is work with users – like getting the logged-in user, creating a new one, or extending the default user model to add more information. Now, Django has a built-in User model, but...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Udemezue John</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OpenAI rolls back ChatGPT’s sycophancy and explains what went wrong]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3006053</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/openai-rolls-back-chatgpts-sycophancy-and-explains-what-went-wrong/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T15:14:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Many organizations may also begin shifting toward open-source alternatives that they can host and tune themselves.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carl Franzen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Three Omani innovators selected for ITEX 2025 in Malaysia]]></title>
        <id>57ab645df98f4874d208689be5dc65c4</id>
        <link href="https://www.muscatdaily.com/2025/04/30/three-omani-innovators-selected-fpr-itex-2025-in-malaysia/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T14:55:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Three Omani innovators selected to compete at ITEX 2025 in Malaysia. Projects include innovations in water filtration, dental materials, and remote control technology]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nisha Joshi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[In kids, EEG monitoring of consciousness safely reduces anesthetic use]]></title>
        <id>https://news.mit.edu/2025/kids-eeg-monitoring-consciousness-safely-reduces-anesthetic-use-0429</id>
        <link href="https://news.mit.edu/2025/kids-eeg-monitoring-consciousness-safely-reduces-anesthetic-use-0429"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T13:46:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Structify raises $4.1M seed to turn unstructured web data into enterprise-ready datasets]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3006010</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/structify-raises-4-1m-seed-to-turn-unstructured-web-data-into-enterprise-ready-datasets/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Brooklyn-based Structify emerges from stealth with $4.1 million in seed funding to transform how businesses prepare data for AI, promising to save data scientists from the task that consumes 80% of their time.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Nuñez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Download: stereotypes in AI models, and the new age of coding]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1115952</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/04/30/1115952/the-download-stereotypes-in-ai-models-and-the-new-age-of-coding/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T12:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is today’s edition of The Download, our weekday newsletter that provides a daily dose of what’s going on in the world of technology. This data set helps researchers spot harmful stereotypes in LLMs What’s new? AI models are riddled with culturally specific biases. A new data set, called SHADES, is designed to help developers combat the…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rhiannon Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This data set helps researchers spot harmful stereotypes in LLMs]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1115946</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/04/30/1115946/this-data-set-helps-researchers-spot-harmful-stereotypes-in-llms/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T09:41:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AI models are riddled with culturally specific biases. A new data set, called SHADES, is designed to help developers combat the problem by spotting harmful stereotypes and other kinds of discrimination that emerge in AI chatbot responses across a wide range of languages. Margaret Mitchell, chief ethics scientist at AI startup Hugging Face, led the…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rhiannon Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Retail & E-Commerce Innovation Marketing & Tech Summit: Malaysia 2025]]></title>
        <id>cd2a0d19be53d9723fc0475f09d0da2d</id>
        <link href="https://marketech-apac.com/conference/retail-e-commerce-innovation-marketing-tech-summit-malaysia-2025/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T09:22:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Retail & E-Commerce Innovation Marketing & Tech Summit: Malaysia 2025]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Zyra Kate Capilastique</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Malaysia attracts US$3.7 billion in digital investments, solidifying]]></title>
        <id>b95e1bfb983c9cc102bc4266d362a8c2</id>
        <link href="https://www.digitalnewsasia.com/digital-economy/malaysia-attracts-us37-billion-digital-investments-solidifying-position-aseans-tech"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T02:31:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Malaysia’s digital economy continues to go from strength to strength, emerging as a strategic engine of growth that creates jobs, opens new opportunities, and fosters local innovation for businesses]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>@DigitalNewsAsia</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MDV powers Malaysia's tech innovation with over RM13bil financing]]></title>
        <id>d3f5fdc4ea236d719dc3a9d352d4620c</id>
        <link href="https://www.nst.com.my/business/corporate/2025/04/1209375/mdv-powers-malaysias-tech-innovation-over-rm13bil-financing"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T01:56:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[KUALA LUMPUR: Malaysia Debt Ventures Bhd (MDV) has emerged as a key enabler of the nation’s innovation and digital transformation agenda, with more than RM13 billion channelled into over 1,000 high-impact, technology-driven projects.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bernama</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[No more window switching: Mastercard’s Agent Pay transforms how enterprises use AI search]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3005997</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/no-more-window-switching-mastercards-agent-pay-transforms-how-enterprises-use-ai-search/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T22:24:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mastercard is working with AI companies and banks to allow AI platforms and agents to facilitate transactions.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Emilia David</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meta unleashes Llama API running 18x faster than OpenAI: Cerebras partnership delivers 2,600 tokens per second]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3005976</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/meta-unleashes-llama-api-running-18x-faster-than-openai-cerebras-partnership-delivers-2600-tokens-per-second/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T20:02:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Meta partners with Cerebras to launch its new Llama API, offering developers AI inference speeds up to 18 times faster than traditional GPU solutions, challenging OpenAI and Google in the fast-growing AI services market.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Nuñez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meta’s first dedicated AI app is here with Llama 4 — but it’s more consumer than productivity or business oriented]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3005961</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/metas-first-dedicated-ai-app-is-here-with-llama-4-but-its-more-consumer-than-productivity-or-business-oriented/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T18:19:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This mainstream exposure will likely accelerate a shift in what people expect not just from consumer apps, but from workplaces...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carl Franzen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tripp launches Kōkua AI as mental wellness coach across multiple platforms]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3005798</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/games/tripp-launches-kokua-ai-as-mental-wellness-coach-across-multiple-platforms/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T13:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tripp launched Kōkua AI, a mental wellness guide designed to deliver real-time, personalized emotional support across multiple platforms.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dean Takahashi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[xMEMS extends micro cooling fan-on-a-chip tech to AI data centers]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3005879</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/game-development/xmems-extends-micro-cooling-fan-on-a-chip-tech-to-ai-data-centers/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[xMEMS Labs, a pioneer of MEMS-based chips, announced that its innovative µCooling fan-on-a-chip tech will be expanded to AI data centers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dean Takahashi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Download: the AI Hype Index, and “normal” AI]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1115932</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/04/29/1115932/the-download-the-ai-hype-index-and-normal-ai/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T12:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is today’s edition of The Download, our weekday newsletter that provides a daily dose of what’s going on in the world of technology. The AI Hype Index: AI agent cyberattacks, racing robots, and musical models Separating AI reality from hyped-up fiction isn’t always easy. That’s why we’ve created the AI Hype Index—a simple, at-a-glance summary of…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rhiannon Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The AI Hype Index: AI agent cyberattacks, racing robots, and musical models]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1115918</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/04/29/1115918/the-ai-hype-index-ai-agent-cyberattacks-racing-robots-and-musical-models/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Separating AI reality from hyped-up fiction isn’t always easy. That’s why we’ve created the AI Hype Index—a simple, at-a-glance summary of everything you need to know about the state of the industry. AI agents are the AI industry’s hypiest new product—intelligent assistants capable of completing tasks without human supervision. But while they can be theoretically…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Editors</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Web3j Six Month Project Update]]></title>
        <id>68109495670a1300013504c2</id>
        <link href="https://blog.web3labs.com/web3j-six-month-project-update/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T09:10:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[November 2024 - April 2025
This report summarizes the activities and accomplishments of Web3j, an LF Decentralized Trust project, from November 2024 to April 2025. During this period, the project made significant strides in improving the framework’s functionality, enhancing user engagement, and bolstering overall community interaction. 
Key]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>George Tebrean</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[We need to start thinking of AI as “normal”]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1115928</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/04/29/1115928/is-ai-normal/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Right now, despite its ubiquity, AI is seen as anything but a normal technology. There is talk of AI systems that will soon merit the term “superintelligence,” and the former CEO of Google recently suggested we control AI models the way we control uranium and other nuclear weapons materials. Anthropic is dedicating time and money…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>James O'Donnell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Alibaba launches open source Qwen3 model that surpasses OpenAI o1 and DeepSeek R1]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3005880</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/alibaba-launches-open-source-qwen3-model-that-surpasses-openai-o1-and-deepseek-r1/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-28T23:56:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Qwen3’s open-weight release under an accessible license marks an important milestone, lowering barriers for developers and organizations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carl Franzen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ex-OpenAI CEO and power users sound alarm over AI sycophancy and flattery of users]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3005850</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/ex-openai-ceo-and-power-users-sound-alarm-over-ai-sycophancy-and-flattery-of-users/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-28T21:49:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crucially, the turbulence also nudges many organizations to explore open-source models they can host, monitor, and fine-tune themselves.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carl Franzen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Beyond A2A and MCP: How LOKA’s Universal Agent Identity Layer changes the game]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3005824</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/beyond-a2a-and-mcp-how-lokas-universal-agent-identity-layer-changes-the-game/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-28T20:35:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The LOKA protocol, a proposed standard for AI agents from Carnegie Mellon University researchers, will give identities and intentions to agents.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Emilia David</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[30 seconds vs. 3: The d1 reasoning framework that’s slashing AI response times]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3005393</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/30-seconds-vs-3-the-d1-reasoning-framework-thats-slashing-ai-response-times/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-28T19:31:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[d1 framework changes boosts diffusion LLMs with novel reinforcement learning, unlocking efficient, problem-solving AI possibilities.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ben Dickson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Writer releases Palmyra X5, delivers near GPT-4.1 performance at 75% lower cost]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3005734</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/writer-releases-palmyra-x5-delivers-near-gpt-4-performance-at-75-lower-cost/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-28T17:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Writer unveils Palmyra X5: The enterprise AI model that processes 1,500 pages at once, costs 75% less than GPT-4, and enables affordable autonomous agents for businesses seeking automation ROI.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Nuñez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[QuickNode: Building the Infrastructure for the Next Generation of Blockchain]]></title>
        <id>6807d5787fb8500001c39b99</id>
        <link href="https://blog.quicknode.com/quicknode-building-the-infrastructure-for-the-next-generation-of-blockchain/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-28T16:02:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Join QuickNode co-founder Dmitry Shklovsky as he discusses blockchain infrastructure, building decentralized applications, and the future of Web3 development on TheCube's Crypto Trailblazer Series.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>QuickNode</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Does RAG make LLMs less safe?  Bloomberg research reveals hidden dangers]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3005592</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/does-rag-make-llms-less-safe-bloomberg-research-reveals-hidden-dangers/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-28T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[RAG is supposed to make enterprise AI more accurate, but it could potentially also make it less safe according to new research.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sean Michael Kerner</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[UPDATED] Malaysia and Maldives explore new ties in solar, defence, and digital tech [WATCH]]]></title>
        <id>2ff00997f9c35cff9b55bf1c234d9fd9</id>
        <link href="https://www.nst.com.my/news/nation/2025/04/1208426/updated-malaysia-and-maldives-explore-new-ties-solar-defence-and-digital"/>
        <updated>2025-04-28T04:17:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[PUTRAJAYA: Malaysia is eager to explore new avenues of cooperation with the Maldives, including floating solar energy, defence, and digital technology, says Datuk Seri Anwar Ibrahim.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hakim Mahari</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Is your AI product actually working? How to develop the right metric system]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3005642</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/is-your-ai-product-actually-working-how-to-develop-the-right-metric-system/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-27T19:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Metrics are critical for determining AI product performance. But where to begin? Here's a framework to apply across various use cases.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sharanya Rao</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bits + Bytes: A Miscellany Of Technology]]></title>
        <id>92c9e6ae0de9449f2a2cd9808d52c95a</id>
        <link href="https://theedgemalaysia.com/node/752832"/>
        <updated>2025-04-27T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[NEWS

Malaysia sees tech salary surge in 2025, led by system engineers

Tech salaries in Malaysia have risen significantly this year, with system engineers recording the highest increase at 8%, according to NodeFlair’s Tech Salary Report 2...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Edge Malaysia</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FORKLIFTACTION, B2B news service and business platform about forklifts and materials handling]]></title>
        <id>20065c212264065b824a3328d06be4fc</id>
        <link href="https://www.forkliftaction.com/pagenotfound.aspx"/>
        <updated>2025-04-27T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[FORKLIFTACTION, B2B news service and business platform about forklifts and materials handling]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Forkliftaction</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Malaysia remains 9th largest global exporter of high-tech products]]></title>
        <id>ec83e12fc9489689eba3a736f7c0fd4e</id>
        <link href="https://e.vnexpress.net/news/tech/tech-news/malaysia-remains-9th-largest-global-exporter-of-high-tech-products-4878750.html"/>
        <updated>2025-04-26T02:41:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Malaysia successfully maintained its position as the ninth-largest exporter of high-tech goods out of 143 economies in 2023, the highest recognition it has achieved in the past decade, Bernama has reported.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>VnExpress</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Malaysia remains 9th largest global exporter of high-tech products]]></title>
        <id>e1054193ac5220fd5f3cf3fb0ac3fcbd</id>
        <link href="https://en.vietnamplus.vn/malaysia-remains-9th-largest-global-exporter-of-high-tech-products-post318075.vnp"/>
        <updated>2025-04-25T18:11:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Malaysia’s high-tech exports increased by 2 billion USD to reach 127 billion USD in 2023. He said high-tech exports comprised 58.69% of total manufacturing exports in 2023, up from 52.48% recorded in 2022.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Vietnam+ (VietnamPlus)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[UK agrees to assist Malaysia in technology, new energy]]></title>
        <id>9bba1ab03b6cc59e6474a313d3bc9d9c</id>
        <link href="https://theedgemalaysia.com/node/753068"/>
        <updated>2025-04-25T15:31:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The UK has agreed to collaborate with Malaysia in various fields, including technology and new energy management, said Deputy Prime Minister Datuk Seri Fadillah Yusof.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Edge Malaysia</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Need to embrace technological advancements, sustainable practices discussed at country's premier real estate event]]></title>
        <id>13ba8e804fd9567fa951b4f7cc51bead</id>
        <link href="https://theedgemalaysia.com/node/753073"/>
        <updated>2025-04-25T12:00:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Industry leaders, policymakers, investors and experts explored the future of Malaysia's real estate landscape at the National Real Estate Convention (NREC) 2025 held here recently.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Edge Malaysia</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cooperations with China continue to drive Malaysia's tech ambitions: experts]]></title>
        <id>7cf31983f27357e33a7e7403d769042c</id>
        <link href="https://english.news.cn/20250423/23952d602d384abe9a3be2f40797fa2d/c.html"/>
        <updated>2025-04-23T09:33:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cooperations with China continue to drive Malaysia's tech ambitions: experts-]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>english.news.cn</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[IBM Tech Innovation Summit]]></title>
        <id>eb7b875c351e513c2d4750bb29a0ab40</id>
        <link href="https://www.malaysiakini.com/news/741130"/>
        <updated>2025-04-23T02:44:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Seats are limited. Register now!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Malaysiakini Team</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Alabama’s Pursell Agri-Tech teams with Wastech on fertilizer venture in Malaysia]]></title>
        <id>af0a46cec4f3cf8c521e3bd5a58cb6d6</id>
        <link href="https://www.madeinalabama.com/2025/04/alabamas-pursell-agri-tech-teams-with-wastech-on-fertilizer-venture-in-malaysia/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-21T18:21:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Pursell and Wastech Group are establishing a state-of-the-art facility in Malaysia to producte advanced controlled release fertilizers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jerry Underwood</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>