<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2025-05-06T14:14:01.049Z</id>
    <title>AngJianming RSS Feed</title>
    <updated>2025-05-06T14:14:01.049Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Is the AWS Advanced Networking Worth It?]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/skillboosttrainer/is-the-aws-advanced-networking-worth-it-5hdl</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/skillboosttrainer/is-the-aws-advanced-networking-worth-it-5hdl"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T14:06:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the ever-expanding universe of cloud computing, AWS reigns supreme. As the undisputed market leader, its infrastructure services power countless businesses worldwide. This dominance fuels an insatiable demand for skilled professionals who can design, implement, and manage sophisticated network configurations within the AWS ecosystem. If you're looking to carve out a niche as a top-tier cloud networking expert, the AWS Advanced Networking – Specialty (ANS-C01) certification might be your golden ticket.
But is this notoriously tough certification truly worth the effort? Let's break it down.
The AWS Certified Advanced Networking – Specialty is not for the faint of heart. It's an expert-level certification designed for seasoned IT professionals who architect and manage complex network syste…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SkillBoostTrainer</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Korl launches platform orchestrating AI agents from OpenAI, Gemini and Anthropic to hyper-customize customer messaging]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3006451</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/how-openai-gemini-and-anthropic-help-korl-prepare-customer-materials-in-minutes/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Korl's platform works across multiple systems, using multi-agent and multimodal AI to create highly-customized customer messaging.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Taryn Plumb</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is Tailgating?]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/clouddefenseai/what-is-tailgating-1kd2</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/clouddefenseai/what-is-tailgating-1kd2"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T13:59:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the world of corporate security, not all breaches involve sophisticated hacking tools—some simply walk through the front door. Tailgating, a subtle yet dangerous form of intrusion, happens when an unauthorized person gains access to a restricted area by following closely behind someone who is authorized. It's a tactic that relies less on technology and more on exploiting human behavior.
Attackers often masquerade as employees, contractors, or delivery workers. They may carry packages, wear uniforms, or claim to have forgotten their access badge—all to lower suspicion. Once inside, these individuals can do far more than just roam the premises. They might access critical systems, plant malicious software, or steal sensitive equipment.
Pretending to be a colleague and asking someone to hol…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CloudDefense.AI</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BNB Coin Could Hit $2,775 by Year-End 2028, Standard Chartered Says]]></title>
        <id>30f232ba-36b9-44cb-8aa7-5ae1d555a057</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/06/bnb-coin-could-hit-2775-by-year-end-2028-standard-chartered-says"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T13:57:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The token has traded like an unweighted mix of bitcoin and ether since May 2021, the report said.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Will Canny</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use n8n with CometAPI]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/_37bbf0c253c0b3edec531e/how-to-use-n8n-with-cometapi-bcd</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/_37bbf0c253c0b3edec531e/how-to-use-n8n-with-cometapi-bcd"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T13:55:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the era of AI-driven workflow automation, combining n8n’s visual orchestration platform with OpenAI’s cutting-edge language models unlocks unprecedented possibilities. CometAPI—a newly launched AI model aggregation platform—addresses this need by unifying access to over 500 models under a single, consistent API interface. CometAPI promises ultra‑high concurrency, low‑latency responses, and simplified billing through a serverless architecture designed for enterprise‑scale workloads. Concurrently, n8n continues to cement its position as a fair‑code, source‑available workflow automation tool, offering hundreds of prebuilt nodes and a versatile HTTP Request node that empowers users to integrate virtually any RESTful service—including CometAPI—into visual workflows with minimal effort.
Comet…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>安萨</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[schema-env v2.1: Now with Pluggable Validation Adapters (Joi, Yup, Your Own!)]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/devvictrix/schema-env-v21-now-with-pluggable-validation-adapters-joi-yup-your-own-2663</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/devvictrix/schema-env-v21-now-with-pluggable-validation-adapters-joi-yup-your-own-2663"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T13:54:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Pain of Missing Env Vars


We've all been there: deploying a Node.js application only to have it crash immediately (or worse, subtly misbehave) because a crucial environment variable like DATABASE_URL was missing, empty, or malformed. Debugging configuration issues after deployment is frustrating and time-consuming. Manually checking process.env properties everywhere is tedious and error-prone.
What if you could guarantee your application's required environment variables are present and valid before any of your core application logic runs? What if you could get full type safety for your process.env object?
schema-env v2.1


That's exactly why I built schema-env! It's a lightweight Node.js library that loads your standard .env files, merges them with process.env, and validates the resul…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Panupong Jaengaksorn</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How GPT-Image‑1 Works: A Deep Dive]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/_37bbf0c253c0b3edec531e/how-gpt-image-1-works-a-deep-dive-4nf2</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/_37bbf0c253c0b3edec531e/how-gpt-image-1-works-a-deep-dive-4nf2"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T13:52:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[GPT-Image‑1 represents a significant milestone in the evolution of multimodal AI, combining advanced natural language understanding with robust image generation and editing capabilities. Unveiled by OpenAI in late April 2025, it empowers developers and creators to produce, manipulate, and refine visual content through simple text prompts or image inputs. This article dives deep into how GPT-Image‑1 works, exploring its architecture, capabilities, integrations, and the latest developments shaping its adoption and impact.
GPT-Image‑1 is the first dedicated image-centric model in OpenAI’s GPT lineup, released via the OpenAI API as a state‑of‑the‑art image generation system. Unlike specialized models such as DALL·E 2 or DALL·E 3, GPT‑Image‑1 is natively multimodal—it processes both text and im…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>安萨</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Day I Discovered enumerate()]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/bhuvaneshm_dev/the-day-i-discovered-enumerate-523f</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/bhuvaneshm_dev/the-day-i-discovered-enumerate-523f"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T13:49:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It was a regular evening debug session. My code was working, but something about it just felt off. I was looping over a list—like always.
for i in range(len(my_list)):
    value = my_list[i]
    # Do something with value and i

Nothing wrong, right?
Except... I was starting to hate reading my own code.
range(len(...)). Too much manual indexing.
👀 The Realization
for i, value in enumerate(my_list):
    # Do something with i and value

Wait... what?
No range(len(...))? No messy indexing?
✅ Cleaner
🧠 Why it works:
enumerate() is a built-in Python function that returns both the index and the value of items in an iterable—in one shot.
It’s like your loop suddenly gained superpowers.
💡 Bonus Tip:
for i, val in enumerate(my_list, start=1):
    print(f"Item {i}: {val}")

Perfect for user-facing counters. No more +1 hacks.
🚫 Never Again...
No more range(len(...)) unless I really need it.
Now, it’s all enumerate(), all day.
✨ Moral of the Story:
If you're reaching for range(len(...)), stop and ask yourself—
What would enumerate() do? 😎]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>BHUVANESH M</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Access Fields with Spaces in Lumerical FDTD Farfield Data?]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/generatecodedev/how-to-access-fields-with-spaces-in-lumerical-fdtd-farfield-data-4n9k</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/generatecodedev/how-to-access-fields-with-spaces-in-lumerical-fdtd-farfield-data-4n9k"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T13:45:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When working with Lumerical FDTD simulations, access to specific fields from the results of a far-field projection monitor might sometimes be challenging, especially when it comes to field names with spaces. In your case, you're able to access standard fields like E2 and Es easily:
farfield = getresult("monitor", "farfield");
E2 = farfield.E2;
Es = farfield.Es;

However, when it comes to the field "Ep vs angle", an error arises. This can happen due to the space in the field name, making direct access using dot notation invalid.
Understanding the Structure of the Farfield Object
The farfield object typically contains several fields, including E2, Es, and multiple arrays or matrices concerning angles and wavelengths. The fields you can access directly using dot notation are designed to be id…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Generatecode</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[be careful with return values in go]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/csm18/be-careful-with-return-values-in-go-ik4</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/csm18/be-careful-with-return-values-in-go-ik4"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T13:45:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[About


I was writing a program in go, where I was calling a function,which takes an existing slice, modifies it and returns it back.Then I had a print statement that prints that slice.
did not assign the return value of the function call,which is the modified slice,to the old slice variable.In Rust or in some other languages,the compiler will yell at us if we leave the return values of a function call without assigning them.
go compiler will not give an error if we leave return values of a function call.
So, always look for the function signature before calling the function.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>csm</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sharpen Your Strategy: Blending Budget Models with Smart Analysis]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/modelreef/sharpen-your-strategy-blending-budget-models-with-smart-analysis-2eag</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/modelreef/sharpen-your-strategy-blending-budget-models-with-smart-analysis-2eag"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T13:43:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In today's rapidly growing markets, successful business is more than just instinct-it is about accurate strategy and numbers. If you are serious about becoming a smarter businessman in 2025, mastery of financial proportions and using the evaluation model can give you a final lead.
The merging model refers to combining various financial analysis methods, such as Discounted Cash Flow (DCF), comparable company analysis (CCA), and price/income (P/E) to create multidimensional views of evaluation, stock or asset.
For example, while DCF focuses on future cash flows, CCA compares similar companies in the industry. By merging both, you avoid the tunnel point of view and make more balanced, accurate business decisions.
Financial ratio breaks the company's performance into easy-to-manipulate insight…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Model Reef</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[🔧 Fixing “Index Signature” Errors in Inertia's useForm with TypeScript]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/anrecky/fixing-index-signature-errors-in-inertias-useform-with-typescript-3dd9</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/anrecky/fixing-index-signature-errors-in-inertias-useform-with-typescript-3dd9"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T13:41:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When developing a web app with Laravel 12, Inertia.js, React.js, and TypeScript, I ran into a subtle but frustrating TypeScript error when using useForm from Inertia.
I defined my form shape using an interface, like this:
interface DepartmentForm {
  name: string;
  abbr: string;
  degree: 's1' | 's2';
  vision: string | null;
  mission: string | null;
  description: string | null;
  order: number | null;
  photo_url?: string;
}

Then passed it into useForm:
const { data, setData, post, processing, errors, reset } = useForm<DepartmentForm>({
  name: '',
  abbr: '',
  degree: 's1',
  vision: '',
  mission: '',
  description: '',
  order: 0,
  photo_url: '',
});

But TypeScript complained about the index signature not being compatible — something like:
Type 'DepartmentForm' does not satisfy the constraint '{ [key: string]: any; }'

type Instead


Changing the interface to a type fixed it immediately:
type DepartmentForm = {
  name: string;
  abbr: string;
  degree: 's1' | 's2';
  vision: string | null;
  mission: string | null;
  description: string | null;
  order: number | null;
  photo_url?: string;
};

No more type errors!
interface in TypeScript doesn’t allow excess properties unless an index signature is explicitly declared. On the other hand, type is more flexible when passed to generic utilities like Inertia's useForm that expect dynamic key access ([key: string]: any).
I hope this helps someone out there who's scratching their head like I was. If you've encountered similar quirks with Inertia and TypeScript, feel free to share in the comments!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>anRecky</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fire TV App Development 101: Tools, Requirements & First Steps]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/malhotraaa/fire-tv-app-development-101-tools-requirements-first-steps-hgk</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/malhotraaa/fire-tv-app-development-101-tools-requirements-first-steps-hgk"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T13:35:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction


Thinking about launching your own streaming app on Amazon Fire TV? Good news — it’s a lot more accessible than you might think. With the rise of OTT (over-the-top) platforms, businesses, content creators, and broadcasters alike are exploring new ways to deliver content straight to viewers’ living rooms. One of the smartest moves you can make is to create a Fire TV app.
In this beginner-friendly guide, we’ll cover everything you need to know about Fire TV app development, from the essential tools and requirements to the basic first steps you should take to get started.
Before we dive into the how-to, let’s quickly cover the why. Fire TV is one of the most popular streaming platforms globally, with millions of active users. By creating your own Fire TV app, you can:
Reach a wi…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Malhotraaa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[I Collapsed My Folder View Because I Was Scared of the Files]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/arbythecoder/i-collapsed-my-folder-view-because-i-was-scared-of-the-files-4lgg</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/arbythecoder/i-collapsed-my-folder-view-because-i-was-scared-of-the-files-4lgg"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T13:35:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This was literally me two years ago. 
As a new developer, nothing intimidated me more than opening VS Code to see dozens of files scattered across mysterious folders. I'd quickly collapse the file tree, praying I wouldn't need to touch anything outside the one file I was working on.
Sound familiar?
Even senior developers get overwhelmed when joining complex projects. It's not just you - it's part of the journey.
But some principles make your code more navigable:
Group by feature, not file type
Keep related code close together
Be consistent with your naming conventions
For Node.js projects, I recommend:
project/
├── src/
│   ├── routes/
│   ├── controllers/
│   ├── models/
│   └── utils/
├── tests/
├── config/
└── package.json

As your project evolves, let your folder structure evolve too. Don't overengineer from day one.
Add a README explaining your organization choices to help future you (and teammates).
The folder structure that terrified me two years ago is now something I build with confidence. That's why I'm building a community for developers who want to level up their project organization skills.
If you've ever collapsed a folder tree out of fear, you're not alone. What's your biggest folder organization challenge? I'm building a community where we tackle these challenges together.
Originally shared on Twitter and LinkedIn]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arbythecoder</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[21Shares Launches ETP Linked to Crypto.com's Cronos]]></title>
        <id>6a70328c-6e4b-4729-9f1f-477a776cf317</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/06/21shares-launches-etp-linked-to-cryptocoms-cronos"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T13:23:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The product allows investors to add CRO exposure to their portfolios without handling crypto wallets or exchanges.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Francisco Rodrigues</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WWII Aircraft Recognition Posters]]></title>
        <id>https://store.pacificwarmuseum.org/products/wwii-aircraft-recognition-posters</id>
        <link href="https://store.pacificwarmuseum.org/products/wwii-aircraft-recognition-posters"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T13:22:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CoinDesk 20 Performance Update: Index Drops 2.2% as All Assets Trade Lower]]></title>
        <id>43299b7f-f086-4d0b-a85e-7f768d3e67a4</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/coindesk-indices/2025/05/06/coindesk-20-performance-update-index-drops-2-2-as-all-assets-trade-lower"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T13:16:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sui (SUI) fell 7.7% and Aave (AAVE) declined 7.5%, leading the index lower.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CoinDesk Indices</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Mining Rig Maker Canaan Could Have 5X Upside, Says Wall Street Analyst]]></title>
        <id>e459b496-aeee-4386-a66b-c3bdca554008</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/06/bitcoin-mining-rig-maker-canaan-could-have-5x-upside-says-wall-street-analyst"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T13:08:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Benchmark's Mark Palmer initiated coverage on the firm's roughed-up shares with a buy rating and $3 price target.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Will Canny</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vibe Coding Is Fun–But Vibe Refactoring Pays the Bills]]></title>
        <id>https://dawidmakowski.com/en/2025/04/vibe-coding-is-fun-but-vibe-refactoring-pays-the-bills/</id>
        <link href="https://dawidmakowski.com/en/2025/04/vibe-coding-is-fun-but-vibe-refactoring-pays-the-bills/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T13:08:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ōura adds AI-driven meal and glucose tracking features with Stelo by Dexcom]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3006449</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/games/oura-adds-ai-driven-meal-and-glucose-tracking-features-with-stelo-by-dexcom/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ōura, maker of a health-monitoring smart ring, announced that it will use AI to track and analyze two new metabolic health features: meals and glucose.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dean Takahashi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DogeOS Raises $6.9M to Launch Dogecoin App Layer]]></title>
        <id>3ea4be2f-eb52-4702-b451-8236cfadd034</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/06/dogeos-raises-usd6-9m-to-launch-dogecoin-app-layer"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The funding will enable DogeOS to support a variety of consumer apps, enhancing the Dogecoin ecosystem and its decentralized finance services.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shaurya Malwa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Here’s what happened in crypto today]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/what-happened-in-crypto-today</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/what-happened-in-crypto-today?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T12:47:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today in crypto, Binance founder Changpeng “CZ” Zhao expects Bitcoin to reach between $500,000 and $1 million this market cycle, driven by institutional adoption, growing government accumulation, and a pro-crypto US policy, Florida has withdrawn its two Bitcoin reserve bills from consideration in a blow to Bitcoin hopefuls, and asset manager VanEck has filed for the first US BNB exchange-traded fund.
Binance founder CZ says Bitcoin could hit $500,000–$1 million this cycle
CZ expects Bitcoin’s price to top at $500,000 to $1 million during this market cycle.
During an interview with Rug Radio published on May 5, Zhao said that he expects Bitcoin to reach up to one million dollars during this market cycle. He also highlighted the role of Bitcoin spot exchange-traded funds (ETFs) in this rise,…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Cointelegraph</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Binance founder CZ says Bitcoin could hit $500K–$1M this cycle]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/cz-says-bitcoin-could-hit-500-k-1-m-this-cycle</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/cz-says-bitcoin-could-hit-500-k-1-m-this-cycle?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T12:40:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Binance co-founder Changpeng “CZ” Zhao expects Bitcoin’s price to top at $500,000 to $1 million during this market cycle.
During an interview with Rug Radio published on May 5, Zhao said that he expects Bitcoin to reach up to one million dollars during this market cycle. He also highlighted the role of Bitcoin spot exchange-traded funds (ETFs) in this rise, saying that the increasing institutionalization of Bitcoin is a good thing for the market:
“There’s the ETFs. There’s this institutionalization of Bitcoin [ … ] it’s a positive in terms of price action, obviously. Our bags are up  —  not the alt‑coins as much, but at least Bitcoin is.”
Zhao explained that the ETFs are “bringing the traditional institution money into crypto” and “most of the money in the US is institutional money.” He sa…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Adrian Zmudzinski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Traders Seek Downside Protection Ahead of Fed Chair Powell’s Comments]]></title>
        <id>e9e20408-1ab5-456d-b406-2cc03272ba33</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/06/bitcoin-traders-seek-downside-protection-ahead-of-fed-chair-powell-s-comments"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T12:36:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We have only seen some nuanced demand for protective BTC puts, reflecting limited caution among sophisticated traders, Deribit's CEO told CoinDesk.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Omkar Godbole</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Singapore’s Grab taps Solana DePIN project Natix to ‘reshape mapping’]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/singapore-grab-solana-depin-autonomous-driving-mapping</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/singapore-grab-solana-depin-autonomous-driving-mapping?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T12:32:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Southeast Asia’s superapp Grab has partnered with Natix, a project within Solana’s decentralized physical infrastructure network (DePIN), to cooperate on mapping and autonomous driving technologies.
The joint collaboration aims to combine Natix’s blockchain-based mapping data with Grab’s camera hardware and mapmaking technology featuring artificial intelligence support, Natix said in an announcement on May 6.
“This partnership brings together the best of both worlds,” the announcement noted, pointing to Grab’s expertise in crowdsourced mapping and Natix’s unique DePIN model that rewards users for providing decentralized data input.
Source: Natix
“By combining GrabMaps’ AI-powered mapping technology with Natix’s decentralized data network, we’re enabling real-time, high-fidelity map updates…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Helen Partz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin risks sub-$92K retest as BTC price fails to match 4% gold gains]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-faces-91-6-k-retest-btc-price-fails-match-gold-gains</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-faces-91-6-k-retest-btc-price-fails-match-gold-gains?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T12:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Key points:

Bitcoin is struggling again as gold retakes the limelight with week-to-date gains of nearly 5%.

Bitcoin’s correlation with gold is under scrutiny amid ongoing macroeconomic shifts.

Traders see a short-term slump amid a wider BTC price rebound.

Bitcoin (BTC) eyed fresh month-to-date lows into the May 6 Wall Street open as “directionless” crypto markets contrasted with a gold rebound.
BTC/USD 1-hour chart. Source: Cointelegraph/TradingView
Analysis: Bitcoin, crypto “largely directionless”
Data from Cointelegraph Markets Pro and TradingView showed BTC price momentum stalling at $95,000 before the latest daily close. 
Inching closer to the key yearly open support level at $93,500, BTC/USD appeared caught in limbo while gold returned to outperform.
XAU/USD was up 1.5% on the day…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by William Suberg</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[US stablecoin bill loses democrats amid Trump corruption concerns]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/us-stablecoin-bill-loses-democratic-support-trump-corruption-concerns</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/us-stablecoin-bill-loses-democratic-support-trump-corruption-concerns?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T12:28:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Democratic lawmakers in Washington are backing off support for crypto legislation amid heightened concerns over corruption, including the conduct of the Trump family’s World Liberty Financial (WLFI).
In March, the GENIUS Act, which would regulate stablecoins in the US, passed a critical committee reading with the support of several pro-crypto Democrats. Democratic Senators Ruben Gallego, Mark Warner, Lisa Blunt Rochester, Andy Kim and Angela Alsobrooks voted with Republicans, opposite lead Democrat and prominent crypto critic Senator Elizabeth Warren.
The bill passed the committee only after a number of changes were made, including stricter requirements for stablecoin issuers and provisions for Anti-Money Laundering, countering terrorism financing and risk management procedures. 
Now, it s…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Aaron Wood</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OpenAI reaches agreement to buy Windsurf for around $3B]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2025-05-06/openai-reaches-agreement-to-buy-startup-windsurf-for-3-billion</id>
        <link href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2025-05-06/openai-reaches-agreement-to-buy-startup-windsurf-for-3-billion"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T12:18:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why is XRP price down today?]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/why-is-xrp-price-down-today</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/why-is-xrp-price-down-today?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T12:15:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Key takeaways:

Ripple's end-to-quarterly market report fuels uncertainty, impacting XRP price negatively.

Low open interest in XRP futures signals weak trader confidence.

XRP price technicals weaken with resistance at $2.27 and declining RSI.

XRP (XRP) fell on May 6, down 3% in the last 24 hours to trade at $2.09, due to numerous factors. Its trading volume has increased by 25% over the same period to $2.5 billion, reinforcing the momentum of the bears. 
XRP/USD four-hour chart. Source: Cointelegraph/TradingView
Let’s look at the factors driving the XRP price down today.
Ripple’s discontinues quarterly reports
On May 5, Ripple revealed plans to end its quarterly XRP markets report, which it has released since 2017. The company attributed the decision to the reports falling short of exp…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Nancy Lubale</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Download: a longevity influencer’s new religion, and humanoid robots’ shortcomings]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1116114</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/05/06/1116114/the-download-a-longevity-influencers-new-religion-and-humanoid-robots-shortcomings/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T12:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is today’s edition of The Download, our weekday newsletter that provides a daily dose of what’s going on in the world of technology. Bryan Johnson wants to start a new religion in which “the body is God” Bryan Johnson is on a mission to not die. The 47-year-old multimillionaire has already applied his slogan “Don’t Die”…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rhiannon Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin price forms two BTC futures gaps after Coinbase premium flips negative]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-price-btc-futures-gaps-after-coinbase-premium-turns-negative</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-price-btc-futures-gaps-after-coinbase-premium-turns-negative?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T12:01:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Key takeaways: 

Bitcoin’s Coinbase premium index turned negative for the first time in 15 days, indicating defensive short-term sentiment among US investors.

Bitcoin CME futures gaps between support at $92,000-$92,500 and resistance at $96,400-$97,400 suggest a period of range-bound trading. 

Bitcoin’s Coinbase premium index, which measures the gap between BTC price at Coinbase Pro and Binance exchange, turned negative after a 15-day positive stint, signaling potential bearish sentiment among US investors.
This drop coincides with Bitcoin (BTC) slipping below $94,000, and the premium’s decline suggests reduced buying pressure on Coinbase, which is viewed as a proxy for both institutional and retail demand.
Bitcoin Coinbase premium. Source: CryptoQuant
Cointelegraph reported early signs …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Biraajmaan Tamuly</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blockchains ready for institutions, lawyers hesitate: DoubleZero CEO]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/institutional-infrastructure-crypto-austin-federa-doublezero</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/institutional-infrastructure-crypto-austin-federa-doublezero?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T11:45:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While blockchain infrastructure may be ready for institutional use, many legal teams at big firms remain cautious about fully integrating the technology. 
At the Token2049 event in Dubai, DoubleZero Labs founder and former Solana head of strategy Austin Federa told Cointelegraph that today’s high-performance blockchains like Solana are technically capable of supporting large-scale institutional usage. However, lawyers need to catch up. 
“Most blockchains nowadays, especially things like Solana, are fast enough for institutions to use them,” Federa said. “It’s really more about the institutions and the institution’s lawyers getting comfortable with crypto.”
Federa added that institutional lawyers and compliance teams are still addressing regulatory concerns. The executive said this may slow…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Ezra Reguerra</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Taking the bite out of Lyme disease]]></title>
        <id>https://news.northwestern.edu/stories/2025/04/taking-the-bite-out-of-lyme-disease/</id>
        <link href="https://news.northwestern.edu/stories/2025/04/taking-the-bite-out-of-lyme-disease/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T11:38:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Propositions as Types (2014) [pdf]]]></title>
        <id>https://homepages.inf.ed.ac.uk/wadler/papers/propositions-as-types/propositions-as-types.pdf</id>
        <link href="https://homepages.inf.ed.ac.uk/wadler/papers/propositions-as-types/propositions-as-types.pdf"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T11:36:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Citi and SDX partner to tokenize traditional private markets]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/citi-sdx-tokenize-private-markets</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/citi-sdx-tokenize-private-markets?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T11:35:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Investment bank Citi and Switzerland’s SIX Digital Exchange (SDX) are teaming up to modernize traditional private markets through tokenization.
The initiative, revealed during the Point Zero Forum in Switzerland, will leverage SDX’s blockchain-based Central Securities Depositary (CSD) platform to tokenize, settle and safekeep assets, according to a May 6 announcement.
The platform, expected to go live by the third quarter of 2025, will make late-stage, pre-initial public offering (IPO) equities accessible to institutional and eligible investors globally.
The project offers issuers a compliant and scalable framework to manage liquidity, particularly for early investors and employees, while maintaining cap table control. For investors, it opens access to high-growth, venture-backed companies…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Amin Haqshanas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[realme Teases New GT 7 Smartphones Launching In Malaysia Soon]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=350727</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/350727/realme-gt-7-series-msia-teaser/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T11:24:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[realme has confirmed that the latest additions to its GT 7 series of smartphones will be launching in Malaysia soon. As you may recall, the base model as well as a newer “T” variant has recently been spotted in SIRIM, indicating their imminent arrival. Meanwhile, the series’ Pro variant had already made its debut locally […]
The post realme Teases New GT 7 Smartphones Launching In Malaysia Soon appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Heirul Kamel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Memory-safe sudo to become the default in Ubuntu]]></title>
        <id>https://trifectatech.org/blog/memory-safe-sudo-to-become-the-default-in-ubuntu/</id>
        <link href="https://trifectatech.org/blog/memory-safe-sudo-to-become-the-default-in-ubuntu/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T11:22:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Research DAO claims paralyzed rats recover after spinal cord fix]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/hydradao-spinal-cord-repair-neuropeg-rats</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/hydradao-spinal-cord-repair-neuropeg-rats?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T11:19:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decentralized autonomous organization (DAO) HydraDAO claims that its researchers were able to use a novel technique to repair severed spines in rats.
In a May 5 X post, decentralized science (DeSci) project HydraDAO said that one of its research projects resulted in “rats who had their spines fully transected” being able to walk again. More notably, recovery from surgery reportedly only took five days.
Source: HydraDAO
The post featured a video of partially shaved (presumably due to surgery) rats walking in what appeared to be a laboratory setting. The effort in question is the Dowell spinal fusogens project led by Michael Lebenstein-Gumovski, which raised 380,700 USDC (USDC) from donors. The dedicated HydraDAO page reads:
“The Dowell team submitted a project proposal to HydraDAO. After ca…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Adrian Zmudzinski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How much Bitcoin can Berkshire Hathaway buy?]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/how-much-bitcoin-can-berkshire-hathaway-buy</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/how-much-bitcoin-can-berkshire-hathaway-buy?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T11:15:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Key takeaways:

Berkshire holds $347B in cash, enough to buy ~18% of Bitcoin’s supply.

Greg Abel has not signaled a shift from Warren Buffett’s anti-Bitcoin stance.

Berkshire already has indirect crypto exposure via Nu Holdings, Jefferies.

Warren Buffett announced at Berkshire Hathaway's annual shareholder meeting on May 3 that he will step down as CEO by the end of 2025, with Greg Abel taking over. This transition raises speculation about Berkshire’s financial capacity to purchase Bitcoin (BTC) under the new leadership.
Source: Discover Crypto
Berkshire can easily surpass Strategy’s BTC stash 
Berkshire ended Q4 2024 with a record $347 billion in cash and US Treasury bills, representing about 32% of its $1.1 trillion market capitalization. 
The company could acquire approximately 3.52 …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Yashu Gola</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Daybook Americas: Can Bitcoin's Regulatory Worry be Bullish for DeFi Tokens?]]></title>
        <id>43ae5db8-dc9e-46b3-8da8-84550f823d54</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/daybook-us/2025/05/06/crypto-daybook-americas-bitcoin-threatened-by-regulation-hiccup-weakening-demand"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T11:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Your day-ahead look for May 6, 2025]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Omkar Godbole</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Getting things “done” in large tech companies]]></title>
        <id>https://www.seangoedecke.com/getting-things-done/</id>
        <link href="https://www.seangoedecke.com/getting-things-done/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T11:04:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Design and evaluation of a parrot-to-parrot video-calling system (2023)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.smithsonianmag.com/smart-news/scientists-taught-pet-parrots-to-video-call-each-other-and-the-birds-loved-it-180982041/</id>
        <link href="https://www.smithsonianmag.com/smart-news/scientists-taught-pet-parrots-to-video-call-each-other-and-the-birds-loved-it-180982041/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T11:03:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Leading Deepfake Porn Site Has Been Shut Down, Forever]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=350656</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/350656/a-leading-deepfake-porn-site-has-been-shut-down-forever/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mr. Deepfakes, one of the largest site for nonconsensual deepfake pornography, is shutting down for good. The site recently posted a notice on its site, saying that it has lost the ability to stay open. “A critical service provider has terminated service permanently. Data loss has made it impossible to continue operation. We will not […]
The post A Leading Deepfake Porn Site Has Been Shut Down, Forever appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John Law</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Is the Paws Telegram mini app legit? What you need to know]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/explained/is-paws-telegram-mini-app-legit-what-you-need-to-know</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/explained/is-paws-telegram-mini-app-legit-what-you-need-to-know?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T10:50:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What is the Paws Telegram Mini App?            
            
                
Paws is a Telegram-based Mini App created by the same team behind other projects, such as Notcoin and Dogs. 
If you’ve been cruising around Telegram lately, chances are you’ve stumbled upon Paws, the viral crypto Mini App that’s got everyone tapping, clicking and inviting their friends like it’s 2010 FarmVille all over again. 
Originally launched in October 2024 on The Open Network (TON) blockchain, Paws exploded in popularity with its ultra-simple tap-to-earn concept. Think of it as a gamified rewards engine embedded directly in Telegram, where users rack up points by completing tasks, referring others and interacting with mini-game elements. 
Within just eight days of going live, Paws pulled in over 20 million …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Shailey Singh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Citi, Switzerland’s SDX Join Forces to Tokenize $75B Pre-IPO Shares Market]]></title>
        <id>04745cbf-1995-485a-8f3e-8eb0c1e2eb18</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2025/05/06/citi-switzerland-s-sdx-join-forces-to-tokenize-usd75b-pre-ipo-shares-market"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T10:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Citi will act as a custodian and issuer agent for tokenized assets on SDX’s digital Central Securities Depository (CSD) platform.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ian Allison</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Prototype Of DJI’s 360-Degree Camera Leaks Online]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=350718</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/350718/dji-360-degree-camera-prototype-leak/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T10:42:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Leaks featuring an alleged prototype of a 360-degree camera by action cam and drone manufacturer DJI have surfaced online. Thanks to tipsters hakasushi and Igor Bogdanov (aka @Quadro_News), details, images and even a Quick Start Guide of the alleged device were shared on X for all to see. Based on the materials provided, the DJI […]
The post A Prototype Of DJI’s 360-Degree Camera Leaks Online appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Heirul Kamel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto spending will grow, but fiat isn’t going anywhere: Mercuryo CEO]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/crypto-payments-mercuryo-ceo-token2049-interview</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/crypto-payments-mercuryo-ceo-token2049-interview?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T10:27:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Petr Kozyakov, CEO of crypto payments platform Mercuryo, told Cointelegraph that the future of finance may not be a winner-takes-all scenario but a blend of digital assets and fiat, each used where it makes the most sense. 
In a Cointelegraph interview, Kozyakov said that while crypto payments are seeing an increase in adoption and demand, the asset class won’t be fully replacing fiat money anytime soon. He said the two asset classes will coexist, with people choosing the more convenient payment option in different situations. 
“We don’t think crypto will replace fiat,” Kozyakov told Cointelegraph. “They will coexist, and people will turn to crypto when it’s the easier, more practical option, whether that’s for payroll, yield or money transfers.”
Mercuryo Petr Kozyakov at the Token2049 eve…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Ezra Reguerra</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[IntoTheBlock and Trident Merge With $25M Backing to Build Institutional DeFi Gateway]]></title>
        <id>cb2296f1-a439-480a-8f41-100c9a802dd2</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2025/05/05/intotheblock-and-trident-merge-secure-usd25m-backing-to-build-institutional-defi-gateway"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The newly formed Sentora aims to offer a compliant DeFi platform for sophisticated investors looking for yield, liquidity and risk management.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Krisztian Sandor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Solana’s Natix and Grab Team Up to Expand DePIN Mapping Into U.S., Europe]]></title>
        <id>cf7927e0-4c80-4d74-bc4a-e4dc1e9eae61</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/tech/2025/05/06/solanas-natix-and-grab-team-up-to-expand-depin-mapping-into-us-europe"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The collaboration will enhance mapping accuracy by combining Natix’s network with Grab’s mapmaking technology.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Margaux Nijkerk</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Xiaomi Lifts SU7 Ultra EV’s Performance Restriction After Customer Complaints]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=350690</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/350690/xiaomi-lifts-su7-ultra-performance-restriction/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T09:59:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At times, people purchase cars to experience their full performance anywhere and anytime they please. Unfortunately, this wasn’t the case for owners of Xiaomi’s SU7 Ultra owners in China after a recent update had pretty much nerfed its 1,548 HP power output to a mere 900HP. As you’d expect, customers weren’t happy with this decision, […]
The post Xiaomi Lifts SU7 Ultra EV’s Performance Restriction After Customer Complaints appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Keran</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[IRS appoints Trish Turner to head crypto division amid resignations]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/trish-turner-irs-crypto-division-leadership-shiftpto-division-amid-leadership-shakeup</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/trish-turner-irs-crypto-division-leadership-shiftpto-division-amid-leadership-shakeup?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T09:50:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Veteran US Internal Revenue Service (IRS) official Trish Turner was appointed to lead the agency’s digital assets division following the departure of two key crypto-focused executives.
Turner, who has spent over 20 years at the IRS and most recently served as a senior adviser within the Digital Assets Office, will now head the unit, according to a report from Bloomberg Tax citing a person familiar with the situation.
Her promotion marks a significant leadership transition at a time when US crypto tax enforcement is facing both internal and external pressures.
On May 5, Sulolit “Raj” Mukherjee and Seth Wilks, two private-sector experts brought in to lead the IRS’s crypto unit, exited after roughly a year in their roles.
Mukherjee served as compliance and implementation executive director, w…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Amin Haqshanas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Technics AZ100 Lightning Review: The Hard-Hitting Sequel]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=350207</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/350207/technics-az100-lightning-review-the-hard-hitting-sequel/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T09:37:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Technics AZ100 launched earlier this year and serve as the successor to the AZ80 that I reviewed nearly two years ago. Considering how its predecessor wowed from the get-go, I actually started out this review with relatively high expectations. And boy, these earbuds did not fail to impress. What Am I Looking At? Both […]
The post Technics AZ100 Lightning Review: The Hard-Hitting Sequel appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John Law</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Florida Withdraws Strategic Bitcoin Reserve Bills From Consideration]]></title>
        <id>a49d3b1b-092e-49e0-b5d6-0f67e3ea2ddc</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2025/05/06/florida-withdraws-strategic-bitcoin-reserve-bills-from-consideration"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T09:23:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The two bills, which were both filed in February, sought to allow investment of public funds in BTC]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Crawley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OKX exec warns against hype amid real-world asset tokenization boom]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/okx-mena-ceo-rwa-tokenization-boom-token2049-dubai</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/okx-mena-ceo-rwa-tokenization-boom-token2049-dubai?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T09:08:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The CEO of crypto exchange OKX’s Middle East and North Africa (MENA) division has called on the industry to prioritize real-world utility as interest in tokenizing real-world assets (RWAs) continues to grow.
In a Cointelegraph interview at the Token20249 event in Dubai, OKX MENA CEO Rifad Mahasneh warned that while tokenization is promising, projects must “clearly demonstrate” the benefits of tokenizing specific assets. 
“In some cases, we’re tokenizing things that don’t need tokenization, but in some cases, we’re tokenizing things that actually give you real, everyday value, right? And if you can see that everyday value, then that is a promising project,” Mahasneh told Cointelegraph.
He said hype can drive project growth in the Web3 space, but providing everyday value should be the priori…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Ezra Reguerra</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why the humanoid workforce is running late]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1116108</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/05/06/1116108/why-the-humanoid-workforce-is-running-late/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On Thursday I watched Daniela Rus, one of the world’s top experts on AI-powered robots, address a packed room at a Boston robotics expo. Rus spent a portion of her talk busting the notion that giant fleets of humanoids are already making themselves useful in manufacturing and warehouses around the world.  That might come as…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>James O'Donnell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin vs. digital fiat is freedom vs. serfdom]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-is-freedom</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-is-freedom?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Opinion by: Simon Cain, contributor at Bitcoin Policy UK
Most jurisdictions globally are researching, developing or implementing retail central bank digital currencies (CBDCs). If you see these as harmless move-with-the-times digital updates of old-fashioned paper money, look again. CBDCs potentially mean financial serfdom via a monetary panopticon where the authorities closely control every transaction. 
If you think this sounds paranoid, just consider the words of Augustin Carstens, head of the Bank for International Settlements — the central bank for the world’s central banks. Lamenting the authorities’ current inability to control cash transactions, he says that with a CBDC, a “central bank will have absolute control on the rules and regulations that will determine use... also we will …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Simon Cain</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google Gemini Now Allows 10 Image Uploads Per Prompt]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=350671</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/350671/google-gemini-now-allows-10-image-uploads-per-prompt/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T08:48:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Gemini, Google’s AI chatbot, has now received an update allowing users to upload up to ten images per prompt. This will affect Android, iOS, and web users. Previously, the limit for uploaded pictures was one for every prompt. Users who attempted to upload more than one image to Gemini prior to the update would receive […]
The post Google Gemini Now Allows 10 Image Uploads Per Prompt appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Newsdesk</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Turkish İ Problem and Why You Should Care (2012)]]></title>
        <id>https://haacked.com/archive/2012/07/05/turkish-i-problem-and-why-you-should-care.aspx/</id>
        <link href="https://haacked.com/archive/2012/07/05/turkish-i-problem-and-why-you-should-care.aspx/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T08:34:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Join the 2025 Web3j Mentorships: Build the Future of Ethereum on the JVM]]></title>
        <id>6819c8dc41eeeb000183d37b</id>
        <link href="https://blog.web3labs.com/join-the-2025-web3j-mentorships-build-the-future-of-ethereum-on-the-jvm/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T08:32:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Linux Foundation’s Decentralized Trust (LFDT) mentorship program is back in 2025 with two exciting opportunities for developers passionate about Ethereum, Android, and the Java Virtual Machine (JVM). Whether you’re a seasoned blockchain developer or an Android enthusiast eager to dive into Web3, these mentorships offer]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>George Tebrean</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Infinix XPAD GT Gets SIRIM Certification]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=350686</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/350686/infinix-xpad-gt-sirim/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T08:29:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Infinix is reportedly working on its first ever gaming tablet called the XPAD GT. The brand has yet to officially confirm the arrival of the upcoming device, but it has made an appearance on the SIRIM database, indicating that it will be making its way to Malaysia soon after its unveiling. The XPAD GT was […]
The post Infinix XPAD GT Gets SIRIM Certification appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ikmal Rozlan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[US Senate crypto bills stall amid Trump ties and ethics concerns]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/senate-crypto-bills-trump-ethics-concerns</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/senate-crypto-bills-trump-ethics-concerns?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T08:23:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Efforts to pass crypto legislation in the US Senate face mounting resistance amid growing ethical concerns around US President Donald Trump’s ties to crypto.
In a May 5 letter to the Office of Government Ethics, Senators Elizabeth Warren and Jeff Merkley said that Trump and his family stand to personally profit from an investment involving UAE state-backed firm MGX, crypto exchange Binance and World Liberty Financial (WLFI).
The senators called for an urgent probe, warning the deal may violate the US Constitution’s Emoluments Clause and federal bribery statutes.
At the center of the controversy is WLFI’s USD1 stablecoin, reportedly chosen for a $2 billion investment MGX plans to make into Binance.
The senators said the transaction amounts to a potential backdoor for foreign influence and s…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Amin Haqshanas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Figment Eyes Up to $200M Worth of Acquisitions in Crypto M&A Push: Report]]></title>
        <id>1ac2ec85-fc79-42c9-a783-a6c402531418</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/06/figment-eyes-up-to-usd200m-worth-of-acquisitions-in-crypto-m-and-a-push-report"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T08:12:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Figment is targeting regional players on Cosmos and Solana networks at a time in which pro-crypto U.S. policy is fueling dealmaking]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Francisco Rodrigues</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Watch Out Bitcoin Bulls, $99.9K Price May Test Your Mettle]]></title>
        <id>52a0b2cb-f241-4423-aaaf-91ebee39b397</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/06/watch-out-bitcoin-bulls-usd99-9k-price-may-test-your-mettle"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T08:10:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin bulls may run into significant selling pressure at around $99,900, on-chain data show.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Omkar Godbole</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Apple Smart Battery Case May Return For The iPhone 17 Air]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=350676</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/350676/apple-smart-battery-case-may-return-for-iphone-17-air/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T07:33:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Apple is reportedly planning on bringing back its Smart Battery Case for the iPhone 17 Air, according to a report by The Information. The reintroduction of the accessory may be intended to compensate for the phone’s poor battery life, as it is rumoured to have a battery capacity of between 3,000mAh and 4,000mAh. The Smart […]
The post Apple Smart Battery Case May Return For The iPhone 17 Air appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nurul Kamil</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[VIRTUAL Surges 200% in a Month as Smart Money Pours Into Virtuals Protocol]]></title>
        <id>a1ef0699-528d-46b7-a449-3bd6fb270e54</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/06/virtual-surges-200-in-a-month-as-smart-money-pours-into-virtuals-protocol"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T07:11:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[VIRTUAL, the cryptocurrency of the Base-native Virtuals Protocol, has surged 207% in 30 days, outperforming major cryptocurrencies like bitcoin]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Omkar Godbole</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cardano’s ADA, XRP Slide as Bitcoin Traders Await ‘Coin-Flip’ FOMC Meeting]]></title>
        <id>bf90180b-db53-4838-bb7c-6e855839eeb5</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/06/cardanos-ada-xrp-slide-as-bitcoin-traders-await-coin-flip-fomc-meeting"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T07:08:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[DeFi tokens such as Hyperliquid’s HYPE are up 70% in the past week, a sign of traders favoring fundamentals as capital allocators remain cautious with their money.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shaurya Malwa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Developers Plan OP_RETURN Limit Removal in Next Release]]></title>
        <id>907ceee3-69b1-4b15-84e1-62a701cc0c54</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/tech/2025/05/06/bitcoin-developers-plan-op_return-removal-in-next-release"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T06:25:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Core’s decision to lift its long-standing 80-byte OP_RETURN limit has reignited tensions within the network’s developer and node-running communities.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sam Reynolds</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OPPO Pad SE Appears On SIRIM Ahead Of Launch]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=350666</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/350666/oppo-pad-se-sirim/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T06:17:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[OPPO is reportedly preparing to launch a new budget tablet called the Pad SE. While nothing has been officially announced about the upcoming device yet, it has recently made an appearance on the SIRIM database, signalling its imminent launch in Malaysia. The Pad SE was listed with the model numbers OPD2420 and OPD2419 on the […]
The post OPPO Pad SE Appears On SIRIM Ahead Of Launch appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ikmal Rozlan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sneakers (1992) – 4K makeover sourced from the original camera negative]]></title>
        <id>https://www.blu-ray.com/movies/Sneakers-4K-Blu-ray/343185/</id>
        <link href="https://www.blu-ray.com/movies/Sneakers-4K-Blu-ray/343185/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T06:15:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ripple’s RLUSD in Focus as Firm Pledges $25M to U.S. Educational Initiatives]]></title>
        <id>7f1e8b8b-07d0-47be-866f-cf22e343d963</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/06/ripples-rlusd-in-focus-as-firm-pledges-25m-to-us-educational-initiatives"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T06:14:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA["RLUSD is proving their value in real-world applications like donations and large-scale transactions,” an XRP Ledger developer said.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shaurya Malwa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Maybank To Add Transaction Limit, Cooling-Off Period For Reloads]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=350664</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/350664/maybank-to-add-transaction-limit-cooling-off-period-for-reloads/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T06:10:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Last year, Maybank announced the addition of a 12-hour cooling-off period for adjustments to online transfer limits. Soon, the bank will be doing the same for reload services, including mobile prepaid plan reloads and game credits with PIN. This naturally also means that these transactions will also get limits when the change takes effect. Per […]
The post Maybank To Add Transaction Limit, Cooling-Off Period For Reloads appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ian Chee</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Core to unilaterally remove controversial OP-Return limit]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-core-unilaterally-remove-controversial-op-return-limit</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-core-unilaterally-remove-controversial-op-return-limit?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T06:04:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Core developers have decided to remove a limit on transaction data in the next network upgrade, enabling more data to be included in a more efficient way. 
“Bitcoin Core’s next release will, by default, relay and mine transactions whose OP_RETURN outputs exceed 80 bytes and allow any number of these outputs,” read the announcement on GitHub by Bitcoin developer Greg Sanders on May 5. 
The long-standing limit was originally a “gentle signal that block space should be used sparingly for non-payment proof of publication data,” has outlived its utility, he added. 
The proposal (PR 32359) was created by Bitcoin pioneer Peter Todd at the request of Chaincode Labs. 
OP_RETURN is a special type of Bitcoin (BTC) transaction output that allows storing small amounts of data on the blockchain,…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Martin Young</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celsius’ Mashinsky lashes out at ‘death-in-prison sentence’]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/celsius-mashinsky-lashes-govt-death-in-prison-sentence</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/celsius-mashinsky-lashes-govt-death-in-prison-sentence?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T06:01:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Alex Mashinsky, the founder and former CEO of bankrupt crypto lending platform Celsius, has blasted the government's 20-year “venom-laced” sentence request, declaring it a “death-in-prison sentence.”
The US Department of Justice requested Mashinsky receive at least 20 years behind bars in the May 8 sentencing for his role in misleading Celsius users and profiting from the price manipulation of Celsius (CEL), which would make the 59-year-old 79 if he serves the whole sentence.
Lawyers acting for Mashinsky argued in a May 5 reply memorandum filed in a New York district court that he should receive no more than 366 days, because the DOJ hasn't taken into account his status as a nonviolent first-time offender with a previously unblemished 30-year history in business.  
“The government's venom-…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Stephen Katte</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The curse of knowing how, or; fixing everything]]></title>
        <id>https://notashelf.dev/posts/curse-of-knowing</id>
        <link href="https://notashelf.dev/posts/curse-of-knowing"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T06:01:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[eToro aims for $4B valuation, $500M raise for US IPO]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/etoro-us-ipo-4-billion-valuation-500-million-raise</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/etoro-us-ipo-4-billion-valuation-500-million-raise?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T05:51:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Israel-based eToro Group says it’s looking for a valuation of up to $4 billion with its initial public offering in the US, as the stock and crypto trading platform forges ahead with listing on the Nasdaq.
The company and existing stockholders are aiming to raise $500 million through offering a total of 10 million shares priced between $46 to $50 apiece, eToro said on May 5.
A filing with the US Securities and Exchange Commission shows eToro is offering 5 million shares, with a further 5 million being put up by the likes of the company’s co-founder and CEO, Yoni Assia; his brother and executive director, Ronen Assia; along with venture firms Spark Capital, BRM Group and Andalusian Private Capital, among others.
The company offers stock and crypto trading targeting retail and plans to li…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Jesse Coghlan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Suspect in $190M Nomad hack to be extradited to the US: Report]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/suspect-behind-190-million-nomad-bridge-hack-extradited-us</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/suspect-behind-190-million-nomad-bridge-hack-extradited-us?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T05:16:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A Russian-Israeli citizen allegedly involved in the $190 million Nomad bridge hack will soon be extradited to the US after he was reportedly arrested at an Israeli airport while boarding a flight to Russia. 
Alexander Gurevich will be investigated for his alleged involvement in several “computer crimes,” including laundering millions of dollars and transferring stolen property allegedly connected to the Nomad Bridge hack in 2022, The Jerusalem Post reported on May 5.
Gurevich returned to Israel from an overseas trip on April 19 but was ordered to appear before the Jerusalem District Court for an extradition hearing soon after, according to the report. 
On April 29, Gurevich changed his name in Israel’s Population Registry to “Alexander Block” and received a passport under that name at Isra…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Brayden Lindrea</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[An Interactive Debugger for Rust Trait Errors]]></title>
        <id>https://cel.cs.brown.edu/blog/an-interactive-debugger-for-rust-trait-errors/</id>
        <link href="https://cel.cs.brown.edu/blog/an-interactive-debugger-for-rust-trait-errors/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T05:09:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ripple to Expand Its Quarterly XRP Markets Report as Institutional Usage Jumps]]></title>
        <id>c51bf97b-48a4-466f-a941-cf9378bad423</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/06/ripple-to-expand-its-quarterly-xrp-markets-report-as-institutional-usage-jumps"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T04:34:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The quarterly report in its current form will be sunset with newer versions delivering additional insights to reflect institutional usage of XRP.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shaurya Malwa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Florida takes strategic Bitcoin reserve bills off the table]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/florida-takes-strategic-bitcoin-reserve-bills-off-the-table</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/florida-takes-strategic-bitcoin-reserve-bills-off-the-table?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T04:24:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Two Florida crypto bills have been removed from the legislative process in the latest blow to American state-level strategic Bitcoin reserve ambitions. 
Florida’s House Bill 487 and Senate Bill 550 have been “indefinitely postponed and withdrawn from consideration” on May 3, according to the Florida Senate. 
Florida’s legislative session adjourned on May 2 without the passage of these two bills, which would have advanced legislation to establish a crypto reserve for the state. The Senate and House agreed to extend the session until June 6 to address budget plans. 
Lawmakers passed about 230 bills during the session, dealing with things like prohibiting putting fluoride in the water, protecting state parks, and a school smartphone ban, but diversifying state treasury portfolios was not amon…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Martin Young</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[IBM thinks that over a billion new applications will be built with gen AI : Here’s how they’re going to help that happen with agentic AI]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3006455</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/agents-are-key-to-enterprise-ai-success-heres-ibms-plan-on-how-to-make-it-happen/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T04:01:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[IBM details its plans to help enterprises to actually do more with AI, with an expanded set of agentic AI capabilities.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sean Michael Kerner</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[An appeal to Apple from Anukari]]></title>
        <id>https://anukari.com/blog/devlog/an-appeal-to-apple</id>
        <link href="https://anukari.com/blog/devlog/an-appeal-to-apple"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T03:40:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tron says DAO X hack cost victims $45K, Curve Finance also hit]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/tron-dao-curve-finance-latest-victims-x-hacks</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/tron-dao-curve-finance-latest-victims-x-hacks?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T03:14:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A hacker who took over the Tron DAO X account is estimated to have made around $45,000 in improperly solicited funds, according to a spokesperson from Tron. 
Speaking to Cointelegraph, the Tron public relations team confirmed that on May 2, the Tron DAO account posted a contract address and sent direct messages to solicit payments in exchange for promotional advertising on the Tron account.
“Our security team quickly identified the intrusion and cut off access to the hacker, but we ask the community to continue to be vigilant. We will never ask anyone for payments like this via DM or otherwise,” they said. 
The team said that based on the illicit contract address the hacker posted, the amount improperly solicited appeared to be around $45,000. 
Asked whether the same hacker could be respon…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Stephen Katte</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Critical CSS]]></title>
        <id>https://critical-css-extractor.kigo.studio/</id>
        <link href="https://critical-css-extractor.kigo.studio/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T03:13:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fresh $1B in Tether mints on Tron, closing gap again with Ethereum]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/fresh-1-billon-tether-mints-tron-closing-gap-with-ethereum</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/fresh-1-billon-tether-mints-tron-closing-gap-with-ethereum?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T02:57:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Tron network has drawn closer to regaining the lead from Ethereum in Tether circulation after another big mint by the US stablecoin issuer.
On May 5, Tether minted another $1 billion Tether (USDT) on the Tron network, according to Arkham Intelligence. This brings the total USDT on Tron to $71.4 billion, according to the Tether Transparency report. 
In comparison, there is currently $72.8 billion USDT circulating on the Ethereum network, so just $1.4 billion more USDT on Tron will see it become the leading network for the world’s largest stablecoin issuer, as it has been previously over the last two years. 
Tron was ahead of Ethereum for USDT circulation between July 2022 and November 2024, but a large $18 billion mint on Ethereum pushed the network ahead again, according to CryptoQuant…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Martin Young</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New crypto bill draft seen to curb big crypto firm influence]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/new-crypto-market-bill-seeks-democratize-crypto</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/new-crypto-market-bill-seeks-democratize-crypto?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T02:38:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The new “Digital Asset Market Structure Discussion Draft” introduced by House Republicans on May 5 could work to reduce the dominance of large crypto firms and promote more participation in the broader market, according to an executive from Paradigm. 
The discussion draft, led by the House agricultural and financial services committee chairs Glenn Thompson and French Hill, is an “incremental, albeit meaningful, rewrite” of the Financial Innovation and Technology for the 21st Century Act (FIT21), Paradigm’s vice president of regulatory affairs Justin Slaughter said in a May 5 X post.
One-pager of the digital asset market structure discussion draft submitted by House Republicans on May 5. Source: US House Agriculture Committee

One of the major changes from FIT21 is that the draft defines an…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Brayden Lindrea</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Samourai Wallet says feds hid advice that crypto mixer was in the clear]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/samourai-wallet-feds-hid-advice-crypto-mixer-didnt-need-license</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/samourai-wallet-feds-hid-advice-crypto-mixer-didnt-need-license?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T01:17:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Samourai Wallet’s lawyers allege federal prosecutors suppressed advice that the firm didn’t need a license before they charged executives at the crypto mixing service months later. 
In a May 5 letter to a Manhattan federal court, lawyers for Samourai co-founders Keonne Rodriguez and William Hill said prosecutors disclosed that the US Treasury Department’s Financial Crimes Enforcement Network (FinCEN) representatives told them six months before they charged the pair “that under FinCEN’s guidance, the Samourai Wallet app would not qualify as a ‘Money Services Business’ requiring a FinCEN license.”
“Shockingly, six months later, the same prosecutors criminally charged Keonne Rodriguez and William Hill with operating just such a business without a FinCEN license,” the lawyers added.
The letter…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Jesse Coghlan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SEC Further Delays Litecoin ETF, Requests Public Comments]]></title>
        <id>6577f7ab-e8cc-49dc-8b7a-a66145090148</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2025/05/05/sec-further-delays-litecoin-etf-requests-public-comments"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T00:54:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Experts predict Litecoin to have the best chances of approval by the end of this year.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Helene Braun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meta, Cisco put open-source LLMs at the core of next-gen SOC workflows]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3006384</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/rsac-2025-cisco-and-meta-put-open-source-ai-at-the-heart-of-enterprise-threat-defense/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T00:08:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cisco’s Foundation-sec-8B LLM & Meta’s AI Defenders redefine cybersecurity with open-source AI for scalable SOCs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Louis Columbus</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Analyzing Modern Nvidia GPU Cores]]></title>
        <id>https://arxiv.org/abs/2503.20481</id>
        <link href="https://arxiv.org/abs/2503.20481"/>
        <updated>2025-05-05T23:38:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New York district gets interim US Attorney as ex-SafeMoon CEO trial kicks off]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/edny-interim-us-attorney-safemoon-ceo-trial</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/edny-interim-us-attorney-safemoon-ceo-trial?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-05T22:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Acting US Attorney for the Eastern District of New York (EDNY) John Durham has departed as President Donald Trump’s pick takes control of the office.
In a May 5 notice, the US Attorney’s Office for EDNY said Joseph Nocella will serve as interim US Attorney for the region for 120 days or until a Senate-confirmed nominee assumes the role. Nocella’s appointment came as jury selection began in the criminal trial of Braden John Karony, the former CEO of crypto firm SafeMoon.
It’s unclear how the advancement of Nocella, appointed by US President Donald Trump this month, could affect prosecutors’ case against Karony, who faces charges of securities fraud conspiracy, wire fraud conspiracy, and money laundering conspiracy. Nocella said he intended to help prosecute “narcotics-traffickers, gang memb…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Turner Wright</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trump’s Ties Make Crypto’s Democrat Allies Stomp Brakes on Bills]]></title>
        <id>2a36d406-3b39-4ef3-9d72-a659f2c573c5</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/news-analysis/2025/05/05/trumps-ties-make-cryptos-democrat-allies-stomp-brakes-on-bills"/>
        <updated>2025-05-05T21:43:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Senate's stablecoin bill's issues may delay work on the far more important market structure legislation.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nikhilesh De</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OpenAI to stay nonprofit, scrap proposed overhaul]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/open-ai-to-stay-nonprofit-scrap-conversion-plans</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/open-ai-to-stay-nonprofit-scrap-conversion-plans?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-05T21:33:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ChatGPT-maker OpenAI has abandoned plans to become a for-profit company and reaffirmed commitment to its nonprofit status. 
In a May 5 blog post, OpenAI confirmed plans to convert its for-profit business unit into a so-called Public Benefit Corporation (PBC), which would remain under the nonprofit’s control. PBCs are for-profit companies that are legally obligated to prioritize a social mission alongside the interests of shareholders. 
The plans mark a reversal for OpenAI, which had previously floated a for-profit conversion involving spinning out the nonprofit entity. 
“OpenAI was founded as a nonprofit, and is today overseen and controlled by that nonprofit. Going forward, it will continue to be overseen and controlled by that nonprofit,” the ChatGPT-maker said. 
This can be done without…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Alex O’Donnell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Good actors were ‘unfairly targeted’ by SEC — OpenSea&#039;s CEO]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/good-actors-were-unfairly-targeted-by-sec-new-approach-thoughtful-devin-finzer</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/good-actors-were-unfairly-targeted-by-sec-new-approach-thoughtful-devin-finzer?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-05T21:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Securities and Exchange Commission’s (SEC) enforcement approach on crypto firms has left a lasting “regulatory overhang” within the industry, according to Devin Finzer, co-founder and CEO of OpenSea. 
Speaking to Cointelegraph, Finzer said that during Biden's administration the agency unfairly targeted good actors in the crypto space, including OpenSea. “There's all sorts of digital assets, you know, you shouldn't treat them all the same. That's obvious. But I think the approach that the prior SEC was taking was kind of this, you know, very, very generic.”
The SEC issued a Wells notice — a formal notification that is often a precursor to enforcement action — to OpenSea in 2024, alleging that the NFT marketplace was operating as an exchange for unregistered securities. At the time, Finz…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Christopher Tepedino</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trump’s crypto dealings face scrutiny as House Republicans unveil digital asset bill]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/crypto-market-structure-bill-hearing-opposition</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/crypto-market-structure-bill-hearing-opposition?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-05T20:53:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[US President Donald Trump’s crypto businesses are drawing increased scrutiny on Capitol Hill and beginning to influence the progress of US digital asset legislation. As Republican lawmakers in the US House of Representatives unveiled their draft of a digital asset market structure bill on May 5, Democrats prepared for a united response to Donald Trump’s deepening connections with the industry.
Speaking to Cointelegraph on May 5, a Democratic staffer with knowledge of the matter said that House Financial Services Committee Ranking Member Maxine Waters planned to lead some members of her party out of a Republican-led hearing discussing digital assets. 
The May 6 hearing, entitled “American Innovation and the Future of Digital Assets” and led by Committee Chair French Hill, could address draf…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Turner Wright</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dreariness Index (2015)]]></title>
        <id>http://us-climate.blogspot.com/2015/03/dreary-weather.html</id>
        <link href="http://us-climate.blogspot.com/2015/03/dreary-weather.html"/>
        <updated>2025-05-05T20:50:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pixels in Islamic Art: Square Kufic Calligraphy (2020)]]></title>
        <id>https://uwithumlaut.wordpress.com/2020/07/24/pixels-in-islamic-art-square-kufic-calligraphy/</id>
        <link href="https://uwithumlaut.wordpress.com/2020/07/24/pixels-in-islamic-art-square-kufic-calligraphy/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-05T20:42:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Replacing Kubernetes with systemd (2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.yaakov.online/replacing-kubernetes-with-systemd/</id>
        <link href="https://blog.yaakov.online/replacing-kubernetes-with-systemd/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-05T20:40:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Show HN: Real-time AI Voice Chat at ~500ms Latency]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/KoljaB/RealtimeVoiceChat</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/KoljaB/RealtimeVoiceChat"/>
        <updated>2025-05-05T20:17:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SHIB Plunges 7.4% in One Week, but Market Sentiment Remains Cautiously Optimistic]]></title>
        <id>93544ee8-b98c-451f-b96f-8f0f973b7b38</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/05/shib-plunges-7-4-in-one-week-but-market-sentiment-remains-cautiously-optimistic"/>
        <updated>2025-05-05T19:52:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Institutional investors accumulate despite volatility, with 109 new SHIB millionaire wallets emerging in April.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>AI Boost</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Leading House Dem Will Block Crypto Market Structure Bill Hearing]]></title>
        <id>fb70c99e-140a-430e-a9ae-d15e8bd63d9e</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2025/05/05/leading-house-dem-will-block-crypto-market-structure-bill-hearing"/>
        <updated>2025-05-05T19:47:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Rep. Maxine Waters said she is concerned about U.S. President Donald Trump's increasing crypto ties.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nikhilesh De</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Faster sorting with SIMD CUDA intrinsics (2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://winwang.blog/posts/bitonic-sort/</id>
        <link href="https://winwang.blog/posts/bitonic-sort/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-05T19:45:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Texas Made the Old West Even Wilder and Bloodier]]></title>
        <id>https://www.texasmonthly.com/being-texan/gunfighters-old-west-wilder-bloodier/</id>
        <link href="https://www.texasmonthly.com/being-texan/gunfighters-old-west-wilder-bloodier/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-05T19:34:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nvidia launches fully open source transcription AI model Parakeet-TDT-0.6B-V2 on Hugging Face]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3006438</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/nvidia-launches-fully-open-source-transcription-ai-model-parakeet-tdt-0-6b-v2-on-hugging-face/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-05T19:17:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An attractive proposition for commercial enterprises and indie developers looking to build speech recognition and transcription services...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carl Franzen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Improve you C++ skills by coding an audio plugin]]></title>
        <id>68190b8f1abafc5ea9d7efbf</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/improve-you-c-skills-by-coding-an-audio-plugin/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-05T19:03:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Do you want to build a practical project to help improve your C++ skills? Have you ever wanted to create your own unique audio effects? Then diving into C++ audio plugin development with the JUCE framework might be your next great step We just publis...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Likely Still 'Rat Poison' at Berkshire Hathaway Even Without Warren Buffett]]></title>
        <id>da174d70-2292-4663-905f-545c9d0c6f84</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2025/05/05/warren-buffett-steps-down-as-berkshire-ceo-but-don-t-expect-a-bitcoin-pivot"/>
        <updated>2025-05-05T19:02:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Oracle's crypto skepticism runs deep and successor Greg Abel is unlikely to chart a new course.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Helene Braun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Samourai Wallet’s Lawyers Say Prosecution Suppressed Critical Evidence, Call for Dismissal]]></title>
        <id>1733b847-2d61-45e6-9681-0b5c2ef67e3a</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2025/05/05/samourai-wallet-s-lawyers-say-prosecution-suppressed-critical-evidence-call-for-dismissal"/>
        <updated>2025-05-05T18:37:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Before SDNY prosecutors filed charges in the case, FinCEN told them that Samourai Wallet didn’t meet the definition of a money transmitting business.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cheyenne Ligon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Evolving OpenAI's Structure]]></title>
        <id>https://openai.com/index/evolving-our-structure/</id>
        <link href="https://openai.com/index/evolving-our-structure/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-05T18:08:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Visa launches ‘Intelligent Commerce’ platform, letting AI agents swipe your card—safely, it says]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3006416</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/visa-launches-intelligent-commerce-platform-letting-ai-agents-swipe-your-card-safely-it-says/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-05T18:01:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Visa launches Intelligent Commerce platform enabling AI assistants to make secure purchases with your credit card, transforming online shopping with personalized automation and consumer-controlled spending limits.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Nuñez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Reflections on Those MSTR Bitcoin ‘Earnings’]]></title>
        <id>d1b523e6-c207-4713-ba51-996c08a493af</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/opinion/2025/05/05/reflections-on-those-mstr-bitcoin-earnings"/>
        <updated>2025-05-05T17:12:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The 'Strategy Model' is good for BTC. But what about the rest of crypto? CoinDesk Indices’ Andy Baehr has questions.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andy Baehr</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build a Dynamic Wardrobe App with React Drag and Drop]]></title>
        <id>6818d1793c6be4514080aea9</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-build-a-dynamic-wardrobe-app-with-react-drag-and-drop/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-05T14:55:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Have you ever found yourself stuck deciding what color outfit to wear? Maybe you’re mixing and matching different tops and bottoms, unsure if the colors go together. It’s a common dilemma – so common that many of us turn to friends or family for a se...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Timothy Olanrewaju</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bryan Johnson wants to start a new religion in which “the body is God”]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1116090</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/05/05/1116090/bryan-johnson-new-religion-body-is-god/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-05T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bryan Johnson is on a mission to not die. The 47-year-old multimillionaire has already applied his slogan “Don’t Die” to events, merchandise, and a Netflix documentary. Now he’s founding a Don’t Die religion. Johnson, who famously spends millions of dollars on scans, tests, supplements, and a lifestyle routine designed to slow or reverse the aging…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jessica Hamzelou</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The great cognitive migration: How AI is reshaping human purpose, work and meaning]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3006326</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/the-great-cognitive-migration-ai-will-win-at-intelligence-but-only-we-can-make-it-matter/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-04T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Humans need to embrace domains where AI still falters, and where human creativity, ethics and emotion emain indispensable.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gary Grossman, Edelman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why does Switzerland have so many bunkers?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thedial.world/articles/news/issue-27/switzerland-civilian-bunkers</id>
        <link href="https://www.thedial.world/articles/news/issue-27/switzerland-civilian-bunkers"/>
        <updated>2025-05-04T01:05:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Carolina Eyck, renowned superstar of the theremin]]></title>
        <id>https://www.smh.com.au/culture/music/even-this-modern-maestro-won-t-touch-the-world-s-weirdest-instrument-20250417-p5lsms.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.smh.com.au/culture/music/even-this-modern-maestro-won-t-touch-the-world-s-weirdest-instrument-20250417-p5lsms.html"/>
        <updated>2025-05-03T23:35:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Understanding Memory Management, Part 5: Fighting with Rust]]></title>
        <id>https://educatedguesswork.org/posts/memory-management-5/</id>
        <link href="https://educatedguesswork.org/posts/memory-management-5/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-03T21:01:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Not everything needs an LLM: A framework for evaluating when AI makes sense]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3006312</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/not-everything-needs-an-llm-a-framework-for-evaluating-when-ai-makes-sense/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-03T19:35:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The answer to 'What customer needs requires an AI solution?' isn’t always 'Yes.' LLMs are still expensive and not always accurate.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sharanya Rao</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[“An independent journalist” who won't remain nameless]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thehandbasket.co/p/independent-journalism-legacy-media-credit</id>
        <link href="https://www.thehandbasket.co/p/independent-journalism-legacy-media-credit"/>
        <updated>2025-05-03T18:53:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[VMOS – Virtual Android on Android]]></title>
        <id>https://www.vmos.com/</id>
        <link href="https://www.vmos.com/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-03T04:08:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Technical analysis of the Signal clone used by Trump officials]]></title>
        <id>https://micahflee.com/tm-sgnl-the-obscure-unofficial-signal-app-mike-waltz-uses-to-text-with-trump-officials/</id>
        <link href="https://micahflee.com/tm-sgnl-the-obscure-unofficial-signal-app-mike-waltz-uses-to-text-with-trump-officials/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-02T23:20:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[RSAC 2025: Why the AI agent era means more demand for CISOS]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3006066</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/security/rsac-2025-why-the-ai-agent-era-means-more-demand-for-cisos/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-02T23:02:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[RSAC 2025 made one thing clear: AI agents are entering security workflows, but boards want proof they work.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Louis Columbus</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Write Good API Documentation]]></title>
        <id>68151f0be5850fcb8543375a</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-write-good-api-docs/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-02T19:37:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Imagine purchasing a standing fan straight out of the box, all parts dismantled, and you have no manual or guide to put them together. Did you imagine that just now? Cool. Here is another scenario: imagine purchasing an LG product, such as a smart TV...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Okoro Emmanuel Nzube</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OpenAI overrode concerns of expert testers to release sycophantic GPT-4o]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3006276</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/openai-overrode-concerns-of-expert-testers-to-release-sycophantic-gpt-4o/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-02T17:57:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Once again, it shows the importance of incorporating more domains beyond the traditional math and computer science into AI development.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carl Franzen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use SonarQube to Improve Your Code Quality]]></title>
        <id>6815023dec2e34790eeb71a8</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-improve-your-code-quality-with-sonarqube/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-02T17:34:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SonarQube is a powerful open-source tool that helps you maintain code quality and security by analyzing your codebase for bugs and vulnerabilities. And it can play a major role when integrated into your CI/CD pipeline. In this tutorial, we will cover...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Divya Valsala Saratchandran</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn Kubernetes – Full Handbook for Developers, Startups, and Businesses]]></title>
        <id>68150214fd424d0874293171</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-kubernetes-handbook-devs-startups-businesses/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-02T17:34:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You’ve probably heard the word Kubernetes floating around, or it’s cooler nickname k8s (pronounced “kates“). Maybe in a job post, a tech podcast, or from that one DevOps friend who always brings it up like it’s the secret sauce to everything 😅. It s...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Prince Onukwili</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Roblox breaks ground on data center in Brazil for early 2026]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3006251</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/games/roblox-breaks-ground-on-data-center-in-brazil-for-early-2026/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-02T16:55:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At Gamescom Latam, Roblox announced it has broken ground on a new data center in Brazil -- slated to go live in early 2026.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dean Takahashi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[From Art School Drop-out to Microsoft Engineer with Shashi Lo [Podcast #170]]]></title>
        <id>6814f2ab33857abe499038b0</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/from-art-school-drop-out-to-microsoft-engineer-with-shashi-lo-podcast-170/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-02T16:28:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On this week's episode of the podcast, I interview Shashi Lo. He's a software engineer at Microsoft. He grew up the child of refugees. He wanted to start earning money and build his family so he abandoned his art school degree and taught himself how ...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Quincy Larson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sea snail teeth top Kevlar, titanium as strongest material (2015)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cbc.ca/radio/asithappens/as-it-happens-thursday-edition-1.2963357/sea-snail-teeth-top-kevlar-titanium-as-world-s-strongest-material-1.2963549</id>
        <link href="https://www.cbc.ca/radio/asithappens/as-it-happens-thursday-edition-1.2963357/sea-snail-teeth-top-kevlar-titanium-as-world-s-strongest-material-1.2963549"/>
        <updated>2025-05-02T16:16:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[RK3588 – Implementing a Vectorscope for processing video in real time]]></title>
        <id>http://jas-hacks.blogspot.com/2025/05/rk3588-implementing-vectorscope-for.html</id>
        <link href="http://jas-hacks.blogspot.com/2025/05/rk3588-implementing-vectorscope-for.html"/>
        <updated>2025-05-02T16:05:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Download: foreign disinformation intel, and gene-edited pork]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1116079</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/05/02/1116079/the-download-foreign-disinformation-intel-and-gene-edited-pork/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-02T12:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is today’s edition of The Download, our weekday newsletter that provides a daily dose of what’s going on in the world of technology. A senior State Department official demanded records of communications with journalists, European officials, and Trump critics A previously unreported document distributed by senior US State Department official Darren Beattie reveals a sweeping effort…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rhiannon Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The US has approved CRISPR pigs for food]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1116059</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/05/02/1116059/the-us-approves-crispr-pigs-for-food/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-02T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Most pigs in the US are confined to factory farms where they can be afflicted by a nasty respiratory virus that kills piglets. The illness is called porcine reproductive and respiratory syndrome, or PRRS. A few years ago, a British company called Genus set out to design pigs immune to this germ using CRISPR gene…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Antonio Regalado</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hidden costs in AI deployment: Why Claude models may be 20-30% more expensive than GPT in enterprise settings]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3006096</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/hidden-costs-in-ai-deployment-why-claude-models-may-be-20-30-more-expensive-than-gpt-in-enterprise-settings/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-01T20:14:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It is a well-known fact that different model families can use different tokenizers. However, there has been limited analysis on how the process of “tokenization” itself varies across these tokenizers. Do all tokenizers result in the same number of tokens for a given input text? If not, how different are the generated tokens? How significant […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lavanya Gupta</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Senior State Department official sought internal communications with journalists, European officials, and Trump critics]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1115988</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/05/01/1115988/senior-state-department-official-sought-internal-communications-with-journalists-european-officials-and-trump-critics/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-01T17:41:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A previously unreported document distributed by senior US State Department official Darren Beattie reveals a sweeping effort to uncover all communications between the staff of a small government office focused on online disinformation and a lengthy list of public and private figures—many of whom are longtime targets of the political right.  The document, originally shared…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eileen Guo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Django Crash Course for Beginners]]></title>
        <id>6813a8237eaea66216eb6819</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/django-crash-course-for-beginners/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-01T16:58:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Django is a high-level web framework built with Python that encourages rapid development and clean, pragmatic design. Django handles much of the heavy lifting involved in web development, so you can focus more on writing your app and less on reinvent...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Incremental Static Regeneration (ISR) Works in Next.js]]></title>
        <id>68139db5555c3ab781a6e0a1</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-incremental-static-regeneration-isr-works-in-nextjs/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-01T16:13:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When you build a website, you often have two main choices for how pages are created: statically or dynamically. Static pages are created once when you build your project. They’re fast because the server doesn’t have to do any extra work when someone ...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joan Ayebola</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Brief Introduction to React]]></title>
        <id>681397cd1168f254478cd514</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/a-brief-introduction-to-react/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-01T15:48:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This tutorial introduces the basics of using React components in your web apps. React is a JavaScript library used to build user interfaces, especially for single-page applications where parts of the page need to update without a full page reload. It...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mark Mahoney</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Astronomer’s $93M raise underscores a new reality: Orchestration is king in AI infrastructure]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3006195</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/astronomer-93m-raise-underscores-a-new-reality-orchestration-is-king-in-ai-infrastructure/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-01T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Astronomer secures $93 million in Series D funding to solve the AI implementation gap through data orchestration, helping enterprises streamline complex workflows and operationalize AI initiatives at scale.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Nuñez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft launches Phi-4-Reasoning-Plus, a small, powerful, open weights reasoning model!]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3006213</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/microsoft-launches-phi-4-reasoning-plus-a-small-powerful-open-weights-reasoning-model/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-01T12:41:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The release demonstrates that with carefully curated data and training techniques, small models can deliver strong reasoning performance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carl Franzen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Download: China’s energy throwback, and choosing between love and immortality]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1115999</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/05/01/1115999/the-download-chinas-energy-throwback-and-choosing-between-love-and-immortality/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-01T12:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is today’s edition of The Download, our weekday newsletter that provides a daily dose of what’s going on in the world of technology. A long-abandoned US nuclear technology is making a comeback in China China has once again beat everyone else to a clean energy milestone—its new nuclear reactor is reportedly one of the first to…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rhiannon Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Salesforce takes aim at ‘jagged intelligence’ in push for more reliable AI]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3006124</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/salesforce-tackles-jagged-intelligence-problem-with-new-ai-benchmarks-and-models/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-01T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Salesforce unveils groundbreaking AI research tackling "jagged intelligence," introducing new benchmarks, models, and guardrails to make enterprise AI agents more intelligent, trusted, and consistently reliable for business use.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Nuñez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A long-abandoned US nuclear technology is making a comeback in China]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1115957</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/05/01/1115957/old-new-nuclear-technology/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-01T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[China has once again beat everyone else to a clean energy milestone—its new nuclear reactor is reportedly one of the first to use thorium instead of uranium as a fuel and the first of its kind that can be refueled while it’s running. It’s an interesting (if decidedly experimental) development out of a country that’s…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Casey Crownhart</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[UiPath’s new orchestrator guides AI agents to follow your enterprise’s rules]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3006059</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/uipaths-new-orchestrator-guides-ai-agents-to-follow-your-enterprises-rules/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T21:20:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[UiPath's agent orchestration layer Maestro moves prompts through three layers: the agent, a human and the robotic process automation system.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Emilia David</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The ‘era of experience’ will unleash self-learning AI agents across the web—here’s how to prepare]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3005579</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/the-era-of-experience-will-unleash-self-learning-ai-agents-across-the-web-heres-how-to-prepare/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T20:38:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AI visionaries predict an 'Era of Experience' where AI learns autonomously, and it will have important implications for application design.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ben Dickson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Qwen swings for a double with 2.5-Omni-3B model that runs on consumer PCs, laptops]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3006114</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/qwen-swings-for-a-double-with-2-5-omni-3b-model-that-runs-on-consumer-pcs-laptops/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T20:31:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Qwen2.5-Omni-3B model is licensed for non-commercial use only under Alibaba Cloud’s Qwen Research License Agreement.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carl Franzen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Breaking the ‘intellectual bottleneck’: How AI is computing the previously uncomputable in healthcare]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3005667</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/breaking-the-intellectual-bottleneck-how-ai-is-computing-the-previously-uncomputible-in-healthcare/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T19:03:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How University of Texas Medical Branch is using AI to identify patients at high cardiovascular risk, flag for stroke and catch 'basic stuff.']]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Taryn Plumb</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How IPv4 Works – A Handbook for Developers]]></title>
        <id>68124752fa6fa6a9a91d9994</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-ipv4-works-a-handbook-for-developers/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T15:52:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Internet Protocol version 4 (IPv4) is one of the core protocols of standards-based internetworking methods in the Internet and other packet-switched networks. IPv4 is still the most widely deployed Internet protocol. Google’s IPv6 Statistics show...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Omer Rosenbaum</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OpenAI rolls back ChatGPT’s sycophancy and explains what went wrong]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3006053</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/openai-rolls-back-chatgpts-sycophancy-and-explains-what-went-wrong/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T15:14:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Many organizations may also begin shifting toward open-source alternatives that they can host and tune themselves.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carl Franzen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Structify raises $4.1M seed to turn unstructured web data into enterprise-ready datasets]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3006010</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/structify-raises-4-1m-seed-to-turn-unstructured-web-data-into-enterprise-ready-datasets/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Brooklyn-based Structify emerges from stealth with $4.1 million in seed funding to transform how businesses prepare data for AI, promising to save data scientists from the task that consumes 80% of their time.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Nuñez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Download: stereotypes in AI models, and the new age of coding]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1115952</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/04/30/1115952/the-download-stereotypes-in-ai-models-and-the-new-age-of-coding/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T12:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is today’s edition of The Download, our weekday newsletter that provides a daily dose of what’s going on in the world of technology. This data set helps researchers spot harmful stereotypes in LLMs What’s new? AI models are riddled with culturally specific biases. A new data set, called SHADES, is designed to help developers combat the…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rhiannon Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This data set helps researchers spot harmful stereotypes in LLMs]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1115946</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/04/30/1115946/this-data-set-helps-researchers-spot-harmful-stereotypes-in-llms/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T09:41:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AI models are riddled with culturally specific biases. A new data set, called SHADES, is designed to help developers combat the problem by spotting harmful stereotypes and other kinds of discrimination that emerge in AI chatbot responses across a wide range of languages. Margaret Mitchell, chief ethics scientist at AI startup Hugging Face, led the…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rhiannon Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[No more window switching: Mastercard’s Agent Pay transforms how enterprises use AI search]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3005997</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/no-more-window-switching-mastercards-agent-pay-transforms-how-enterprises-use-ai-search/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T22:24:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mastercard is working with AI companies and banks to allow AI platforms and agents to facilitate transactions.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Emilia David</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meta unleashes Llama API running 18x faster than OpenAI: Cerebras partnership delivers 2,600 tokens per second]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3005976</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/meta-unleashes-llama-api-running-18x-faster-than-openai-cerebras-partnership-delivers-2600-tokens-per-second/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T20:02:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Meta partners with Cerebras to launch its new Llama API, offering developers AI inference speeds up to 18 times faster than traditional GPU solutions, challenging OpenAI and Google in the fast-growing AI services market.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Nuñez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meta’s first dedicated AI app is here with Llama 4 — but it’s more consumer than productivity or business oriented]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3005961</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/metas-first-dedicated-ai-app-is-here-with-llama-4-but-its-more-consumer-than-productivity-or-business-oriented/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T18:19:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This mainstream exposure will likely accelerate a shift in what people expect not just from consumer apps, but from workplaces...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carl Franzen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tripp launches Kōkua AI as mental wellness coach across multiple platforms]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3005798</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/games/tripp-launches-kokua-ai-as-mental-wellness-coach-across-multiple-platforms/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T13:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tripp launched Kōkua AI, a mental wellness guide designed to deliver real-time, personalized emotional support across multiple platforms.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dean Takahashi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[xMEMS extends micro cooling fan-on-a-chip tech to AI data centers]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3005879</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/game-development/xmems-extends-micro-cooling-fan-on-a-chip-tech-to-ai-data-centers/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[xMEMS Labs, a pioneer of MEMS-based chips, announced that its innovative µCooling fan-on-a-chip tech will be expanded to AI data centers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dean Takahashi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Web3j Six Month Project Update]]></title>
        <id>68109495670a1300013504c2</id>
        <link href="https://blog.web3labs.com/web3j-six-month-project-update/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T09:10:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[November 2024 - April 2025
This report summarizes the activities and accomplishments of Web3j, an LF Decentralized Trust project, from November 2024 to April 2025. During this period, the project made significant strides in improving the framework’s functionality, enhancing user engagement, and bolstering overall community interaction. 
Key]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>George Tebrean</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Alibaba launches open source Qwen3 model that surpasses OpenAI o1 and DeepSeek R1]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3005880</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/alibaba-launches-open-source-qwen3-model-that-surpasses-openai-o1-and-deepseek-r1/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-28T23:56:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Qwen3’s open-weight release under an accessible license marks an important milestone, lowering barriers for developers and organizations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carl Franzen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[QuickNode: Building the Infrastructure for the Next Generation of Blockchain]]></title>
        <id>6807d5787fb8500001c39b99</id>
        <link href="https://blog.quicknode.com/quicknode-building-the-infrastructure-for-the-next-generation-of-blockchain/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-28T16:02:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Join QuickNode co-founder Dmitry Shklovsky as he discusses blockchain infrastructure, building decentralized applications, and the future of Web3 development on TheCube's Crypto Trailblazer Series.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>QuickNode</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>