<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2025-05-05T13:06:49.224Z</id>
    <title>AngJianming RSS Feed</title>
    <updated>2025-05-05T13:06:49.224Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Convertir un forEach con if a un Stream con filter en Java]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/asjordi/convertir-un-foreach-con-if-a-un-stream-con-filter-en-java-3okl</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/asjordi/convertir-un-foreach-con-if-a-un-stream-con-filter-en-java-3okl"/>
        <updated>2025-05-05T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[En el post anterior vimos cómo convertir un bucle for con incremento distinto de 1, y un bucle for infinito a un estilo completamente funcional utilizando el método iterate() de IntStream. En este post veremos como convertir un bucle foreach de un estilo imperativo a un estilo funcional, además de cómo filtrar elementos de acuerdo a una condición.
En Java 5 se introdujo la sintaxis de foreach, la cual se utiliza para iterar sobre colecciones de elementos. Por ejemplo, para iterar una colección de cadenas que representan nombres, podemos escribir for(String name: names){}. En segundo plano, él foreach se convierte, a nivel de código de bytes, para utilizar un Iterator, mientras que el iterator nos dice que hay un elemento, busca el siguiente elemento para procesarlo. En otras palabras, él f…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jordi Ayala</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[So, Don't Overreact But... I'm So Over React]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/besworks/so-dont-overreact-but-im-so-over-react-i52</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/besworks/so-dont-overreact-but-im-so-over-react-i52"/>
        <updated>2025-05-05T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[More accurately, I’m over everyone treating it like the only answer.





I'm a devout supporter of Web Components and have been preaching the gospel of W3C standards for decades. That guy you always hear muttering "Why use a library when the browser gives you everything you need?"
I have lived through five versions of HTML (2,3,4,XHTML,5) and watched as libraries like jQuery and frameworks like Angular have come and gone from the spotlight. And I'm here now to tell you that you never NEEDED any of them and this has never been more true than it is today.
Custom Elements, Shadow DOM, HTML Templates. These tools provide everything we need to build robust, modern apps without relying on heavy abstractions. But still, in 2025, the web development world clings tightly to libraries like React.
I…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Besworks</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Logging in Spring Boot with SL4J]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/mspilari/logging-in-spring-boot-with-sl4j-12ig</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/mspilari/logging-in-spring-boot-with-sl4j-12ig"/>
        <updated>2025-05-05T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Logging is a fundamental part of software development that provides insights into an application's behavior, making debugging and monitoring easier. A well-structured logging system helps developers understand how an application is running, identify issues, and optimize performance.
Why Are Logs Important?


Logs serve several critical purposes, including:
Debugging & Troubleshooting: Logs help track down issues, especially in production environments where debugging directly is not feasible.
Monitoring & Observability: Logs allow teams to monitor application health and detect anomalies.
Security Auditing: Logs keep records of critical events, such as user authentication attempts and database queries, which are essential for security audits.
Performance Optimization: By analyzing logs, deve…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matheus Bernardes Spilari</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to test the impact of a MongoDB index?]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/loukilaymen/how-to-test-the-impact-of-a-mongodb-index-4mlk</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/loukilaymen/how-to-test-the-impact-of-a-mongodb-index-4mlk"/>
        <updated>2025-05-05T12:59:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Finding the right MongoDB indexes is crucial for performance, but it's not always obvious which ones will give the best results. I created a tool to solve this problem : Benchmark, test, and validate the impact of an index before applying it.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Aymen Loukil</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Strategy, Semler bag 2K Bitcoin as price edged toward $100K last week]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/strategy-semler-buy-2000-bitcoin-price-tested-97000-last-week</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/strategy-semler-buy-2000-bitcoin-price-tested-97000-last-week?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-05T12:51:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Michael Saylor’s Strategy, one of the world’s largest corporate Bitcoin investors, slowed its BTC purchases last week as the cryptocurrency briefly surged above $97,000.
Strategy acquired a new batch of 1,895 Bitcoin (BTC) for $180.3 million during the week from April 28 to May 4 at an average price of $95,167 per BTC, the firm announced in its latest Form-8 filing with the US Securities and Exchange Commission.
Strategy’s latest Bitcoin purchase is one of the smallest made by the company this year, alongside a comparatively meagre 130 BTC purchase in March.
Source: Michael Saylor
The latest buy is 87% less than the previous purchase of 15,355 BTC announced last Monday.
Semler boosts buying despite rising prices
While Saylor’s Strategy cooled its Bitcoin buying spree last week, others upped their appetite for BTC.
Semler Scientific, a publicly traded healthtech firm in the US, bought 167 Bitcoin for $16.2 million in the period from April 30 to May 2 at an average purchase price of $97,093 BTC.
Announced on May 5, the new purchase by Semler was up at least 50% from the previous 111 BTC purchase by the firm announced on April 25.
Bitcoin price chart in the past 30 days. Source: CoinGecko
As of May 2, 2025, Semler held 3,634 BTC, acquired for an aggregate of $322.3 million at an average purchase price of $88,668 per BTC.
Semler’s Bitcoin holdings are considerably smaller than Strategy’s, which held a total of 555,450 BTC as of May 4, acquired for $68,550 per BTC.
This is a developing story, and further information will be added as it becomes available.
Magazine: Crypto wanted to overthrow banks, now it’s becoming them in stablecoin fight]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Helen Partz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Building Voice AI Agents with the OpenAI Agents SDK]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/cloudx/building-voice-ai-agents-with-the-openai-agents-sdk-2aog</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/cloudx/building-voice-ai-agents-with-the-openai-agents-sdk-2aog"/>
        <updated>2025-05-05T12:49:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Beyond Single Turns: OpenAI Enters the Voice Agent Arena


In our previous post, Building Multi-Agent Conversations with WebRTC & LiveKit, we explored how to create complex, multi-stage voice interactions using the real-time power of WebRTC and the orchestration capabilities of the LiveKit Agents framework. We saw how crucial low latency and effective state management are for natural conversations, especially when handing off between different agent roles.
Recently, OpenAI has significantly enhanced its offerings for building agentic systems, including dedicated tools and SDKs for creating voice agents. While the core concept of chaining Speech-to-Text (STT), Large Language Model (LLM), and Text-to-Speech (TTS) remains, OpenAI now provides more integrated primitives and an SDK designed to …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Roman Piacquadio</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Fix Data Fetching Issues in Flutter Web?]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/generatecodedev/how-to-fix-data-fetching-issues-in-flutter-web-2e56</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/generatecodedev/how-to-fix-data-fetching-issues-in-flutter-web-2e56"/>
        <updated>2025-05-05T12:45:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you're new to Flutter web and are encountering issues fetching JSON data, you're not alone. Many developers face similar challenges, especially when transitioning from mobile to web development in Flutter. Your specific issue arises from a problem with HTTP requests to an external API, which may not be returning the data as expected. In this article, we will explore common reasons for this issue and provide a comprehensive guide on how to properly fetch JSON data in Flutter.
Understanding the Problem
When working with Flutter web applications, particularly when fetching data over the internet, it is essential to ensure that your application has the right permissions and configurations. One common issue when developing for the web is CORS (Cross-Origin Resource Sharing). If the API you a…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Generatecode</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Create a scroll progress bar with Tailwind CSS and Javascript]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/mike_andreuzza/create-a-scroll-progress-bar-with-tailwind-css-and-javascript-337f</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/mike_andreuzza/create-a-scroll-progress-bar-with-tailwind-css-and-javascript-337f"/>
        <updated>2025-05-05T12:43:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today we are starting a new series of tutorials, but with a twist. We are leaving Alpinejs behind and instead using vainilla JavaScript to create our components.
Originally posted on: https://lexingtonthemes.com/tutorials/how-to-create-a-scroll-progress-bar-with-tailwind-css-and-javascript/
What is a scroll progress bar?
A scroll progress bar is a bar that shows the progress of the user’s scrolling through a page. It is typically used to indicate the amount of content that has been scrolled and the remaining amount of content to be scrolled. The scroll progress bar can be used to provide feedback to the user about their scrolling experience and to help them understand how much content is left to read.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Andreuzza</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ng-News 25/18: Agentic Angular Apps]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/this-is-angular/ng-news-2518-agentic-angular-apps-1hjn</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/this-is-angular/ng-news-2518-agentic-angular-apps-1hjn"/>
        <updated>2025-05-05T12:40:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mark Thompson and Devin Chasanoff demonstrated agentic Angular apps, where LLMs process user input and trigger UI changes or function calls—marking a deeper integration between Angular and AI. Meanwhile, the Angular team confirmed that Signal Forms won’t make it into Angular 20.





  
  
  Agentic Angular Apps


Mark Thompson and Devin Chasanoff did two live streams focused entirely on live coding.
They demonstrated how to integrate LLMs into an Angular application to build what’s called an agentic Angular app.
Agentic apps are applications that still take user input through the UI — as usual — but then use that input to prompt an LLM directly. The response from the LLM is then used to trigger changes in the UI or even call application functions if the model deems it necessary. This lead…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ng-news</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Go's singleflight package and why it's awesome for concurrent requests]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/nickytonline/gos-singleflight-package-and-why-its-awesome-for-concurrent-requests-4122</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/nickytonline/gos-singleflight-package-and-why-its-awesome-for-concurrent-requests-4122"/>
        <updated>2025-05-05T12:40:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Concurrency in Go is fun… until duplicate work starts hammering your backend.
I’m still pretty new to Go, but thanks to my awesome crew at Pomerium, I’ve been learning fast by jumping into real-world code.
One recent pull request (PR) from my teammate Caleb really made this click. He introduced me to singleflight, a super handy tool for avoiding redundant work in concurrent code.
#5491
    
  
calebdoxsey
         posted on Feb 20, 2025
      
Summary


If a burst of requests come in with the same IdP tokens we would attempt to validate and create sessions for those tokens many times. This PR update the code to wrap session creation in a singleflight so that the token has to be validated once.
Related issues



ENG-2025
Checklist



[x] reference any related issues
[ ] updated unit tests
[…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nick Taylor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Just deployed my first major project: a full-stack quiz app]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/ritish_saini_94e2916cfeab/just-deployed-my-first-major-project-a-full-stack-quiz-app-4n6n</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/ritish_saini_94e2916cfeab/just-deployed-my-first-major-project-a-full-stack-quiz-app-4n6n"/>
        <updated>2025-05-05T12:38:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Live site: https://quiz-app-cp2h.onrender.com
https://github.com/MaXiMo000/Quiz-App
I recently finished and deployed my first full-stack web app. It’s a quiz platform where users can take quizzes, track performance, and manage questions through an admin panel.
The stack includes React, Node.js, MongoDB, and a bit of AI integration for generating questions.
It’s hosted on Render and still a work in progress, but fully functional. Would appreciate any feedback or suggestions.
Thanks for checking it out.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ritish Saini</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[License-Token: Empowering Open Source Creators – A New Era of Licensing Innovations]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/zhangwei42/license-token-empowering-open-source-creators-a-new-era-of-licensing-innovations-215k</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/zhangwei42/license-token-empowering-open-source-creators-a-new-era-of-licensing-innovations-215k"/>
        <updated>2025-05-05T12:36:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Abstract:

In today's fast‐paced technological ecosystem, open source projects drive innovation and collaboration. However, managing licensing, attribution, and monetization continues to present hurdles for projects and developers. License-Token emerges as a transformative solution that leverages blockchain technology to streamline open source licensing while creating automated attribution systems and tokenized revenue models. In this post, we dive into the background, core concepts, real-world applications, challenges, and future outlook of License-Token. We analyze how smart contracts, blockchain transparency, and decentralized community engagement are redefining open source licensing. Key related topics include open source licensing complexity, blockchain-based smart contracts, tokeniza…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Zhang Wei</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Next Fronteiras Interview: Daniel Feitosa on Technical Debt Management]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/adolfont/next-fronteiras-interview-daniel-feitosa-on-technical-debt-management-1el1</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/adolfont/next-fronteiras-interview-daniel-feitosa-on-technical-debt-management-1el1"/>
        <updated>2025-05-05T12:36:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Next week, on May 12th, 2025, we are going to interview Daniel Feitosa, a Brazilian Software Engineering professor at the Faculty of Science and Engineering, University of Groningen.

When I write "we," I mean the Frontiers of Software Engineering podcast, which is in Portuguese. I would love to have something like it in English, but as far as I know, there is no podcast that regularly interviews Software Engineering professors and researchers to discuss their work and publications.
We always ask our interviewees what they would like to talk about, and Daniel chose Technical Debt Management. It's a very important topic in practice for software engineering professionals, isn't it?
We also ask our interviewees to share 2 to 4 publications, and these are the ones Daniel sent us:
C. Zhong, D. Feitosa, P. Avgeriou, H. Huang, Y. Li, H. Zhang. PairSmell: A Novel Perspective Inspecting Software Modular Structure. In Proceedings of the IEEE/ACM 47th International Conference on Software Engineering (ICSE '25), 2025. Distinguished Paper Award. https://arxiv.org/abs/2411.01012

J.P. Biazotto, D. Feitosa, P. Avgeriou, E.Y. Nakagawa. Automating Technical Debt Management: Insights from Practitioner Discussions in Stack Exchange. In Proceedings of the 8th ACM/IEEE International Conference on Technical Debt (TechDebt '25). 
J.P. Biazotto, D. Feitosa, P. Avgeriou, E.Y. Nakagawa. Technical Debt Management Automation: State of the Art and Future Perspectives. Information and Software Technology, 167:107375, 2024. https://doi.org/10.1016/j.infsof.2023.107375

J. Tan, D. Feitosa, P. Avgeriou. The Lifecycle of Technical Debt that Manifests in Both Source Code and Issue Trackers. Information and Software Technology, 159:107216, 2023. https://doi.org/10.1016/j.infsof.2023.107216



If you want to watch or listen to our episodes, check out https://www.youtube.com/@fronteirases.
On YouTube, you can enable automatic translations to view subtitles in English.
Let me know if you'd like a version adapted for social media or a blog format.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Adolfo Neto</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Binance co-founder CZ proposes Bitcoin, BNB for Kyrgyzstan reserves]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/kyrgyzstan-crypto-reserve-bitcoin-bnb-binance-cofounder-cz</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/kyrgyzstan-crypto-reserve-bitcoin-bnb-binance-cofounder-cz?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-05T12:31:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Binance co-founder Changpeng “CZ” Zhao has proposed Bitcoin and BNB as the first digital assets to build Kyrgyzstan’s national crypto reserves.
On May 5, Zhao shared on X that he had advised Kyrgyzstan to start with Bitcoin (BTC) and BNB (BNB) when building its national crypto reserve. In 2024, Forbes claimed that Zhao holds about 94 million BNB tokens, or 64% of BNB’s circulating supply. At the time of writing, these tokens are worth about $55 billion. 
The proposal followed Zhao’s earlier announcement that he had begun advising Kyrgyzstan’s National Investment Agency (NIA) on blockchain and crypto-related matters.  
On April 3, Zhao confirmed he’s been officially and unofficially advising governments on crypto frameworks and blockchain solutions. The former Binance CEO said that he finds…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Ezra Reguerra</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Internet usage pattern during power outage in Spain and Portugal]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.akamai-mpulse.com/blog/2025-05-03-iberian-power-outage/</id>
        <link href="https://blog.akamai-mpulse.com/blog/2025-05-03-iberian-power-outage/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-05T12:29:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cointelegraph and TheBlock announce strategic media partnership to strengthen global Web3 and virtual asset collaboration]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/cointelegraph-theblock-dubai-web3-partnership</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/cointelegraph-theblock-dubai-web3-partnership?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-05T12:22:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dubai, UAE – May 2025 — TheBlock, the International Chamber of Virtual Assets, has announced a strategic partnership with Cointelegraph, the world’s leading Web3 media platform. The collaboration brings together two major players in the blockchain and virtual asset space, with the shared goal of amplifying the global adoption of tokenisation, advancing regulatory dialogue, and supporting builders entering the MENA region.
The agreement, signed during Token2049 Dubai, highlights Cointelegraph’s growing collaboration with key players in the UAE. This new partnership will foster deeper collaboration and mutual support across TheBlock’s ecosystem.
As part of the collaboration, Cointelegraph will set up a presence at TheBlock’s headquarters in Dubai World Trade Center, offering opportunities fo…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Cointelegraph</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Michael Saylor's Strategy Adds 1,895 Bitcoin, Bringing Company Stack to 555,450 BTC]]></title>
        <id>edafe553-1fd4-45a8-b5fa-339ff50674e3</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2025/05/05/michael-saylor-s-strategy-adds-1-895-bitcoin-bringing-company-stack-to-555-450-btc"/>
        <updated>2025-05-05T12:19:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A combination of sales of common stock and STRK preferred stock funded the latest purchase.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephen Alpher</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TQ Wuling To Debut In Malaysia With Affordable EV, The Wuling Bingo]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=350560</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/350560/tq-wuling-msia-debut-bingo-ev/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-05T12:16:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Chinese automaker SAIC-GM-Wuling Automobile (SGMW) is set to launch in Malaysia in the very near future. The company will instead debut as “TQ Wuling” locally and will also introduce a budget, locally-assembled (CKD) EV model to the market within the fourth quarter of 2025. The vehicle in question is the Wuling Bingo, which is assembled […]
The post TQ Wuling To Debut In Malaysia With Affordable EV, The Wuling Bingo appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Keran</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vitalik Buterin Wants to Make Ethereum as Simple as Bitcoin]]></title>
        <id>9951b8be-c4a5-4e94-8518-1408d68aec23</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/05/vitalik-buterin-wants-to-make-ethereum-as-simple-as-bitcoin"/>
        <updated>2025-05-05T12:15:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Buterin put out thoughts for a long-term roadmap that drastically reduces the complexity of Ethereum’s technology.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shaurya Malwa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[XRP price risks 45% decline to $1.20 — Here is why]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/xrp-price-risks-45-decline-to-1-20-here-is-why</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/xrp-price-risks-45-decline-to-1-20-here-is-why?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-05T11:54:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Key takeaways:

XRP forms a bearish descending triangle on the daily chart, risking a 45% drop to $1.20.

Declining daily active addresses signal reduced transaction activity and liquidity.

A breakout above $2.18 could invalidate the bearish pattern.

The XRP (XRP) price flashes warning signs as a bearish technical pattern emerges on its daily chart, coinciding with declining network activity. 
XRP descending triangle hints at 45% price drop
The XRP price chart has been forming a descending triangle pattern on its daily chart since its late 2024 rally, characterized by a flat support level and a downward-sloping resistance line.
A descending triangle chart pattern that forms after a strong uptrend is seen as a bearish reversal indicator. As a rule, the setup resolves when the price breaks…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Nancy Lubale</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto funds raked in $2B last week, pushing 3-week haul to $5.5B]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/crypto-funds-add-2b-in-weekly-inflows-reaching-5-5b-in-three-weeks</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/crypto-funds-add-2b-in-weekly-inflows-reaching-5-5b-in-three-weeks?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-05T11:52:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency investment products attracted $2 billion in new inflows last week, according to the European investment firm CoinShares.
Global crypto exchange-traded products (ETPs) have added $5.5 billion in inflows in the past three weeks, according to the latest weekly report from CoinShares.
With the new inflows, total assets under management (AUM) in all crypto ETPs worldwide jumped 3.3% from $151 billion to $156 billion.
Although the positive trend has continued for the past three weeks, the latest weekly inflows were down 41% from last week’s $3.4 billion of inflows — the third-largest crypto ETP inflows on record.
Inflows slowed down despite new Bitcoin gains
The slowdown in crypto ETP inflows came despite Bitcoin (BTC) seeing some brief gains last week, with the price rising from …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Helen Partz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mattel Launches New “Brick Shop” Brand With Seven Iconic Car Models]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=350528</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/350528/mattel-brick-shop-seven-iconic-car-models/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-05T11:44:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mattel, has recently announced its first-ever brick models under its new Mattel Brick Shop brand. The line-up of these new brick models consists of seven iconic cars that they get to build from scratch via various parts – much like LEGO. It’s worth mentioning that while the brand says that this is done in collaboration […]
The post Mattel Launches New “Brick Shop” Brand With Seven Iconic Car Models appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Keran</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Built a Security Tool. It Introduced a Security Risk]]></title>
        <id>https://www.token.security/blog/aws-built-a-security-tool-it-introduced-a-security-risk</id>
        <link href="https://www.token.security/blog/aws-built-a-security-tool-it-introduced-a-security-risk"/>
        <updated>2025-05-05T11:37:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Effects of repetitive transcranial magnetic stimulation on sleep bruxism]]></title>
        <id>https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC4822180/</id>
        <link href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC4822180/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-05T11:15:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Daybook Americas: Bitcoin Dips, but ETF Inflows, Fed Week Keep Bulls Interested]]></title>
        <id>d9a5fcb0-d052-492c-a450-31c9f54af625</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/daybook-us/2025/05/05/crypto-daybook-americas-bitcoin-dips-but-etf-inflows-fed-week-keep-bulls-interested"/>
        <updated>2025-05-05T11:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Your day-ahead look for May 5, 2025]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Omkar Godbole</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gandi March 9, 2025 incident postmortem]]></title>
        <id>https://news.gandi.net/en/2025/03/gandi-incident-on-march-9-2025/</id>
        <link href="https://news.gandi.net/en/2025/03/gandi-incident-on-march-9-2025/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-05T11:10:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Aptos exec sees Web 2.5 platforms earning ‘tons’ of revenue]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/aptos-ecosystem-web2-5-revenue-adoption-token2049</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/aptos-ecosystem-web2-5-revenue-adoption-token2049?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-05T10:59:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While many crypto ecosystems focus on decentralization as the core tenet of Web3, Aptos is seeing success with hybrid platforms that blend Web2 and Web3 technologies, commonly referred to as “Web2.5.”
In an interview at the Token2049 event in Dubai, Aptos’ head of ecosystem, Ash Pampati, told Cointelegraph that Web2.5 platforms are earning “tons of revenue” within Aptos. He noted that consumer-focused applications, in particular, are thriving in the network.
Web2.5 is a term used to describe platforms or applications that blend centralized Web2 experiences with decentralized Web3 elements. 
These applications avoid full decentralization, often drawing criticism for not fully embracing the Web3 vision.  
Ash Pampati at the Token2049 media lounge in Dubai. Source: Cointelegraph
Consumer-focu…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Ezra Reguerra</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Watch these Bitcoin price levels as BTC meets ‘decision point’]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/watch-these-bitcoin-price-levels-btc-meets-decision-point</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/watch-these-bitcoin-price-levels-btc-meets-decision-point?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-05T10:51:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Key takeaways:

Bitcoin failed to break the $98,000 resistance amid increased profit-taking.

BTC price needs to close above $95,000 on the daily chart for a push to $100,000.

Bitcoin’s (BTC) price failed to break above resistance at $98,000 on May 3. Since April 22, BTC prices have formed daily candle highs between $93,000 and $97,900, but they could not close above $97,440.
BTC/USD four-hour chart. Source: Cointelegraph/TradingView
Bitcoin price action has been choppy and within a narrow range for the past few days. With elevated profit-taking and a lot of supply in profit, markets could see volatile price swings toward key BTC price levels over the next few days. 
Realized profits above “statistical levels”
Senior researcher at Glassnode, CryptoVizArt.₿, said that Bitcoin’s rally to th…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Nancy Lubale</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The vocal effects of Daft Punk]]></title>
        <id>https://bjango.com/articles/daftpunkvocaleffects/</id>
        <link href="https://bjango.com/articles/daftpunkvocaleffects/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-05T10:48:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tether AI platform to support Bitcoin and USDT payments, CEO says]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/tether-ai-support-bitcoin-usdt-payments-paolo-ardoino</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/tether-ai-support-bitcoin-usdt-payments-paolo-ardoino?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-05T10:23:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tether AI, the forthcoming artificial intelligence platform from stablecoin giant Tether, will feature payments in major cryptocurrencies, including USDt and Bitcoin.
Tether CEO Paolo Adroino took to X on May 5 to tease the imminent launch of Tether AI, the company’s new AI platform designed to offer “personal infinite intelligence.”
According to Ardoino, Tether’s AI platform will be integrated with USDt (USDT) and Bitcoin (BTC) payments, allowing users to make transactions directly through a peer-to-peer (P2P) network.
Source: Paolo Ardoino
The initiative builds on Tether’s December 2024 announcement that it was developing a website for the AI tool, targeting a launch by the end of the first quarter of 2025.  
Support of “any hardware and device”
Ardoino emphasized that Tether AI will not…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Helen Partz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[iQOO Buds 1i Launches In Indonesia With 50-Hour Battery Life]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=350545</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/350545/iqoo-buds-1i-launches-in-indonesia-with-50-hour-battery-life/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-05T10:16:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[vivo’s iQOO sub-brand has launched the Buds 1i, a pair of TWS earbuds. The device is seemingly available in both China and international markets, although it comes in two different variants. While one of its main selling points is its 50-hour battery life, that particular variation is only sold in Indonesia. The Chinese market gets […]
The post iQOO Buds 1i Launches In Indonesia With 50-Hour Battery Life appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Newsdesk</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tether Enters AI Arena With Tether.AI]]></title>
        <id>07f2a32b-e814-44f8-a6e4-7d22bfba7ca9</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/05/tether-enters-ai-arena-with-tetherai"/>
        <updated>2025-05-05T10:06:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tether CEO Paolo Ardoino Tether AI tech will enable an unstoppable peer-to-peer network of billions of AI agents]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sam Reynolds</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PayNet Launches Malaysia’s First Fintech-Focused Accelerator And Community Hub]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=350547</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/350547/paynet-launches-fintech-hub-initiative-for-startups/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-05T10:05:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Payments Network Malaysia Sdn Bhd (PayNet) has launched the country’s first dedicated fintech accelerator and community platform, the PayNet Fintech Hub, aimed at fast-tracking the development of Malaysia’s fintech sector. The initiative is designed to provide selected fintech startups with capital access, mentorship, industry partnerships, and international exposure. According to the company, the Fintech Hub […]
The post PayNet Launches Malaysia’s First Fintech-Focused Accelerator And Community Hub appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Heirul Kamel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vitalik Buterin says rollups must prove security before decentralizing]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/vitalik-buterin-rollups-decentralization-guidelines</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/vitalik-buterin-rollups-decentralization-guidelines?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-05T10:00:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum co-founder Vitalik Buterin explained when rollup-based layer-2 platforms should go decentralized, and why “as soon as possible” is not the correct answer.
In a May 5 X post, Buterin said there is a right time for rollup-based scalability solutions to transition to a decentralized model. This moment depends on how low the proof system’s failure probability has fallen compared with the risks introduced by centralization.
Buterin’s thread came in response to a separate post by decentralized exchange Loopring founder and CEO Daniel Wang. Wang said in his thread that the maturity of a system matters to its security:
“Not all code is created equal. A rollup can be Stage 2, but running fresh code that’s never been tested under real stress.“
Rollup development is classified into stages: s…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Adrian Zmudzinski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to set up stop-loss and take-profit orders]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/how-to-set-up-stop-loss-and-take-profit-orders</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/how-to-set-up-stop-loss-and-take-profit-orders?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-05T09:42:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Key takeaways

Bitcoin and crypto traders can rely on automated orders on their trading platform to limit losses and secure gains.

Stop-loss orders in Bitcoin trading started as manual risk management in the early 2010s. Now, they have become advanced, automated tools on today’s exchanges.


In the algorithm era and bot pestering, proper trading tools like stop-loss and take-profit orders will help you protect your trades.

Setting up advanced BTC trading strategies doesn’t guarantee a successful risk management plan. Monitoring the market regularly helps you understand current conditions. This way, you can avoid strategic mistakes.

Stop-loss and take-profit orders in trading were used long before Bitcoin. In traditional financial markets, they were already used as a risk management and …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Emi Lacapra</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Jobstreet Malaysia: “Resume Approved” Calls Are Scams]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=350530</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/350530/jobstreet-malaysia-resume-approved-calls-are-scams/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-05T09:30:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the past few days, you may have gotten strange scam calls noting that “your resume has been approved” on Jobstreet, telling you to contact the caller via WhatsApp. These calls come from various numbers, including apparent landline numbers as well, and these calls would be extra weird if you don’t have an account on […]
The post Jobstreet Malaysia: “Resume Approved” Calls Are Scams appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ian Chee</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Design of Compact Elastic Binary Trees (Cebtree)]]></title>
        <id>http://wtarreau.blogspot.com/2025/03/on-design-of-compact-elastic-binary.html</id>
        <link href="http://wtarreau.blogspot.com/2025/03/on-design-of-compact-elastic-binary.html"/>
        <updated>2025-05-05T09:25:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bryan Johnson wants to start a new religion in which “the body is God”]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1116090</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/05/05/1116090/bryan-johnson-new-religion-body-is-god/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-05T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bryan Johnson is on a mission to not die. The 47-year-old multimillionaire has already applied his slogan “Don’t Die” to events, merchandise, and a Netflix documentary. Now he’s founding a Don’t Die religion. Johnson, who famously spends millions of dollars on scans, tests, supplements, and a lifestyle routine designed to slow or reverse the aging…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jessica Hamzelou</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[America’s crypto renaissance is already failing; but we can fix it]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/america-s-crypto-renaissance</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/america-s-crypto-renaissance?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-05T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Opinion by: Shane Molidor, Founder, Forgd
For years, launching a crypto project in the United States has been a maze of uncertainty. Legal ambiguity and a hostile regulatory environment have driven founders offshore, turning places like Switzerland and the Cayman Islands into global hubs for blockchain innovation. 
With Trump’s election, things finally started to change, with a US administration openly declaring its intention to be crypto-friendly. Yet, despite the rhetoric, nothing concrete has changed so far.
Launching a crypto project in the US is just as difficult as ever. US regulatory agencies continue to offer nothing but vague threats and “regulation by enforcement” lawsuits. America wants to be a leader in crypto, but, even under the Trump administration, it isn’t taking action to…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Shane Molidor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Indonesia suspends Sam Altman’s World project over suspicious activity]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/indonesia-suspend-world-id-registration-rule-violation</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/indonesia-suspend-world-id-registration-rule-violation?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-05T08:53:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[OpenAI CEO Sam Altman’s digital identity project, World, formerly known as Worldcoin, faces challenges in Indonesia after local regulators temporarily suspended its registration certificates.
The Indonesian Ministry of Communications and Digital (Komdigi) has halted the Electronic System Operator Certificate Registration (TDPSE) for World and World ID over suspicious activity and alleged registration violations, the ministry announced on May 4.
After the suspension, Komdigi plans to summon World’s local subsidiaries, PT Terang Bulan Abadi and PT Sandina Abadi Nusantara, to provide clarification on the alleged violations, it stated.
According to a preliminary investigation, World’s PT Terang Bulan Abadi was allegedly operating without TDPSE, while PT Sandina Abadi Nusantara — the subsidiary…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Helen Partz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Notcoin says tap-to-earn ‘probably dead’ as Telegram games see shift]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/notcoin-telegram-gaming-tap-to-earn-dead-token2049</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/notcoin-telegram-gaming-tap-to-earn-dead-token2049?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-05T08:24:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Notcoin, one of the most prominent Web3 gaming projects of 2024, said the tap-to-earn genre is “probably dead” as Web3 gaming shifts to more fun and engaging projects.
During Token2049 in Dubai, Notcoin co-founders Sasha and Vladimir Plotvinov, along with Uliana Salo, the head of design and product lead for NotGames, spoke with Cointelegraph about the state of Telegram-based Web3 gaming. 
Vladimir told Cointelegraph that game builders are shifting to different genres as tap-to-earn has failed to sustain players’ interests. 
“We’re going to see different types of games, as tap-to-earn games are probably dead because they’re not sustainable,” he said. 
Notcoin’s Sasha Plotvinov (left), Uliana Salo (middle) and Vladimir Plotvinov (right) at the Token2049 event in Dubai. Source: Cointelegraph
…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Ezra Reguerra</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ether-Bitcoin 'Squeeze' Hints at Imminent Volatility as Ethereum Pectra Upgrade Nears]]></title>
        <id>4daee880-6f1b-4961-b8cb-6b5bfe49561b</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/05/ether-bitcoin-squeeze-hints-at-imminent-volatility-as-ethereum-spectra-upgrade-nears"/>
        <updated>2025-05-05T08:22:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum's Pectra upgrade, set for May 7, aims to improve scalability and may impact market activity.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Omkar Godbole</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Show HN: CodeCafé – A real-time collaborative code editor in the browser]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/mrktsm/codecafe</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/mrktsm/codecafe"/>
        <updated>2025-05-05T08:08:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OnePlus Nord CE 5 Specs May Include MediaTek Dimensity 8350]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=350508</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/350508/oneplus-nord-ce-5-specs-may-include-mediatek-dimensity-8350/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-05T08:07:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There is a chance that OnePlus might unveil its Nord CE 5 soon. The successor to last year’s Nord CE 4, details of the apparent device were shared by @Gadgetsdata through a post on X. Among the various specs, the leakster claims that the phone will come with a MediaTek Dimensity 8350 chipset, and house […]
The post OnePlus Nord CE 5 Specs May Include MediaTek Dimensity 8350 appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Newsdesk</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How cybercriminals are exploiting digital twins to scam crypto users]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/explained/how-cybercriminals-are-exploiting-digital-twins-to-scam-crypto-users</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/explained/how-cybercriminals-are-exploiting-digital-twins-to-scam-crypto-users?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-05T08:05:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What is a digital twin?            
            
                
A digital twin is a virtual model or replica of a physical object, system or process. It’s like a digital mirror, allowing us to simulate, monitor and predict the behavior of real-world entities in real-time. 
These virtual counterparts are designed to pull data from physical sensors or inputs, providing a continuous feedback loop that helps with analysis, optimization and decision-making. Digital twins can represent almost anything, from machinery in a manufacturing plant to human behavior or entire cities.
In industries like healthcare, automotive, manufacturing and urban planning, digital twins allow for better resource management, predictive maintenance and more accurate simulations before physical changes are made. In e…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by SK Arora</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Stablecoin fever: 5 major stablecoins are growing crypto adoption]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/major-stablecoins-growing-crypto-adoption</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/major-stablecoins-growing-crypto-adoption?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-05T08:04:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Increasing institutional interest and moves toward legal frameworks for stablecoins have seen the space grow, with five major projects slated to expand the market in the near future. 
In the EU, the Markets in Crypto-Assets (MiCA) regulatory package is in full force and has given stablecoin issuers clear guidelines by which they can enter European markets. In the US, the STABLE Act and the GENIUS Act, which would provide rules for stablecoins, are making their way through Congress. 
As a result, major payments firms like Mastercard and Visa are stepping up support for stablecoin systems, and new coins have appeared, boosting the overall market capitalization of the stablecoin market. 
Here are five major stablecoin initiatives projected to grow crypto adoption.

Tether to relaunch in the U…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Aaron Wood</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[vivo Y19s Pro Quietly Listed; Malaysian Launch Imminent]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=350518</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/350518/vivo-19s-pro/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-05T08:03:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[vivo has quietly introduced a new entry-level smartphone called the Y19s Pro on its Colombian website. The Pro counterpart to the Y19s, it seems to be nearly identical to the vanilla model except for a smaller battery and an upgraded charging speed. Just like the standard version, the Y19s Pro sports a 6.68-inch 720p LCD […]
The post vivo Y19s Pro Quietly Listed; Malaysian Launch Imminent appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ikmal Rozlan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Donald Trump Denies Claims of Profiting From TRUMP Token]]></title>
        <id>b9ecfa2c-dc2b-464c-a51f-9c549156e7eb</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2025/05/05/donald-trump-denies-claims-of-profiting-from-trump-token"/>
        <updated>2025-05-05T07:49:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The TRUMP token is up 20% over the last month, according to market data]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sam Reynolds</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[LG Smartphones To Lose Update Support In June]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=350513</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/350513/lg-smartphones-to-lose-update-support-in-june/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-05T07:36:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nearly four years after leaving the smartphone business, LG has announced that it is shutting down update servers for its existing smartphones. Users who are still in possession of an LG smartphone are advised to update their devices before 30 June 2025, after which, support services will be terminated. Affected services include LG Electronics Mobile […]
The post LG Smartphones To Lose Update Support In June appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nurul Kamil</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Solana Quietly Fixes Bug That Could Have Let Attackers Mint and Steal Certain Tokens]]></title>
        <id>6ca8a5b1-c49f-42dc-bf3c-90d462ef6366</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/05/solana-quietly-fixes-bug-that-could-have-let-attackers-mint-and-steal-certain-tokens"/>
        <updated>2025-05-05T07:10:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A sophisticated attacker could forge invalid proofs that the on-chain verifier would still accept. This would have allowed unauthorized actions such as minting unlimited tokens or withdrawing tokens from other accounts.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shaurya Malwa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BTC dominance due ‘collapse’ at 71%: 5 things to know in Bitcoin this week]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/btc-dominance-due-to-collapse-5-things-bitcoin-this-week</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/btc-dominance-due-to-collapse-5-things-bitcoin-this-week?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-05T07:00:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin (BTC) starts the first full week of May with yearly open support in focus ahead of a key US economic policy decision.

BTC price action attempts to hold the yearly open as support after some downside at the weekly close, but bullish perspectives remain intact.

The US Federal Reserve interest rate decision is the key macro event of the week, with Chair Jerome Powell tipped to “move markets.”

Jobless claims and Coinbase earnings add to a mixed bag of potential volatility triggers as recession talk gets louder.

Bitcoin dominance hits 65% for the first time in over four years, but analysis thinks its days are numbered.

Bitcoin “FOMO” is still waiting in the wings as sentiment flips positive.


Bitcoin traders stay bullish with $93,500 intact
Bitcoin saw some sell pressure into the …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by William Suberg</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kyrgyzstan's Gold-Backed Dollar Pegged Stablecoin USDKG to Debut in Q3]]></title>
        <id>425ea71c-20b4-4662-87ad-f9b2d7a39dd9</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/05/kyrgyzstan-s-gold-backed-dollar-pegged-stablecoin-usdkg-to-debut-in-q3"/>
        <updated>2025-05-05T06:39:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The stablecoin will be backed by $500 million in gold from the Kyrgyz Ministry of Finance, with plans to expand reserves to $2 billion.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Omkar Godbole</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trump Says He Will Extend TikTok Deadline If Deal Still Not Reached]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=350496</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/350496/trump-tiktok-deadline-extension-june/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-05T06:18:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[US President Donald Trump has stated that he would extend the 19 June deadline for TikTok, should the social media platform’s parent company, ByteDance, still fail to find a buyer for its US business. During an interview with NBC, he said that he would like to “see it done.” TikTok’s fate in the US has […]
The post Trump Says He Will Extend TikTok Deadline If Deal Still Not Reached appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John Law</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Maldives Could Soon Become a Crypto Hub Thanks to Dubai Family Office's $9B Commitment]]></title>
        <id>314a39d3-04c3-4832-b315-c9522f1f9e32</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2025/05/05/maldives-could-soon-become-a-crypto-hub-thanks-to-dubai-family-offices-9b-commitment"/>
        <updated>2025-05-05T06:18:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The investment aims to help the Maldives diversify its economy beyond tourism and fisheries and address its debt obligations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shaurya Malwa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Donald Trump gives conflicting answers over memecoin profits]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/donald-trump-conflicting-answers-memecoin-profits</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/donald-trump-conflicting-answers-memecoin-profits?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-05T06:11:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[US President Donald Trump gave clashing answers to whether he has profited from the crypto memecoin he launched in January, just days before he re-entered the White House.
In a wide-ranging interview with Kristen Welker on NBC News’ Meet the Press released on May 4, Trump said he was “not profiting from anything” when asked to respond to critics who said he’s profiting from the presidency through the memecoin.
“So you’re not profiting off of the cryptocurrency at all?” Welker asked Trump.
“I haven’t even looked,” Trump admitted.
“But I’ll tell you what. Look, if I own stock in something and I do a good job, and the stock market goes up, I guess I’m profiting.”
Trump launched his memecoin, Official Trump (TRUMP), on Jan. 17, which hit a peak of $73.43 two days later, just a day before he wa…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Jesse Coghlan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Comms Ministry Open To Discuss AI Use Guidelines In Journalism]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=350499</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/350499/comms-ministry-open-to-discuss-ai-use-guidelines-in-journalism/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-05T05:59:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Communications Ministry has expressed “readiness” to meet with representatives from media groups to discuss guidelines on AI use in journalism. Specifically mentioned are the National Union of Journalists Malaysia (NUJM) and the Malaysian Press Institute (MPI), according to Bernama. Comms Minister Fahmi Fadzil was quoted as saying that “I am ready to meet and […]
The post Comms Ministry Open To Discuss AI Use Guidelines In Journalism appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ian Chee</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OKX to restart DEX with anti-abuse upgrades after Lazarus ‘misuse’]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/okx-restart-dex-with-anti-abuse-upgrades-after-misuse-by-lazarus</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/okx-restart-dex-with-anti-abuse-upgrades-after-misuse-by-lazarus?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-05T05:41:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto exchange OKX has brought its decentralized exchange (DEX) aggregator back online with new security upgrades after it was paused in March to prevent further misuse by the North Korean hacking crew, the Lazarus Group.
OKX founder and CEO Star Xu said in a May 4 statement to X that the DEX aggregator, OKX Web3, will resume with several new features, including a “real-time abuse detecting and blocking system.”
A DEX aggregator is a service that pulls data from multiple decentralized exchanges and market makers and then presents it to users to assist with trading. Xu says, “OKX Web3 is a browser and search engine for blockchain.”
Source: Star Xu
At the same time, OKX said in a May 4 statement that the latest upgrade includes other new security measures to identify suspicious or fraudulen…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Stephen Katte</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin pioneer and felon says he’s ‘vibe coding’ to restart the BTC faucet]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-pioneer-felon-bringing-back-the-bitcoin-faucet</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-pioneer-felon-bringing-back-the-bitcoin-faucet?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-05T05:37:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Early Bitcoin entrepreneur Charlie Shrem says he’s working on bringing back the Bitcoin faucet — a website that hands out Bitcoin to whoever solves CAPTCHA tasks, normally used to distinguish humans from machines.
Shrem shared his new Bitcoin (BTC) faucet website — 21million.com — in a May 4 X post, which mimics the first-ever Bitcoin CAPTCHA page created by early Bitcoin innovator Gavin Andresen back in 2010.
The 21million.com website currently displays a screenshot of a CAPTCHA task and a box to enter a receiving Bitcoin address, which was not functional at the time of writing. 
Shrem’s Bitcoin faucet website also shows that there are 0 Bitcoin available to claim.
Like Andresen’s old website, Shrem’s page explains what Bitcoin is and how to receive Bitcoin.
Charlie Shrem’s Bitcoin faucet…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Brayden Lindrea</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Industry calls for urgent crypto law reforms after Australian election]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/industry-calls-urgent-crypto-law-reforms-after-australian-election</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/industry-calls-urgent-crypto-law-reforms-after-australian-election?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-05T05:32:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Australian crypto industry has called on the newly reelected Labor government to urgently make digital asset legislation a top priority to ensure Australia doesn’t fall further behind global markets.
The incumbent Australian Labor Party was returned in a landslide on May 3, picking up 54.9% of the two-party-preferred vote, against the Liberal and National Parties on 45.1%. Both parties went to the election promising crypto law reform, but only the opposition pledged to deliver draft legislation within 100 days. 
Coinbase managing director for APAC John O’Loghlen said on May 5 the reelected Albanese Government has the “opportunity and the responsibility to move quickly on this issue” and called for a Crypto-Asset Taskforce to be established within its first 100 days “with the aim of bri…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Andrew Fenton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Hovers Above $94K as Market Awaits News on U.S.- China Trade Deal]]></title>
        <id>0c560cc9-1fc1-4c44-827f-b64c9a980d7e</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/05/bitcoin-hovers-above-94k-as-market-awaits-news-on-us-china-trade-deal"/>
        <updated>2025-05-05T05:26:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The market is cautiously optimistic that a deal can be reached and traders are taking a breather.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sam Reynolds</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[US Bitcoin ETFs bought 6x more than BTC miners produced last week]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/us-bitcoin-etfs-bought-6x-more-btc-than-produced-by-miners-last-week</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/us-bitcoin-etfs-bought-6x-more-btc-than-produced-by-miners-last-week?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-05T05:19:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Spot Bitcoin exchange-traded funds (ETFs) in the United States bought up nearly six times as many Bitcoin as were produced by miners over the last week.
The US-based Bitcoin (BTC) funds bought a whopping 18,644 Bitcoin over the past week when only 3,150 BTC were mined for the period, reported asset allocator HODL15Capital on May 4.
This accumulation by institutions and ETF issuers represents almost six times the amount of the asset being produced since miners only generate 450 coins per day.  
The total inflow for the past five trading days was around $1.8 billion, with a net outflow on April 30, according to Farside Investors. There has only been one outflow day since April 16, as the inflows have mirrored market recovery. 
Last week’s accumulation followed an increase in BTC spot prices …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Martin Young</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Modern Latex]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/mrkline/modern-latex</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/mrkline/modern-latex"/>
        <updated>2025-05-05T05:18:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AI Meets WinDBG]]></title>
        <id>https://svnscha.de/posts/ai-meets-windbg/</id>
        <link href="https://svnscha.de/posts/ai-meets-windbg/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-05T05:11:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Malaysia's Krenovator secures seed funding to enhance AI-powered tech talent platform]]></title>
        <id>05862c4715c807e784bd1fc7c9c4d03b</id>
        <link href="https://technode.global/2025/05/05/malaysias-krenovator-secures-seed-funding-to-enhance-ai-powered-tech-talent-platform/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-05T04:43:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Krenovator Technology Sdn. Bhd., a Malaysia-based artificial intelligence (AI)-powered tech talent platform, announced Monday that it has secured seed funding from Ignite Asia, a venture capital and private equity principals firm in Singapore and Malaysia.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>TechNode Global Staff</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OpenAI ignored experts when it released overly agreeable ChatGPT]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/openai-ignored-experts-overly-agreeable-chatgpt-model-release</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/openai-ignored-experts-overly-agreeable-chatgpt-model-release?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-05T03:30:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[OpenAI has admitted that it disregarded warnings from its expert testers when releasing an update to its flagship ChatGPT model, which made the AI overly agreeable.
The company released an update to its GPT‑4o model on April 25 that made it “noticeably more sycophantic,” which it then rolled back three days later due to safety concerns, OpenAI said in a May 2 postmortem blog post.
The ChatGPT maker said its new models undergo safety and behavior checks, and its “internal experts spend significant time interacting with each new model before launch,” meant to catch issues missed by other tests.
During the latest model’s review process before it went public, OpenAI said that “some expert testers had indicated that the model’s behavior ‘felt’ slightly off” but decided to launch “due to the pos…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Jesse Coghlan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hackers use New York Post’s X account to send scam DMs, users report]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/hackers-accessed-new-york-post-x-account-scam-crypto-twitter</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/hackers-accessed-new-york-post-x-account-scam-crypto-twitter?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-05T03:27:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Malicious actors appear to have infiltrated the New York Post’s X account in an attempt to scam crypto users on the microblogging platform. 
Some X users from the crypto community have recently reported having received a private message from the New York Post’s X account inviting them to feature in a podcast and to contact them via Telegram. 
The spurious messages were first discovered on May 3 by Kerberus founder and CEO Alex Katz, who shared a screenshot of a message made out to be from author and journalist Paul Sperry via the official nypost account. 
“What’s interesting about this case is that the scammer gained unauthorized access but didn’t post a Pump.fun address or wallet drainer. Instead, they’re messaging users and then directing them to Telegram,” observed cybersecurity enginee…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Martin Young</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Solana devs fix bug that allowed unlimited minting of certain tokens]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/solana-devs-validators-fix-critical-bug-criticism-mounts</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/solana-devs-validators-fix-critical-bug-criticism-mounts?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-05T02:36:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Solana Foundation has confirmed that a zero-day vulnerability that allowed an attacker to potentially mint certain tokens and even withdraw those tokens from user accounts has been fixed. 
A May 3 post-mortem from the Solana Foundation said that the security vulnerability, first discovered on April 16, could have allowed an attacker to forge an invalid proof affecting Solana’s privacy-enabling “Token-22 confidential tokens.”
There is no known exploit of the vulnerability, and Solana validators have since adopted the patched version, the foundation said.
Solana zero-day security bug affected Token-22 confidential tokens
The Solana Foundation said the security vulnerability concerned two programs: Token-2022 and ZK ElGamal Proof.
Token-2022 handles the main application logic for token mi…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Brayden Lindrea</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Driving Compilers (2023)]]></title>
        <id>https://fabiensanglard.net/dc/index.php</id>
        <link href="https://fabiensanglard.net/dc/index.php"/>
        <updated>2025-05-05T02:17:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mattel to wind down its Hot Wheels Virtual Garage NFTs]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/mattel-sunsets-hot-wheels-virtual-garage-nfts</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/mattel-sunsets-hot-wheels-virtual-garage-nfts?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-05T01:55:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Toymaking giant Mattel is putting the brakes on its Hot Wheels Virtual Garage non-fungible tokens, pending a decision on the collection’s future.
There will be no future releases of any new NFT series or feature drops for the “foreseeable future,” Mattel said in an update on its website. The company said it will decide on the “long-term future” of Mattel digital collectibles.
“Your unwavering support and enthusiasm for the Hot Wheels Virtual Garage has been legendary, and we’re incredibly grateful to have been on this journey with you,” the company said.
“As we evaluate the changing world of virtual collectibles, we’ve determined the time has come to end our Series and Feature Drops in 2025 and onward.”
There are no plans for any new NFT series or feature drops for Mattel's Hot Wheels Virt…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Stephen Katte</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Show HN: My AI Native Resume]]></title>
        <id>https://ai.jakegaylor.com/</id>
        <link href="https://ai.jakegaylor.com/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-05T01:44:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Unparalleled Misalignments]]></title>
        <id>https://rickiheicklen.com/unparalleled-misalignments.html</id>
        <link href="https://rickiheicklen.com/unparalleled-misalignments.html"/>
        <updated>2025-05-05T01:19:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin price cools going into Fed rate hike week, HYPE, AAVE, RNDR, FET still look bullish]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-price-cools-going-into-fed-rate-hike-week-hype-aave-rndr-fet-still-look-bullish</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-price-cools-going-into-fed-rate-hike-week-hype-aave-rndr-fet-still-look-bullish?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-05T01:05:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Key points:

Bitcoin’s positive sentiment should remain intact if BTC price stays above the 20-day EMA near $92,000.

Several altcoins show bullish chart patterns in the 4-hour and 1-day timeframes.

Bitcoin (BTC) has given back some of the gains over the weekend, and the price has pulled back to the breakout level of $95,000. Buyers will have to successfully hold the $95,000 level to keep the bullish momentum intact.
Bitcoin network economist Timothy Peterson said in a post on X that Bitcoin could surge to a new all-time high and reach a target of $135,000 in the next 100 days if certain conditions are met. Peterson believes a drop in the CBOE Volatility Index below 18 could trigger a “risk-on environment” favoring Bitcoin. The other crucial points needed for the Bitcoin rally are a fall …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Rakesh Upadhyay</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Matrix-vector multiplication implemented in off-the-shelf DRAM for Low-Bit LLMs]]></title>
        <id>https://arxiv.org/abs/2503.23817</id>
        <link href="https://arxiv.org/abs/2503.23817"/>
        <updated>2025-05-04T23:35:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[On Not Carrying a Camera – Cultivating memories instead of snapshots]]></title>
        <id>https://hedgehogreview.com/issues/after-neoliberalism/articles/on-not-carrying-a-camera</id>
        <link href="https://hedgehogreview.com/issues/after-neoliberalism/articles/on-not-carrying-a-camera"/>
        <updated>2025-05-04T23:32:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[V.S. Naipaul: The Grief and the Glory]]></title>
        <id>https://granta.com/vs-naipaul-the-grief-and-the-glory/</id>
        <link href="https://granta.com/vs-naipaul-the-grief-and-the-glory/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-04T23:11:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Helmdar: 3D Scanning Brooklyn on Rollerblades]]></title>
        <id>https://owentrueblood.com/blog/2025/05/04/helmdar/</id>
        <link href="https://owentrueblood.com/blog/2025/05/04/helmdar/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-04T21:49:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Here’s what happened in crypto today]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/what-happened-in-crypto-today</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/what-happened-in-crypto-today?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-04T21:47:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today in crypto, the government of Maldives signs $9 billion deal to establish crypto hub, a group of pro-crypto US Senate Democrats have said they would oppose a stablecoin bill in its current form, and OKX founder and CEO has responded to Justin Sun’s criticism.
Maldives signs $9 billion deal to become international crypto hub
The government of the Maldives signed a $9 billion deal with Dubai-based family office MBS Global Investments to develop a crypto hub in the island nation's capital of Malé and to attract foreign investment opportunities.
Part of the development deal includes plans for an 830,000-square-meter facility used to house and host blockchain, crypto, and Web3 firms.
Maldives sits between Africa, Asia, and Australia. Source: Worldometer
According to the Financial Times, wh…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Cointelegraph</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kidnapped dad of crypto businessman freed from ransom attempt: Report]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/kidnapped-dad-crypto-entrepreneur-freed-ransom-attempt</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/kidnapped-dad-crypto-entrepreneur-freed-ransom-attempt?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-04T21:27:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The father of an unnamed crypto entrepreneur was freed by police in Paris, France, during a law enforcement raid of the property where the man was held captive for ransom over several days.
According to a report by Le Monde, the May 3 raid resulted in five arrests. Local outlet Le Parisien also said the kidnappers demanded between 5 million and 7 million euros, or up to $7.9 million, to release the captive man.
Although the details on the identity of the victims remain scant, likely for security reasons, the crypto entrepreneur and his father co-owned a crypto marketing firm based in Malta, French media reports.
This incident features similarities to the kidnapping of Ledger co-founder David Balland in France in January 2025. Balland was also held for a crypto ransom until he was freed by …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Vince Quill</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Graceful Shutdown in Go: Practical Patterns]]></title>
        <id>https://victoriametrics.com/blog/go-graceful-shutdown/index.html</id>
        <link href="https://victoriametrics.com/blog/go-graceful-shutdown/index.html"/>
        <updated>2025-05-04T21:09:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[KaiPod Learning (YC S21) Is Hiring VP of Engineering]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ycombinator.com/companies/kaipod-learning/jobs/Bs3H9uB-vp-of-engineering</id>
        <link href="https://www.ycombinator.com/companies/kaipod-learning/jobs/Bs3H9uB-vp-of-engineering"/>
        <updated>2025-05-04T21:01:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Maldives to build $9 billion crypto hub to attract investment: Report]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/maldives-building-9-billion-crypto-hub</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/maldives-building-9-billion-crypto-hub?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-04T19:40:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The government of Maldives signed an agreement with MBS Global Investments, a Dubai-based family office, to develop a $9 billion crypto and blockchain hub in Malé, the capital of the South Pacific archipelago nation.
According to a report from the Financial Times, the agreement, which was signed on May 4, was done in the hopes of moving the Maldives away from reliance on tourism and fisheries by attracting foreign direct investment into blockchain and Web3 technologies.
The project outlines plans for the Maldives International Financial Centre, an 830,000-square-meter facility that will reportedly employ up to 16,000 individuals.
Completing the project will take an estimated five years and the capital requirements for the ambitious development are more than the $7 billion in annual gross d…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Vince Quill</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[I'd rather read the prompt]]></title>
        <id>https://claytonwramsey.com/blog/prompt/</id>
        <link href="https://claytonwramsey.com/blog/prompt/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-04T19:17:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Traders’ Favorite Lottery Ticket for the First Half of the Year — The $300K BTC Call]]></title>
        <id>cc358427-d0a0-40fe-89d5-53fd74d3dc30</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/04/bitcoin-traders-favorite-lottery-ticket-for-the-first-half-of-the-year-the-usd300k-btc-call"/>
        <updated>2025-05-04T18:41:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA["There are always folks that want the hyperinflation hedge," one observer said, explaining the solid open interest build up in the $300K call option expiring on June 26.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Omkar Godbole</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Design for 3D-Printing]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.rahix.de/design-for-3d-printing/</id>
        <link href="https://blog.rahix.de/design-for-3d-printing/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-04T17:38:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Saylor signals impending Bitcoin purchase following Q1 earnings call]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/michael-saylor-signals-bitcoin-purchase-following-earnings-call</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/michael-saylor-signals-bitcoin-purchase-following-earnings-call?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-04T16:43:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Strategy co-founder Michael Saylor hinted at an impending Bitcoin (BTC) purchase, marking the fourth consecutive week of purchases by the BTC treasury company.
The company's most recent acquisition occurred on April 28 when Strategy purchased 15,355 BTC, valued at over $1.4 billion at the time, bringing the company's total holdings to 553,555 BTC.
According to data from SaylorTracker, Strategy is up approximately 39% on its investment, representing over $15 billion in unrealized gains.
Strategy’s history of Bitcoin acquisition. Source: SaylorTracker
Bitcoin investors continue closely monitoring the company, which has been a major driver of direct institutional exposure to BTC by popularizing the Bitcoin corporate treasury concept and indirectly through institutions holding Strategy's stock…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Vince Quill</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The great cognitive migration: How AI is reshaping human purpose, work and meaning]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3006326</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/the-great-cognitive-migration-ai-will-win-at-intelligence-but-only-we-can-make-it-matter/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-04T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Humans need to embrace domains where AI still falters, and where human creativity, ethics and emotion emain indispensable.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gary Grossman, Edelman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chart of the Week: '10x Money Multiplier' for Bitcoin Could Take Wall Street by Storm]]></title>
        <id>cb8b2561-896a-4b39-9a17-7b5ec70ae1ac</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/04/chart-of-the-week-10x-money-multiplier-for-bitcoin-could-take-wall-street-by-storm"/>
        <updated>2025-05-04T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Publicly traded firms relentlessly buying bitcoin for their balance sheet could result in 'significant buy pressure.']]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Aoyon Ashraf</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[An Alabama landline that keeps ringing]]></title>
        <id>https://oxfordamerican.org/oa-now/the-alabama-landline-that-keeps-ringing</id>
        <link href="https://oxfordamerican.org/oa-now/the-alabama-landline-that-keeps-ringing"/>
        <updated>2025-05-04T12:02:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Local cosmetics sector can be launchpad to position Malaysia as innovation-led economy: Sirim chief tech officer]]></title>
        <id>f3d9620891e0882d2a66ea582395ca3a</id>
        <link href="https://thesun.my/business-news/local-cosmetics-sector-can-be-launchpad-to-position-malaysia-as-innovation-led-economy-sirim-chief-tech-officer-AH14020110"/>
        <updated>2025-05-03T20:35:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SHAH ALAM: The Malaysian cosmetics sector can serve as a launchpad to position the nation as an innovation-led economy, said Sirim Bhd chief technolog...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hayatun Razak</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Not everything needs an LLM: A framework for evaluating when AI makes sense]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3006312</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/not-everything-needs-an-llm-a-framework-for-evaluating-when-ai-makes-sense/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-03T19:35:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The answer to 'What customer needs requires an AI solution?' isn’t always 'Yes.' LLMs are still expensive and not always accurate.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sharanya Rao</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gold-Backed Crypto Minting Volume Hits 3-Year High as Central Bank Buying Drops]]></title>
        <id>965a38b6-6be7-404a-a8ab-68148c671d6e</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/03/gold-backed-crypto-minting-volume-hits-3-year-high-as-central-bank-buying-drops"/>
        <updated>2025-05-03T19:15:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A surge in demand, particularly from ETFs, pushed the average quarterly gold price to a record high.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Francisco Rodrigues</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Tiny Company Wants to Buy $20M TRUMP Token to Change U.S.-Mexico Trade Deals]]></title>
        <id>893602ea-e9cf-4e7d-aee8-d24977a98a69</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/03/a-tiny-company-wants-to-buy-usd20m-trump-token-to-change-u-s-mexico-trade-deals"/>
        <updated>2025-05-03T16:47:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Freight Technologies, which also invested in FET tokens, says it's aiming to strengthen its technology and geopolitical positioning.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Francisco Rodrigues</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ghost in the machine? Legend of the 'haunted' N64 video game cartridge]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bbc.com/future/article/20250501-the-haunted-video-game-that-traumatised-the-web</id>
        <link href="https://www.bbc.com/future/article/20250501-the-haunted-video-game-that-traumatised-the-web"/>
        <updated>2025-05-03T16:41:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Arizona Governor Calls Crypto an ‘Untested Investment,’ Vetoes Bitcoin Reserve Bill]]></title>
        <id>f4c091c5-cb7d-4741-8b59-d066c99d0c2a</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2025/05/03/arizona-governor-calls-crypto-an-untested-investment-vetoes-bitcoin-reserve-bill"/>
        <updated>2025-05-03T16:01:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The bill, Senate Bill 1025, aimed to create a digital assets reserve managed by the state.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Francisco Rodrigues</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘Like Spitting on a Fire’: Tether CEO Slams EU Deposit Protections Amid Bank Failure Warnings]]></title>
        <id>8fe34898-f626-4e9a-a14b-6435b54c6d95</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/03/like-spitting-on-a-fire-tether-ceo-slams-eu-deposit-protections-amid-bank-failure-warnings"/>
        <updated>2025-05-03T15:35:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Paolo Ardoino criticizes EU rules that could force stablecoin issuers to rely on fragile banks and warned about potential bank failures in the future.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Francisco Rodrigues</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CME Group Crypto Derivatives Volume Soars 129% in April With ETH Leading the Charge]]></title>
        <id>0e1767d2-530f-48a3-b42b-4144a50565db</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/03/cme-group-crypto-derivatives-volume-soars-129-in-april-with-eth-leading-the-charge"/>
        <updated>2025-05-03T14:07:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The exchange saw its crypto derivatives volumes rise sharply to $8.9 billion in April, led by ether futures growth.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Francisco Rodrigues</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[State of Crypto: IRS Departures]]></title>
        <id>243d623c-f6d2-41f3-952d-c8dadc84112f</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2025/05/03/state-of-crypto-irs-departures"/>
        <updated>2025-05-03T13:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Seth Wilks and Raj Mukherjee, two IRS digital asset directors, are leaving the agency just over a year after joining it.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nikhilesh De</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Archers Didn't Volley Fire]]></title>
        <id>https://acoup.blog/2025/05/02/collections-why-archers-didnt-volley-fire/</id>
        <link href="https://acoup.blog/2025/05/02/collections-why-archers-didnt-volley-fire/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-03T08:28:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fuzzy images are our first look at Amazon's super-secret satellites]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/space/2025/05/we-finally-know-a-little-more-about-amazons-super-secret-satellites/</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/space/2025/05/we-finally-know-a-little-more-about-amazons-super-secret-satellites/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-03T01:20:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[I turned a 40 year old Apple Mouse into a speech to text button]]></title>
        <id>https://workshop.cjpais.com/projects/handy-m0100</id>
        <link href="https://workshop.cjpais.com/projects/handy-m0100"/>
        <updated>2025-05-03T01:12:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Technical analysis of TM SGNL, the unofficial Signal app Trump officials used]]></title>
        <id>https://micahflee.com/tm-sgnl-the-obscure-unofficial-signal-app-mike-waltz-uses-to-text-with-trump-officials/</id>
        <link href="https://micahflee.com/tm-sgnl-the-obscure-unofficial-signal-app-mike-waltz-uses-to-text-with-trump-officials/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-02T23:20:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[RSAC 2025: Why the AI agent era means more demand for CISOS]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3006066</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/security/rsac-2025-why-the-ai-agent-era-means-more-demand-for-cisos/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-02T23:02:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[RSAC 2025 made one thing clear: AI agents are entering security workflows, but boards want proof they work.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Louis Columbus</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A 1903 Proposal to Preserve the Dead in Glass Cubes]]></title>
        <id>https://hyperallergic.com/406959/preserving-the-dead-in-glass/</id>
        <link href="https://hyperallergic.com/406959/preserving-the-dead-in-glass/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-02T22:28:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[IRS' Crypto Leads Are Leaving the Agency After Accepting DOGE Deals]]></title>
        <id>66182685-6c87-4550-97ed-788ff310982a</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2025/05/02/irs-crypto-leads-are-leaving-the-agency-after-accepting-doge-deals"/>
        <updated>2025-05-02T20:10:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The pair took voluntary resignation offers and left their positions after only a little more than a year of government service, according to two people.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nikhilesh De</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[API Documentation: The Importance of Clear and Concise API Documentation]]></title>
        <id>68151f0be5850fcb8543375a</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-write-good-api-docs/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-02T19:37:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Imagine purchasing a standing fan straight out of the box, all parts dismantled, and you have no manual or guide to put them together. Did you imagine that just now? Cool. Here is another scenario: imagine purchasing an LG product, such as a smart TV...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Okoro Emmanuel Nzube</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OpenAI overrode concerns of expert testers to release sycophantic GPT-4o]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3006276</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/openai-overrode-concerns-of-expert-testers-to-release-sycophantic-gpt-4o/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-02T17:57:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Once again, it shows the importance of incorporating more domains beyond the traditional math and computer science into AI development.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carl Franzen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use SonarQube to Improve Your Code Quality]]></title>
        <id>6815023dec2e34790eeb71a8</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-improve-your-code-quality-with-sonarqube/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-02T17:34:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SonarQube is a powerful open-source tool that helps you maintain code quality and security by analyzing your codebase for bugs and vulnerabilities. And it can play a major role when integrated into your CI/CD pipeline. In this tutorial, we will cover...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Divya Valsala Saratchandran</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn Kubernetes – Full Handbook for Developers, Startups, and Businesses]]></title>
        <id>68150214fd424d0874293171</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-kubernetes-handbook-devs-startups-businesses/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-02T17:34:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You’ve probably heard the word Kubernetes floating around, or it’s cooler nickname k8s (pronounced “kates“). Maybe in a job post, a tech podcast, or from that one DevOps friend who always brings it up like it’s the secret sauce to everything 😅. It s...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Prince Onukwili</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The SEC Can Learn From the IRS in Making Regulation Simpler for Crypto]]></title>
        <id>78bdc336-22b5-4c24-908f-f66947f9e820</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/opinion/2025/05/02/the-sec-can-learn-from-the-irs-in-making-regulation-simpler-for-crypto"/>
        <updated>2025-05-02T17:17:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The IRS has relied on voluntary disclosure programs to bring taxpayers into compliance rather than imposing punitive actions upfront. A similar model should be applied to crypto regulation as well, says Miles Fuller, Director of Government Solutions, TaxBit.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Miles Fuller</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CoinDesk Recap: Movement’s Very Bad Week]]></title>
        <id>01956a2f-bd75-40e4-9784-ab38707d3d2c</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/news-analysis/2025/05/02/coindesk-recap-movements-very-bad-week"/>
        <updated>2025-05-02T17:06:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Plus: Mastercard, World, Strategy, Kraken, and Trump]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Benjamin Schiller</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Roblox breaks ground on data center in Brazil for early 2026]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3006251</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/games/roblox-breaks-ground-on-data-center-in-brazil-for-early-2026/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-02T16:55:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At Gamescom Latam, Roblox announced it has broken ground on a new data center in Brazil -- slated to go live in early 2026.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dean Takahashi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Franklin Templeton Backs Bitcoin DeFi Push, Citing ‘New Utility’ for Investors]]></title>
        <id>a8a2a3e7-0dc5-43bd-ac1b-139bb8b38afb</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2025/05/02/bitcoin-defi-shows-infrastructure-progress-versus-store-of-value-franklin-templeton-s-kevin-farrelly"/>
        <updated>2025-05-02T16:35:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA["I don’t think focusing on Bitcoin DeFi will dilute or complicate Bitcoin’s core narrative." Farrelly said.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Omkar Godbole</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[From Art School Drop-out to Microsoft Engineer with Shashi Lo [Podcast #170]]]></title>
        <id>6814f2ab33857abe499038b0</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/from-art-school-drop-out-to-microsoft-engineer-with-shashi-lo-podcast-170/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-02T16:28:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On this week's episode of the podcast, I interview Shashi Lo. He's a software engineer at Microsoft. He grew up the child of refugees. He wanted to start earning money and build his family so he abandoned his art school degree and taught himself how ...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Quincy Larson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cambodian Huione Group Received $98B in Crypto Leading to U.S. Crackdown: Elliptic]]></title>
        <id>02505ce6-423f-4a8e-a0bf-663db3a1c932</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2025/05/02/cambodian-huione-group-received-usd98b-in-crypto-leading-to-u-s-crackdown-elliptic"/>
        <updated>2025-05-02T15:50:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The group rolled out its own stablecoin in January to avoid traditional currency restrictions.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Oliver Knight</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kevin O’Leary: ‘Crypto Will Be the 12th Sector of the Economy’]]></title>
        <id>bccd1491-f322-4da3-bbbb-d9ede5c9a6ac</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/consensus-toronto-2025-coverage/2025/05/02/kevin-oleary-crypto-will-be-the-12th-sector-of-the-economy"/>
        <updated>2025-05-02T15:36:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ahead of Consensus 2025, the investor and TV personality shares his crypto portfolio strategy, why he won’t touch bitcoin ETFs, and what could unleash trillions into digital assets.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jennifer Sanasie</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Strategy’s $84B Bitcoin Expansion Plan Backed by Wall Street Analysts]]></title>
        <id>948ec075-9ba8-47be-b191-c8726a971c72</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/02/strategy-s-usd84b-bitcoin-expansion-plan-backed-by-wall-street-analysts"/>
        <updated>2025-05-02T14:34:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sell-side bulls from Benchmark and TD Cowen viewed Michael Saylor and team's plan as a bold yet realistic escalation of its bitcoin-focused strategy amid rising institutional interest.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Helene Braun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Download: foreign disinformation intel, and gene-edited pork]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1116079</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/05/02/1116079/the-download-foreign-disinformation-intel-and-gene-edited-pork/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-02T12:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is today’s edition of The Download, our weekday newsletter that provides a daily dose of what’s going on in the world of technology. A senior State Department official demanded records of communications with journalists, European officials, and Trump critics A previously unreported document distributed by senior US State Department official Darren Beattie reveals a sweeping effort…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rhiannon Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The US has approved CRISPR pigs for food]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1116059</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/05/02/1116059/the-us-approves-crispr-pigs-for-food/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-02T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Most pigs in the US are confined to factory farms where they can be afflicted by a nasty respiratory virus that kills piglets. The illness is called porcine reproductive and respiratory syndrome, or PRRS. A few years ago, a British company called Genus set out to design pigs immune to this germ using CRISPR gene…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Antonio Regalado</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hidden costs in AI deployment: Why Claude models may be 20-30% more expensive than GPT in enterprise settings]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3006096</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/hidden-costs-in-ai-deployment-why-claude-models-may-be-20-30-more-expensive-than-gpt-in-enterprise-settings/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-01T20:14:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It is a well-known fact that different model families can use different tokenizers. However, there has been limited analysis on how the process of “tokenization” itself varies across these tokenizers. Do all tokenizers result in the same number of tokens for a given input text? If not, how different are the generated tokens? How significant […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lavanya Gupta</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Towards the Cutest Neural Network]]></title>
        <id>https://kevinlynagh.com/towards-the-cutest-neural-network/</id>
        <link href="https://kevinlynagh.com/towards-the-cutest-neural-network/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-01T18:10:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Senior State Department official sought internal communications with journalists, European officials, and Trump critics]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1115988</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/05/01/1115988/senior-state-department-official-sought-internal-communications-with-journalists-european-officials-and-trump-critics/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-01T17:41:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A previously unreported document distributed by senior US State Department official Darren Beattie reveals a sweeping effort to uncover all communications between the staff of a small government office focused on online disinformation and a lengthy list of public and private figures—many of whom are longtime targets of the political right.  The document, originally shared…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eileen Guo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Django Crash Course for Beginners]]></title>
        <id>6813a8237eaea66216eb6819</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/django-crash-course-for-beginners/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-01T16:58:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Django is a high-level web framework built with Python that encourages rapid development and clean, pragmatic design. Django handles much of the heavy lifting involved in web development, so you can focus more on writing your app and less on reinvent...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Incremental Static Regeneration (ISR) Works in Next.js]]></title>
        <id>68139db5555c3ab781a6e0a1</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-incremental-static-regeneration-isr-works-in-nextjs/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-01T16:13:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When you build a website, you often have two main choices for how pages are created: statically or dynamically. Static pages are created once when you build your project. They’re fast because the server doesn’t have to do any extra work when someone ...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joan Ayebola</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Brief Introduction to React]]></title>
        <id>681397cd1168f254478cd514</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/a-brief-introduction-to-react/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-01T15:48:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This tutorial introduces the basics of using React components in your web apps. React is a JavaScript library used to build user interfaces, especially for single-page applications where parts of the page need to update without a full page reload. It...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mark Mahoney</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Astronomer’s $93M raise underscores a new reality: Orchestration is king in AI infrastructure]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3006195</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/astronomer-93m-raise-underscores-a-new-reality-orchestration-is-king-in-ai-infrastructure/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-01T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Astronomer secures $93 million in Series D funding to solve the AI implementation gap through data orchestration, helping enterprises streamline complex workflows and operationalize AI initiatives at scale.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Nuñez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft launches Phi-4-Reasoning-Plus, a small, powerful, open weights reasoning model!]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3006213</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/microsoft-launches-phi-4-reasoning-plus-a-small-powerful-open-weights-reasoning-model/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-01T12:41:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The release demonstrates that with carefully curated data and training techniques, small models can deliver strong reasoning performance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carl Franzen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Download: China’s energy throwback, and choosing between love and immortality]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1115999</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/05/01/1115999/the-download-chinas-energy-throwback-and-choosing-between-love-and-immortality/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-01T12:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is today’s edition of The Download, our weekday newsletter that provides a daily dose of what’s going on in the world of technology. A long-abandoned US nuclear technology is making a comeback in China China has once again beat everyone else to a clean energy milestone—its new nuclear reactor is reportedly one of the first to…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rhiannon Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Salesforce takes aim at ‘jagged intelligence’ in push for more reliable AI]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3006124</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/salesforce-tackles-jagged-intelligence-problem-with-new-ai-benchmarks-and-models/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-01T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Salesforce unveils groundbreaking AI research tackling "jagged intelligence," introducing new benchmarks, models, and guardrails to make enterprise AI agents more intelligent, trusted, and consistently reliable for business use.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Nuñez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Urtext: The Python plaintext library for people who've tried everything else]]></title>
        <id>https://urtext.co/</id>
        <link href="https://urtext.co/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-01T09:27:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A long-abandoned US nuclear technology is making a comeback in China]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1115957</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/05/01/1115957/old-new-nuclear-technology/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-01T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[China has once again beat everyone else to a clean energy milestone—its new nuclear reactor is reportedly one of the first to use thorium instead of uranium as a fuel and the first of its kind that can be refueled while it’s running. It’s an interesting (if decidedly experimental) development out of a country that’s…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Casey Crownhart</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Thunderscope update: My take: Why open source is better]]></title>
        <id>https://www.crowdsupply.com/eevengers/thunderscope/updates/revving-up-for-production</id>
        <link href="https://www.crowdsupply.com/eevengers/thunderscope/updates/revving-up-for-production"/>
        <updated>2025-05-01T00:16:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[UiPath’s new orchestrator guides AI agents to follow your enterprise’s rules]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3006059</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/uipaths-new-orchestrator-guides-ai-agents-to-follow-your-enterprises-rules/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T21:20:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[UiPath's agent orchestration layer Maestro moves prompts through three layers: the agent, a human and the robotic process automation system.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Emilia David</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The ‘era of experience’ will unleash self-learning AI agents across the web—here’s how to prepare]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3005579</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/the-era-of-experience-will-unleash-self-learning-ai-agents-across-the-web-heres-how-to-prepare/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T20:38:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AI visionaries predict an 'Era of Experience' where AI learns autonomously, and it will have important implications for application design.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ben Dickson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Qwen swings for a double with 2.5-Omni-3B model that runs on consumer PCs, laptops]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3006114</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/qwen-swings-for-a-double-with-2-5-omni-3b-model-that-runs-on-consumer-pcs-laptops/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T20:31:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Qwen2.5-Omni-3B model is licensed for non-commercial use only under Alibaba Cloud’s Qwen Research License Agreement.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carl Franzen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Breaking the ‘intellectual bottleneck’: How AI is computing the previously uncomputable in healthcare]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3005667</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/breaking-the-intellectual-bottleneck-how-ai-is-computing-the-previously-uncomputible-in-healthcare/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T19:03:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How University of Texas Medical Branch is using AI to identify patients at high cardiovascular risk, flag for stroke and catch 'basic stuff.']]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Taryn Plumb</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How IPv4 Works – A Handbook for Developers]]></title>
        <id>68124752fa6fa6a9a91d9994</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-ipv4-works-a-handbook-for-developers/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T15:52:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Internet Protocol version 4 (IPv4) is one of the core protocols of standards-based internetworking methods in the Internet and other packet-switched networks. IPv4 is still the most widely deployed Internet protocol. Google’s IPv6 Statistics show...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Omer Rosenbaum</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Get Your First SaaS Customers]]></title>
        <id>681242328ca367c7e5d58873</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-get-your-first-saas-customers/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T15:30:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Starting a SaaS (Software as a Service) business is exciting. You’ve put in the long hours building something you believe people will love. But now comes the big question: How do you get your first customers? Getting those first few users can feel li...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Udemezue John</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Get the User Model in Django – A Simple Guide With Examples]]></title>
        <id>68123f859249b83d2215937d</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-get-user-model-in-django/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T15:19:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When I’m working with Django, one of the first things I often need to do is work with users – like getting the logged-in user, creating a new one, or extending the default user model to add more information. Now, Django has a built-in User model, but...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Udemezue John</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OpenAI rolls back ChatGPT’s sycophancy and explains what went wrong]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3006053</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/openai-rolls-back-chatgpts-sycophancy-and-explains-what-went-wrong/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T15:14:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Many organizations may also begin shifting toward open-source alternatives that they can host and tune themselves.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carl Franzen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Three Omani innovators selected for ITEX 2025 in Malaysia]]></title>
        <id>57ab645df98f4874d208689be5dc65c4</id>
        <link href="https://www.muscatdaily.com/2025/04/30/three-omani-innovators-selected-fpr-itex-2025-in-malaysia/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T14:55:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Three Omani innovators selected to compete at ITEX 2025 in Malaysia. Projects include innovations in water filtration, dental materials, and remote control technology]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nisha Joshi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Structify raises $4.1M seed to turn unstructured web data into enterprise-ready datasets]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3006010</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/structify-raises-4-1m-seed-to-turn-unstructured-web-data-into-enterprise-ready-datasets/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Brooklyn-based Structify emerges from stealth with $4.1 million in seed funding to transform how businesses prepare data for AI, promising to save data scientists from the task that consumes 80% of their time.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Nuñez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Download: stereotypes in AI models, and the new age of coding]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1115952</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/04/30/1115952/the-download-stereotypes-in-ai-models-and-the-new-age-of-coding/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T12:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is today’s edition of The Download, our weekday newsletter that provides a daily dose of what’s going on in the world of technology. This data set helps researchers spot harmful stereotypes in LLMs What’s new? AI models are riddled with culturally specific biases. A new data set, called SHADES, is designed to help developers combat the…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rhiannon Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This data set helps researchers spot harmful stereotypes in LLMs]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1115946</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/04/30/1115946/this-data-set-helps-researchers-spot-harmful-stereotypes-in-llms/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T09:41:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AI models are riddled with culturally specific biases. A new data set, called SHADES, is designed to help developers combat the problem by spotting harmful stereotypes and other kinds of discrimination that emerge in AI chatbot responses across a wide range of languages. Margaret Mitchell, chief ethics scientist at AI startup Hugging Face, led the…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rhiannon Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Retail & E-Commerce Innovation Marketing & Tech Summit: Malaysia 2025]]></title>
        <id>cd2a0d19be53d9723fc0475f09d0da2d</id>
        <link href="https://marketech-apac.com/conference/retail-e-commerce-innovation-marketing-tech-summit-malaysia-2025/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T09:22:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Retail & E-Commerce Innovation Marketing & Tech Summit: Malaysia 2025]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Zyra Kate Capilastique</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Malaysia attracts US$3.7 billion in digital investments, solidifying]]></title>
        <id>b95e1bfb983c9cc102bc4266d362a8c2</id>
        <link href="https://www.digitalnewsasia.com/digital-economy/malaysia-attracts-us37-billion-digital-investments-solidifying-position-aseans-tech"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T02:31:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Malaysia’s digital economy continues to go from strength to strength, emerging as a strategic engine of growth that creates jobs, opens new opportunities, and fosters local innovation for businesses]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>@DigitalNewsAsia</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MDV powers Malaysia's tech innovation with over RM13bil financing]]></title>
        <id>d3f5fdc4ea236d719dc3a9d352d4620c</id>
        <link href="https://www.nst.com.my/business/corporate/2025/04/1209375/mdv-powers-malaysias-tech-innovation-over-rm13bil-financing"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T01:56:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[KUALA LUMPUR: Malaysia Debt Ventures Bhd (MDV) has emerged as a key enabler of the nation’s innovation and digital transformation agenda, with more than RM13 billion channelled into over 1,000 high-impact, technology-driven projects.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bernama</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[No more window switching: Mastercard’s Agent Pay transforms how enterprises use AI search]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3005997</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/no-more-window-switching-mastercards-agent-pay-transforms-how-enterprises-use-ai-search/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T22:24:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mastercard is working with AI companies and banks to allow AI platforms and agents to facilitate transactions.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Emilia David</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meta unleashes Llama API running 18x faster than OpenAI: Cerebras partnership delivers 2,600 tokens per second]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3005976</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/meta-unleashes-llama-api-running-18x-faster-than-openai-cerebras-partnership-delivers-2600-tokens-per-second/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T20:02:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Meta partners with Cerebras to launch its new Llama API, offering developers AI inference speeds up to 18 times faster than traditional GPU solutions, challenging OpenAI and Google in the fast-growing AI services market.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Nuñez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meta’s first dedicated AI app is here with Llama 4 — but it’s more consumer than productivity or business oriented]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3005961</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/metas-first-dedicated-ai-app-is-here-with-llama-4-but-its-more-consumer-than-productivity-or-business-oriented/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T18:19:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This mainstream exposure will likely accelerate a shift in what people expect not just from consumer apps, but from workplaces...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carl Franzen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tripp launches Kōkua AI as mental wellness coach across multiple platforms]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3005798</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/games/tripp-launches-kokua-ai-as-mental-wellness-coach-across-multiple-platforms/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T13:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tripp launched Kōkua AI, a mental wellness guide designed to deliver real-time, personalized emotional support across multiple platforms.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dean Takahashi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[xMEMS extends micro cooling fan-on-a-chip tech to AI data centers]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3005879</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/game-development/xmems-extends-micro-cooling-fan-on-a-chip-tech-to-ai-data-centers/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[xMEMS Labs, a pioneer of MEMS-based chips, announced that its innovative µCooling fan-on-a-chip tech will be expanded to AI data centers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dean Takahashi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Download: the AI Hype Index, and “normal” AI]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1115932</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/04/29/1115932/the-download-the-ai-hype-index-and-normal-ai/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T12:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is today’s edition of The Download, our weekday newsletter that provides a daily dose of what’s going on in the world of technology. The AI Hype Index: AI agent cyberattacks, racing robots, and musical models Separating AI reality from hyped-up fiction isn’t always easy. That’s why we’ve created the AI Hype Index—a simple, at-a-glance summary of…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rhiannon Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The AI Hype Index: AI agent cyberattacks, racing robots, and musical models]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1115918</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/04/29/1115918/the-ai-hype-index-ai-agent-cyberattacks-racing-robots-and-musical-models/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Separating AI reality from hyped-up fiction isn’t always easy. That’s why we’ve created the AI Hype Index—a simple, at-a-glance summary of everything you need to know about the state of the industry. AI agents are the AI industry’s hypiest new product—intelligent assistants capable of completing tasks without human supervision. But while they can be theoretically…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Editors</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Web3j Six Month Project Update]]></title>
        <id>68109495670a1300013504c2</id>
        <link href="https://blog.web3labs.com/web3j-six-month-project-update/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T09:10:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[November 2024 - April 2025
This report summarizes the activities and accomplishments of Web3j, an LF Decentralized Trust project, from November 2024 to April 2025. During this period, the project made significant strides in improving the framework’s functionality, enhancing user engagement, and bolstering overall community interaction. 
Key]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>George Tebrean</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Alibaba launches open source Qwen3 model that surpasses OpenAI o1 and DeepSeek R1]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3005880</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/alibaba-launches-open-source-qwen3-model-that-surpasses-openai-o1-and-deepseek-r1/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-28T23:56:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Qwen3’s open-weight release under an accessible license marks an important milestone, lowering barriers for developers and organizations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carl Franzen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ex-OpenAI CEO and power users sound alarm over AI sycophancy and flattery of users]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3005850</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/ex-openai-ceo-and-power-users-sound-alarm-over-ai-sycophancy-and-flattery-of-users/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-28T21:49:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crucially, the turbulence also nudges many organizations to explore open-source models they can host, monitor, and fine-tune themselves.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carl Franzen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Beyond A2A and MCP: How LOKA’s Universal Agent Identity Layer changes the game]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3005824</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/beyond-a2a-and-mcp-how-lokas-universal-agent-identity-layer-changes-the-game/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-28T20:35:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The LOKA protocol, a proposed standard for AI agents from Carnegie Mellon University researchers, will give identities and intentions to agents.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Emilia David</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[30 seconds vs. 3: The d1 reasoning framework that’s slashing AI response times]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3005393</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/30-seconds-vs-3-the-d1-reasoning-framework-thats-slashing-ai-response-times/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-28T19:31:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[d1 framework changes boosts diffusion LLMs with novel reinforcement learning, unlocking efficient, problem-solving AI possibilities.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ben Dickson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Writer releases Palmyra X5, delivers near GPT-4.1 performance at 75% lower cost]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3005734</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/writer-releases-palmyra-x5-delivers-near-gpt-4-performance-at-75-lower-cost/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-28T17:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Writer unveils Palmyra X5: The enterprise AI model that processes 1,500 pages at once, costs 75% less than GPT-4, and enables affordable autonomous agents for businesses seeking automation ROI.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Nuñez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[QuickNode: Building the Infrastructure for the Next Generation of Blockchain]]></title>
        <id>6807d5787fb8500001c39b99</id>
        <link href="https://blog.quicknode.com/quicknode-building-the-infrastructure-for-the-next-generation-of-blockchain/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-28T16:02:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Join QuickNode co-founder Dmitry Shklovsky as he discusses blockchain infrastructure, building decentralized applications, and the future of Web3 development on TheCube's Crypto Trailblazer Series.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>QuickNode</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Does RAG make LLMs less safe?  Bloomberg research reveals hidden dangers]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3005592</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/does-rag-make-llms-less-safe-bloomberg-research-reveals-hidden-dangers/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-28T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[RAG is supposed to make enterprise AI more accurate, but it could potentially also make it less safe according to new research.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sean Michael Kerner</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[UPDATED] Malaysia and Maldives explore new ties in solar, defence, and digital tech [WATCH]]]></title>
        <id>2ff00997f9c35cff9b55bf1c234d9fd9</id>
        <link href="https://www.nst.com.my/news/nation/2025/04/1208426/updated-malaysia-and-maldives-explore-new-ties-solar-defence-and-digital"/>
        <updated>2025-04-28T04:17:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[PUTRAJAYA: Malaysia is eager to explore new avenues of cooperation with the Maldives, including floating solar energy, defence, and digital technology, says Datuk Seri Anwar Ibrahim.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hakim Mahari</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Is your AI product actually working? How to develop the right metric system]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3005642</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/is-your-ai-product-actually-working-how-to-develop-the-right-metric-system/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-27T19:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Metrics are critical for determining AI product performance. But where to begin? Here's a framework to apply across various use cases.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sharanya Rao</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bits + Bytes: A Miscellany Of Technology]]></title>
        <id>92c9e6ae0de9449f2a2cd9808d52c95a</id>
        <link href="https://theedgemalaysia.com/node/752832"/>
        <updated>2025-04-27T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[NEWS

Malaysia sees tech salary surge in 2025, led by system engineers

Tech salaries in Malaysia have risen significantly this year, with system engineers recording the highest increase at 8%, according to NodeFlair’s Tech Salary Report 2...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Edge Malaysia</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FORKLIFTACTION, B2B news service and business platform about forklifts and materials handling]]></title>
        <id>20065c212264065b824a3328d06be4fc</id>
        <link href="https://www.forkliftaction.com/pagenotfound.aspx"/>
        <updated>2025-04-27T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[FORKLIFTACTION, B2B news service and business platform about forklifts and materials handling]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Forkliftaction</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Malaysia remains 9th largest global exporter of high-tech products]]></title>
        <id>ec83e12fc9489689eba3a736f7c0fd4e</id>
        <link href="https://e.vnexpress.net/news/tech/tech-news/malaysia-remains-9th-largest-global-exporter-of-high-tech-products-4878750.html"/>
        <updated>2025-04-26T02:41:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Malaysia successfully maintained its position as the ninth-largest exporter of high-tech goods out of 143 economies in 2023, the highest recognition it has achieved in the past decade, Bernama has reported.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>VnExpress</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Malaysia remains 9th largest global exporter of high-tech products]]></title>
        <id>e1054193ac5220fd5f3cf3fb0ac3fcbd</id>
        <link href="https://en.vietnamplus.vn/malaysia-remains-9th-largest-global-exporter-of-high-tech-products-post318075.vnp"/>
        <updated>2025-04-25T18:11:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Malaysia’s high-tech exports increased by 2 billion USD to reach 127 billion USD in 2023. He said high-tech exports comprised 58.69% of total manufacturing exports in 2023, up from 52.48% recorded in 2022.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Vietnam+ (VietnamPlus)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[UK agrees to assist Malaysia in technology, new energy]]></title>
        <id>9bba1ab03b6cc59e6474a313d3bc9d9c</id>
        <link href="https://theedgemalaysia.com/node/753068"/>
        <updated>2025-04-25T15:31:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The UK has agreed to collaborate with Malaysia in various fields, including technology and new energy management, said Deputy Prime Minister Datuk Seri Fadillah Yusof.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Edge Malaysia</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Need to embrace technological advancements, sustainable practices discussed at country's premier real estate event]]></title>
        <id>13ba8e804fd9567fa951b4f7cc51bead</id>
        <link href="https://theedgemalaysia.com/node/753073"/>
        <updated>2025-04-25T12:00:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Industry leaders, policymakers, investors and experts explored the future of Malaysia's real estate landscape at the National Real Estate Convention (NREC) 2025 held here recently.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Edge Malaysia</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cooperations with China continue to drive Malaysia's tech ambitions: experts]]></title>
        <id>7cf31983f27357e33a7e7403d769042c</id>
        <link href="https://english.news.cn/20250423/23952d602d384abe9a3be2f40797fa2d/c.html"/>
        <updated>2025-04-23T09:33:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cooperations with China continue to drive Malaysia's tech ambitions: experts-]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>english.news.cn</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[IBM Tech Innovation Summit]]></title>
        <id>eb7b875c351e513c2d4750bb29a0ab40</id>
        <link href="https://www.malaysiakini.com/news/741130"/>
        <updated>2025-04-23T02:44:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Seats are limited. Register now!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Malaysiakini Team</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Alabama’s Pursell Agri-Tech teams with Wastech on fertilizer venture in Malaysia]]></title>
        <id>af0a46cec4f3cf8c521e3bd5a58cb6d6</id>
        <link href="https://www.madeinalabama.com/2025/04/alabamas-pursell-agri-tech-teams-with-wastech-on-fertilizer-venture-in-malaysia/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-21T18:21:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Pursell and Wastech Group are establishing a state-of-the-art facility in Malaysia to producte advanced controlled release fertilizers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jerry Underwood</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>