<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2025-06-13T21:43:47.347Z</id>
    <title>AngJianming RSS Feed</title>
    <updated>2025-06-13T21:43:47.347Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Building a Retro Console from Scratch (Part 2): Game Engine Foundations and Hardware Wrestling]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/calebgdm/building-a-retro-console-from-scratch-part-2-game-engine-foundations-and-hardware-wrestling-1n4a</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/calebgdm/building-a-retro-console-from-scratch-part-2-game-engine-foundations-and-hardware-wrestling-1n4a"/>
        <updated>2025-06-13T21:16:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[📌 TL;DR:
The anatomy of a bare-metal game loop
Input handling
Sprite animation system
Hardware deep dive: Why my breadboard looks like a spider's nest
👉 For those who missed: Part 1
When I first wired the SH1106 display, I faced a blank screen of judgment. The problem? I assumed all I2C OLEDs were created equal.
Hardware Truth Bombs:
Address Confusion: Some SH1106 use 0x3C, others 0x3D (mine needed a solder bridge change)
Voltage Sag: Running both screen and Pico from USB caused intermittent resets
OLED Connections

*(War Story Sidebar: "The 20ms Init Delay Mystery" - Recap your datasheet discovery from Part 1)

Current Minimalist Setup
buttons = {
            'A': Pin(17, Pin.IN, Pin.PULL_DOWN),
            'B': Pin(18, Pin.IN, Pin.PULL_DOWN),
            'UP': Pin(19, Pin.IN, Pin.PULL_…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Caleb García</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Step-by-Step Guide: Posts by Month in Bear Blog]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/yordiverkroost/step-by-step-guide-posts-by-month-in-bear-blog-4mda</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/yordiverkroost/step-by-step-guide-posts-by-month-in-bear-blog-4mda"/>
        <updated>2025-06-13T21:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The default list of all blog posts on Bear blog works fine, but can get quite long and a bit unorganized when you've blogged for a long time and posted a lot of content.
I wrote a plugin that organizes your posts a little more neatly by year and month. For example, if you wrote five posts in June 2025, a header for this month is added to the default blog posts page with those five post titles displayed below it.
If you only came here to add this custom feature to your own Bear blog, follow the steps below.
Copy the following script:

<script src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/froodooo/bear-plugins@0.0.44/bear/blog-posts.js"></script>

(See my bear-plugins GitHub repository for the latest release number)


From your Bear blog dashboard, click on your blog name, then on Settings, then on Heade…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yordi Verkroost</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing Sulka, the Hardened Yocto Distro]]></title>
        <id>https://ejaaskel.dev/introducing-sulka-the-hardened-yocto-distro/</id>
        <link href="https://ejaaskel.dev/introducing-sulka-the-hardened-yocto-distro/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-13T21:08:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Excel is used in real -World Data Analysis.]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/sumeya/how-excel-is-used-in-real-world-data-analysis-iic</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/sumeya/how-excel-is-used-in-real-world-data-analysis-iic"/>
        <updated>2025-06-13T21:08:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Excel is spreadsheet tool used for data entry, basic analysis and visualization. Excel is commonly used for quick data summaries , creating charts , and performing basic statistical operations .
Excel also helps businesses analyze historical data to identify trends and forecast future outcomes ,it also used to create budgets, profit and loss statements, and perform variance analysis and it also helps marketers track key performance indicators(KPI).
Since i started learning excel i have been able to learn about its features such as Pivot Table which is used for summarizing and analyzing large data sets for example a sales manager can use Pivot Tables to see total sales by region , or by product . Another feature is Conditional Formatting which is used in highlighting important data visually for example a teacher can use conditional formatting to highlight score difference in different colors. The other feature that i have learnt is VLOOKUP/XLOOKUP which is used to find and retrieve data from a table for example a HR manager can use XLOOKUP to find an employee's department or salary based on their ID number.
As someone who is a beginner in learning excel i could say that my view on excel has profoundly changed . I always saw excel just as mere numbers in boxes but now i see it more as a dynamic tool for analysis and decision-making. Before learning excel i used to think that handling large dataset as overwhelming but now i have learnt to organize and structure data efficiently using tables , sorting and filtering. I have also learnt about excel tools such as Pivot Table and charts, and i can now identify patterns and trends within data. Excel has also taught me that data isn't about just numbers; its tells a story. Through learning excel analysis tools are easier for me to use when i am performing complex analyses such as regression and ANOVA without needing advanced statistical software .]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>sumaya</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[.NET Moderno em Comunicação com MongoDB]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/daniloopinheiro/net-moderno-em-comunicacao-com-mongodb-29ma</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/daniloopinheiro/net-moderno-em-comunicacao-com-mongodb-29ma"/>
        <updated>2025-06-13T21:07:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A comunicação entre aplicações .NET modernas e o banco de dados MongoDB tornou-se mais robusta, escalável e produtiva com os avanços das versões recentes da plataforma .NET (como .NET 6, .NET 7 e .NET 8) e a evolução do próprio driver MongoDB para C#. Neste artigo, vamos explorar as melhores práticas, abordagens modernas e exemplos de código prático para integração entre C# e MongoDB.
MongoDB é um banco NoSQL orientado a documentos, que armazena dados em formato BSON (um tipo binário de JSON). Isso o torna extremamente flexível para aplicações que evoluem rapidamente, com requisitos de schema dinâmico.
Aliado ao C#, oferece:
Facilidade de serialização e deserialização com System.Text.Json ou Newtonsoft.Json

Performance em consultas assíncronas com async/await

Tipagem forte com POCOs (Pla…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Danilo O. Pinheiro, dopme.io</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DEPENDENCY INVERSION IS REALLY USEFUL?]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/yzpeedro/dependency-inversion-is-really-useful-3ag6</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/yzpeedro/dependency-inversion-is-really-useful-3ag6"/>
        <updated>2025-06-13T21:01:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction


You've probably heard of — or even use on a daily basis — libraries or applications in laravel that implement "dependency inversion", but have you ever taken the time to understand what it's actually for, or looked for the best way to apply it in your own project? in this article, we'll explore what dependency inversion is, why it matters, and the best ways to implement it in your laravel project.
dependency inversion is a fundamental software design principle that aims to increase code flexibility and maintainability. in short, it suggests that high-level classes should not depend directly on low-level classes — instead, both should depend on abstractions.
but what does that actually mean in practice?
imagine the following scenario: we have an application where one of the c…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pedro Pessoa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Former Blockchain exec joins SEC as director of trading and markets]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/former-blockchain-exec-joins-sec</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/former-blockchain-exec-joins-sec?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-06-13T20:55:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The former global head of institutional markets for Blockchain.com and a partner at a Washington, DC-based law firm will be the latest additions to SEC staff.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Turner Wright</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mumps (Programming Language)]]></title>
        <id>https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/MUMPS</id>
        <link href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/MUMPS"/>
        <updated>2025-06-13T20:52:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Troubleshooting AI: How to Fix Bad AI-Generated Responses]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/mikuiwai/troubleshooting-ai-how-to-fix-bad-ai-generated-responses-44od</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/mikuiwai/troubleshooting-ai-how-to-fix-bad-ai-generated-responses-44od"/>
        <updated>2025-06-13T20:49:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You've dived into the world of AI, filled with promises of efficiency and innovation. You craft a prompt, hit enter, and... the response is a dud. Generic, off-topic, repetitive, or just plain bland. It's easy to feel frustrated, perhaps even betrayed by the hype. But before you write off AI as another overblown trend, consider this: the "bad" response isn't always the AI's fault. More often than not, it's a symptom of a conversation gone awry, a signal that your instructions weren't quite clear enough.
Think of AI not as a magic genie, but as an incredibly fast, highly literal intern. It can process vast amounts of information and generate text at lightning speed, but it lacks inherent understanding, intuition, or the ability to read between the lines. It relies entirely on the quality of…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>miku iwai</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Optimizing Cybersecurity: Integrating Lean Six Sigma with Risk Assessment and Infrastructure Management]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/robertpurpose/optimizing-cybersecurity-integrating-lean-six-sigma-with-risk-assessment-and-infrastructure-12gb</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/robertpurpose/optimizing-cybersecurity-integrating-lean-six-sigma-with-risk-assessment-and-infrastructure-12gb"/>
        <updated>2025-06-13T20:47:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In today's evolving threat landscape, cybersecurity is no longer a siloed IT function - it is a critical pillar of enterprise resilience and business continuity. As organizations strive to improve their risk posture, reduce vulnerabilities, and align with regulatory frameworks, there's an urgent need to move beyond reactive defense models. This is where Lean Six Sigma (LSS) - a methodology rooted in process improvement and waste reduction - becomes a powerful ally in strengthening cybersecurity infrastructure through disciplined risk assessment and management.
The Intersection of Cybersecurity and Lean Six Sigma
DMAIC Meets Cyber Risk Assessment
Eliminating Cyber Waste: Lean Thinking in Action
Lean thinking encourages security teams to identify and remove these non-value-adding elements. By applying Value Stream Mapping (VSM), organizations can visualize every step in the cyber defense lifecycle - from threat detection to response - and optimize it for speed, accuracy, and compliance.
Quantifying Risk Like a Black Belt
By treating risk management as a process improvement problem, cybersecurity teams can shift from static compliance checklists to dynamic, metrics-driven governance.
Success Story: Lean Cybersecurity in Practice
The result? A 38% reduction in provisioning time, fewer audit flags, and a stronger control environment that aligns with both NIST 800–171 and CMMC practices.
Conclusion: The Future is Lean and Secure
About the Author
Dr. Robert A. Morgan, MSc is a Senior Cyber Security Software Engineer, and cybersecurity strategist.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Robert A. Morgan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learning Web3 From the Ground Up: Understanding Selective Disclosure]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/devsofmidnight/learning-web3-from-the-ground-up-understanding-selective-disclosure-4n7</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/devsofmidnight/learning-web3-from-the-ground-up-understanding-selective-disclosure-4n7"/>
        <updated>2025-06-13T20:44:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As I delve deeper into the world of Web3, I've been working my way through foundational concepts to have a better understanding of the industry (check out my last five posts on the Midnight Dev Diaries!). This week, I dove into one of the most practical and privacy-focused ideas I’ve encountered so far: selective disclosure.
Selective disclosure is more than just a technical feature—it’s the working expression of a broader idea known as rational privacy. It allows individuals to prove or reveal only what’s necessary in a given interaction, keeping everything else private. In an ecosystem where trust must be earned without a central authority, this ability to protect personal data while still meeting legal or operational requirements is critical.
This post examines how selective disclosure …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Samantha Holstine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Iterative Prompting: How to Refine AI Outputs with Follow-Up Questions]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/mikuiwai/iterative-prompting-how-to-refine-ai-outputs-with-follow-up-questions-4f8d</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/mikuiwai/iterative-prompting-how-to-refine-ai-outputs-with-follow-up-questions-4f8d"/>
        <updated>2025-06-13T20:41:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You’ve probably felt the frustration: hitting 'generate' on your AI tool and getting something… almost right. It’s bland, off-brand, or just plain doesn't sing. In the fast-paced world of marketing, where every word, every headline, and every call-to-action directly impacts your conversion rates, "almost right" simply isn't good enough. Generic AI outputs don’t build trust, they don't capture attention, and they certainly don't drive sales.
So, how do you bridge the gap between basic AI output and high-converting marketing gold? The answer lies in mastering a powerful technique: iterative prompting.
Think of your AI as a brilliant but sometimes naive junior copywriter. You wouldn't hand them a single instruction and expect a perfect, final draft of a sales page. You'd review their work, of…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>miku iwai</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Title: Passwordless Authentication ROI: TCO & Implementation Guide for Devs]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/deepakgupta/title-passwordless-authentication-roi-tco-implementation-guide-for-devs-2o8k</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/deepakgupta/title-passwordless-authentication-roi-tco-implementation-guide-for-devs-2o8k"/>
        <updated>2025-06-13T20:41:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[TL;DR

This article breaks down the total cost of ownership (TCO) for authentication methods, with a developer’s view on implementing passwordless authentication. We’ll cover cost frameworks, technical trade-offs, sample integration code, and practical advice for SaaS and enterprise environments.
Introduction: The Real Cost of Authentication
Technical Context: Why Devs Should Care
Cost Breakdown: Hidden vs. Visible Expenses
Password vs. MFA vs. Passwordless: A Developer’s Comparison
Passwordless Implementation: Key Technical Details
Code Samples: WebAuthn, Biometrics, and More
Technical Challenges and Solutions
Discussion Point
Conclusion & Resources
Most developers know authentication is essential, but few realize how much it impacts the bottom line. When CTOs and CISOs look at authentica…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Deepak Gupta</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Using AI Personas to Generate Creative Marketing Angles]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/mikuiwai/using-ai-personas-to-generate-creative-marketing-angles-2c64</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/mikuiwai/using-ai-personas-to-generate-creative-marketing-angles-2c64"/>
        <updated>2025-06-13T20:40:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a landscape saturated with messaging, the quest for a marketing angle that genuinely resonates feels increasingly like searching for a needle in a haystack. We churn out content, craft ads, and launch campaigns, often to find our efforts dissolving into the digital ether, indistinguishable from the noise. The conventional wisdom of "know your audience" is foundational, yet relying solely on broad demographic data or static, idealized customer profiles often leads to generic campaigns that miss the mark.
What if there was a way to dive deeper, to virtually sit across from your ideal customer, understand their nuanced world, and tap into their unspoken desires and frustrations? This isn't a hypothetical anymore. Welcome to the era of AI-powered personas, a revolutionary approach that does…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>miku iwai</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin price breakout to $119K possible if oil rally pattern holds]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-price-rebound-oil-rally-setup-119k-target</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-price-rebound-oil-rally-setup-119k-target?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-06-13T20:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Data shows that Bitcoin's price gained at least 16% within a week of sharp oil price rallies.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Marcel Pechman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Anne Wojcicki Wins Bidding for 23andMe]]></title>
        <id>https://www.wsj.com/tech/biotech/anne-wojcicki-wins-bidding-for-23andme-92dcfd5b</id>
        <link href="https://www.wsj.com/tech/biotech/anne-wojcicki-wins-bidding-for-23andme-92dcfd5b"/>
        <updated>2025-06-13T20:31:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[There’s Nothing Introductory About RRC’s Game Dev Program — And That’s the Real Problem]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/formantaudio/theres-nothing-introductory-about-rrcs-game-dev-program-and-thats-the-real-problem-37fj</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/formantaudio/theres-nothing-introductory-about-rrcs-game-dev-program-and-thats-the-real-problem-37fj"/>
        <updated>2025-06-13T20:31:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When I applied to Red River College’s Game Development – Programming Advanced Diploma, I assumed the program, while competitive, would at least be fair. I also assumed the selection process would be clear.
Neither turned out to be true.
🎯 The Reality
Despite how it’s marketed — with vague admissions language like “good programming fundamentals” and “interest in game development” — this is a post-secondary filtered selection system.
The actual requirements, whether stated outright or not, demand:
Second-year university-level Java knowledge
Unity game engine experience
Real-time game logic and architecture
2D/3D animation systems
Authentication and backend security
Math for games and applied system logic
Project documentation, version control, and production pipelines
That’s not “introducto…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tyler Johnston-Kent</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SEC, Ripple file motion to release $125M in escrow as case winds down]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/sec-ripple-motion-release-125-million-case-winds-down</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/sec-ripple-motion-release-125-million-case-winds-down?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-06-13T20:16:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The lawsuit against Ripple, filed by the United States Securities and Exchange Commission in December 2020, is finally wrapping up.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Vince Quill</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The case for embedding audit trails in AI systems before scaling]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3011858</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/the-case-for-embedding-audit-trails-in-ai-systems-before-scaling/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-13T20:13:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With more AI applications and agents going into production, enterprises need robust and auditable AI pipelines more than ever.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Emilia David</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Apple's Liquid Glass is prep work for AR interfaces, not just a design refresh]]></title>
        <id>https://omc345.substack.com/p/from-skeuomorphic-to-liquid-glass</id>
        <link href="https://omc345.substack.com/p/from-skeuomorphic-to-liquid-glass"/>
        <updated>2025-06-13T19:44:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin flash crash presents prime buy opportunity if historic pattern repeats]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-flash-crash-presents-prime-buy-opportunity-if-historic-pattern-repeats</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-flash-crash-presents-prime-buy-opportunity-if-historic-pattern-repeats?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-06-13T19:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin’s flash crash could be followed by a 64% rally if historical data rings true again.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Biraajmaan Tamuly</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum Foundation pledges $500K to Roman Storm’s defense]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/ethereum-foundation-donation-roman-storm-defense</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/ethereum-foundation-donation-roman-storm-defense?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-06-13T19:25:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Roughly two years after the initial indictment, the Tornado Cash developer’s criminal trial is expected to begin on July 14.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Turner Wright</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Here’s what happened in crypto today]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/what-happened-in-crypto-today</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/what-happened-in-crypto-today?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-06-13T19:18:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Need to know what happened in crypto today? Here is the latest news on daily trends and events impacting Bitcoin price, blockchain, DeFi, NFTs, Web3 and crypto regulation.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Cointelegraph</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Self-Adapting Language Models]]></title>
        <id>https://arxiv.org/abs/2506.10943</id>
        <link href="https://arxiv.org/abs/2506.10943"/>
        <updated>2025-06-13T19:03:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Simulink (Matlab) Copilot]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/Kaamuli/Bloxi</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/Kaamuli/Bloxi"/>
        <updated>2025-06-13T18:58:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Claude Bliss Attractor]]></title>
        <id>https://www.astralcodexten.com/p/the-claude-bliss-attractor</id>
        <link href="https://www.astralcodexten.com/p/the-claude-bliss-attractor"/>
        <updated>2025-06-13T18:55:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Bounces to $106K After Iran-Israel Jitters, but Analysts Warn of Deeper Pullback]]></title>
        <id>2ef87929-6fbb-4457-b7fa-e0567d6f70b5</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/06/13/bitcoin-bounces-to-106k-after-iran-israel-jitters-but-analysts-warn-of-deeper-pullback"/>
        <updated>2025-06-13T18:52:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Circle is up 13% on news that Amazon and Walmart are moving into stablecoins.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Krisztian Sandor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Circle’s NYSE debut marks start of crypto IPO season: Are Kraken, Gemini and Bullish next?]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/crypto-ipos-circle-gemini-kraken-wall-street-2025</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/crypto-ipos-circle-gemini-kraken-wall-street-2025?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-06-13T18:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto IPO season is underway. Circle’s explosive debut has fueled filings from Gemini and Bullish, with Kraken, BitGo, and Consensys potentially next.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Marie Poteriaieva</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Biz: Meta’s AI bet, Fortune 500’s stablecoin push]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/stablecoins-meta-ai-scale-ripple-crypto-biz</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/stablecoins-meta-ai-scale-ripple-crypto-biz?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-06-13T18:31:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mark Zuckerberg bets $15 billion on an AI company as stablecoins win over Fortune 500 companies.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Sam Bourgi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Radio pulses detected coming from ice in Antarctica]]></title>
        <id>https://www.psu.edu/news/research/story/strange-radio-pulses-detected-coming-ice-antarctica#</id>
        <link href="https://www.psu.edu/news/research/story/strange-radio-pulses-detected-coming-ice-antarctica#"/>
        <updated>2025-06-13T18:30:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SUI Drops 10% to $3.02, but Is a Turnaround Forming After Buyers Step In Near $3?]]></title>
        <id>01445cbe-8f76-4b8a-ac8d-58b640fa7c49</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/06/13/sui-drops-10-to-usd3-02-but-is-a-turnaround-forming-after-buyers-step-in-near-usd3"/>
        <updated>2025-06-13T18:05:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SUI plunged nearly 13% before stabilizing above $3 as high-volume sell pressure gave way to cautious dip buying.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Siamak Masnavi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[I convinced HP's board to buy Palm and watched them kill it]]></title>
        <id>https://philmckinney.substack.com/p/i-convinced-hps-board-to-buy-palm</id>
        <link href="https://philmckinney.substack.com/p/i-convinced-hps-board-to-buy-palm"/>
        <updated>2025-06-13T18:03:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Saylor says Bitcoin could fix Apple’s stock buybacks: Finance Redefined]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/saylor-bitcoin-fix-apple-stock-buybacks-finance-redefined</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/saylor-bitcoin-fix-apple-stock-buybacks-finance-redefined?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-06-13T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin exposure may provide more shareholder value to Apple investors, as the tech firm’s stock is struggling to reverse a downtrend.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Zoltan Vardai</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Weekly Recap: Milestones Galore for Stablecoins]]></title>
        <id>c16822b7-82a2-449f-bbc9-9f488bfce38f</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/news-analysis/2025/06/13/weekly-recap-milestones-galore-for-stablecoins"/>
        <updated>2025-06-13T17:49:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Walmart and Amazon are both considering issuing stablecoins, potentially revolutionizing payments.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Benjamin Schiller</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Solana's SOL Falls 8% to $147 Despite Standard Chartered’s $275 Year-End Target]]></title>
        <id>cc9710c7-c958-4e14-b7e6-98ad5d827709</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/06/13/solana-s-sol-falls-8-to-usd147-despite-standard-chartered-s-usd275-year-end-target"/>
        <updated>2025-06-13T17:46:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Solana’s SOL sharp pullback contrasts with Standard Chartered’s late-May forecast calling for nearly 90% upside by the end of the year.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Siamak Masnavi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Price predictions 6/13: BTC, ETH, XRP, BNB, SOL, DOGE, ADA, HYPE, SUI, LINK]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/price-predictions-6-13-btc-eth-xrp-bnb-sol-doge-ada-hype-sui-link</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/price-predictions-6-13-btc-eth-xrp-bnb-sol-doge-ada-hype-sui-link?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-06-13T17:39:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dip buyers stepped in to absorb this week’s downside in Bitcoin and select altcoins.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Rakesh Upadhyay</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build a Medical Chatbot with Flutter and Gemini: A Beginner’s Guide]]></title>
        <id>684c61db3b494a20ba49fddb</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-build-a-medical-chatbot-with-flutter-and-gemini/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-13T17:37:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In today's digital age, the demand for accessible and accurate health information is higher than ever. Leveraging the power of artificial intelligence, we can create intelligent chatbots that provide reliable health-related guidance. This beginner's ...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Atuoha Anthony</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Using computers more freely and safely (2023)]]></title>
        <id>https://akkartik.name/freewheeling/</id>
        <link href="https://akkartik.name/freewheeling/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-13T17:27:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Closing Strait of Hormuz is biggest risk to BTC price this weekend — Analyst]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/closing-strait-hormuz-biggest-risk-btc-price-weekend</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/closing-strait-hormuz-biggest-risk-btc-price-weekend?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-06-13T17:08:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Risk assets would take a significant hit if Iran closes the Strait of Hormuz, a narrow waterway supplying 20% of the global oil trade.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Vince Quill</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ADA Drops 6% as Cardano Community Debates $100M Stablecoin Liquidity Proposal]]></title>
        <id>e4ddd530-7f7c-472e-8cfc-fbe5a7ef7950</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/06/13/ada-drops-6-as-cardano-community-debates-usd100m-stablecoin-liquidity-proposal"/>
        <updated>2025-06-13T17:05:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cardano's ADA token dipped more than 6% as Charles Hoskinson defended a proposal to deploy 140M ADA from the treasury to kick-start stablecoin liquidity.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Siamak Masnavi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Vue Composables Work – Explained with Code Examples]]></title>
        <id>684c58453ee20021234073af</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-vue-composables-work/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-13T16:56:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Vue composables are a very helpful tool when developing Vue applications. They give developers an easy way to reuse logic across our applications. In addition to allowing for “stateless” logic (things like formatting or routine calculations), composa...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brian Barrow</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[When random people give money to random other people (2017)]]></title>
        <id>https://quomodocumque.wordpress.com/2017/06/27/when-random-people-give-money-to-random-other-people/</id>
        <link href="https://quomodocumque.wordpress.com/2017/06/27/when-random-people-give-money-to-random-other-people/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-13T16:49:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Improve Your Phone’s Privacy]]></title>
        <id>684c50b9c6ec6bf605276b54</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-improve-your-phones-privacy/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-13T16:24:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We use our phones for everything  –  texting, banking, browsing, tracking our health, even unlocking our homes. But with all that convenience comes a lot of risk. Apps are hungry for your data. Hackers are always looking for cracks in your security. ...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Manish Shivanandhan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NEAR Protocol Surges 4% After 12.8% Correction, User Growth Shines]]></title>
        <id>ac02cff0-a1fb-40b7-b088-5d7c44f579ac</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/06/13/near-protocol-surges-4-after-12-8-correction-user-growth-shines"/>
        <updated>2025-06-13T16:19:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Despite recent price struggles, NEAR Protocol becomes second most used L1 blockchain with 46 million monthly active users, signaling strong fundamentals amid market volatility.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Oliver Knight</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ATOM Tumbles 9% as Crypto Market Plunges Amid Middle East Tensions]]></title>
        <id>66633d67-ce8f-4fc9-8e0b-4b0764d4de68</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/06/13/atom-tumbles-9-as-crypto-market-plunges-amid-middle-east-tensions"/>
        <updated>2025-06-13T16:12:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new support zone has been established, suggesting a short-term bottom.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Oliver Knight</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SharpLink Acquires $463M in Ether, Shares Remain 66% Lower]]></title>
        <id>8b09a36e-8aff-48e8-a329-b3ab660fe65f</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2025/06/13/sharplink-acquires-463m-in-ether-shares-remain-66-lower"/>
        <updated>2025-06-13T16:05:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The purchase announcement did little to the stock, which tumbled 70% on a late Thursday filing that allowed investors to sell shares.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Krisztian Sandor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[UNI Drops Hard After V-Shaped Rebound Fizzles Amid Mounting Middle East Tension]]></title>
        <id>b6101246-32d2-4684-94c0-a91db2e518f8</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/06/13/uni-drops-hard-after-v-shaped-rebound-fizzles-amid-mounting-middle-east-tension"/>
        <updated>2025-06-13T15:54:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Uniswap (UNI) reversed steep losses after a flash crash but slipped again as Trump warned of “more brutal” strikes against Iran.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Siamak Masnavi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to legally stake crypto in 2025: What is now allowed after the SEC’s latest move]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/how-to-legally-stake-crypto</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/how-to-legally-stake-crypto?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-06-13T15:51:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The SEC’s 2025 guideline clarifies the regulatory stance regarding crypto staking. It states what is and isn’t allowed and how you can stake lawfully.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Dilip Kumar Patairya</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto legislation in the US is at a ‘critical’ juncture, says industry exec]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/crypto-legislation-deadline-2026-marta-belcher-warning</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/crypto-legislation-deadline-2026-marta-belcher-warning?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-06-13T15:48:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The latest episode of Decentralize with Cointelegraph unpacks why US crypto legislation must pass in 2025 or risk renewed crackdowns and political blowback.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Savannah Fortis</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Panic or opportunity? What crypto capitulation tells smart investors]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/what-is-crypto-market-capitulation-and-its-significance</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/what-is-crypto-market-capitulation-and-its-significance?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-06-13T15:34:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto market capitulation refers to a point of extreme selling pressure when investors panic and sell off assets, often marking the bottom of a market cycle.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Onkar Singh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin clings to $105K as opinions diverge on oil price outlook]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-clings-to-105k-opinions-diverge-oil-price-outlook</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-clings-to-105k-opinions-diverge-oil-price-outlook?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-06-13T15:32:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Oil price talk leads macro analysis amid Middle East tensions, but whether Bitcoin will suffer as a result is up for debate as traders see a BTC price comeback.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by William Suberg</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[America’s Dollar Dominance Depends on GENIUS]]></title>
        <id>54bacf35-7689-43e3-9788-3da88c7144ca</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/opinion/2025/06/13/americas-dollar-dominance-depends-on-genius"/>
        <updated>2025-06-13T15:32:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This week's vote on stablecoin legislation ensures that finance will continue to be dollar-denominated and governed by American values, says Kristin Smith.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kristin Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[US Senate to vote on amended stablecoin bill on June 17]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/senate-amended-stablecoin-bill-vote</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/senate-amended-stablecoin-bill-vote?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-06-13T15:24:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Though concerns about the Trump family’s connections to World Liberty Financial’s stablecoin shadowed debate on the GENIUS Act, the bill is closer to passing the Senate.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Turner Wright</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Positive U.S. Regulatory Environment More Conducive for Crypto Corporate Activity: JPMorgan]]></title>
        <id>807f9f0c-6662-4c44-a78d-c0e22b1099b8</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/06/13/positive-us-regulatory-environment-more-conducive-for-crypto-corporate-activity-jpmorgan"/>
        <updated>2025-06-13T15:20:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The number of crypto IPOs year-to-date matches the pace of offerings seen in the bull market of 2021, the report said.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Will Canny</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AVAX Plunges 13% as Crypto Sinks on Rise in Mideast Tensions]]></title>
        <id>f5a5855f-5b26-4938-a579-c2c4b72370a0</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/06/13/avax-plunges-13-as-crypto-sinks-on-rise-in-mideast-tensions"/>
        <updated>2025-06-13T15:17:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Avalanche's native token faces significant selling pressure, though buyers have emerged at a key short-term support level.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CD Analytics</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Hat, the Spectre and SAT Solvers (2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nhatcher.com/post/on-hats-and-sats/</id>
        <link href="https://www.nhatcher.com/post/on-hats-and-sats/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-13T15:14:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Luxe Game Engine]]></title>
        <id>https://luxeengine.com/</id>
        <link href="https://luxeengine.com/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-13T15:12:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ETF filings explode in 2025, heating hopes of an ‘altcoin summer’]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/etf-filings-2025-altcoin-summer</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/etf-filings-2025-altcoin-summer?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-06-13T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This year has seen an uptick in the number of altcoin ETF applications, with at least 31 filed in the first half of 2025, Cointelegraph Research found.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Aaron Wood</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blockchain is the missing trust layer in sports analytics]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/blockchain-sports-analytics</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/blockchain-sports-analytics?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-06-13T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Blockchain can reshape sports analytics as a secure, open and verifiable source of truth for performance data. From elite leagues to fantasy sports, blockchain breaks down data silos, ensures real-time accuracy and embeds trust in the sports ecosystem.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Tristan Thompson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Senator’s RISE Act would require AI developers to list training data, evaluation methods in exchange for ‘safe harbor’ from lawsuits]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3012021</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/senators-rise-act-would-require-ai-developers-to-list-training-data-evaluation-methods-in-exchange-for-safe-harbor-from-lawsuits/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-13T14:59:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The developer must also publish known failure modes, keep all documentation current, and push updates within 30 days of a version change.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carl Franzen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TON Down 8% After Israeli Strikes Against Iran]]></title>
        <id>b7e02720-22c6-4788-a24b-aa6a81ed8dd7</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/06/13/ton-down-8-after-israeli-strikes-against-iran"/>
        <updated>2025-06-13T14:53:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Though sharply lower, TON is showing signs of stabilization, according to the charts.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CD Analytics</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How a YouTuber hacked an $800K crypto scam hub in Cebu, Philippines]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/explained/how-a-youtuber-hacked-an-800k-crypto-scam-hub-in-cebu-philippines</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/explained/how-a-youtuber-hacked-an-800k-crypto-scam-hub-in-cebu-philippines?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-06-13T14:50:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A YouTuber exposed an $800,000 crypto scam in Cebu by hacking CCTV, confronting scammers live and revealing their global fraud operation.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Dilip Kumar Patairya</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[100 years of Zermelo's axiom of choice: What was the problem with it? (2006)]]></title>
        <id>https://research.mietek.io/mi.MartinLof2006.html</id>
        <link href="https://research.mietek.io/mi.MartinLof2006.html"/>
        <updated>2025-06-13T14:46:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brazilian Firm Meliuz's Shares Fall After Planning to Raise $32.4M to Buy Bitcoin]]></title>
        <id>8991ea1a-8d0c-466f-95d2-f40ec2454ba6</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/06/13/brazilian-firm-meliuzs-shares-fall-after-planning-to-raise-324m-to-buy-bitcoin"/>
        <updated>2025-06-13T14:43:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The fintech company strengthened its crypto strategy with a discounted share offering and a bitcoin acquisition plan.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>James Van Straten</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OxCaml - a set of extensions to the OCaml programming language.]]></title>
        <id>https://oxcaml.org/</id>
        <link href="https://oxcaml.org/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-13T14:20:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Miners Just Had One of Their Best Quarters on Record, JPMorgan Says]]></title>
        <id>228fa5e4-d1e7-4daa-ac3a-43d22cfbd786</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/06/13/bitcoin-miners-just-had-one-of-their-best-quarters-on-record-jpmorgan-says"/>
        <updated>2025-06-13T14:15:50.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Will Canny</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Powering next-gen services with AI in regulated industries]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1118600</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/06/13/1118600/powering-next-gen-services-with-ai-in-regulated-industries/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-13T14:09:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Businesses in highly-regulated industries like financial services, insurance, pharmaceuticals, and health care are increasingly turning to AI-powered tools to streamline complex and sensitive tasks. Conversational AI-driven interfaces are helping hospitals to track the location and delivery of a patient’s time-sensitive cancer drugs. Generative AI chatbots are helping insurance customers answer questions and solve problems. And agentic…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>MIT Technology Review Insights</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Show HN: Tattoy – a text-based terminal compositor]]></title>
        <id>https://tattoy.sh/</id>
        <link href="https://tattoy.sh/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-13T14:04:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SharpLink buys $463M in ETH, becomes largest public ETH holder]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/sharplink-largest-public-eth-holder-463m</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/sharplink-largest-public-eth-holder-463m?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-06-13T13:54:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While SharpLink has become the largest publicly traded holder of Ether globally, some entities, including the Ethereum Foundation and BlackRock, are still holding more ETH.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Helen Partz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ask HN: How do I give back to people helped me when I was young and had nothing?]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=44268448</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=44268448"/>
        <updated>2025-06-13T13:42:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Geometry from Quantum Temporal Correlations]]></title>
        <id>https://arxiv.org/abs/2502.13293</id>
        <link href="https://arxiv.org/abs/2502.13293"/>
        <updated>2025-06-13T13:21:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CoinDesk 20 Performance Update: Bitcoin Price (BTC) Falls 2.2% as All Assets Decline]]></title>
        <id>2ab7cd91-98b8-4822-a362-653a44a0e9b6</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/coindesk-indices/2025/06/13/coindesk-20-performance-update-bitcoin-price-btc-falls-2-2-as-all-assets-decline"/>
        <updated>2025-06-13T13:18:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ripple (XRP) also traded lower from Thursday, declining 2.9%.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CoinDesk Indices</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Miner Price Targets Raised to Reflect Improved Industry Economics: JPMorgan]]></title>
        <id>8b0c52ca-0dd8-4981-91eb-13c148ca00d4</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/06/13/bitcoin-miner-price-targets-raised-to-reflect-improved-industry-economics-jpmorgan"/>
        <updated>2025-06-13T13:10:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The bank increased its CleanSpark, Riot Platforms and MARA Holdings price targets.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Will Canny</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meta invests $14.3B in Scale AI to kick-start superintelligence lab]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nytimes.com/2025/06/12/technology/meta-scale-ai.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.nytimes.com/2025/06/12/technology/meta-scale-ai.html"/>
        <updated>2025-06-13T13:09:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cardano's Charles Hoskinson Suggests Swapping $100M of ADA for Bitcoin, Stablecoins]]></title>
        <id>7474cf5a-8ced-4646-b48d-0bf02a98f1f6</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2025/06/13/cardano-s-charles-hoskinson-proposes-selling-usd100m-of-ada-to-kickstart-defi"/>
        <updated>2025-06-13T13:04:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The proposal appears at to be at odds with previous comments from Cardano Foundation CEO Frederik Gregaard.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Oliver Knight</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Red team AI now to build safer, smarter models tomorrow]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3010828</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/security/red-team-ai-now-to-build-safer-smarter-models-tomorrow/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-13T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AI models are under attack. Traditional defenses are failing. Discover why red teaming is crucial for thwarting adversarial threats.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Louis Columbus</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Download: gambling with humanity’s future, and the FDA under Trump]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1118731</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/06/13/1118731/the-download-gambling-with-humanitys-future-and-the-fda-under-trump/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-13T12:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is today’s edition of The Download, our weekday newsletter that provides a daily dose of what’s going on in the world of technology. Tech billionaires are making a risky bet with humanity’s future Sam Altman, Jeff Bezos, Elon Musk, and others may have slightly different goals, but their grand visions for the next decade and beyond…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rhiannon Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to use Grok for real-time crypto trading signals]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/how-to-use-grok-for-crypto-trading</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/how-to-use-grok-for-crypto-trading?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-06-13T12:07:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Grok scans posts and sentiment shifts on X to help crypto traders identify early signals, memes and macro-driven momentum plays.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Callum Reid</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kyber (YC W23) Is Hiring a Technical Account Manager]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ycombinator.com/companies/kyber/jobs/5kSq3Jd-technical-account-manager-tam</id>
        <link href="https://www.ycombinator.com/companies/kyber/jobs/5kSq3Jd-technical-account-manager-tam"/>
        <updated>2025-06-13T12:01:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BlackRock quietly accumulated 3% of all Bitcoin. Here’s what that means]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/explained/blackrock-quietly-accumulated-3-of-all-bitcoin-heres-what-that-means</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/explained/blackrock-quietly-accumulated-3-of-all-bitcoin-heres-what-that-means?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-06-13T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How Much Bitcoin Does BlackRock Own and Why It Matters in 2025.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Bradley Peak</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin mirrors 80% rally setup that preceded 2024 Israel-Iran conflict]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-mirrors-80-rally-setup-that-preceded-2024-israel-iran-conflict</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-mirrors-80-rally-setup-that-preceded-2024-israel-iran-conflict?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-06-13T11:58:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One analyst spots a bullish fractal driven by 2024-like liquidity grabs, hinting that Bitcoin may breakout toward new all-time highs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Yashu Gola</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tencent Is Looking to Buy Nexon, the Creator of Web 3 Gaming Franchise MapleStory]]></title>
        <id>b9705177-2bf3-4e0c-afc1-96cad2a4c8b6</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/web3/2025/06/13/tencent-is-looking-to-buy-nexon-the-creator-of-web-3-gaming-franchise-maplestory"/>
        <updated>2025-06-13T11:54:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The deal could help Tencent secure long-term control over popular intellectual property and expand its presence in the South Korean gaming market.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Francisco Rodrigues</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ether Plunges 7% as Traders Flee to Dollar and Gold After Israel Strikes Iran]]></title>
        <id>206eff62-41fa-442e-9f3e-08c51aec5ce0</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/06/13/ether-drops-below-usd2-550-as-israel-iran-escalation-sparks-flight-to-safety"/>
        <updated>2025-06-13T11:39:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ether plunged to a 10-day low as investors rushed into the dollar and gold following Israeli airstrikes on Iran.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Siamak Masnavi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Daybook Americas: Bitcoin Weathers Market Rout as Israel Hits Iran]]></title>
        <id>28284aed-c507-4387-bad5-0a928bc5a561</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/daybook-us/2025/06/13/crypto-daybook-americas-bitcoin-weathers-market-rout-as-israel-hits-iran"/>
        <updated>2025-06-13T11:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Your day-ahead look for June 13, 2025]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Francisco Rodrigues</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin 2025 builders predict DeFi will unseat traditional finance]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-2025-defi-traditional-finance</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-2025-defi-traditional-finance?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-06-13T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin’s foundational security is powering a new frontier: DeFi systems built on self-sovereignty, security and real-world financial inclusion.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Michael Tabone</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Walmart, Amazon Mull Dollar-Pegged Stablecoins in the U.S.: WSJ]]></title>
        <id>26bdd8ee-2514-4004-bfb7-b22c4d1ff772</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/06/13/walmart-amazon-mull-dollar-pegged-stablecoins-in-the-us-wsj"/>
        <updated>2025-06-13T10:53:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Wall Street Journal reported that the retail giants are exploring digital currencies to bypass card fees and banks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>James Van Straten</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Anthony Pompliano to lead new Bitcoin-buying group raising $750M: FT]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/anthony-pompliano-lead-bitcoin-buying-vehicle-raise-750-million-ft</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/anthony-pompliano-lead-bitcoin-buying-vehicle-raise-750-million-ft?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-06-13T10:50:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Under Pompliano’s leadership, ProCapBTC would reportedly seek to raise $750 million in equity and convertible debt as part of a merger with Columbus Circle Capital 1.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Helen Partz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NVIDIA GeForce RTX 5050 Allegedly Getting 20Gbps GDDR6 Memory]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=355850</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/355850/nvidia-rtx-5050-gddr6-20gbps/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-13T10:38:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[NVIDIA is reportedly steamrolling ahead with its plans of getting the GeForce RTX 5050 out by this July. Recently, a rumour from a prominent leakster suggests that the entry-level GPU will not be using GDDR7, but GDDR6 memory. More specifically, and according to MEGASizeGPU, the RTX 5050 could end up being fitted with GDDR6 that […]
The post NVIDIA GeForce RTX 5050 Allegedly Getting 20Gbps GDDR6 Memory appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John Law</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mavcom Urges Affected Malaysian Passengers To Act Ahead of Jetstar Asia’s Closure]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=355860</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/355860/mavcom-jetstar-asia-closure-passenger-advisory/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-13T10:36:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Malaysian Aviation Commission (Mavcom) has issued an advisory for consumers affected by the upcoming shutdown of Jetstar Asia Airways, urging them to take prompt action. The airline, a Singapore-based low-cost carrier under the Jetstar Group, is scheduled to cease operations on 31 July 2025. Jetstar Asia’s closure follows a decision announced by Australia’s Qantas […]
The post Mavcom Urges Affected Malaysian Passengers To Act Ahead of Jetstar Asia’s Closure appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Heirul Kamel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Neta Auto Reportedly Files For Bankruptcy Reorganisation]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=355852</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/355852/neta-auto-files-for-bankruptcy-reorganisation/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-13T10:32:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Chinese automaker Neta appears to be facing mounting challenges. According to a report by Car China News, the company is set to start bankruptcy reorganisation proceedings. This development follows the circulation of a video on social media showing employees confronting Neta’s chairman, Fang Yunzhou, over overdue wages at the company’s new Shanghai office. These financial […]
The post Neta Auto Reportedly Files For Bankruptcy Reorganisation appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Keran</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Walmart, Amazon consider issuing own stablecoins: WSJ]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/walmart-amazon-explore-stablecoins-payments</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/walmart-amazon-explore-stablecoins-payments?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-06-13T10:11:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Retail giants Walmart and Amazon are reportedly evaluating digital currencies to streamline e‑commerce and boost cross‑border transactions.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Zoltan Vardai</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tech billionaires are making a risky bet with humanity’s future]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1118198</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/06/13/1118198/agi-ai-superintelligence-billionaires/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-13T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“The best way to predict the future is to invent it,” the famed computer scientist Alan Kay once said. Uttered more out of exasperation than as inspiration, his remark has nevertheless attained gospel-like status among Silicon Valley entrepreneurs, in particular a handful of tech billionaires who fancy themselves the chief architects of humanity’s future.  Sam…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bryan Gardiner</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Polkadot community split on selling 500K DOT for Bitcoin reserve]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/polkadot-bitcoin-reserve-proposal-sparks-mixed-reactions</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/polkadot-bitcoin-reserve-proposal-sparks-mixed-reactions?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-06-13T09:58:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Polkadot’s community is split over a proposal to convert 500,000 DOT tokens into tBTC using a year-long DCA strategy amid market volatility.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Arijit Sarkar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin price Bollinger Bands &#039;failure&#039; risks end of uptrend at $112K]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-price-bollinger-bands-failure-risks-end-uptrend-112k</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-price-bollinger-bands-failure-risks-end-uptrend-112k?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-06-13T09:51:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Bollinger Bands analysis leads to potentially grim conclusions about the fate of the BTC price rebound, which began at sub-$75,000 lows in April.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by William Suberg</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GameStop shares tank 22% after boosting raise to $2.25B for Bitcoin strategy]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/gamestop-sink-20-500m-upsizing-btc-investments</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/gamestop-sink-20-500m-upsizing-btc-investments?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-06-13T09:39:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[GameStop boosted its convertible note offering to $2.25 billion, fueling its Bitcoin treasury strategy and raising speculation about future crypto investments.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Zoltan Vardai</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[XRP Could Capture 14% of SWIFT’s Global Volume, Ripple CEO Says]]></title>
        <id>75cfc537-88a1-4d4b-b407-a989554f932c</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/06/13/xrp-could-capture-14-of-swifts-global-volume-ripple-ceo-says"/>
        <updated>2025-06-13T09:25:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SWIFT dominates interbank messaging for cross-border transfers. Ripple can compete on its ability to seamlessly to move capital, Brad Garlinghouse said.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shaurya Malwa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why is the crypto market down today?]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/why-is-the-crypto-market-down-today</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/why-is-the-crypto-market-down-today?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-06-13T09:22:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto market volatility rises in reaction to Israel’s attack on Iran, but the technical setup suggesting that the uptrend still remains intact.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Nancy Lubale</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Transport Minister: KEJARA Demerit System Is Not Working]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=355836</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/355836/transport-minister-kejara-demerit-system-is-not-working/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-13T09:21:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Recently, the Transport Minister Anthony Loke said that the KEJARA driving license demerit points system needs to overhauled. He also added that the system is not working as it was intended to. For the uninitiated, KEJARA (Keselamatan Jalan Raya) is a Demerit Points System implemented in 1984 under the Motor Vehicles (Demerit Points) Rules 1997. […]
The post Transport Minister: KEJARA Demerit System Is Not Working appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Keran</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Garmin Introduces New Venu X1 Smartwatch]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=355838</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/355838/garmin-introduces-new-venu-x1-smartwatch/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-13T09:14:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Garmin has introduced its new high-end smartwatch, the Venu X1. It is touted to feature the largest display ever from the brand’s Venu series, while maintaining an “ultrathin” form factor. Design-wise, the new Garmin Venu X1 sports rounded square design that’s reminiscent of Apple’s smartwatches. Its screen features a 2-inch AMOLED panel that’s protected by […]
The post Garmin Introduces New Venu X1 Smartwatch appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Heirul Kamel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Anthony Pompliano Set to Head $750M Bitcoin Investment Vehicle: FT]]></title>
        <id>7347911a-9336-44cf-926b-49b666202ce0</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/06/13/anthony-pompliano-set-to-head-750m-bitcoin-investment-vehicle-ft"/>
        <updated>2025-06-13T09:10:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The crypto advocate is preparing to lead ProCapBTC in bid to mirror the bitcoin treasury strategy pioneered by Strategy's Michael Saylor, the Financial Times reported.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>James Van Straten</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bose Unveils Upgraded QuietComfort Ultra Earbuds]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=355825</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/355825/bose-unveils-upgraded-quietcomfort-ultra-earbuds/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-13T09:00:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Back in 2023, Bose introduced the QuietComfort Ultra Earbuds as part of its QuietComfort range of audio products. Now, the company has announced an upgraded version with improvements in terms of noise cancellation and voice pickup. Like the previous model, the QuietComfort Ultra Earbuds (2nd Gen) feature Immersive Audio, which is Bose’s spatial audio technology. […]
The post Bose Unveils Upgraded QuietComfort Ultra Earbuds appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nurul Kamil</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Here’s what food and drug regulation might look like under the Trump administration]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1118638</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/06/13/1118638/food-and-drug-regulation-under-trump-administration/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-13T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Earlier this week, two new leaders of the US Food and Drug Administration published a list of priorities for the agency. Both Marty Makary and Vinay Prasad are controversial figures in the science community. They were generally highly respected academics until the covid pandemic, when their contrarian opinions on masking, vaccines, and lockdowns turned many…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jessica Hamzelou</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ripple, SEC File Joint Motion to Release $125M Held in Escrow]]></title>
        <id>503fae71-356c-40a9-acc5-9ebeca4cd1b1</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/06/13/ripple-sec-file-joint-motion-to-release-125m-held-in-escrow"/>
        <updated>2025-06-13T08:58:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The joint motion seeks to end all pending appeals and avoid further legal proceedings between the two parties.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shaurya Malwa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[If the moon were only 1 pixel: A tediously accurate solar system model (2014)]]></title>
        <id>https://joshworth.com/dev/pixelspace/pixelspace_solarsystem.html</id>
        <link href="https://joshworth.com/dev/pixelspace/pixelspace_solarsystem.html"/>
        <updated>2025-06-13T08:40:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Local Retailers Already List Hong Kong Nintendo Switch 2 Sets]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=355795</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/355795/local-retailers-already-list-hong-kong-nintendo-switch-2-sets/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-13T08:36:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Late last month, the official Nintendo Southeast Asia Facebook page announced that Malaysia was not included in the first official batch of the Switch 2 release. Since then, we’ve seen its controllers – the Pro controller and both Joy-Cons – appearing in the SIRIM database, without the main unit itself. While it may not be […]
The post Local Retailers Already List Hong Kong Nintendo Switch 2 Sets appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ian Chee</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mercedes-Benz G580 Makes An Appearance At MBFW 2025]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=355808</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/355808/mercedes-benz-g580-makes-an-appearance-at-mbfw-2025/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-13T07:43:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Starting today (13 June) until 15 June 2025, Mercedes-Benz is publicly previewing its upcoming G580 model, powered by ‘EQS Technology’, during the Mercedes Benz Fashion Week 2025 at the TRX Exchange mall. The first ever fully electric G-Class is expected to debut in Malaysia at the end of this month. However, the wagon that is […]
The post Mercedes-Benz G580 Makes An Appearance At MBFW 2025 appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Keran</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Scalpers Are Selling The ASUS ROG Astral RTX 5090 Dhahab Edition For As Much As US$22,900]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=355801</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/355801/scalpers-are-selling-the-asus-rog-astral-rtx-5090-dhahab-edition-for-as-much-as-us22900/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-13T06:52:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Earlier in May, ASUS launched its ROG Astral RTX 5090 Dhahab Edition GPU for the Middle Eastern market, with an SRP of more than US$7,000 (~RM29,715). Fast forward a month later and scalpers who’ve managed to get their hands on the card are now selling what is essentially a collector’s item for more than the […]
The post Scalpers Are Selling The ASUS ROG Astral RTX 5090 Dhahab Edition For As Much As US$22,900 appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John Law</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Casio G-Shock GA-V01 Priced At RM679; Pre-Orders Now Available Exclusively Via Crossover]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=355799</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/355799/casio-g-shock-ga-v01-malaysia-pre-order-price/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-13T06:19:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Casio has confirmed the pre-order availability for its forthcoming G-Shock GA-V01 collection for the Malaysian market. As you may recall, the company initially teased the line-up’s arrival back in March this year via an exclusive media preview which we attended. To recap, the new G-SHOCK GA-V01 first debuted in China in February, introducing an all-new […]
The post Casio G-Shock GA-V01 Priced At RM679; Pre-Orders Now Available Exclusively Via Crossover appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Heirul Kamel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rendering Crispy Text on the GPU]]></title>
        <id>https://osor.io/text</id>
        <link href="https://osor.io/text"/>
        <updated>2025-06-13T02:27:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Jemalloc Postmortem]]></title>
        <id>https://jasone.github.io/2025/06/12/jemalloc-postmortem/</id>
        <link href="https://jasone.github.io/2025/06/12/jemalloc-postmortem/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-13T01:37:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meta’s new world model lets robots manipulate objects in environments they’ve never encountered before]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3011867</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/metas-new-world-model-lets-robots-manipulate-objects-in-environments-theyve-never-encountered-before/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-12T22:22:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A robot powered by V-JEPA 2 can be deployed in a new environment and successfully manipulate objects it has never encountered before.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ben Dickson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cloud collapse: Replit and LlamaIndex knocked offline by Google Cloud identity outage]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3011926</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/cloud-collapse-replit-llamaindex-knocked-offline-by-google-cloud-identity-outage/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-12T22:05:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Many AI developers started their morning amid a Google Cloud outage affecting many of the tools they use to build products.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Emilia David</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Frequent reauth doesn't make you more secure]]></title>
        <id>https://tailscale.com/blog/frequent-reath-security</id>
        <link href="https://tailscale.com/blog/frequent-reath-security"/>
        <updated>2025-06-12T19:05:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TensorWave deploys AMD Instinct MI355X GPUs in its cloud platform]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3011697</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/games/tensorwave-deploys-amd-instinct-mi355x-gpus-in-its-cloud-platform/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-12T18:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[TensorWave, a leader in AMD-powered AI infrastructure solutions, today announced the deployment of AMD Instinct MI355X GPUs in its high-performance cloud platform.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dean Takahashi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AMD debuts AMD Instinct MI350 Series accelerator chips with 35X better inferencing]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3011704</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/games/amd-debuts-amd-instinct-mi350-series-accelerator-chips-with-35x-better-inferencing/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-12T18:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AMD announced its new AMD Instinct MI350 Series accelerators, which are four times faster on AI compute and 35 times faster on inferencing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dean Takahashi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Shoring up global supply chains with generative AI]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1118533</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/06/12/1118533/shoring-up-global-supply-chains-with-generative-ai/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-12T18:10:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The outbreak of covid-19 laid bare the vulnerabilities of global, interconnected supply chains. National lockdowns triggered months-long manufacturing shutdowns. Mass disruption across international trade routes sparked widespread supply shortages. Costs spiralled. And wild fluctuations in demand rendered tried-and-tested inventory planning and forecasting tools useless. “It was the black swan event that nobody had accounted for,…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>MIT Technology Review Insights</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google DeepMind just changed hurricane forecasting forever with new AI model]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3011661</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/google-deepmind-just-changed-hurricane-forecasting-forever-with-new-ai-model/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-12T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google DeepMind launches Weather Lab platform for AI hurricane forecasting, showing improved accuracy in early tests with U.S. National Hurricane Center partnership.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Nuñez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Download: AI agents’ autonomy, and sodium-based batteries]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1118609</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/06/12/1118609/the-download-ai-agents-autonomy-and-sodium-based-batteries/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-12T12:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is today’s edition of The Download, our weekday newsletter that provides a daily dose of what’s going on in the world of technology. Are we ready to hand AI agents the keys? In recent months, a new class of agents has arrived on the scene: ones built using large language models. Any action that can be…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rhiannon Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A receipt printer cured my procrastination]]></title>
        <id>https://www.laurieherault.com/articles/a-thermal-receipt-printer-cured-my-procrastination</id>
        <link href="https://www.laurieherault.com/articles/a-thermal-receipt-printer-cured-my-procrastination"/>
        <updated>2025-06-12T11:41:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Are we ready to hand AI agents the keys?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1118189</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/06/12/1118189/ai-agents-manus-control-autonomy-operator-openai/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-12T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On May 6, 2010, at 2:32 p.m. Eastern time, nearly a trillion dollars evaporated from the US stock market within 20 minutes—at the time, the fastest decline in history. Then, almost as suddenly, the market rebounded. After months of investigation, regulators attributed much of the responsibility for this “flash crash” to high-frequency trading algorithms, which…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Grace Huckins</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[These new batteries are finding a niche]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1118556</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/06/12/1118556/sodium-batteries-niche/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-12T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Lithium-ion batteries have some emerging competition: Sodium-based alternatives are starting to make inroads. Sodium is more abundant on Earth than lithium, and batteries that use the material could be cheaper in the future. Building a new battery chemistry is difficult, mostly because lithium is so entrenched. But, as I’ve noted before, this new technology has…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Casey Crownhart</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Attackers Steal Data from Websites (And How to Stop Them)]]></title>
        <id>6849e4d1a3aec42347669919</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-attackers-steal-data-from-websites-and-how-to-stop-them/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-11T20:19:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Across platforms, behind every app, and on your own website, hackers may patiently wait.  These days, everyone should have identity theft protections, and be informed about data threats lurking in the trenches of the world-wide-web’s war on privacy a...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alex Tray</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft-backed Mistral launches European AI cloud to compete with AWS and Azure]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3011628</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/microsoft-backed-mistral-launches-european-ai-cloud-to-compete-with-aws-and-azure/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-11T17:51:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mistral AI partners with Nvidia to launch European AI infrastructure platform, challenging US cloud giants while unveiling breakthrough reasoning models that rival OpenAI.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Nuñez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Databricks open-sources declarative ETL framework powering 90% faster pipeline builds]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3011579</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/data-infrastructure/databricks-open-sources-declarative-etl-framework-powering-90-faster-pipeline-builds/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-11T17:29:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With Apache Spark Declarative Pipelines, engineers describe what their pipeline should do using SQL or Python, and Apache Spark handles the execution.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shubham Sharma</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘Generative AI helps us bend time’: CrowdStrike, Nvidia embed real-time LLM defense, changing how enterprises secure AI]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3011386</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/security/crowdstrike-falcon-now-powers-runtime-defense-in-nvidias-llms/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-11T16:39:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Falcon is now built into Nvidia’s LLMs, delivering native runtime threat defense and eliminating blind spots across AI pipelines.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Louis Columbus</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Asset sprawl, siloed data and CloudQuery’s search for unified cloud governance]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3011440</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/data-infrastructure/asset-sprawl-siloed-data-and-cloudquerys-search-for-unified-cloud-governance/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-11T13:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CloudQuery's developer-first approach to cloud governance pulls data from 60-plus sources into a single, queryable data warehouse.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Taryn Plumb</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why most enterprise AI agents never reach production and how Databricks plans to fix it]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3011290</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/why-most-enterprise-ai-agents-never-reach-production-and-how-databricks-plans-to-fix-it/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-11T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Databricks Agent Bricks automates enterprise AI agent optimization and evaluation, eliminating manual processes that block production deployments.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sean Michael Kerner</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Outset raises $17M to replace human interviewers with AI agents for enterprise research]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3011482</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/outset-raises-17m-to-replace-human-interviewers-with-ai-agents-for-enterprise-research/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-11T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Outset raises $17M Series A to scale its AI-moderated research platform used by Nestlé, Microsoft, and WeightWatchers that's 8x faster and 81% cheaper than traditional market research.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Nuñez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lemony is a plug-and-play device for secure on-premise AI]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3011497</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/games/lemony-is-a-plug-and-play-device-for-secure-on-premise-ai/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-11T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Lemony launched a simple-looking device to deliver on-premise artificial intelligence to redefine how organizations deploy generative AI.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dean Takahashi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Wandercraft raises $75M for acceleration of AI-powered humanoid robotics and exoskeletons]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3011520</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/games/wandercraft-raises-75m-for-acceleration-of-ai-powered-humanoid-robotics-and-exoskeletons/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-11T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Wandercraft, a maker of self-balancing robotic mobility systems, has secured $75 million in funding to accelerate AI-powered robotics.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dean Takahashi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Quantum Art integrates Nvidia for its scalable quantum computers]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3011543</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/games/quantum-art-integrates-nvidia-for-its-scalable-quantum-computers/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-11T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Quantum Art a developer of full-stack quantum computers, has integrated Nvidia's CUDA-Q hybrid quantum-classical platform into its "qubits."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dean Takahashi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Download: Amsterdam’s welfare AI experiment, and making humanoid robots safer]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1118528</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/06/11/1118528/the-download-amsterdams-welfare-ai-experiment-and-making-humanoid-robots-safer/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-11T12:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is today’s edition of The Download, our weekday newsletter that provides a daily dose of what’s going on in the world of technology. Inside Amsterdam’s high-stakes experiment to create fair welfare AI Amsterdam thought it was on the right track. City officials in the welfare department believed they could build technology that would prevent fraud while…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rhiannon Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nvidia believes physical AI systems are a $50 trillion market opportunity]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3011509</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/games/nvidia-believes-physical-ai-systems-are-a-50-trillion-market-opportunity/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-11T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jensen Huang, CEO of Nvidia, said Nvidia's physical AI systems are poised to revolutionize industries, with a $50 trillion market opportunity.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dean Takahashi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Get Information About Your Linux System Through the Command Line]]></title>
        <id>68495738cb7b75f7a33a73c4</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/get-linux-system-info-through-cli/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-11T10:15:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Whether you’ve just gained access to a new Linux system, ethically hacked into one as part of a security test, or you’re just curious to know more about your current machine, this article will guide you through the process. You’ll learn how you can g...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Zaira Hira</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why humanoid robots need their own safety rules]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1118519</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/06/11/1118519/humanoids-safety-rules/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-11T10:11:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Last year, a humanoid warehouse robot named Digit set to work handling boxes of Spanx. Digit can lift boxes up to 16 kilograms between trolleys and conveyor belts, taking over some of the heavier work for its human colleagues. It works in a restricted, defined area, separated from human workers by physical panels or laser…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Victoria Turk</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AlphaSense launches its own Deep Research for the web AND your enterprise files — here’s why it matters]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3011457</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/alphasense-launches-its-own-deep-research-for-the-web-and-your-enterprise-files-heres-why-it-matters/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-11T00:49:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Every report generated by Deep Research includes clickable citations to underlying content, enabling both verification and deeper follow-up.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carl Franzen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Student discovers fungus predicted by Albert Hoffman]]></title>
        <id>https://wvutoday.wvu.edu/stories/2025/06/02/wvu-student-makes-long-awaited-discovery-of-mystery-fungus-sought-by-lsd-s-inventor</id>
        <link href="https://wvutoday.wvu.edu/stories/2025/06/02/wvu-student-makes-long-awaited-discovery-of-mystery-fungus-sought-by-lsd-s-inventor"/>
        <updated>2025-06-11T00:36:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[EDAN: Towards Understanding Memory Parallelism and Latency Sensitivity in HPC [pdf]]]></title>
        <id>https://spcl.inf.ethz.ch/Publications/.pdf/shen-ics-2025-edan.pdf</id>
        <link href="https://spcl.inf.ethz.ch/Publications/.pdf/shen-ics-2025-edan.pdf"/>
        <updated>2025-06-10T22:19:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OpenAI launches o3-pro AI model, offering increased reliability and tool use for enterprises — while sacrificing speed]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3011390</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/openai-launches-o3-pro-ai-model-offering-increased-reliability-and-tool-use-for-enterprises-while-sacrificing-speed/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-10T22:19:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[OpenAI released the latest in its o-series of reasoning model that promises more reliable and accurate responses for enterprises.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Emilia David</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[High-speed fluorescence light field tomography of whole freely moving organisms]]></title>
        <id>https://opg.optica.org/optica/fulltext.cfm?uri=optica-12-5-674&amp;id=570897</id>
        <link href="https://opg.optica.org/optica/fulltext.cfm?uri=optica-12-5-674&amp;id=570897"/>
        <updated>2025-06-10T21:43:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The five security principles driving open source security apps at scale]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3010821</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/security/top-five-security-principles-driving-open-source-cyber-apps-at-scale/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-10T20:52:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Open-source AI is shaping the future of cybersecurity innovation, consistently breaking down barriers and delivering results.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Louis Columbus</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AlphaOne gives AI developers a new dial to control LLM ‘thinking’ and boost performance]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3011239</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/alphaone-gives-ai-developers-a-new-dial-to-control-llm-thinking-and-boost-performance/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-10T20:34:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new framework called AlphaOne is a novel way to modulate LLM thinking, improving model accuracy and efficiency without costly retraining.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ben Dickson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Apple Code Signing Handbook]]></title>
        <id>68489084490c709f6b3070ed</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/apple-code-signing-handbook/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-10T20:07:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this handbook, I’ll demystify the Apple app code signing process. Apple's ecosystem is powerful, but its distribution mechanisms – with various identifiers, certificates, and profiles – can appear complex. This guide attempts to make that journey ...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sravan Karuturi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hyperliquid in 2025: A High-Performance DEX Building the Future of Onchain Finance]]></title>
        <id>6846e8f8529c590001648fa0</id>
        <link href="https://blog.quicknode.com/hyperliquid-protocol-analysis-2025/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-10T19:47:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Explore how hyperliquid became the leading perp DEX: A deep dive of architecture, metrics, tokenomics, and vision for onchain finance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Unhashed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mistral’s first reasoning model, Magistral, launches with large and small Apache 2.0 version]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3011320</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/mistrals-first-reasoning-model-magistral-launches-with-large-and-small-apache-2-0-version/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-10T18:55:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The company is signaling that the future of reasoning AI will be both powerful and, in a meaningful way, open to all.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carl Franzen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OpenAI announces 80% price drop for o3, it’s most powerful reasoning model]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3011288</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/openai-announces-80-price-drop-for-o3-its-most-powerful-reasoning-model/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-10T18:08:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It could benefit startups, research teams, and individual developers who previously found higher-tier model access cost-prohibitive.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carl Franzen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Deploy a Next.js App To Vercel With GitHub Actions]]></title>
        <id>684871b16bc1898625c952fd</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/deploy-to-vercel-with-github-actions/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-10T17:56:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Vercel is a cloud platform or Platform-as-a-Service (PaaS) designed to help frontend developers create, preview, and deploy web applications swiftly and efficiently. In this tutorial, we’ll focus on deploying a Next.js application to Vercel using Git...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chidiadi Anyanwu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Qualcomm shares its vision for the future of smart glasses with on-glass Gen AI]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3011107</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/games/qualcomm-shares-its-vision-for-the-future-of-smart-glasses-with-on-glass-gen-ai/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-10T16:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Qualcomm has enabled what one of its executives said was a strange and "most interesting" conversations with generative AI-powered smart glasses.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dean Takahashi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Thiings]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thiings.co/things</id>
        <link href="https://www.thiings.co/things"/>
        <updated>2025-06-10T15:30:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn the MERN Stack in 2025]]></title>
        <id>68483a699e226a329abe4dee</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-the-mern-stack-in-2025/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-10T14:00:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you’ve been meaning to learn full-stack web development but don’t know where to start, this new course is a solid way in. Whether you're aiming to get a job in web dev or just want to build your own projects, understanding how the pieces fit toget...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vanta’s AI agent wants to run your compliance program — and it just might]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3011165</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/vantas-ai-agent-wants-to-run-your-compliance-program-and-it-just-might/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-10T13:01:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Vanta launches autonomous AI agent that automates security compliance workflows, helping enterprises save 12+ hours weekly on policy management and audit preparation.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Nuñez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Zip debuts 50 AI agents to kill procurement inefficiencies—OpenAI is already on board]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3010781</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/zip-debuts-50-ai-agents-to-kill-procurement-inefficiencies-openai-is-already-on-board/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-10T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Zip launches 50 AI agents to automate enterprise procurement for OpenAI, Canva, targeting $4.4B in savings through automated contract reviews and compliance checks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Nuñez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Zencoder just launched an AI that can replace days of QA work in two hours]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3011083</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/zencoder-just-launched-an-ai-that-can-replace-days-of-qa-work-in-two-hours/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-10T12:59:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Zencoder launches Zentester, an AI-powered testing agent that automates end-to-end software testing, as the startup competes with GitHub Copilot and other AI coding tools in the rapidly consolidating market.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Nuñez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Subtype Inference by Example]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.polybdenum.com/2020/07/04/subtype-inference-by-example-part-1-introducing-cubiml.html</id>
        <link href="https://blog.polybdenum.com/2020/07/04/subtype-inference-by-example-part-1-introducing-cubiml.html"/>
        <updated>2025-06-10T00:04:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What are Onchain Agents: An Introduction to Autonomous, Agent-Driven Web]]></title>
        <id>6840a302a1fc8e00012e657d</id>
        <link href="https://blog.quicknode.com/introduction-to-onchain-agents/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-09T15:37:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An introduction to onchain AI agents: autonomous programs that combine blockchain trustlessness with AI intelligence. Learn how they work.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Unhashed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Top Blockchain Data Tools: How to be Informed Onchain?]]></title>
        <id>6840a419a1fc8e00012e658d</id>
        <link href="https://blog.quicknode.com/top-blockchain-data-tools/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-09T15:32:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Web3 in 2025 runs on data. This guide covers the best onchain data tools and analytics platforms and how QuickNode Streams powers them.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Unhashed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Common Solana RPC Errors & Fixes Using QuickNode Logs]]></title>
        <id>6840a20da1fc8e00012e6573</id>
        <link href="https://blog.quicknode.com/solana-rpc-errors-quicknode-logs/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-09T15:28:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn how to identify and fix common Solana RPC errors using QuickNode Logs that provide real-time insights into every request and response.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Unhashed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Developer's Guide to Monad: EVM-Compatible L1 Architecture and Implementation]]></title>
        <id>6840a4c8a1fc8e00012e6598</id>
        <link href="https://blog.quicknode.com/monad-developer-guide/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-09T15:09:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Build faster, cheaper, and better on Monad: A deep dive into Monad’s architecture, performance features, and developer workflows.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Unhashed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[From electrical engineering student to CTO with Hitesh Choudhary [Podcast #175]]]></title>
        <id>6842e00169a5099a551058ce</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/from-electrical-engineering-student-to-cto-with-hitesh-choudhary-podcast-175/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-06T12:33:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On this week's episode of the podcast, freeCodeCamp founder Quincy Larson interviews former CTO and prolific programming teacher Hitesh Choudhary.   We talk about: The limits of AI in building a robust codebase Time management Higher Education in ...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Protect Your Remote Workforce from Cyber Attacks]]></title>
        <id>6842cf8a6fcd9b03c19d04ea</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/protect-remote-workforce-from-cyber-attacks/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-06T11:22:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Working remotely gives your team flexibility, but it also opens the door to cyber threats. Remote workers are more exposed without the protection of office firewalls and on-site IT teams.  Hackers know that people often use weak passwords, forget to ...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Manish Shivanandhan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>