<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2025-05-28T07:13:58.280Z</id>
    <title>AngJianming RSS Feed</title>
    <updated>2025-05-28T07:13:58.280Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PlayStation Days Of Play 2025 Ongoing Until 11 June]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=354143</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/354143/playstation-days-of-play-2025-until-11-june/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T07:08:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[PlayStation has announced this year’s iteration of Days of Play, which is ongoing from now until 11 June. As usual, this means discounts across the board, from hardware to software. But while there is an extensive list of items being discounted, the discounts themselves could be more substantial. Starting with the hardware, all models of […]
The post PlayStation Days Of Play 2025 Ongoing Until 11 June appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ian Chee</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[iQOO Neo 10 Listed By Local Retailers Ahead Of Malaysian Launch]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=354140</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/354140/iqoo-neo-10-price/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T07:01:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[iQOO is set to release its latest mid-range smartphone, the Neo 10, in Malaysia next week. However, ahead of the launch, a local retailer has already put up the upcoming device for sale, revealing the pricing for the Malaysian market. According to MMG Distribution, the Neo 10 with a 16GB+512GB configuration will retail for RM2,199, […]
The post iQOO Neo 10 Listed By Local Retailers Ahead Of Malaysian Launch appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ikmal Rozlan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[🎉 You Asked, We Delivered: The Code to Image Generator App Just Leveled Up]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/myogeshchavan97/you-asked-we-delivered-the-code-to-image-generator-app-just-leveled-up-5hm0</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/myogeshchavan97/you-asked-we-delivered-the-code-to-image-generator-app-just-leveled-up-5hm0"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T07:00:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In my previous post, I introduced you to the Best Code to Image Generator App
And I’ve got something BIG to share with you today - it’s something you’ve been asking for. 🙌
You already love the Code to Image Generator App for turning clean code into stunning visuals. But today, we're taking it to the next level.
Your feedback was loud and clear:
"I want to save my favorite presets from Save Preset tab, without losing them when I clear my browser cache."

"More customization options, please!"

"Can I access the full source code to tweak it myself?"
Now... you can.
Pro Plan:



  
  
  💾 Unlimited Preset Saves – Stored Securely in the Cloud Database


No more relying on fragile local storage. Your favorite styles and settings are safe, synced, and ready, no matter where you log in.
Want to …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yogesh Chavan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[🕵️‍♂️ The Shadow DOM: Power Tool or Pain in the Ass? 🕵️‍♂️]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/marie_berezhna/the-shadow-dom-power-tool-or-pain-in-the-ass-3dh6</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/marie_berezhna/the-shadow-dom-power-tool-or-pain-in-the-ass-3dh6"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Shadow DOM is like the secret room in a house — it’s hidden, self-contained, and not everyone knows how to use it.
On one hand, it’s a magical tool for building components that are encapsulated from the rest of your app. On the other hand, it can make you question your life choices when things go wrong.
Let’s break it down, shall we?
What is the Shadow DOM


The Shadow DOM is a part of the Web Components spec that lets you create encapsulated DOM for your elements. Essentially, you can create a "mini DOM" inside a parent element, and it won’t mess with the global styles or scripts.
For example:
<custom-element>
  <div>Hello, World!</div>
</custom-element>

Inside your <custom-element>, you can create a Shadow DOM like so:
class CustomElement extends HTMLElement {
  constructor() {
    …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Marie Berezhna</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MySQL Performance Optimization]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/ten/mysql-performance-optimization-5h4d</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/ten/mysql-performance-optimization-5h4d"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T06:59:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Complete Guide to MySQL Performance Optimization


MySQL is one of the most popular relational databases, but it can experience performance issues in large-scale applications or high-traffic environments. This document provides strategies and techniques for optimizing MySQL database performance.
Scalability
Performance Optimization
Data Consistency & High Availability
Query Optimization
Hardware & System Configuration
Partitioning
Advanced Optimization Techniques
Case Studies
New Features in MySQL 8.0+
Key Performance Monitoring Metrics
Upgrade to a server with more powerful CPU, memory, and storage
Steps to distribute read traffic across multiple replicas:
Prepare two servers


Modify or add the following values in /etc/mysql/my.cnf:



server-id = 1        # Must be unique across servers…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ten</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[These Hermes Headphones Will Cost You US$15,000]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=354142</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/354142/hermes-headphones-usd15000/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T06:53:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Headphones don’t exactly rank high on the list of products you would expect from Hermes, but that is exactly what the French luxury fashion house has recently unveiled. The brand’s first ever headphones were designed and developed over two years by its 50-strong bespoke division, Ateliers Horizons. Inspired by Hermes’ own Kelly bag, the headphones […]
The post These Hermes Headphones Will Cost You US$15,000 appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nurul Kamil</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Google I/O 2025 Put AI at the Center of Everything https://www.googlereseller.com/how-google-i-o-2025-put-ai-at-the-center-of-everything/]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/nicknemeth/how-google-io-2025-put-ai-at-the-center-of-everything-561p</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/nicknemeth/how-google-io-2025-put-ai-at-the-center-of-everything-561p"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T06:53:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A post by Nick Nemeth]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nick Nemeth</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[10 Months as a Software Engineer]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/rasheedmozaffar/10-months-as-a-software-engineer-45me</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/rasheedmozaffar/10-months-as-a-software-engineer-45me"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T06:49:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Howdy folks 👋🏻


10 months ago, I got my first real job at an American startup working remotely, and that was a significant transition in my life, moving from working on simple learning projects by myself to working with a team of 4, with product management, agile methods and a bunch of new everyday tools, so here's my overview of my first 10 months as an entry level software engineer.
After I graduated high school in 2022, I started learning web development on my own with C# and ASP.NET Core, and I was building some simple projects like a todo management app, a clinic management system, and a real-time chat app. Until June 2024, that's when I was hired as a Software Engineer 1, or basically, an entry-level Software Engineer.
For starter, I had to go through an onboarding project to fami…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rasheed K Mozaffar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Effective Troubleshooting - A Comprehensive Guide]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/ten/effective-troubleshooting-a-comprehensive-guide-4l8k</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/ten/effective-troubleshooting-a-comprehensive-guide-4l8k"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T06:48:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Troubleshooting Guide for Developers



  
  
  Overview: A Systematic Approach to Problem Solving


Troubleshooting is the systematic process of identifying, analyzing, and resolving issues in systems, applications, networks, and infrastructure. Rather than merely addressing symptoms, it involves diagnosing root causes and implementing measures to prevent recurrence.
For developers and system operators, troubleshooting is an essential skill. This guide covers fundamental principles, real-world examples, and effective tool usage strategies.
The troubleshooting process typically follows these steps (most issues become simpler once you can reproduce them):
Recognize that a problem exists and clearly identify the symptoms.
Examples: "The server is down," "API returns 500 errors," "Database pe…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ten</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is Vibe Data Engineering? Definition, Features & Use Cases (2025 Guide)]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/powerdrill_ai/what-is-vibe-data-engineering-definition-features-use-cases-2025-guide-obn</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/powerdrill_ai/what-is-vibe-data-engineering-definition-features-use-cases-2025-guide-obn"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T06:48:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction: Why "Vibe Data Engineering" Is Gaining Attention


As AI-powered applications proliferate across industries, a new flavor of data engineering is emerging to meet evolving needs: Vibe Data Engineering.
Unlike traditional data engineering, which focuses on building robust pipelines, managing schemas, and ensuring data quality, Vibe Data Engineering is about delivering the right data experience—curated, emotionally resonant, and contextually adaptive. It's where the rigor of data engineering meets the nuance of user-centric design.
The rise of AI copilots, LLM agents, and adaptive interfaces has created a demand for systems that don’t just serve data, but do so in a way that aligns with how humans think, feel, and interact. Vibe Data Engineers play a critical role in shaping the…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Powerdrill AI</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[🧩 Applets vs Servlets in Java]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/sudhakar_v_c404997aeec839/applets-vs-servlets-in-java-337i</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/sudhakar_v_c404997aeec839/applets-vs-servlets-in-java-337i"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T06:46:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Applets and Servlets are both Java technologies, but they serve very different purposes:

Applets



  
  
  🔹 What is an Applet?



A Java program that runs in a web browser.
Meant for client-side execution.
Requires a Java plugin in the browser (now deprecated and unsupported by most browsers).



Feature
Description




Execution
Runs on the client machine (browser).


GUI Support
Yes (Swing or AWT).


Use Case
Old-school interactive web UIs.


Security
Runs in a sandbox (restricted).


Obsolete?
✅ Yes. No longer supported by browsers.



import java.applet.Applet;
import java.awt.Graphics;

public class HelloApplet extends Applet {
    public void paint(Graphics g) {
        g.drawString("Hello from Applet!", 20, 20);
    }
}

Servlets



  
  
  🔹 What is a Servlet?



A Java class …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sudhakar V</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[🔥 Why Everyone Is Talking About HTMX: The Game-Changer for Web Development]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/muzammilriaz/why-everyone-is-talking-about-htmx-the-game-changer-for-web-development-5fpi</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/muzammilriaz/why-everyone-is-talking-about-htmx-the-game-changer-for-web-development-5fpi"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T06:45:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Forget React & Vue — HTMX Brings Simplicity, Speed, and Power Back to HTML


Suno developers!
HTMX ke naam ho gaya hai. Har developer community — Twitter, Reddit, DEV.to — sab jagah log isi ki baat kar rahe hain. Aakhir aisa kya hai HTMX mein jo React, Vue, Angular jaise heavy frameworks se alag khada karta hai?
Aaj ka article tumhare liye ek complete guide hai — kya hai HTMX, kyun hai yeh trending, aur kaise tum isse apne next project mein use kar sakte ho.
🚀 What Is HTMX?
powerful JavaScript library hai jo tumhe HTML ke andar hi dynamic web interactions create karne ki power deta hai.
Bina SPA architecture (React/Vue) adopt kiye, tum server se partial updates fetch kar sakte ho — sirf kuch HTML attributes likh ke.
💡 Key Features (SEO Keywords: HTMX, server-side rendering, lightweight frontend)
hx-get, hx-post, hx-swap
⚡ Why Developers Love HTMX (SEO Keywords: developers, trends, 2025 web dev)
HTMX ek fresh breath hai.
Faster Time to Market — Kam code, jaldi deploy.
Better SEO — SSR apps HTMX ke saath easily rank karte hain (no JS-rendering problem).
Less Complexity — No virtual DOM, no giant JS runtime.
🔥 Real-Life Code Example
<a hx-get="/load/profile" hx-target="#profile-section" hx-swap="innerHTML">
  Load Profile
</a>

Yeh sirf ek link hai, lekin jaise hi click hoga, /load/profile se HTML fetch hogi aur #profile-section mein inject ho jaayegi — bina reload ke, bina extra JS ke.
🌍 Who Should Use HTMX?
Django / Flask / Rails developers
Express / Node.js backend lovers
🔗 Useful Resources
Official HTMX Docs
HTMX on GitHub
HTMX + Django Example
Why HTMX Is the Future (Blog)
💬 Final Thoughts (Call to Action)
Suno developers!
HTMX ko zaroor try karo. Yeh ek revolution hai jo React ya Vue ka alternative nahi, complement ban sakta hai — aur tumhare existing stack mein easily fit ho jaata hai.
Aapne HTMX try kiya hai? Comments mein apna experience share karo! 🚀
follow me on:
🐙 GitHub
💼 LinkedIn
✍️ Medium]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Muzammil Riaz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DevOpsDays Prague 2025]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/bogomil/devopsday-prague-2025-1djh</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/bogomil/devopsday-prague-2025-1djh"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T06:45:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[DevOpsDays Prague 2025 is over, and I sit on my chair today to write something special about it. Not because someone asked me, but because I liked the event so much. Two years ago, I was a media partner, but this year, I visited as a freelancer, which has shaped my experience a bit.
Tomas Kubica - (No) Future of coding and scripting in the AI era
Tomas covered some exciting areas on how AI will soon shape the roles of programmers. His talk was practical, a bit scary, but full of great ideas. The first part covered how to utilize Copilot to create comprehensive documentation about your services. The leading consumer of this documentation will be an AI agent, after all. I recommend watching his recording if available. 
The TL;DR was that if you are a junior developer, AI can help you learn f…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bogomil Shopov - Бого</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Founder Studies]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/shaneso/the-founder-studies-34lp</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/shaneso/the-founder-studies-34lp"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T06:45:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Technical resources for startup founders and engineers.
Repository Link]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shane</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ECESCON 15 years later…]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/agileactors/ecescon-15-years-later-1of9</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/agileactors/ecescon-15-years-later-1of9"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T06:44:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s been a few years (maybe not so few…) years since I entered the software development industry and started out my dynamic career that took me from developing software to creating tests that would challenge it to the breaking point! There have been many twists and turns in my journey, as expected, but one thing has remained constant throughout; my appreciation for the ever-evolving technologies that drive us forward.
I can recall my student years filled with curiosity, working on different projects, and attending meetups and conferences to keep up with what was going on in the industry, one of which was EESTEC.
Allow me to take you on a journey on a timeline with my EESTEC experience!
May 2007: I had come across a new conference. It was the first time that Electrical and Computer Enginee…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kostas Sidiropoulos</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Another way electric cars clean the air: study says brake dust reduced by 83%]]></title>
        <id>https://electrek.co/2025/05/27/another-way-electric-cars-clean-the-air-study-says-brake-dust-reduced-by-83/</id>
        <link href="https://electrek.co/2025/05/27/another-way-electric-cars-clean-the-air-study-says-brake-dust-reduced-by-83/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T06:40:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Xiaomi Mix Flip 2 May Launch In June; Global Release To Follow Soon After]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=354134</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/354134/xiaomi-mix-flip-2-launch-june/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T06:37:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Xiaomi launched the Mix Flip, its clamshell foldable, last year. In keeping with its product launch cycle, leakster it is now being alleged that the Mix Flip 2 could make its debut in China this June, with a global release to follow soon after. As per the report on Weibo, the Xiaomi Mix Flip 2 […]
The post Xiaomi Mix Flip 2 May Launch In June; Global Release To Follow Soon After appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Newsdesk</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[As a developer, my most important tools are a pen and a notebook]]></title>
        <id>https://hamatti.org/posts/as-a-developer-my-most-important-tools-are-a-pen-and-a-notebook/</id>
        <link href="https://hamatti.org/posts/as-a-developer-my-most-important-tools-are-a-pen-and-a-notebook/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T06:27:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto czar Sacks says US could possibly ‘acquire more Bitcoin’]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/david-sacks-us-potentially-acquire-more-bitcoin</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/david-sacks-us-potentially-acquire-more-bitcoin?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T06:21:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[White House AI and crypto czar David Sacks says the US could buy more Bitcoin if the government can fund the purchase in a “budget-neutral” way without a tax or adding to the growing national debt.
Sacks told Gemini co-founders Cameron and Tyler Winklevoss during a May 27 fireside chat at the Bitcoin 2025 conference that while he “can’t promise anything,” a pathway does exist for the government to buy more Bitcoin (BTC).
However, it would require convincing Commerce Secretary Howard Lutnick or Treasury Secretary Scott Besson to OK the buy and fund it “without a new tax or adding to the debt,” Sacks said, adding that “maybe by finding the money from some other program that’s not using it — then we could potentially acquire more Bitcoin.”
David Sacks said the US could buy more Bitcoin, but h…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Stephen Katte</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Australian regulator takes former Blockchain Global director to court]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/australian-regulator-legal-action-former-blockchain-global-director</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/australian-regulator-legal-action-former-blockchain-global-director?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T06:16:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Australia’s markets regulator has filed civil proceedings against Liang “Allan” Guo, the former director of Blockchain Global. 
Guo will face the court on “allegations relating to multiple breaches of his directors’ duties,” the Australian Securities and Investments Commission said in a May 28 press release.
ASIC alleged Guo made multiple breaches of directors’ duties relating to his dealings with ACX Exchange customer funds, and claimed he made false and misleading statements about those dealings and failed to maintain proper books and records. 
The now-liquidated Blockchain Global operated the ACX Exchange from mid-2016 until December 2019, when it collapsed as customers could no longer withdraw their assets. 
During liquidator’s examinations in 2022, the courts were told that ACX exchan…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Martin Young</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Altcoin ‘wildfire’ inbound as trader shuts down bear market fears]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/altcoin-season-sparks-crypto-trader-shuts-down-bear-market-fears</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/altcoin-season-sparks-crypto-trader-shuts-down-bear-market-fears?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T06:08:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A crypto trader has pushed back against claims that altcoin season is already over, arguing that it hasn’t even started yet, as many tokens are still near their local price bottoms.
“I don’t understand why people start claiming that a bear market is around the corner,” MN Trading Capital founder Michaël van de Poppe said in a May 28 X post.
Calls for altcoin season mount
“They are literally on the bottom,” van de Poppe added before stating that the “final easy 12-24 months are coming.” While many altcoins have posted gains over the past 30 days, they remain below their levels from the market uptrend until US President Donald Trump’s inauguration in January.
Solana (SOL) posted 17.84% gains over the past 30 days, trading at $175.17, but is still down 32% since Jan. 19, according to CoinMark…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Ciaran Lyons</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sui Network Steps in to Compensate Cetus Losses in Full After $223M Exploit]]></title>
        <id>30ac7fbc-8a4a-491e-b202-fa2fbcd85c68</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/28/sui-network-steps-in-to-compensate-cetus-losses-in-full-after-223m-exploit"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T06:04:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Sui Foundation has extended a loan to Cetus to fully reimburse affected users, with repayment contingent on an upcoming on-chain community vote.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shaurya Malwa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[IMF says El Salvador to make ‘efforts’ to stop Bitcoin buys with $120M payments deal]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/imf-el-salvador-efforts-stop-bitcoin-buys-120m-payments-deal</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/imf-el-salvador-efforts-stop-bitcoin-buys-120m-payments-deal?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T06:01:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The International Monetary Fund said it has reached an agreement with El Salvador to pay the country $120 million following an initial review of its $1.4 billion loan agreement struck last year.
The IMF said on May 27 that as part of the deal, El Salvador will need to fulfill its prior obligations around limiting further government involvement in Bitcoin (BTC), and it will have to cease its involvement in the Chivo wallet by the end of July.
“On Bitcoin, efforts will continue to ensure that the total amount of Bitcoin held across all government-owned wallets remains unchanged,” the global lender said.
The planned payout, subject to IMF executive board approval, is part of a larger $1.4 billion, 40-month loan deal struck in December, which saw El Salvador agree to confine its Bitcoin ambiti…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Tarang Khaitan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Traders Eye New Highs by End of Summer; Ether Rises 3% on Treasury Optimism]]></title>
        <id>6e04b4fe-7b4e-4dfa-adcc-e2cd2140bafd</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/28/bitcoin-traders-eye-new-highs-by-end-of-summer-ether-rises-3-on-treasury-optimism"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T05:58:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With volatility elevated ahead of an upcoming Bitcoin conference, investors eye a summer breakout as ETH rises and BTC consolidates near $110,000.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shaurya Malwa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Uptrend at Risk Ahead of Nvidia Earnings, Fed Minutes; XRP Holds Key Support Amid XRPFi Narrative]]></title>
        <id>46d2bfbb-d26c-403c-a39d-e0b23568e2da</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/28/bitcoin-uptrend-at-risk-ahead-of-nvda-earnings-fed-minutes-xrp-holds-key-support-amid-xrpfi-narrative"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T05:35:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Federal Reserve's minutes and Nvidia's earnings are key events that could influence market movements.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Omkar Godbole</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DWARF as a Shared Reverse Engineering Format]]></title>
        <id>https://lief.re/blog/2025-05-27-dwarf-editor/</id>
        <link href="https://lief.re/blog/2025-05-27-dwarf-editor/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T05:34:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CFTC’s Goldsmith Romero says commissioner exodus ‘not a great situation’]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/goldsmith-romero-cf-exodus-not-a-great-situation</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/goldsmith-romero-cf-exodus-not-a-great-situation?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T05:10:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Outgoing US Commodity Futures Trading Commission commissioner Christy Goldsmith Romero says the exodus of the agency’s top brass is “not a great situation” for crypto regulations.
The CFTC could be headed by just one commissioner once the other four depart later this year, which Goldsmith Romero said in a May 27 interview at the Brookings Institution will make creating regulations harder because it leaves a less diverse pool of opinions. 
“I think it’s not a great situation if you have one person who’s determining what the rules should be; you lose the benefit of this back-and-forth, this push-and-pull as to what’s the right thing to do,” she said.
“I’ve always wanted to hear from my fellow commissioners about what makes sense to them, and there are many things that they’ve convinced me of…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Stephen Katte</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trump’s CFTC pick Quintenz discloses crypto links, $3.4M assets]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/trump-cftc-pick-quintenz-discloses-crypto-links-assets</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/trump-cftc-pick-quintenz-discloses-crypto-links-assets?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T05:01:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[US President Donald Trump’s pick to chair the Commodity Futures Trading Commission has disclosed millions of dollars worth of assets, along with his various ties to crypto-related organizations.
In paperwork released by the US Office of Government Ethics on May 25, Brian Quintenz disclosed his key positions in crypto and market firms that would directly relate to the CFTC’s regulatory priorities and disclosed assets worth at least $3.4 million, according to a May 27 Bloomberg report. 
Quintenz was a CFTC commissioner from 2017 to 2021 and is currently the global head of crypto policy at Andreessen Horowitz, a position he said he will step down from if the Senate confirms him as CFTC chair. 
He holds an interest in three AH Capital Management investment funds, CNK Fund III, CNK Seed 1 Fund,…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Martin Young</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Indonesia Introduces Homegrown Aletra L8 Electric MPV]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=354119</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/354119/indonesia-introduces-homegrown-aletra-l8-electric-mpv/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T04:57:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Like many countries embracing the electric vehicle revolution, Indonesia has joined the movement with the launch of its homegrown EV brand, Aletra. The brand’s inaugural model, the fully electric Aletra L8 MPV, has officially entered production at PT Handal Indonesia Motor’s manufacturing facility in West Java. Aletra is a new Indonesian electric vehicle (EV) brand […]
The post Indonesia Introduces Homegrown Aletra L8 Electric MPV appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Keran</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rep. Steil urges restraint on adding ‘non-germane items’ to crypto bills]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/steil-wants-lawmakers-restrain-adding-non-relevant-items-crypto-bills</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/steil-wants-lawmakers-restrain-adding-non-relevant-items-crypto-bills?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T04:46:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[US Representative Bryan Steil wants lawmakers to stop adding “non-germane items” into two key crypto bills, claiming that doing so is slowing the implementation of a regulatory framework for the industry.
“Individuals, when they see legislation that’s going to move forward, want to attach non-germane items to any bill that’s going to move through and be signed into law,” Steil, a Republican from Wisconsin who chairs the House Financial Services Subcommittee on crypto, told Cointelegraph at the Bitcoin 2025 conference in Las Vegas on May 27.
“We have to restrain ourselves from that instinct and attempt by our colleagues — both sides of the aisle,” he added.
Congress’s biggest crypto backers hope to pass the stablecoin-regulating Guiding and Establishing National Innovation for US Stablecoin…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Brayden Lindrea</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft Announces Launch Of Malaysia West Cloud Region]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=354116</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/354116/microsoft-announces-launch-malaysia-west-cloud-region/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T04:25:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A couple of months back, Microsoft Malaysia announced that the Malaysia West cloud region will be going live in Q2 of the year. Today, as part of its AI Tour for businesses, the company announced the general availability of the cloud region. Also announced were a number of companies that have already started making use […]
The post Microsoft Announces Launch Of Malaysia West Cloud Region appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ian Chee</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Singularities in Space-Time Prove Hard to Kill]]></title>
        <id>https://www.quantamagazine.org/singularities-in-space-time-prove-hard-to-kill-20250527/</id>
        <link href="https://www.quantamagazine.org/singularities-in-space-time-prove-hard-to-kill-20250527/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T04:04:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Taobao App Now Available In Bahasa Malaysia]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=354103</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/354103/taobao-bahasa-melaysia/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T03:44:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Taobao has officially announced the rollout of a Bahasa Malaysia interface on its mobile app. Available starting from today, users can head into the language settings of the app and change it to “Bahasa Melayu”, with the in-app translation covering even the product reviews. Last year, Malaysia and Singapore became the first markets in the […]
The post Taobao App Now Available In Bahasa Malaysia appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ikmal Rozlan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[An Extreme Cousin for Pluto? Possible Dwarf Planet at Solar System Edge]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ias.edu/news/extreme-cousin-pluto-possible-dwarf-planet-discovered-solar-systems-edge</id>
        <link href="https://www.ias.edu/news/extreme-cousin-pluto-possible-dwarf-planet-discovered-solar-systems-edge"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T03:23:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Jack Dorsey’s Block to bring Bitcoin payments to Square by 2026]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/block-inc-bitcoin-payments-square-2026</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/block-inc-bitcoin-payments-square-2026?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T03:21:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jack Dorsey’s financial services firm Block, Inc. will launch Bitcoin payments on Square, its payments processing arm, with a rollout to begin later this year before a full launch in 2026.
The company announced the plan at the Bitcoin 2025 conference in Las Vegas on May 27, where Block demonstrated the feature at the BTC Inc. merchandise store.
Merchants will be able to accept Bitcoin (BTC) payments through existing Square hardware using the Lightning Network, Bitcoin’s faster, lower-cost layer-2 scaling network. 
“Merchants can choose to hold the Bitcoin, or auto-convert it to fiat in real-time,” Dorsey said on X. 
The company said it expects to start rolling out in the second half of 2025, reaching all eligible Square sellers by 2026, subject to regulatory approvals. 
The move builds on …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Martin Young</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Global Samsung Galaxy Z Flip7 Might Get Snapdragon 8 Elite]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=354105</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/354105/global-samsung-galaxy-z-flip7-might-get-snapdragon-8-elite/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T03:20:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Samsung is expected to launch its latest set of foldables, namely the Galaxy Z Flip7 and Fold7, in July. Naturally, these upcoming devices have been subject to a myriad of rumours and supposed leaks. The Flip7’s chipset has been of particular interest, with conflicting information surfacing over the past few months. Back in April, it […]
The post Global Samsung Galaxy Z Flip7 Might Get Snapdragon 8 Elite appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nurul Kamil</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Acer Accidentally Confirms Existence Of NVIDIA RTX 5050 For Laptops]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=354095</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/354095/acer-accidentally-confirms-nvidia-rtx-5050-laptops/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T03:05:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Acer may have accidentally confirmed the existence of the yet unreleased NVIDIA GeForce RTX 5050 laptop GPU. The GPU’s existence was discovered on Acer’s GPU power specifications page for its Predator and Nitro gaming laptops. At the time of writing, the listing has seemingly disappeared but as this is the internet, screenshots of the listing […]
The post Acer Accidentally Confirms Existence Of NVIDIA RTX 5050 For Laptops appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John Law</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin’s ‘aggressive leg higher’ in Q3 still up in the air: Analyst]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-price-aggressive-leg-q3-uncertain-bitfinex-analysts</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-price-aggressive-leg-q3-uncertain-bitfinex-analysts?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T03:04:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin’s recent all-time high of $111,970 has sparked optimism among crypto market participants, but whether that carries through into the third quarter of this year remains uncertain, analysts say.
“The coming weeks will likely determine whether Bitcoinʼs latest breakout was a local high or the prelude to a more aggressive leg higher in Q3,” Bitfinex analysts said in a May 28 markets note.
Consolidation or mild retracement may “be healthy”
Bitcoin (BTC) reached new all-time highs of $111,970 on May 22; however, Bitfinex analysts say a continued price increase alone won’t necessarily confirm the uptrend heading into the next quarter. 
“A period of consolidation or mild retracement would not only be healthy but also provide a more sustainable foundation for the next leg higher,” the analys…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Ciaran Lyons</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Global high-performance proof-of-stake blockchain with erasure coding]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/qkniep/alpenglow</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/qkniep/alpenglow"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T02:47:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trump Administration Halts Student Visa Processing]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=354097</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/354097/trump-admin-halts-student-visa-processing/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T02:46:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Trump administration has instructed US embassies to stop scheduling new appointments for student visa applicants, according to a memo that was first discovered by Politico. In the document, US Secretary of State Marco Rubio ordered embassies to suspend unbooked student visa interviews “until further guidance is issued.” The message added that the move is […]
The post Trump Administration Halts Student Visa Processing appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Heirul Kamel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Show HN: AutoThink – Boosts local LLM performance with adaptive reasoning]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=44112326</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=44112326"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T02:39:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Using Postgres pg_test_fsync tool for testing low latency writes]]></title>
        <id>https://tanelpoder.com/posts/using-pg-test-fsync-for-testing-low-latency-writes/</id>
        <link href="https://tanelpoder.com/posts/using-pg-test-fsync-for-testing-low-latency-writes/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T02:15:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Real-world assets could revitalize dying NFT lending market: DappRadar]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/real-world-assets-revitalize-dying-nft-lending-dappradar</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/real-world-assets-revitalize-dying-nft-lending-dappradar?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T02:11:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Real-world assets linking up with non-fungible tokens (NFTs) is one of a few key catalysts that could reignite the waning NFT lending sector, which is suffering from a collapse in volumes and user activity, says blockchain analytics platform DappRadar.
Volumes in the NFT lending market, which allows NFT holders to take out a loan against their token, have dropped 97% from a peak of around $1 billion in January 2024 to $50 million in May, DappRadar analyst Sara Gherghelas said in a May 27 report.
Gherghelas said for NFT lending to “move beyond survival mode,” it needs “new catalysts” to reignite the sector, such as real-world asset NFTs, like tokenized real estate or yield-bearing assets that could unlock more stable, trusted collateral sources.
“So far, 2025 has not delivered a compelling …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Stephen Katte</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Asia Morning Briefing: Bitcoin Becomes ‘Generational Asset’ as Speculators Ditch Rolexes]]></title>
        <id>3bdfdfa2-66d8-46b4-b7c7-362d6d9a1206</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/27/asia-morning-briefing-bitcoin-becomes-generational-asset-as-speculators-ditch-rolexes"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T01:33:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[PLUS: ETH's rally might be in its early stages, but there are a few headwinds holding it back]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>AI Boost</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Donald Trump Jr. Says Getting ‘Debanked, De-Insured, De-Everything’ Orange-Pilled Him]]></title>
        <id>af40f189-a0b6-47f0-a70a-10e1d3d04350</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2025/05/27/donald-trump-jr-says-getting-debanked-de-insured-de-everything-orange-pilled-him"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T01:08:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The eldest son of U.S. President Donald Trump said his family’s interest in crypto was, at least at first, “a product of necessity.”]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cheyenne Ligon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nasdaq files for 21Shares Sui ETF, kicking off SEC review]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/nasdaq-files-21-shares-sui-etf-sec-review</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/nasdaq-files-21-shares-sui-etf-sec-review?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T01:05:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nasdaq has filed for crypto asset manager 21Shares to list a spot Sui exchange-traded fund (ETF) in the US, initiating the Securities and Exchange Commission’s review process.
The stock market’s May 23 19b-4 filing, which asks the SEC to list the 21Shares SUI ETF, follows 21Shares’ April 30 submission of its S-1 registration statement to the SEC, which asked the regulator to approve trading of the proposed fund.
Both regulatory filings are needed for the Sui (SUI) tracking fund to go live, with the 19b-4 filing kicking off the SEC’s review process. The agency must decide whether to accept, reject or delay the application within 45 days and it can delay its decision multiple times, for a maximum review period of 240 days.
The SEC must decide on 21Shares’ application by Jan. 18, 2026, at the…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Brayden Lindrea</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Everyone’s looking to get in on vibe coding — and Google is no different with Stitch, its follow-up to Jules]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3009114</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/everyones-looking-to-get-in-on-vibe-coding-and-google-is-no-different-with-stitch-its-follow-up-to-jules/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T00:49:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google is looking to compete in vibe coding with Stitch, which designs user interfaces (UIs) with one prompt.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Taryn Plumb</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A privilege escalation from Chrome extensions (2023)]]></title>
        <id>https://0x44.xyz/blog/cve-2023-4369/</id>
        <link href="https://0x44.xyz/blog/cve-2023-4369/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T00:48:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spott’s AI-native recruiting platform scores $3.2M to end hiring software chaos]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3009108</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/spotts-ai-native-recruiting-platform-scores-3-2m-to-end-hiring-software-chaos/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T00:07:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Spott secures $3.2 million in funding to build an all-in-one AI-native recruitment platform that automates workflows and eliminates tech fragmentation for recruitment agencies seeking to focus on high-value activities.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Nuñez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Look ma, no bubbles designing a low-latency megakernel for Llama-1B]]></title>
        <id>https://hazyresearch.stanford.edu/blog/2025-05-27-no-bubbles</id>
        <link href="https://hazyresearch.stanford.edu/blog/2025-05-27-no-bubbles"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T00:01:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A UEFI app that sends LLDP-MED pkt at boot to negotiate PoE+ power before the OS]]></title>
        <id>https://roderickkhan.com/posts/2025-05-16-poe-uefi-solution</id>
        <link href="https://roderickkhan.com/posts/2025-05-16-poe-uefi-solution"/>
        <updated>2025-05-27T23:45:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Anthropic debuts Claude conversational voice mode on mobile that searches your Google Docs, Drive, Calendar]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3009105</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/anthropic-debuts-conversational-voice-mode-for-claude-mobile-apps/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-27T23:23:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With the rollout of voice mode, Anthropic continues to broaden Claude's functionality and accessibility to all users.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carl Franzen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sen. Lummis on Push for Stablecoin Bill: ‘I Had No Idea How Hard This Was Going to Be’]]></title>
        <id>4e014c49-2796-42b1-ab27-e9fbd45be515</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2025/05/27/sen-lummis-on-push-for-stablecoin-bill-i-had-no-idea-how-hard-this-was-going-to-be"/>
        <updated>2025-05-27T23:18:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Wyoming Republican said she’s concerned the Senate Banking Committee has lost the “muscle memory” needed to actually legislate.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cheyenne Ligon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OpenTPU: Open-Source Reimplementation of Google Tensor Processing Unit (TPU)]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/UCSBarchlab/OpenTPU</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/UCSBarchlab/OpenTPU"/>
        <updated>2025-05-27T23:10:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ether price target shifts to $3K after SharpLink adopts ETH ‘treasury strategy’]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/ethereum-price-target-shifts-to-3k-after-sharplink-adopts-eth-treasury-strategy</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/ethereum-price-target-shifts-to-3k-after-sharplink-adopts-eth-treasury-strategy?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-27T22:34:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Key takeaways:

SharpLink Gaming establishes the first ETH treasury, backed by Ethereum co-founder Joe Lubin. SharpLink will invest $425 million to acquire 120,000 ETH. 

Ethereum futures open interest hits an all-time high of $36.1 billion, with ETH price climbing 4.5% on the daily chart. 

Nasdaq-listed SharpLink Gaming (SBET) announced a $425 million private investment in public equity (PIPE), acquiring approximately 69.1 million shares at $6.15 each to establish the first Nasdaq-listed Ethereum treasury company.
Spearheaded by Ethereum co-founder Joe Lubin, this move mirrors Strategy’s (MSTR) successful Bitcoin treasury strategy, which has yielded over $8.2 billion in gains in 2025, by leveraging stock and bond sales to acquire Bitcoin (BTC).
Former Ethereum core developer and contribu…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Biraajmaan Tamuly</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Third individual arrested in NYC crypto torture and kidnapping case]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/third-suspect-arrested-in-nyc-crypto-torture-case</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/third-suspect-arrested-in-nyc-crypto-torture-case?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-27T22:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A third individual, suspected of being connected to the recent kidnapping, torture and attempted extortion of an Italian tourist in New York City, surrendered to law enforcement on May 27.
33-year-old William Duplessie was taken into custody by the New York Police Department (NYPD) and will be charged with “kidnapping and false imprisonment of an associate,” NYPD Commissioner Jessica Tisch said.
The incident comes amid a string of kidnappings and ransom attempts targeting crypto investors and their loved ones, prompting additional security measures from investors and industry executives.
According to reporting from The New York Times, Duplessie and crypto investor John Woeltz, who was previously arrested by police in connection with the case, both had connections to an NYC-based crypto hed…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Vince Quill</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security leaders lose visibility as consultants deploy shadow AI copilots to stay employed]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008925</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/security/shadow-ai-is-consultings-survival-strategy-in-the-genai-era/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-27T22:15:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fearing sweeping layoffs driven by AI and automation, elite consultants and high performers are turning to shadow AI for a competitive edge.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Louis Columbus</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Here’s what happened in crypto today]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/what-happened-in-crypto-today</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/what-happened-in-crypto-today?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-27T22:04:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today in crypto, Representative Bryan Steil tells Cointelegraph he wants lawmakers to stop adding non-relevant clauses into crypto bills, Trump Media confirmed a capital raise to buy Bitcoin after initially denying reports it would, and Circle announced its initial public offering on the New York Stock Exchange.
Rep. Steil wants restraint on crypto bill additions
Republican Representative Bryan Steil told Cointelegraph on May 27 that he wants lawmakers to stop adding what he considers are non-relevant clauses into two key crypto bills, claiming that doing so is slowing the implementation of a regulatory framework for the industry.
“Individuals, when they see legislation that’s going to move forward, want to attach non-germane items to any bill that’s going to move through and be signed int…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Cointelegraph</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Growing BTC reserve requires Congressional legislation — VanEck exec]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/btc-reserve-requires-congressional-legislation</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/btc-reserve-requires-congressional-legislation?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-27T21:52:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Building a permanent US strategic Bitcoin reserve would likely require targeted legislation rather than executive action, according to VanEck’s head of digital assets, Matthew Sigel. Speaking at Bitcoin 2025 in Las Vegas, Sigel said the most viable path forward may involve inserting Bitcoin mining incentives into the congressional budget reconciliation process.
According to Sigel, the most effective path to growing a US strategic Bitcoin reserve would be through targeted amendments to congressional budget legislation. These could include tax credits for mining companies that use methane gas and other incentives aimed at encouraging miners to share a portion of their mined BTC with the federal government. 
He argued that such an approach would allow the reserve to grow organically over time…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Vince Quill</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mustard Watches (1990)]]></title>
        <id>https://girard.perso.math.cnrs.fr/mustard/article.html</id>
        <link href="https://girard.perso.math.cnrs.fr/mustard/article.html"/>
        <updated>2025-05-27T21:48:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trump supports bill to buy 1 million BTC — Senator Lummis]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/president-trump-supports-bitcoin-bill-senator-lummis</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/president-trump-supports-bitcoin-bill-senator-lummis?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-27T21:38:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[US President Donald Trump supports the BITCOIN Act and has a team of experts in the White House working to roll out landmark digital asset legislation in the coming weeks, according to Wyoming Senator Cynthia Lummis. 
Speaking at the Bitcoin 2025 conference in Las Vegas, Nevada, Lummis said she is bringing the BITCOIN ACT to the “attention of the American people and the world,” adding that, “President Trump supports the bill.”
In March, Lummis reintroduced the BITCOIN Act — landmark legislation that directs the US government to acquire 1 million Bitcoin (BTC) over five years. The acquisitions would be financed using existing funds within the Federal Reserve System and the Treasury Department. 
As Cointelegraph reported, the Trump administration has reiterated the need to use “budget-neutra…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Sam Bourgi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[IMF Says 'Efforts Will Continue' to Ensure El Salvador Doesn't Accumulate More BTC]]></title>
        <id>8d143099-8963-43dd-8726-4c9137d7092d</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2025/05/27/imf-says-efforts-will-continue-to-ensure-el-salvador-doesn-t-accumulate-more-btc"/>
        <updated>2025-05-27T21:36:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[El Salvador has kept purchasing bitcoin, but the IMF seems unfazed.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tom Carreras</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Solana Network Is Now Live on MetaMask]]></title>
        <id>877b0eae-e56b-4a47-827c-511acb4f3b8f</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/tech/2025/05/27/the-solana-network-is-now-live-on-metamask"/>
        <updated>2025-05-27T21:30:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It's the first time that MetaMask integrates a non-EVM network.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tom Carreras</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Selling Bitcoin is like playing in a ‘bad house-rate casino’ — Adam Back]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/selling-bitcoin-like-playing-bad-house-rate-casino-adam-back</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/selling-bitcoin-like-playing-bad-house-rate-casino-adam-back?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-27T21:24:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Selling Bitcoin is like “playing in a really bad house-rate casino,” according to Adam Back, CEO of Blockstream and one of Bitcoin’s earliest adopters. In a recent interview with Bitcoin financial services firm Unchained, Back said the odds are stacked against traders trying to time the market.
Back came to this conclusion in the early days of Bitcoin, he said, when the price “was going up basically exponentially but it [was] extremely volatile.”
“So [...] if you see something that’s going up exponentially but with volatility, if you sell it to time the market a bit falling, the odds are against you,” Back said, adding:
“The trend line is up and to the right, exponential, and so there’s extremely bad trading odds attached to selling because you’re really hoping that it falls.”
Adam Back du…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Christopher Tepedino</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OKX Global General Counsel Is Latest Legal Exec to Leave the Exchange]]></title>
        <id>633a6f62-6d22-4b53-9232-7492f2bf883d</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2025/05/27/okx-global-general-counsel-gone-as-exchange-s-legal-compliance-purge-continues"/>
        <updated>2025-05-27T20:53:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The new chief legal officer, Linda Lacewell, is said to be restructuring the firm's legal and compliance divisions, according to a source familiar with the situation.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ian Allison</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Show HN: My LLM CLI tool can run tools now, from Python code or plugins]]></title>
        <id>https://simonwillison.net/2025/May/27/llm-tools/</id>
        <link href="https://simonwillison.net/2025/May/27/llm-tools/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-27T20:53:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Maple Finance, FalconX secure Bitcoin-backed loans from Cantor Fitzgerald — Report]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/maple-finance-falconx-secure-bitcoin-backed-loans-from-cantor-fitzgerald-report</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/maple-finance-falconx-secure-bitcoin-backed-loans-from-cantor-fitzgerald-report?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-27T20:30:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Wall Street financial firm Cantor Fitzgerald has closed its first Bitcoin lending deal nearly a year after announcing its crypto lending services.
According to a May 27 Bloomberg report, Cantor provided Bitcoin-backed loans to FalconX and Maple Finance. FalconX, a digital asset broker, said it secured a facility worth over $100 million as part of a “broader credit framework,” while Maple Finance reportedly closed the first tranche of an agreement with Cantor.
The service allows companies holding Bitcoin to borrow funds and use the cryptocurrency as collateral, providing a way to unlock liquidity without selling their BTC holdings. Cantor announced its Bitcoin financing business with an initial capital of $2 billion in July 2024, targeting institutional investors seeking to leverage their B…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Ana Paula Pereira</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Square Pilots Real-Time Bitcoin Payments in Vegas, Plans Full Availability to Customers in 2026]]></title>
        <id>e8e1111b-4022-4d8e-8b3f-054d29702ccf</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/tech/2025/05/27/square-pilots-real-time-bitcoin-payments-in-vegas-plans-full-availability-to-customers-in-2026"/>
        <updated>2025-05-27T20:05:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The feature would still need regulatory approval in order to be made available to all customers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Helene Braun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Third Arrest Made in Manhattan Bitcoin Kidnapping, Torture Case]]></title>
        <id>3a087997-0aca-4f4d-8637-34c5ac7bbab5</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2025/05/27/third-arrest-made-in-manhattan-bitcoin-kidnapping-torture-case"/>
        <updated>2025-05-27T19:33:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The incident, involving alleged abduction and abuse for nearly three weeks, comes amid a growing trend of physical attacks on cryptocurrency users.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Francisco Rodrigues</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin price held up by corporate adoption and ‘inflation hedge’ narratives]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-price-held-up-by-corporate-adoption-and-inflation-hedge-narratives</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-price-held-up-by-corporate-adoption-and-inflation-hedge-narratives?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-27T19:20:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Key takeaways:

Institutional investor demand and corporate adoption may push Bitcoin higher despite recession fears.

Investors’ belief that the US Federal Reserve will hold rates favors Bitcoin price upside.

Stock markets around the world responded positively to the temporary suspension of import tariffs between the United States and the European Union, with the S&P 500 rising 1.5% on May 27. However, concerns over a global economic recession persist, capping Bitcoin’s (BTC) upside, especially since the baseline US import rates have been raised for most regions.
Bitcoin remains antifragile and poised to outperform in uncertain times
Given the growing investor uncertainty about economic conditions, Bitcoin hovering around the $110,000 level has taken investors by surprise as it consolida…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Marcel Pechman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mistral launches API for building AI agents that run Python, generate images, perform RAG and more]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3009083</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/mistral-launches-api-for-building-ai-agents-that-run-python-generate-images-perform-rag-and-more/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-27T18:52:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For professionals like the Lead AI Engineer or Senior AI Engineer, the Mistral Agents API represents a powerful addition to their AI toolkit.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carl Franzen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trump Media Group reverses stance, confirms $2.5B Bitcoin capital raise]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/trump-media-group-tmtg-2b-btc-deal</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/trump-media-group-tmtg-2b-btc-deal?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-27T18:42:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Trump Media and Technology Group (TMTG), the company that owns US President Donald Trump’s Truth Social platform and is partially owned by the president, confirmed a $2.5 billion capital raise to purchase Bitcoin (BTC) after denying earlier reports of the deal.
According to a May 27 announcement from the company, the capital raise comprises a $1.5 billion stock sale and $1 billion in convertible senior secured bonds, with a 0% coupon. The sale is expected to close on May 29. TMTG CEO Devin Nunes said:
“We view Bitcoin as an apex instrument of financial freedom, and now Trump Media will hold cryptocurrency as a crucial part of our assets. This investment will help defend our Company against harassment and discrimination by financial institutions."
TMTG spokespeople responded to the initial …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Vince Quill</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Steak n’ Shake COO Says Bitcoin Payments Cut Processing Fees in Half]]></title>
        <id>a8c010d3-3217-42a6-93e7-d1f067a9b224</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/27/steak-n-shake-coo-says-bitcoin-payments-cut-processing-fees-in-half"/>
        <updated>2025-05-27T18:38:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The American fast-food chain started accepting bitcoin payments earlier this month. Next step: robo taxies, cyber chefs, and drones.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cheyenne Ligon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ramaswami’s Strive raises $750M for ‘alpha-generating’ Bitcoin buy strategy]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/strive-raises-750m-alpha-generating-bitcoin-buy-strategy</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/strive-raises-750m-alpha-generating-bitcoin-buy-strategy?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-27T18:24:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Strive, an asset manager founded by American entrepreneur and politician Vivek Ramaswamy, has announced a $750 million raise to establish “alpha-generating” strategies through Bitcoin-related purchases. 
According to a May 27 announcement, the strategies will include buying undervalued biotech companies, purchasing “distressed Bitcoin claims” like those associated with crypto hacks and bankruptcies, and acquiring bottom tranches of Bitcoin credit vehicles at discounted prices. 
“ [...] our alpha-generating Bitcoin accumulation strategies are designed to drive sustained outperformance relative to Bitcoin itself, which requires a new valuation framework,” Strive CEO Matt Cole said. 
Related: Strive targets Intuit for Bitcoin buys after orange-pilling GameStop
The $750 million raise could exp…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Christopher Tepedino</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Build a Rocket Boy drops trailer detailing MindsEye’s blend of Grand Theft Auto and AI robot combat]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3009068</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/games/build-a-rocket-boy-drops-trailer-detailing-mindseyes-blend-of-grand-theft-auto-and-ai-robot-combat/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-27T18:21:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[IOI Partners and Build a Rocket Boy dropped a new trailer on MindsEye, a new title coming on June 10 from the co-creator of Grand Theft Auto V.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dean Takahashi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MARA’s Fred Thiel Says U.S. Should Start Mining Bitcoin to Fill Strategic Reserve]]></title>
        <id>bd4ed8d7-8332-46b7-8194-2dee8c8b1697</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/27/maras-fred-thiel-says-us-should-start-mining-bitcoin-to-fill-strategic-reserve"/>
        <updated>2025-05-27T18:08:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“I think it’s critical, the U.S. making a statement that we’re going to have a strategic reserve is an empty statement unless you start putting stuff into it," he said.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cheyenne Ligon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Running GPT-2 in WebGL: Rediscovering the Lost Art of GPU Shader Programming]]></title>
        <id>https://nathan.rs/posts/gpu-shader-programming/</id>
        <link href="https://nathan.rs/posts/gpu-shader-programming/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-27T18:02:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BlackRock in-house portfolio boosts IBIT Bitcoin ETF exposure by 25%]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/blackrock-portfolio-ibit-etf-exposure</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/blackrock-portfolio-ibit-etf-exposure?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-27T17:52:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BlackRock’s in-house portfolio has been quietly accumulating shares of its Bitcoin exchange-traded fund (ETF), underscoring the asset manager’s growing commitment to the cryptocurrency as part of a broader diversification strategy.
As of March 31, 2025, the BlackRock Strategic Income Opportunities Portfolio held 2,123,592 shares of the company’s iShares Bitcoin Trust (IBIT), valued at $99.4 million, according to filings with the US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC). That’s a notable uptick from Dec. 31, 2024, when the portfolio held 1,691,143 IBIT shares. 
The BlackRock Strategic Income Opportunities Portfolio’s consolidated schedule of investments as of March 31, 2025. Source: SEC
BlackRock’s IBIT was among 11 spot Bitcoin ETFs approved by the SEC in January 2024. Since then, it ha…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Sam Bourgi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin profit taking lingers, but rally to $115K will liquidate $7B shorts]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-profit-taking-lingers-but-rally-to-115k-will-liquidate-7b-shorts</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-profit-taking-lingers-but-rally-to-115k-will-liquidate-7b-shorts?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-27T17:38:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Key takeaways:

Bitcoin could turn parabolic if prices move above $115,000 to liquidate more than $7 billion in short positions.

Onchain indicators enter overheated territory, suggesting prolonged profit taking from BTC investors.

Bitcoin (BTC) showed strength on May 27, briefly tagging $110,700 after a strong US equities market open and the Trump Media and Technology Group’s announcement that it would raise $2.5 billion for a Bitcoin treasury. 
Bitcoin’s bullish momentum aligns with the favorable US financial conditions, as noted by Ecoinometrics. The macroeconomic-focused Bitcoin newsletter highlighted that the National Financial Conditions Index (NFCI) shows a rapid shift to ultra-loose territory after a tightening phase in February 2025. 
The NFCI, published by the Federal Reserve Ba…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Biraajmaan Tamuly</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Salesforce’s $8B acquisition of Informatica means for enterprise data and AI]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3009056</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/data-infrastructure/what-salesforces-8b-acquisition-of-informatica-means-for-enterprise-data-and-ai/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-27T17:20:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Industry analysts explain how Salesforce's $8 billion Informatica acquisition will transform enterprise data management and accelerate agentic AI adoption .]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sean Michael Kerner</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[XRP Bounces Back as Bulls Defend Key Technical Support]]></title>
        <id>5046f1f3-a5d2-4aa0-9ec8-77f339ad8147</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/27/xrp-bounces-back-as-bulls-defend-key-technical-support"/>
        <updated>2025-05-27T17:16:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Market cap swings nearly $4B as XRP weathers capital outflows, holding firm above 50-day SMA despite global economic headwinds.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>AI Boost</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[KindlyMD Acquires 21 Bitcoin Ahead of Merger with Nakamoto]]></title>
        <id>f5ae7ffc-30a3-4d52-bfbb-fe31203dce97</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/27/kindlymd-acquires-21-bitcoin-ahead-of-merger-with-nakamoto"/>
        <updated>2025-05-27T16:50:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The firm now symbolically owns one millionth of the total bitcoin circulating supply, but its objective is to have one million BTC.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tom Carreras</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dogecoin Rebounds 5.5% as Whale Accumulation Fuels Bullish Momentum]]></title>
        <id>e454e2ea-5f2a-486b-a0fb-548db6e5a605</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/27/dogecoin-rebounds-5-5-as-whale-accumulation-fuels-bullish-momentum"/>
        <updated>2025-05-27T16:40:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Despite market uncertainty and global tensions, DOGE stands out with strong support levels and rising demand from large holders fueling investor interest.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>AI Boost</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Launch HN: Relace (YC W23) – Models for fast and reliable codegen]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=44108206</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=44108206"/>
        <updated>2025-05-27T15:59:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[93% of all Bitcoin is already mined. Here’s what that means]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/explained/93-of-all-bitcoin-is-already-mined-heres-what-that-means</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/explained/93-of-all-bitcoin-is-already-mined-heres-what-that-means?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-27T15:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How much Bitcoin is left to mine?            
            
                
Bitcoin’s total supply is hardcoded at 21 million BTC, a fixed upper limit that cannot be altered without a consensus-breaking change to the protocol. This finite cap is enforced at the protocol level and is central to Bitcoin’s value proposition as a deflationary asset.
As of May 2025, approximately 19.6 million Bitcoin (BTC) have been mined, or about 93.3% of the total supply. That leaves roughly 1.4 million BTC yet to be created, and those remaining coins will be mined very slowly.
The reason for this uneven distribution is Bitcoin’s exponential issuance schedule, governed by an event called the halving. When Bitcoin launched in 2009, the block reward was 50 BTC. Every 210,000 blocks — or approximately every fou…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Bradley Peak</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Square Theory]]></title>
        <id>https://aaronson.org/blog/square-theory</id>
        <link href="https://aaronson.org/blog/square-theory"/>
        <updated>2025-05-27T15:33:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum flashes ‘altseason’ signal as ETH price eyes $4.1K]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/ethereum-flashes-altseason-signal-eth-price-4-1k</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/ethereum-flashes-altseason-signal-eth-price-4-1k?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-27T15:26:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Key takeaways:

Ethereum has reclaimed a key level that preceded 100%+ rallies and triggered past altseasons.

Altcoin market cap could surge toward $15 trillion if Bitcoin dominance repeats its post-halving drop.

Despite bullish signals, ETH remains fragile, with $123B in supply near cost basis at risk of flipping into a loss.

Ethereum’s native token, Ether (ETH), has reclaimed a key technical level that has historically preceded sharp price gains and marked the start of an “altseason” across multiple market cycles in the last five years.
ETH price can double in the coming months
The level in question is the mid-line (~$2,600) of the Gaussian Channel — a moving average-based band that tracks long-term momentum — on the 2-week chart.
ETH/USD two-week price chart. Source: TradingView
In 2…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Yashu Gola</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Can Bitcoin Break Conference Curse at This Week's Las Vegas Event?]]></title>
        <id>898bee1f-acda-49ac-850f-94f927833aef</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/27/can-bitcoin-break-conference-curse-at-this-weeks-las-vegas-event"/>
        <updated>2025-05-27T15:08:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin has been on a heater over the past few weeks, but previous years' conferences have proven to be decent selling opportunities.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>James Van Straten</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum Surges 4% on Massive Volume as Institutional Interest Grows]]></title>
        <id>d8d314b8-c185-47df-a603-8ac9e52ba9bc</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/27/ethereum-surges-4-on-massive-volume-as-institutional-interest-grows"/>
        <updated>2025-05-27T15:06:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum's dramatic recovery from $2,513 low demonstrates renewed market confidence amid volatility.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>AI Boost</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pyrefly vs. Ty: Comparing Python's two new Rust-based type checkers]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.edward-li.com/tech/comparing-pyrefly-vs-ty/</id>
        <link href="https://blog.edward-li.com/tech/comparing-pyrefly-vs-ty/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-27T15:01:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A new sodium metal fuel cell could help clean up transportation]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1117456</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/05/27/1117456/sodium-fuel-cell/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-27T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new type of fuel cell that runs on sodium metal could one day help clean up sectors where it’s difficult to replace fossil fuels, like rail, regional aviation, and short-distance shipping. The device represents a departure from technologies like lithium-based batteries and is more similar conceptually to hydrogen fuel cell systems.  The sodium-air fuel…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Casey Crownhart</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ZKPs can prove I&#039;m old enough without telling you my age]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/zkps-can-prove-identity</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/zkps-can-prove-identity?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-27T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Opinion by: Andre Omietanski, General Counsel, and Amal Ibraymi, Legal Counsel at Aztec Labs
What if you could prove you're over 18, without revealing your birthday, name, or anything else at all? Zero-knowledge proofs (ZKPs) make this hypothetical a reality and solve one of the key challenges online: verifying age without sacrificing privacy. 
The need for better age verification today
We're witnessing an uptick in laws being proposed restricting minors' access to social media and the internet, including in Australia, Florida, and China. To protect minors from inappropriate adult content, platform owners and governments often walk a tightrope between inaction and overreach. 
For example, the state of Louisiana in the US recently enacted a law meant to block minors from viewing porn. Sites…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Andre Omietanski and Amal Ibraymi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SharpLink Gaming Soars 400% as Joseph Lubin's Consensys Leads $425M Funding for ETH Treasury Strategy]]></title>
        <id>573397f6-9425-4de7-9d35-e901e99a9155</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/27/sharplink-gaming-soars-400-as-joseph-lubin-s-consensys-leads-usd425m-investment-for-eth-treasury-strategy"/>
        <updated>2025-05-27T14:56:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Ethereum co-founder will also be joining the SharpLink board as its chairman.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Helene Braun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Is XRP price going to crash again?]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/is-xrp-price-going-to-crash-again</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/is-xrp-price-going-to-crash-again?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-27T14:46:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Key points:

XRP derivatives markets turn bearish amid reducing institutional demand, suggesting further downside for XRP price.

XRP’s descending triangle breakout could lead to a decline toward $1.96.

XRP (XRP) has rebounded by more than 45% since April 7 lows to trade at $2.31 on May 27. But the price remains 31% below its January 2025 peak of $3.40, raising concerns about XRP’s ability to rise higher.
Will XRP’s price drop from the current levels in the coming days?
XRP derivatives data lean bearish  
One of the clearest signs that there could be trouble ahead for XRP is the presence of neutral funding rates and decreasing open interest (OI) in its futures markets.
Funding rates are periodic payments made between long and short traders in perpetual futures contracts to keep prices ali…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Yashu Gola</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Wall Street Giant Cantor Debuts Bitcoin Lending Business With First Tranches to FalconX, Maple]]></title>
        <id>f1e0e76a-f939-46fd-a21b-8accbdc9cc18</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2025/05/27/wall-street-giant-cantor-debuts-bitcoin-lending-business-with-first-tranches-to-falconx-maple"/>
        <updated>2025-05-27T14:43:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The financing will help Maple Finance, a major crypto lending platform itself, to speed up its growth, CEO Sidney Powell said.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Krisztian Sandor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use Your Raspberry Pi Headlessly with VS Code and SSH (No Monitor Needed)]]></title>
        <id>6835cf3101fd0876c3c66de0</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-your-raspberry-pi-headlessly-with-vs-code-and-ssh/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-27T14:41:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Raspberry Pi is a portable computer with an onboard processor that fits comfortably in the palm of your hand. Compared with general purpose computers, it’s an affordable option developed by the Raspberry Pi Foundation. The Raspberry Pi Model B wa...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Josiah Adesola</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SharpLink launches Ethereum treasury, taps Joe Lubin as board chair]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/sharplink-ethereum-treasury-joseph-lubin-board-chair</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/sharplink-ethereum-treasury-joseph-lubin-board-chair?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-27T14:34:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Betting platform SharpLink Gaming has launched an Ethereum-based corporate treasury strategy and nominated Ethereum co-founder Joseph Lubin as chairman of its board of directors, the company announced May 27.
According to the announcement, SharpLink Gaming, a publicly traded company on Nasdaq, entered into a securities purchase agreement for a private investment in public equity worth $425 million. Ethereum infrastructure firm Consensys was among the investors.
“On close, Consensys looks forward to partnering with SharpLink to explore and develop an Ethereum Treasury Strategy and to work with them in their core business as a strategic advisor,” Consensys founder and CEO Lubin said.
SharpLink Gaming’s stock is up approximately 400% at the time of writing, changing hands at nearly $33.50. Tr…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Adrian Zmudzinski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is a cryptocurrency mixer and how does it work?]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/explained/what-is-a-cryptocurrency-mixer-and-how-does-it-work</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/explained/what-is-a-cryptocurrency-mixer-and-how-does-it-work?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-27T14:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency mixers explained            
            
                
A cryptocurrency mixer is a specialized service designed to increase the privacy and anonymity of blockchain transactions. 
Unlike traditional financial transactions, which are private by default, most cryptocurrencies such as Bitcoin (BTC) and Ether (ETH) operate on public blockchains. This means every transaction is permanently recorded and accessible to anyone, making it possible for blockchain analysts or malicious actors to trace the flow of funds between wallets.
A crypto mixer’s primary function is to break the link between the sender’s wallet and the recipient’s wallet. It does so by pooling together coins from many users and then redistributing them in a way that makes it difficult to track which coins went …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by SK Arora</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin 2024 conference sparked 30% price crash — Can bulls escape this year?]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-2024-conference-sparked-30-btc-price-crash-bulls-escape-this-year</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-2024-conference-sparked-30-btc-price-crash-bulls-escape-this-year?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-27T14:24:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Key points:

Bitcoin rebounds from another support retest, but fears over a Nashville conference-induced comedown are growing.

The biggest Bitcoin gathering tends to accompany BTC price weakness.

BTC price action can and will continue to experience drawdowns of 10%-20%, analysis stresses.

Bitcoin (BTC) circled $110,000 at the May 27 Wall Street open amid concerns over a 30% BTC price crash.
BTC/USD 1-hour chart. Source: Cointelegraph/TradingView

Bitcoin “market memory” may recall 2024 crash
Data from Cointelegraph Markets Pro and TradingView showed BTC/USD recovering after its latest support retest around $107,000.
As large-volume traders took advantage of the volatility, market commentators turned to potential risk factors, these coming from multiple sources.
Uncertainty over US trade…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by William Suberg</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Building customer-centric convenience]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1116819</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/05/27/1116819/building-customer-centric-convenience/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-27T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the U.S., two-thirds of the country’s 150,000 convenience stores are run by independent operators. Mom-and-pop shops, powered by personal relationships and local knowledge, are the backbone of the convenience sector. These neighborhood operators have long lacked the resources needed to compete with larger chains when it comes to technology, operations, and customer loyalty programs. …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>MIT Technology Review Insights</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trump Media Raising $2.5B for Bitcoin Treasury Strategy]]></title>
        <id>0ec0f71d-e209-4e2a-8dff-38c14c6c35fe</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/27/trump-media-raising-25b-for-bitcoin-treasury-strategy"/>
        <updated>2025-05-27T13:38:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With the move, the operator of Truth Social is joining a growing roster of publicly-traded firms to raise capital for buying crypto assets like bitcoin.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Krisztian Sandor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CoinDesk 20 Performance Update: Index Climbs 1.9% as All Assets Trade Higher]]></title>
        <id>dc13a5de-f25b-4c63-9739-b4b3d03b77a8</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/coindesk-indices/2025/05/27/coindesk-20-performance-update-index-climbs-1-9-as-all-assets-trade-higher"/>
        <updated>2025-05-27T13:20:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Aave (AAVE) gained 5.3% and NEAR Protocol (NEAR) rose 4.8%, leading the index higher.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CoinDesk Indices</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Global Crypto Ownership Increased in 2025, Led by the UK, Gemini Survey Reveals]]></title>
        <id>abe74394-c9b6-4f6b-b136-e92f8e6645cb</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/27/global-crypto-ownership-increased-in-2025-led-by-the-uk-gemini-survey-reveals"/>
        <updated>2025-05-27T13:15:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[UK ownership jumped from 18% to 24%, according to a survey by the crypto exchange.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Will Canny</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Strive Closes $750M Investment Deal to Power 'Alpha-Generating' Bitcoin Strategy]]></title>
        <id>9d31da62-6045-44ac-9a2b-8e1e01366898</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/27/strive-closes-usd750m-investment-deal-to-power-alpha-driven-bitcoin-strategy"/>
        <updated>2025-05-27T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Investment sets stage for $1.5 billion total proceeds and strategic bitcoin accumulation with alpha-generating focus]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>James Van Straten</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blockchain.com to Expand Across Africa as Crypto Regulation Begins to Take Shape]]></title>
        <id>eb0232dd-5ac3-4f15-a7e8-5db065038fb1</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/27/blockchaincom-to-expand-across-africa-as-crypto-regulation-begins-to-take-shape"/>
        <updated>2025-05-27T12:29:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The firm is expanding its presence in the continent as it begins to develop clearer regulations around cryptocurrency.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Francisco Rodrigues</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Download: nuclear-powered AI, and a short history of creativity]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1117453</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/05/27/1117453/the-download-nuclear-powered-ai-and-a-short-history-of-creativity/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-27T12:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is today’s edition of The Download, our weekday newsletter that provides a daily dose of what’s going on in the world of technology. Can nuclear power really fuel the rise of AI? In the AI arms race, all the major players say they want to go nuclear. Over the past year, the likes of Meta, Amazon,…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rhiannon Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How a hawk learned to use traffic signals to hunt more successfully]]></title>
        <id>https://www.frontiersin.org/news/2025/05/23/street-smarts-hawk-use-traffic-signals-hunting</id>
        <link href="https://www.frontiersin.org/news/2025/05/23/street-smarts-hawk-use-traffic-signals-hunting"/>
        <updated>2025-05-27T11:46:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BGP handling bug causes widespread internet routing instability]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.benjojo.co.uk/post/bgp-attr-40-junos-arista-session-reset-incident</id>
        <link href="https://blog.benjojo.co.uk/post/bgp-attr-40-junos-arista-session-reset-incident"/>
        <updated>2025-05-27T11:15:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[LumoSQL]]></title>
        <id>https://lumosql.org/src/lumosql/doc/trunk/README.md</id>
        <link href="https://lumosql.org/src/lumosql/doc/trunk/README.md"/>
        <updated>2025-05-27T10:39:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Every wondered how Facebook spoofs Gmail message list snippet text?]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=44101385</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=44101385"/>
        <updated>2025-05-26T20:32:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[From disruption to reinvention: How knowledge workers can thrive after AI]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008969</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/from-disruption-to-reinvention-how-knowledge-workers-can-thrive-after-ai/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-26T19:05:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We are beginning a cognitive migration: Away from what AI now does well, and toward a redefinition of what humans are now made for.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gary Grossman, Edelman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A thought on JavaScript "proof of work" anti-scraper systems]]></title>
        <id>https://utcc.utoronto.ca/~cks/space/blog/web/JavaScriptScraperObstacles</id>
        <link href="https://utcc.utoronto.ca/~cks/space/blog/web/JavaScriptScraperObstacles"/>
        <updated>2025-05-26T05:01:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nanoparticle-cell link enables EM wireless programming of transgene expression]]></title>
        <id>https://phys.org/news/2025-05-nanoparticle-cell-interface-enables-electromagnetic.html</id>
        <link href="https://phys.org/news/2025-05-nanoparticle-cell-interface-enables-electromagnetic.html"/>
        <updated>2025-05-26T01:52:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google’s ‘world-model’ bet: building the AI operating layer before Microsoft captures the UI]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008900</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/googles-world-model-bet-building-the-ai-operating-layer-before-microsoft-captures-the-ui/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-25T17:42:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google doubles down on its ‘world-model’ vision, racing to build an AI operating layer to drive a universal personal assistant with Gemini. Even as Microsoft moves to capture the enterprise UI. Here's what's at stake.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matt Marshall</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Level Design Book]]></title>
        <id>https://book.leveldesignbook.com/</id>
        <link href="https://book.leveldesignbook.com/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-25T11:03:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Ingredients of a Productive Monorepo]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.swgillespie.me/posts/monorepo-ingredients/</id>
        <link href="https://blog.swgillespie.me/posts/monorepo-ingredients/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-25T10:49:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Developing first petahertz-speed phototransistor in ambient conditions]]></title>
        <id>https://news.arizona.edu/news/u-researchers-developing-worlds-first-petahertz-speed-phototransistor-ambient-conditions</id>
        <link href="https://news.arizona.edu/news/u-researchers-developing-worlds-first-petahertz-speed-phototransistor-ambient-conditions"/>
        <updated>2025-05-25T05:57:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Space Selfie]]></title>
        <id>https://space.crunchlabs.com/</id>
        <link href="https://space.crunchlabs.com/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-25T01:36:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Beyond single-model AI: How architectural design drives reliable multi-agent orchestration]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008888</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/beyond-single-model-ai-how-architectural-design-drives-reliable-multi-agent-orchestration/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-24T22:35:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Successful AI agents require enterprises to orchestrate interactions, manage shared knowledge and plan for failure.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nikhil Gupta, Atlassian</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[There Is No Diffie-Hellman but Elliptic Curve Diffie-Hellman]]></title>
        <id>https://keymaterial.net/2025/05/23/there-is-no-diffie-hellman-but-elliptic-curve-diffie-hellman/</id>
        <link href="https://keymaterial.net/2025/05/23/there-is-no-diffie-hellman-but-elliptic-curve-diffie-hellman/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-24T20:53:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Hobby Computer Culture]]></title>
        <id>https://technicshistory.com/2025/05/24/the-hobby-computer-culture/</id>
        <link href="https://technicshistory.com/2025/05/24/the-hobby-computer-culture/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-24T14:33:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OpenAI updates Operator to o3, making its $200 monthly ChatGPT Pro subscription more enticing]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008828</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/openai-updates-operator-to-o3-making-its-200-monthly-chatgpt-subscription-more-enticing/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-23T21:51:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Operator remains a research preview and is accessible only to ChatGPT Pro users. The Responses API version will continue to use GPT-4o.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carl Franzen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The battle to AI-enable the web: NLweb and what enterprises need to know]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008795</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/the-battle-to-ai-enable-the-web-nlweb-and-what-enterprises-need-to-know/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-23T21:05:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft's NLWeb protocol transforms websites into AI-powered apps with conversational interfaces.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sean Michael Kerner</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The 3 biggest bombshells from this week’s AI extravaganza]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008808</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/the-3-biggest-bombshells-from-this-weeks-ai-extravaganza/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-23T20:29:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Enterprises looking to build with AI should find plenty to look forward to with the announcements from Microsoft, Google & Anthropic this week.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nick Mokey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build a Testing Framework for E-Commerce Checkout and Payments]]></title>
        <id>68308f32f4205e3b843cfb37</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-build-a-testing-framework-for-e-commerce-checkout-and-payments/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-23T15:07:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When I first started working on E-commerce applications, I assumed testing checkout flows and payments would be straightforward. My expectation was simple: users select items, provide an address, pay, and receive confirmation. But I quickly learned t...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Venkata Sai Sandeep</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Architecture of Mathematics – And How Developers Can Use it in Code]]></title>
        <id>68308ee8ccde6bc325c82393</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/the-architecture-of-mathematics-and-how-developers-can-use-it-in-code/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-23T15:06:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA["To understand is to perceive patterns." - Isaiah Berlin Math is not just numbers. It is the science of finding complex patterns that shape our world. This means that to truly understand it, we need to see beyond numbers, formulas, and theorems and ...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tiago Capelo Monteiro</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Feature Fridays: dTelecom]]></title>
        <id>682f3eb8646f7c0001399182</id>
        <link href="https://blog.quicknode.com/feature-fridays-dtelecom/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-23T13:37:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[dTelecom is reshaping digital communication with decentralized, AI-powered infrastructure for Web3 developers and businesses.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>QuickNode</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use React 19 in Power Apps PCF Components]]></title>
        <id>6830767c62d9a28c0de11007</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-react-19-in-pcf-components/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-23T13:22:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Power Apps Component Framework – PCF for short – lets you create complex custom components using traditional web development tools like HTML, CSS, and JavaScript. When creating a new PCF project, you can choose from two types of controls: standar...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brandon Wozniewicz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why enterprise RAG systems fail: Google study introduces ‘sufficient context’ solution]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008684</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/why-enterprise-rag-systems-fail-google-study-introduces-sufficient-context-solution/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-23T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google's "sufficient context" helps refine RAG systems, reduce LLM hallucinations, and boost AI reliability for business applications.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ben Dickson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Download: meet Cathy Tie, and Anthropic’s new AI models]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1117399</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/05/23/1117399/the-download-meet-cathy-tie-and-anthropics-new-ai-models/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-23T12:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is today’s edition of The Download, our weekday newsletter that provides a daily dose of what’s going on in the world of technology. Meet Cathy Tie, Bride of “China’s Frankenstein” Since the Chinese biophysicist He Jiankui was released from prison in 2022, he has sought to make a scientific comeback and to repair his reputation after…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rhiannon Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Laid off but not afraid with X-senior Microsoft Dev MacKevin Fey [Podcast #173]]]></title>
        <id>68304756ecdb03ab557f3974</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/laid-off-but-not-afraid-with-x-senior-microsoft-dev-mackevin-fey-podcast-173/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-23T10:00:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On this week's episode of the podcast, freeCodeCamp founder Quincy Larson interviews MacKevin Fey. He just got laid off last week from his senior engineering role at Microsoft. We talk about: How Mack's approaching the job search after being laid of...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The FDA plans to limit access to covid vaccines. Here’s why that’s not all bad.]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1117329</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/05/23/1117329/fda-limit-access-covid-vaccines/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-23T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This week, two new leaders at the US Food and Drug Administration announced plans to limit access to covid vaccines, arguing that there is not much evidence to support the value of annual shots in healthy people. New vaccines will be made available only to the people who are most vulnerable—namely, those over 65 and…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jessica Hamzelou</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meet Cathy Tie, Bride of “China’s Frankenstein”]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1117373</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/05/23/1117373/cathy-tie-he-jiankui-china-crispr-x-twitter-feed/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-23T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Since the Chinese biophysicist He Jiankui was released from prison in 2022, he has sought to make a scientific comeback and to repair his reputation after a three-year incarceration for illegally creating the world’s first gene-edited children.  While he has bounced between cities, jobs, and meetings with investors, one area of visible success on his…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Caiwei Chen, Antonio Regalado</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[After GPT-4o backlash, researchers benchmark models on moral endorsement—find sycophancy persists across the board]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008691</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/after-gpt-4o-backlash-researchers-benchmark-models-on-moral-endorsement-find-sycophancy-persists-across-the-board/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-22T23:46:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new benchmark can test how much LLMs become sycophants, and found that GPT-4o was the most sycophantic of the models tested.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Emilia David</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn Vue.js in This Beginner's Course]]></title>
        <id>682f84537a13a40bfa336307</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-vuejs-in-this-beginners-course/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-22T20:08:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you’ve been meaning to add Vue.js to your front-end toolbelt, today’s your day. We just published a full, 6-hour Vue 3 course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel. Instructor Bhrugen Patel walks you through everything you need to build modern, ...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Anthropic faces backlash to Claude 4 Opus behavior that contacts authorities, press if it thinks you’re doing something ‘egregiously immoral’]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008672</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/anthropic-faces-backlash-to-claude-4-opus-behavior-that-contacts-authorities-press-if-it-thinks-youre-doing-something-immoral/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-22T19:12:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bowman later edited his tweet and the following one in a thread to read as follows, but it still didn't convince the naysayers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carl Franzen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Anthropic’s new hybrid AI model can work on tasks autonomously for hours at a time]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1117338</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/05/22/1117338/anthropics-new-hybrid-ai-model-can-work-on-tasks-autonomously-for-hours-at-a-time/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-22T16:51:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Anthropic has announced two new AI models that it claims represent a major step toward making AI agents truly useful. AI agents trained on Claude Opus 4, the company’s most powerful model to date, raise the bar for what such systems are capable of by tackling difficult tasks over extended periods of time and responding…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rhiannon Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Anthropic overtakes OpenAI: Claude Opus 4 codes seven hours nonstop, sets record SWE-Bench score and reshapes enterprise AI]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008575</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/anthropic-claude-opus-4-can-code-for-7-hours-straight-and-its-about-to-change-how-we-work-with-ai/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-22T16:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Anthropic's Claude Opus 4 outperforms OpenAI's GPT-4.1 with unprecedented seven-hour autonomous coding sessions and record-breaking 72.5% SWE-bench score, transforming AI from quick-response tool to day-long collaborator.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Nuñez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Deploy Your FastAPI + PostgreSQL App on Render: A Beginner's Guide]]></title>
        <id>682f4900bcc94cb9bccbf905</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/deploy-fastapi-postgresql-app-on-render/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-22T15:55:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This guide is a comprehensive roadmap for deploying a FastAPI backend connected to a PostgreSQL database using Render, a cloud platform that supports hosting Python web apps and managed PostgreSQL databases.   You can find the complete source code he...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Preston Osoro</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[An Animated Introduction to Elixir]]></title>
        <id>682f44e3dcb21c615cf1a12d</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/an-animated-introduction-to-elixir/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-22T15:38:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Elixir is a dynamic, functional programming language designed for building scalable and maintainable applications. It leverages the battle-tested Erlang VM, known for running low-latency, distributed, and fault-tolerant systems. Elixir is based on an...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mark Mahoney</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Time Magazine appears to accidentally publish embargoed story confirming new Anthropic model]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008649</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/time-magazine-appears-to-accidentally-publish-embargoed-story-confirming-anthropic-claude-4-opus/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-22T15:26:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Someone also appears to have published a full scrape of the Time article online on the news aggregator app Newsbreak.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carl Franzen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Enchant launches zero-equity accelerator for gaming and AI startups]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008571</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/games/enchant-launches-zero-equity-accelerator-for-gaming-and-ai-startups/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-22T12:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Enchant is launching a new zero-equity accelerator for gaming and AI startups, with applications now open for its three-month program.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dean Takahashi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Download: the desert data center boom, and how to measure Earth’s elevations]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1117300</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/05/22/1117300/the-download-the-desert-data-center-boom-and-how-to-measure-earths-elevations/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-22T12:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is today’s edition of The Download, our weekday newsletter that provides a daily dose of what’s going on in the world of technology. The data center boom in the desert In the high desert east of Reno, Nevada, construction crews are flattening the golden foothills of the Virginia Range, laying the foundations of a data center…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rhiannon Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Three takeaways about AI’s energy use and climate impacts]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1117277</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/05/22/1117277/ai-energy-three-takeaways/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-22T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This week, we published Power Hungry, a package all about AI and energy. At the center of this package is the most comprehensive look yet at AI’s growing power demand, if I do say so myself.  This data-heavy story is the result of over six months of reporting by me and my colleague James O’Donnell…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Casey Crownhart</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A new atomic clock in space could help us measure elevations on Earth]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1117294</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/05/22/1117294/a-new-atomic-clock-in-space-could-help-us-measure-elevations-on-earth/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-22T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In 2003, engineers from Germany and Switzerland began building a bridge across the Rhine River simultaneously from both sides. Months into construction, they found that the two sides did not meet. The German side hovered 54 centimeters above the Swiss side. The misalignment occurred because the German engineers had measured elevation with a historic level…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sophia Chen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[At Google I/O, Sergey Brin makes surprise appearance — and declares Google will build the first AGI]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008490</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/at-google-i-o-sergey-brin-makes-surprise-appearance-and-declares-google-will-build-the-first-agi/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-21T22:20:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google co-founder Sergey Brin makes surprise appearance at Google I/O, declaring "Gemini will be the very first AGI," revealing philosophical tensions with DeepMind CEO Hassabis who urges scientific caution in the high-stakes AI race.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Nuñez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Master Database Management Systems]]></title>
        <id>682e3c04117e792e5f46edc3</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/master-database-management-systems/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-21T20:48:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Understanding how to manage data effectively is a critical skill for anyone pursuing a career in tech. And we just published a course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will teach you all about Database Management Systems (DBMS). This in-de...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Refactor Complex Codebases – A Practical Guide for Devs]]></title>
        <id>682df5a0f2057ab279952dbe</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-refactor-complex-codebases/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-21T15:47:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Developers often see refactoring as a secondary concern that they can delay indefinitely because it doesn’t immediately contribute to revenue or feature development. And managers frequently view refactoring as "not a business need" until it boils ove...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ankur Tyagi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OpenAI updates its new Responses API rapidly with MCP support, GPT-4o native image gen, and more enterprise features]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008465</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/programming-development/openai-updates-its-new-responses-api-rapidly-with-mcp-support-gpt-4o-native-image-gen-and-more-enterprise-features/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-21T15:30:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Support for remote Model Context Protocol servers, integration of image generation and Code Interpreter tools, and upgrades to file search...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carl Franzen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mistral AI launches Devstral, powerful new open source SWE agent model that runs on laptops]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008458</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/mistral-ai-launches-devstral-powerful-new-open-source-swe-agent-model-that-runs-on-laptops/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-21T14:57:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Beyond performance and portability, its Apache 2.0 license offers a compelling proposition for commercial applications.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carl Franzen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AMD unveils new Threadripper CPUs and Radeon GPUs for gamers at Computex 2025]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008206</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/games/amd-unveils-new-threadripper-cpus-and-radeon-gpus-for-gamers-at-computex-2025/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-21T03:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AMD held a Computex press event to introduce its Radeon RX 9060 XT graphics cards and Threadripper CPUs for next-gen gaming and workstations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dean Takahashi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google finally launches NotebookLM mobile app at I/O: hands-on, first impressions]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008400</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/google-finally-launches-notebooklm-mobile-app-at-i-o-hands-on-first-impressions/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T19:29:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As NotebookLM matures, its emerging business-tier capabilities suggest growing alignment with the productivity and compliance...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carl Franzen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google just leapfrogged every competitor with mind-blowing AI that can think deeper, shop smarter, and create videos with dialogue]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008346</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/google-just-leapfrogged-every-competitor-with-mind-blowing-ai-that-can-think-deeper-shop-smarter-and-create-videos-with-dialogue/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T17:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google unveiled major AI advancements at I/O 2025, including Gemini 2.5 with Deep Think, AI Mode in Search, Veo 3 for video with audio, and a $249 Ultra plan aimed at power users and enterprises.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Nuñez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google’s Jules aims to out-code Codex in battle for the AI developer stack]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008361</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/googles-jules-aims-to-out-code-codex-in-battle-for-the-ai-developer-stack/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T17:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google released Jules, its coding agent, into beta as autonomous coding agents are quickly gaining market share.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Emilia David</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Inside Google’s AI leap: Gemini 2.5 thinks deeper, speaks smarter and codes faster]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008366</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/inside-google-ai-leap-gemini-2-5-thinks-deeper-speaks-smarter-codes-faster/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T17:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google is moving closer to its goal of autonomous agentic AI with a series of enhancements to Gemini 2.5 Pro and Flash.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Taryn Plumb</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blazing-fast Solana data via gRPC: access the freshest Solana data from Shredstream leaders]]></title>
        <id>68273f14bf73460001094b35</id>
        <link href="https://blog.quicknode.com/yellowstone-grpc/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T15:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Access the fastest Solana data with the Yellowstone Geyser gRPC self-serve add-on or with the premium hybrid dedicated gRPC node.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>QuickNode</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft just launched an AI that discovered a new chemical in 200 hours instead of years]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008310</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/microsoft-just-launched-an-ai-that-discovered-a-new-chemical-in-200-hours-instead-of-years/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T18:34:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft launches Discovery platform that uses agentic AI to compress years of scientific research into days, transforming R&D across pharmaceuticals, materials science, and semiconductor industries.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Nuñez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is Sui: A Comprehensive Guide to Web3 Scalability]]></title>
        <id>6823533984101f00013a5ca4</id>
        <link href="https://blog.quicknode.com/what-is-sui-a-comprehensive-guide-to-web3-scalability/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-15T23:34:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Explore how Sui Network achieves 300,000 TPS through parallel processing, and its applications in gaming, DeFi, and supply chain management.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>QuickNode</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AI Meets Blockchain: Transforming Technology for the Next Era]]></title>
        <id>682354c584101f00013a5cb9</id>
        <link href="https://blog.quicknode.com/ai-and-blockchain-transforming-technology-together/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-15T23:34:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discover how AI and blockchain integration enhances security, efficiency, and innovation in healthcare, supply chains, and financial services.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>QuickNode</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Adventure Layer: AI Native Onchain Games, Unleashed]]></title>
        <id>6824c55abf73460001094973</id>
        <link href="https://blog.quicknode.com/adventure-layer-launches-on-quicknode-raas/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-15T12:04:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Adventure Layer launches layer-2 chain leveraging QuickNode's Rollup-as-a-Service (RaaS) product.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>QuickNode</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[QuickLee V2: An Improved Transparent Look into RPC Provider Latency]]></title>
        <id>680fc8e1f8ae810001969b47</id>
        <link href="https://blog.quicknode.com/quicklee-v2/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-14T13:57:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[View public and real-time dashboards to better understand latency and speed when evaluating RPC providers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>QuickNode</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>