<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2025-04-30T14:45:20.795Z</id>
    <title>AngJianming RSS Feed</title>
    <updated>2025-04-30T14:45:20.795Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Local cosmetics sector can be launchpad to position Malaysia as innovation-led economy: Sirim chief tech officer]]></title>
        <id>f3d9620891e0882d2a66ea582395ca3a</id>
        <link href="https://thesun.my/business-news/local-cosmetics-sector-can-be-launchpad-to-position-malaysia-as-innovation-led-economy-sirim-chief-tech-officer-AH14020110"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T17:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SHAH ALAM: The Malaysian cosmetics sector can serve as a launchpad to position the nation as an innovation-led economy, said Sirim Bhd chief technolog...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hayatun Razak</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Is A Secure Test Infrastructure Important?]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/shubham-theqa/why-is-a-secure-test-infrastructure-important-49n</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/shubham-theqa/why-is-a-secure-test-infrastructure-important-49n"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T14:40:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In today’s fast-paced software and digital world, speed and accuracy play a crucial role. The end users are keen on expecting the software updates to be on time and the functionality to be top-notch. A delay in updates and a bad user experience can lead to their sheer disappointment, the rolling out of negative reviews about the product, and even uninstallation or rejection. To avoid such circumstances, developers and testers are testing their applications rigorously using automated testing techniques to verify their functionality and user experience. As per GMInsights, the automation testing market has been forecast to grow by 15% CAGR by 2032, proving the readiness of companies to apply automated testing approaches like DevOps and Agile methods.
Cloud-based testing has grown in popularit…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shubham Joshi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Singleton]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/breno_baudson/singleton-kf2</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/breno_baudson/singleton-kf2"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T14:38:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Singleton é um padrão criacional que garante uma única instância para um objeto, além de fornecer um ponto de acesso global para essa instância. Em outras palavras, o objeto será criado apenas uma vez em todo o processo.
Imagine que você está construindo um sistema para uma escola. Este sistema deverá viabilizar dentre outras funcionalidades, a matricula de alunos. Durante o processo de cadastro é necessário indicar o diretor vigente, que é único. Dentre várias possibilidades, o padrão Singleton tem o objetivo de solucionar este tipo de problema.
Vamos implementar um código na prática sem um padrão bem definido e com o Singleton. Acompanhe:
Classe Diretor com construtor publico
@Getter
public class Diretor {

    private String nome;
    private String sobrenome;

    public Diretor(String…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Breno Baudson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin price recovers, Ethereum RWA value up 20%: April in charts]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-price-recovers-ethereum-rwa-value-up-april-2025</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-price-recovers-ethereum-rwa-value-up-april-2025?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T14:37:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[April 2025 witnessed crypto markets rocked by more tariffs at the direction of US President Donald Trump — controversial policies that could have influenced the outcome of Canada’s elections on April 28. 
On April 2, Trump levied “discounted reciprocal tariffs” on 185 countries and territories. The Dow Jones Industrial Average dropped 2,200 points on April 4, while the S&P 500 dropped nearly 6%, its largest decline since March 2020. Bitcoin (BTC) went along for the ride but broke from stocks as it recovered toward the end of the month. 
Blockchain adoption metrics for Ethereum are looking good, as the network now boasts 60% real-world asset (RWA) tokenization value. Major firms like BlackRock are sure the blockchain will be the standard for RWAs, but other observers believe that scaling is…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Aaron Wood</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vector Databases: their utility and functioning (RAG usage)]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/aairom/vector-databases-their-utility-and-functioning-rag-usage-11lm</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/aairom/vector-databases-their-utility-and-functioning-rag-usage-11lm"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T14:36:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A reflection on vector databases and their usage by LLMs, by implementing a rudimentary one!

TLDR;
Vector databases have emerged as a critical infrastructure component in the era of Large Language Models (LLMs). Traditional databases, designed for structured data and exact keyword matching, fall short when dealing with the nuanced, high-dimensional data that LLMs process and generate. LLMs excel at understanding the semantic meaning of text and other data types, transforming them into dense vector embeddings that capture these relationships. Vector databases are specifically engineered to store, index, and efficiently query these complex vector embeddings.
The necessity of vector databases for LLMs stems from the following key reasons:
Semantic Understanding: LLMs convert text, images, au…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alain Airom</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dear Developers Consider these Five Things Before Choosing Your Next Tech Stack]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/data_fortune_64fa15d5eff3/dear-developers-consider-these-five-things-before-choosing-your-next-tech-stack-36fh</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/data_fortune_64fa15d5eff3/dear-developers-consider-these-five-things-before-choosing-your-next-tech-stack-36fh"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T14:36:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[## 
When you're picking between MEAN and MERN stacks, you're really choosing between Angular and React for your frontend. Angular is like that super-organized friend who has a place for everything. It gives you a complete toolkit with rules about how things should be done. React, on the other hand, is more like that creative friend who's always finding clever new solutions. It gives you building blocks (components) but lets you decide how to put them together. 
If you're working at a large company where many developers need to coordinate, Angular's structure helps everyone stay on the same page. The built-in TypeScript catches mistakes before they become problems, which is a lifesaver in big projects. For startups or small teams that need to adapt quickly, React's simpler approach might fe…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Data Tech Master</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Collisional Thinking Theory (CTT): The Role of ‘Waste of Thinking” by Jalal Khawaldeh]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/nourscene/collisional-thinking-theory-ctt-the-role-of-waste-of-thinking-by-jalal-khawaldeh-4oek</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/nourscene/collisional-thinking-theory-ctt-the-role-of-waste-of-thinking-by-jalal-khawaldeh-4oek"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T14:34:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Collisional Thinking Theory (CTT), developed by Jalal Khawaldeh, is a cognitive framework that emphasizes the deliberate collision of diverse, contrasting, and discarded ideas — referred to as “Waste of Thinking” — to foster creativity, innovation, and accelerated human consciousness. ​ The theory redefines traditional problem-solving and creativity by integrating overlooked or neglected ideas into the cognitive process, unlocking untapped potential for intellectual advancement. ​
Key aspects of CTT include:
Waste of Thinking: Discarded ideas are revisited and repurposed as valuable resources for generating innovative solutions. ​


Intentional Conflict: Contradictory or unrelated ideas are deliberately brought into collision to uncover novel relationships and insights. ​


Dynamic Adaptat…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>NourScene</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[10 Best Cloud Monitoring Tools for 2025]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/cbartlett/10-best-cloud-monitoring-tools-for-2025-3lmd</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/cbartlett/10-best-cloud-monitoring-tools-for-2025-3lmd"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T14:33:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As cloud adoption becomes nearly universal, with 96% of companies utilizing at least one public cloud and 84% employing private cloud solutions, the reliance on cloud services has intensified. This widespread dependence underscores the critical need for robust cloud monitoring to ensure system reliability and performance.
Cloud monitoring tools provide real-time insights into your infrastructure, applications, and services, enabling proactive management and rapid issue resolution.
Whether you're operating in a public, private, or hybrid cloud setup, selecting the right cloud monitoring solution is crucial for maintaining operational excellence.
Before we read into the list, let me ask you this – how much do you depend on cloud services and SaaS providers? Wouldn’t it be great to monitor th…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Colin Bartlett</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Fresh Approach to Local MQTT Development]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/supcik/a-fresh-approach-to-local-mqtt-development-2heo</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/supcik/a-fresh-approach-to-local-mqtt-development-2heo"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T14:30:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Need a local MQTT instance on your machine? Want to integrate Node-Red too? Docker makes this incredibly simple. I'll show you exactly how to get everything up and running with minimal effort.
Before we begin, verify that Docker is properly installed on your system. You can download Docker Desktop from the official website where you'll also find comprehensive installation instructions.
I also suggest installing just, a useful tool that simplifies running commands from your terminal with minimal typing.
Create a new directory and add the following compose.yml file :
services:
  mosquitto:
    image: eclipse-mosquitto
    ports:
      - "1883:1883/tcp"
      - "8090:8090"
    volumes:
      - ./mosquitto/config.txt:/mosquitto/config/config.txt
    environment:
      - TZ=Europe/Zurich

  node-red:
    image: nodered/node-red
    ports:
      - "1880:1880"
    volumes:
      - ./node-red/data:/data
    environment:
      - TZ=Europe/Zurich
    links:
      - "mosquitto:mqtt-broker"
      - "mosquitto:mqtt"
      - "mosquitto:broker"

Adapt the timezone to your location.
Create a directory mosquitto and add the following mosquitto.conf file :
# Config file for mosquitto
listener 1883
protocol mqtt
listener 8090
protocol websockets
allow_anonymous true

Create another directory node-red and add the following Dockerfile :
FROM nodered/node-red

RUN npm install @flowfuse/node-red-dashboard
RUN npm install @flowfuse/node-red-dashboard-2-ui-led]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jacques Supcik</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[¡Nuevo entorno de pruebas disponible para AppDTE!]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/esteban_guenul_a8b43f3f31/nuevo-entorno-de-pruebas-disponible-para-appdte-54n9</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/esteban_guenul_a8b43f3f31/nuevo-entorno-de-pruebas-disponible-para-appdte-54n9"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T14:28:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[¡Nuevo entorno de pruebas disponible para AppDTE!
“Si tu sistema funciona, no te pedimos que lo cambies. Te damos una puerta para conectarte al presente y al futuro.”]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>esteban guenul</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CSS Survival Bootcamp Day 1: Selector Survival Skills]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/teki_solves_fb72717580279/css-survival-bootcamp-day-1-selector-survival-skills-1007</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/teki_solves_fb72717580279/css-survival-bootcamp-day-1-selector-survival-skills-1007"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T14:26:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ever waste way too much time trying to target the right element?

Selectors are the backbone of CSS, but even pros get tripped up by specificity, advanced patterns, or just plain forgetting the right syntax.
Today, let’s sharpen your selector skills so you can style smarter, not harder.
1. Attribute Selector
input[type="email"] {
  border: 2px solid #43a047;
}

Target elements based on attributes for precise styling.
2. :not() Pseudo-Class
li:not(.active) {
  opacity: 0.5;
}

Style everything except what you want to exclude.
3. Child & Sibling Combinators
ul > li {
  font-weight: bold;
}
h2 + p {
  margin-top: 0;
}

Control relationships between elements for cleaner code.
Combine selectors for powerful targeting:
.menu li:not(.disabled) > a

Watch out for specificity wars! Inline styles and IDs will override your best efforts.
Drop your trickiest selector question or tip in the comments!
Tomorrow: We’ll tackle responsive layouts and make your designs bulletproof on any device.
Want all the best selectors and more in one place? Stay tuned for Day 3, or check out the full CSS Survival Kit now for just $5.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Teki Solves</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Programming Content Should Bring Value — Not Vibes, Pic Random]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/yaroslav_vynnychuck_51a03/programming-content-should-bring-value-not-vibes-pic-random-2d64</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/yaroslav_vynnychuck_51a03/programming-content-should-bring-value-not-vibes-pic-random-2d64"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T14:25:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There’s a growing trend in dev writing that makes me feel like I accidentally opened Instagram. Blog posts full of personal preference, soft takes, and “this just clicks for me” vibes — but zero real value. I’m not here to hear about your emotional journey learning a language. I’m here to figure out how to actually build, fix, or survive something.
We’ve lost the core idea that programming is applied logic. It’s engineering. It’s structured chaos. You don’t debug production with feelings. You don’t scale infrastructure because it aligns with your “developer aesthetic.” If you write for other devs, your post should give someone tools, patterns, or hard-won knowledge — not vague declarations of tech love or hate.
Not everything needs to be a deep dive, but it should do something. Share a workaround. Explain a system. Show how you solved a problem the hard way. If all your post does is say “I prefer X over Y because it feels better,” cool — that’s a tweet, not an article.
So yeah. You can keep writing “Why I love Python” posts for karma and claps. Or you can write something that actually helps another dev not lose two hours of their life to some undocumented nightmare. Your call. Just don’t be surprised when nobody reads your blog after realizing it’s just Medium-flavored diary entries in camelCase.
Real devs don’t vibe.
We ship.
´´´#copypasta #bringbackdocs #notyourtechcrush´´´]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yaroslav Vynnychuck</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Top 10 Findings from 2025 IBMi Marketplace Survey: How AS400/IBMi Modernization Services Can Help]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/vijendra22/top-10-findings-from-2025-ibmi-marketplace-survey-how-as400ibmi-modernization-services-can-help-2meg</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/vijendra22/top-10-findings-from-2025-ibmi-marketplace-survey-how-as400ibmi-modernization-services-can-help-2meg"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T14:24:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The 2025 IBMi Marketplace Survey, conducted by Fortra (formerly HelpSystems), continues to serve as a critical benchmark for businesses relying on IBM i (formerly AS400) systems. With participation from hundreds of IBM i professionals worldwide, this annual survey reveals evolving trends, strategic concerns, and technological directions for organizations across industries. As legacy systems evolve under mounting pressure for modernization, the 2025 survey reveals a clear theme—businesses must adapt or risk falling behind.
In this blog, we explore the top 10 key findings from the 2025 IBMi Marketplace Survey and analyze how AS400/IBMi modernization services can directly address these insights, ensuring businesses remain competitive and future-ready.
The most significant takeaway from the 20…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Vijendra Yadav</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Top Headless E-commerce Platforms]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/engroso/the-top-headless-e-commerce-platforms-cmm</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/engroso/the-top-headless-e-commerce-platforms-cmm"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T14:23:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The world of e-commerce is constantly changing, and staying ahead of the competition requires flexibility, customisation, and scalability. With platforms like Bigcommerce and Shopify Plus leading the charge in headless commerce, businesses now have access to powerful tools that separate the frontend user experience from the backend operations. But what exactly is headless commerce, and how can it benefit your business? 
What is Headless Commerce?
Headless commerce is a decoupled architecture where the frontend (what customers see) is separated from the backend (where data and functionality live). This separation allows businesses to create highly customised and flexible customer experiences without being limited by the constraints of traditional e-commerce platforms. 
One of the key benefi…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Engroso</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Study finds that budget cuts to public R&D would significantly hurt the economy]]></title>
        <id>https://impa.american.edu/costs-of-cutting-scientific-research/</id>
        <link href="https://impa.american.edu/costs-of-cutting-scientific-research/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T14:23:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Here’s what happened in crypto today]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/what-happened-in-crypto-today</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/what-happened-in-crypto-today?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T13:58:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today in crypto, an elderly US individual is reportedly the victim of a recent $330 million Bitcoin social engineering attack, a US judge ruled that Tornado Cash can’t be sanctioned again, and the US Securities and Exchange Commission delayed its decision on Dogecoin and XRP exchange-traded funds.
$330 million Bitcoin social engineering theft victim is elderly US citizen
An elderly US individual is reportedly the victim of a devastating $330 million Bitcoin heist, now ranked as the fifth-largest crypto hack in history.
The attacker used advanced social engineering tactics to gain access to the victim’s wallet, onchain investigator ZachXBT said in an April 30 update on X.
The hack took place on April 28, 2025, when ZachXBT flagged a suspicious transfer involving 3,520 Bitcoin (BTC), valued …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Cointelegraph</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[China’s DeepSeek launches new open-source AI after R1 took on OpenAI]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/china-s-deep-seek-launches-new-open-source-ai-after-its-r1-took-on-open-ai</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/china-s-deep-seek-launches-new-open-source-ai-after-its-r1-took-on-open-ai?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T13:47:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Chinese artificial intelligence development company DeepSeek has released a new open-weight large language model (LLM).
DeepSeek uploaded its newest model, Prover V2, to the hosting service Hugging Face on April 30. The latest model, released under the permissive open-source MIT license, aims to tackle math proof verification.
 DeepSeek-Prover-V2 HuggingFace repository. Source: HuggingFace
Prover V2 has 671 billion parameters, making it significantly larger than its predecessors, Prover V1 and Prover V1.5, which were released in August 2024. The paper accompanying the first version explained that the model was trained to translate math competition problems into formal logic using the Lean 4 programming language — a tool widely used for proving theorems.  
The developers say Prover V2 compr…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Adrian Zmudzinski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vitalik outlines vision as Ethereum ecosystem addresses hit new high]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/vitalik-shares-ethereum-vision-as-addresses-hit-record-high</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/vitalik-shares-ethereum-vision-as-addresses-hit-record-high?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T13:34:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum co-founder Vitalik Buterin released another update on what he believes the future of the network should entail.
In an April 30 post on blockchain-based social media platform Farcaster, Buterin outlined his personal areas of focus for Ethereum development this year. These include investigating changes to the network infrastructure to achieve single-slot finality, updates to smart contract execution and enhancements to privacy.
The post comes as the Ethereum network hits a new milestone. GrowThePie data shows that the weekly number of unique addresses interacting with the Ethereum ecosystem reached a new high of over 15.4 million, with nearly 13.45 million on layer-2 protocols.
Weekly chart of unique active addresses in the Ethereum ecosystem. Source: GrowThePie
Buterin recently arg…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Adrian Zmudzinski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Stagflationary Data Puts Pressure on Bitcoin, Stocks Early in U.S. Day]]></title>
        <id>3c744e3b-2623-4d12-9ee3-371eda918810</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/04/30/stagflationary-data-puts-pressure-on-bitcoin-stocks-early-in-u-s-day"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T13:34:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[U.S. GDP turned negative in the first quarter, while prices rose more than forecast; ADP jobs data was the weakest in nearly one year.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephen Alpher</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[No as a Service]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/hotheadhacker/no-as-a-service</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/hotheadhacker/no-as-a-service"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T13:33:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trump's Crypto Sherpa Bo Hines Says Crypto Legislation on Target for Quick Completion]]></title>
        <id>4faa7f7a-b9c4-4d0c-9168-a7dd151d1185</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/consensus-toronto-2025-coverage/2025/04/30/trumps-crypto-sherpa-bo-hines-says-crypto-legislation-on-target-for-quick-completion"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T13:28:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The head of the Presidential Council of Advisers for Digital Assets says new laws could be set by August, and Trump's own crypto interests aren't a factor.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jesse Hamilton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[$330M Bitcoin social engineering theft victim is elderly US citizen]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/elderly-us-victim-loses-330m-bitcoin-in-social-engineering-theft</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/elderly-us-victim-loses-330m-bitcoin-in-social-engineering-theft?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T13:18:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An elderly US individual is reportedly the victim of a devastating $330 million Bitcoin heist, now ranked as the fifth-largest crypto hack in history.
The attacker used advanced social engineering tactics to gain access to the victim’s wallet, onchain investigator ZachXBT said in an April 30 update on X.
The hack took place on April 28, 2025, when ZachXBT flagged a suspicious transfer involving 3,520 Bitcoin (BTC), valued at $330.7 million.
Following the transfer, the stolen stash was quickly laundered through over six instant exchanges and swapped into privacy-focused cryptocurrency Monero (XMR).
Onchain data shows that the victim had held over 3,000 BTC since 2017, with no prior history of large-scale transactions.
ZachXBT confirming the victim of the hack. Source: ZachXBT
Once stolen, t…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Amin Haqshanas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CoinDesk 20 Performance Update: Index Declines 2% as Nearly All Assets Trade Lower]]></title>
        <id>c1cd9dad-e07b-4abe-9187-978f1d043b24</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/coindesk-indices/2025/04/30/coindesk-20-performance-update-index-declines-2-as-nearly-all-assets-trade-lower"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T13:12:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Aave (AAVE) fell 4.7% and Ripple (XRP) dropped 4%, leading the index lower from Tuesday.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CoinDesk Indices</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Port of Los Angeles says shipping volume will plummet 35% next week]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cnbc.com/2025/04/29/port-of-los-angeles-sees-shipping-volume-down-35percent-next-week-as-tariffs-bite.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.cnbc.com/2025/04/29/port-of-los-angeles-sees-shipping-volume-down-35percent-next-week-as-tariffs-bite.html"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T13:07:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Show HN: Kexa.io – Open-Source IT Security and Compliance Verification]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=43844665</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=43844665"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T13:04:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The open source debate: Is crypto losing its soul?]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/open-source-debate-crypto-losing-soul</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/open-source-debate-crypto-losing-soul?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T13:03:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto was born from an open-source ethos, where code was shared publicly, accessible for review and shaped by community contributions. Transparency and verifiability are foundational principles that enable trust in Bitcoin.
But as the space matured, some disadvantages of open source surfaced. Innovative smart contract platforms and decentralized finance (DeFi) applications were forked to create direct competitors — from the wave of Uniswap clones to Ethereum forks — which prioritized speed and lower fees over decentralization.
As a result, some projects opted for closed-source development to protect proprietary designs and reduce the risk of exploits, hoping to delay or deter malicious actors by making the code harder to analyze. This approach is often criticized as “security through obsc…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Yohan Yun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto hackers hit DeFi for $92M in April as attacks double from March]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/crypto-hackers-steal-92-m-april-hacked-funds-1-7-b-2025</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/crypto-hackers-steal-92-m-april-hacked-funds-1-7-b-2025?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T13:00:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency hackers stole more than $90 million in April, dealing another blow to the industry’s mainstream reputation despite ongoing efforts to improve cybersecurity.
Hackers made off with $92 million of digital assets across 15 incidents in April, according to an April 30 research report by blockchain cybersecurity firm Immunefi.
The total marks a 124% month-over-month increase from March, when hackers stole $41 million.
Crypto stole in April 2025. Source: Immunefi
The month’s largest hack on open-source platform UPCX accounted for most of the damage in April, with over $70 million in losses, while KiloEx lost $7.5 million as April’s second-largest hack.
The KiloEx exploiter returned the stolen funds just days after the attack occurred.
All of April’s reported attacks targeted decent…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Zoltan Vardai</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Structify raises $4.1M seed to turn unstructured web data into enterprise-ready datasets]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3006010</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/structify-raises-4-1m-seed-to-turn-unstructured-web-data-into-enterprise-ready-datasets/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Brooklyn-based Structify emerges from stealth with $4.1 million in seed funding to transform how businesses prepare data for AI, promising to save data scientists from the task that consumes 80% of their time.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Nuñez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[U.S. Economy Contracts at 0.3% Rate in First Quarter]]></title>
        <id>https://www.wsj.com/economy/us-gdp-q1-2025-1f82f689</id>
        <link href="https://www.wsj.com/economy/us-gdp-q1-2025-1f82f689"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T12:38:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mantra links OM token crash to risky crypto exchange policies]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/mantra-om-token-crash-exchange-risk-policies</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/mantra-om-token-crash-exchange-risk-policies?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T12:34:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decentralized finance (DeFi) platform Mantra has called for industry-wide cooperation to reduce investor risks in the aftermath of its OM token crash.
On April 30, Mantra published its latest update since the sudden collapse of its OM token, claiming that the incident was “bigger than Mantra.”
“Liquidation cascades could happen to any project in the crypto industry,” Mantra CEO John Mullin warned in the post, pointing to the role of “aggressive leverage positions” on exchanges as a broader threat to investor safety.
Mantra’s industry-wide call to action is the biggest section in the latest OM crash update. Source: Mantra
“We’re cooperating with major exchanges to improve market stability, and we’re calling on the rest of our industry to provide input on how exchange policies can minimize —…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Helen Partz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OCaml's Wings for Machine Learning]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/raven-ml/raven</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/raven-ml/raven"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T12:31:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tokenized Apollo Credit Fund Makes DeFi Debut With Levered-Yield Strategy by Securitize, Gauntlet]]></title>
        <id>677307ee-e3e4-4cc2-bf42-97ffd9c4e6fd</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/04/30/tokenized-apollo-credit-fund-makes-defi-debut-with-levered-yield-strategy-by-securitize-gauntlet"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T12:17:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The offering aims to make real-world asset tokens competitive with stablecoins for DeFi yield strategies, Securitize's Reid Simon said.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Krisztian Sandor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin macro indicator that predicted 2022 bottom flashes &#039;buy signal&#039;]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-macro-indicator-predicted-2022-bottom-flashes-buy</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-macro-indicator-predicted-2022-bottom-flashes-buy?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T12:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Key takeaways:

Macro Chain Index issues first buy signal since 2022, hinting at a new Bitcoin bull run.

RSI crossover on the MCI aligns with past cycle bottoms that preceded 500%+ BTC rallies.

Bitcoin price recovers from $74K to $95K amid rising open interest and positive funding rates.

A key Bitcoin (BTC) indicator that accurately signaled the 2022 market bottom has just flashed another buy signal, suggesting the cryptocurrency may be entering a new bull phase.
Bitcoin metric hints at “absolute bottom”
Dubbed the Macro Chain Index (MCI), the indicator is a composite of several long-term on-chain and macroeconomic metrics. 
It analyzes factors such as accumulation behavior, network activity, and supply trends, helping identify whether Bitcoin is undervalued or overvalued relative to it…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Yashu Gola</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FIFA shifts NFT platform to new Ethereum-compatible blockchain]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/fifa-collect-nfts-move-to-evm-blockchain</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/fifa-collect-nfts-move-to-evm-blockchain?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T12:12:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Federation Internationale de Football Association (FIFA) plans to launch a new blockchain network to support its non-fungible token (NFT) collectibles, the organization announced on April 30.
FIFA will launch its “FIFA Blockchain,” with Ethereum Virtual Machine (EVM) compatibility and aims to provide “better performance, future features, and improved scalability.”
As part of the move, FIFA Collect — its official NFT collection — will migrate from the Algorand blockchain to the new FIFA Blockchain. The migration is scheduled to begin no earlier than May 20, FIFA said.  
FIFA announces new blockchain for FIFA collection migration. Source: collect.fifa.com

“At this stage, no immediate action is required. When the migration process begins, we will provide clear, step-by-step instructions …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Zoltan Vardai</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Download: stereotypes in AI models, and the new age of coding]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1115952</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/04/30/1115952/the-download-stereotypes-in-ai-models-and-the-new-age-of-coding/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T12:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is today’s edition of The Download, our weekday newsletter that provides a daily dose of what’s going on in the world of technology. This data set helps researchers spot harmful stereotypes in LLMs What’s new? AI models are riddled with culturally specific biases. A new data set, called SHADES, is designed to help developers combat the…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rhiannon Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mastercard Introduces Agent Pay, A New System For AI-Led Commerce]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=350185</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/350185/mastercard-introduces-agent-pay/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T12:04:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mastercard has introduced a new technology called “Agent Pay”, aimed at powering secure and intelligent payments in a world increasingly shaped by artificial intelligence. Developed with companies including Microsoft and other leading AI platforms, the system is designed to allow AI agents – such as virtual assistants, chatbots, or autonomous shopping tools – to initiate […]
The post Mastercard Introduces Agent Pay, A New System For AI-Led Commerce appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Heirul Kamel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vanar Chain tackles AWS-style outages with AI-powered data storage]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/vanar-chain-launches-neutron-ai-onchain-compression</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/vanar-chain-launches-neutron-ai-onchain-compression?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T11:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Vanar Chain, a layer-1 blockchain network, has launched a new artificial intelligence-powered compression and data authentication layer designed to address the industry’s longstanding issue with onchain storage.
Vanar Chain is launching Neutron, an AI-native blockchain layer with data compression ratios of up to 500:1, which can reduce a standard 25 megabyte file to just 50 kilobytes, transforming it into a “Neutron Seed” that can be stored on the blockchain ledger.
The new blockchain compression layer aims to solve the industry’s data storage issue, with traditional blockchains lacking the capacity to store data, only to reference it.
This design introduces potential single points of failure. Vanar's Neutron aims to solve this by enabling fully onchain, verifiable data storage.
Neutron is…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Zoltan Vardai</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Retailers will soon have only about 7 weeks of full inventories left]]></title>
        <id>https://fortune.com/article/retailers-weeks-of-inventory-left-trump-china-trade-war/</id>
        <link href="https://fortune.com/article/retailers-weeks-of-inventory-left-trump-china-trade-war/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T11:42:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lessons from the Lebanese Space Program – Kasurian]]></title>
        <id>https://kasurian.com/p/lebanese-space-program</id>
        <link href="https://kasurian.com/p/lebanese-space-program"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T11:41:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Secret Deals, Foreign Investments: The Rise of Trump’s Crypto Firm]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nytimes.com/2025/04/29/us/politics/trump-crypto-world-liberty-financial.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.nytimes.com/2025/04/29/us/politics/trump-crypto-world-liberty-financial.html"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T11:19:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Daybook Americas: Robinhood Earnings to Preview Trump's 'Damage']]></title>
        <id>0b8f55d6-8763-4cc6-9352-6bfcb3db8bab</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/daybook-us/2025/04/30/crypto-daybook-americas-biggest-tokens-show-restraint-for-now-but-damage-has-already-been-done"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T11:17:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Your day-ahead look for April 30, 2025]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Francisco Rodrigues</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin traders predict BTC price gains ahead of $96K liquidity clash]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-traders-predict-btc-price-gains-ahead-of-96k-liquidity-clash</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-traders-predict-btc-price-gains-ahead-of-96k-liquidity-clash?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T11:11:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Key points:

Bitcoin consolidates after upside momentum stalls, but traders are confident that upside breakout will result.

Major risk-asset volatility is expected as US macro data precedes the monthly candle close.

April BTC price performance is on track to be the best since 2020.

Bitcoin (BTC) spent another day around $95,000 on April 30 as volatility waited in the wings.
BTC/USD 1-hour chart. Source: Cointelegraph/TradingView
Bitcoin enjoys the calm before the storm
Data from Cointelegraph Markets Pro and TradingView showed calm trading conditions with hours to go until the monthly close and key US macro data.
The latter comes in the form of Q1 GDP and the March print of the Personal Consumption Expenditures (PCE) index, known as the Federal Reserve’s “preferred” inflation gauge.
The…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by William Suberg</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nasdaq Seeks SEC Approval to List 21Shares Dogecoin ETF]]></title>
        <id>11f6cfaa-74d7-43a5-b5cd-081a49c73d92</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/04/30/nasdaq-seeks-sec-approval-to-list-21shares-dogecoin-etf"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T11:06:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase Custody Trust will hold the fund’s tokens and serve as the official custodian for the ETF.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shaurya Malwa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Inside Movement’s Token-Dump Scandal: Secret Contracts, Shadow Advisors and Hidden Middlemen]]></title>
        <id>ca25f2fb-f887-4098-86ec-a0104210e64e</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/tech/2025/04/30/inside-movement-s-token-dump-scandal-backroom-deals-shadow-advisors-and-secret-middlemen"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Movement, backed by Trump's World Liberty Financial, says it was duped into an agreement that experts say incentivized price manipulation.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sam Kessler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Week In Gaming: EA Cancels Titanfall Game, Borderlands 4 Gets New Release Date, And More]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=350162</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/350162/this-week-in-gaming/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T10:53:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’re halfway through the week, and in the world of gaming, some things have happened but not in such a major fashion that it would make waves. That being said, their occurrence is still important enough to warrant a report and as such, here’s a quick list of them. EA Lays Off Hundreds Of Staff, […]
The post This Week In Gaming: EA Cancels Titanfall Game, Borderlands 4 Gets New Release Date, And More appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John Law</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[KuCoin Commits $2B to 'Trust Project' Focusing on Crypto Security, Transparency]]></title>
        <id>2a3c88da-cd66-4d75-8f07-1dbedc9e3cc9</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2025/04/30/kucoin-commits-usd2-billion-to-trust-project-focusing-on-crypto-security-and-transparency"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T10:08:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[KuCoin’s native token, KCS, will play a more pivotal role in the ecosystem.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Omkar Godbole</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin volatility lowest in 563 days, Hayes predicts $1M BTC by 2028]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-volatility-563-day-low-hayes-predicts-1-m-btc-2028</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-volatility-563-day-low-hayes-predicts-1-m-btc-2028?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T10:02:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin is showing signs of maturity as a global financial asset, with price volatility dropping to its lowest level in more than 500 days, according to new research.
Volatility refers to the degree of variation of a trading price over time, which indicates the uncertainty about the size of changes in an asset’s value.
Bitcoin (BTC) weekly volatility hit a 563-day low on April 30, said Vetle Lunde, the head of research at K33 Research.
Source: Vetle Lunde
Bitcoin’s decreasing volatility suggests BTC is maturing as a global financial asset, leading to a more stable price trajectory.
Bitcoin has become the seventh-largest asset globally by market capitalization, reaching $1.87 trillion. It now ranks above Silver, Meta and Saudi Aramco, according to Companiesmarketcap.
Top 10 global assets by…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Zoltan Vardai</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Samsung One UI 8 Might Bring AI Video Summarisation]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=350177</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/350177/samsung-one-ui-8-might-bring-ai-video-summarisation/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T09:50:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Samsung will reportedly bring an AI video summarisation tool in its One UI 8 based on Android 16. As reported by SammyGuru, the tool will be able to analyse a video, based on speech, visuals, and captions. A multi-modal AI model will then summarise the main points of the video. The feature will apparently be […]
The post Samsung One UI 8 Might Bring AI Video Summarisation appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Newsdesk</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This data set helps researchers spot harmful stereotypes in LLMs]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1115946</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/04/30/1115946/this-data-set-helps-researchers-spot-harmful-stereotypes-in-llms/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T09:41:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AI models are riddled with culturally specific biases. A new data set, called SHADES, is designed to help developers combat the problem by spotting harmful stereotypes and other kinds of discrimination that emerge in AI chatbot responses across a wide range of languages. Margaret Mitchell, chief ethics scientist at AI startup Hugging Face, led the…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rhiannon Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Finland Bans Smartphones in Schools]]></title>
        <id>https://yle.fi/a/74-20158886</id>
        <link href="https://yle.fi/a/74-20158886"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T09:17:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chery Tiggo Cross HEV To Get Malaysian Appearance In May]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=350155</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/350155/chery-tiggo-cross-hev-to-get-malaysian-appearance-in-may/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T09:04:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This year’s edition of the Malaysia Auto Show is scheduled to happen in May as it usually does, but it looks like Chery may have a hybrid car to showcase during the event. This may come in the form of the Tiggo Cross, which may be known instead as the Tiggo 4 elsewhere. Paul Tan […]
The post Chery Tiggo Cross HEV To Get Malaysian Appearance In May appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ian Chee</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Circle taps Onafriq to cut Africa’s cross-border payment costs with USDC]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/circle-onafriq-partner-to-cut-africa-payment-costs-with-usdc</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/circle-onafriq-partner-to-cut-africa-payment-costs-with-usdc?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Stablecoin issuer Circle has partnered with Onafriq, Africa’s largest payments gateway, to reduce the high cost of cross-border payments across the continent using USDC.
According to a press release shared with Cointelegraph, Circle aims to pilot USDC (USDC) settlements within Onafriq’s vast network, which connects over 500 wallets and 200 million bank accounts in more than 40 countries.
“By integrating USDC, we aim to simplify financial transactions for institutions and individuals, reduce costs and strengthen trust,” Onafriq founder and CEO Dare Okoudjou said.
He added that the integration of USDC will simplify transactions and boost trust in digital financial services.
Currently, over 80% of intra-African transactions are routed through correspondent banks outside the continent and sett…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Amin Haqshanas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Xiaomi Debuts Its Own AI Model]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=350157</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/350157/xiaomi-debuts-its-own-ai-model/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T08:57:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Xiaomi has recently unveiled MiMo, its in-house open source AI model with reasoning capabilities. With the release of the large language model, the company has joined the ranks of China’s tech firms, hoping to gain a foothold in the AI industry. According to Xiaomi, MiMo was developed by Core, a specialised AI task force. The […]
The post Xiaomi Debuts Its Own AI Model appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nurul Kamil</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Xiaomi MiMo Reasoning Model]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/XiaomiMiMo/MiMo</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/XiaomiMiMo/MiMo"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T08:48:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Debate on Looser Data Limits Brings to Mind the Divisive Ordinals Controversy]]></title>
        <id>6feae542-2b1a-4681-be27-d67fdf8e8d0f</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/tech/2025/04/30/bitcoin-debate-on-looser-data-limits-brings-to-mind-the-divisive-ordinals-controversy"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T08:44:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Removing the blockchain's OP_RETURN size controls would allow more data to be embedded in transactions. Critics say this will only be used for spam.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sam Reynolds</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin May Evolve Into Low-Beta Equity Play Reflexively, BlackRock's Mitchnik Says]]></title>
        <id>74f0300a-3daa-4fd9-a866-5e9ec9ac6149</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2025/04/30/bitcoin-may-evolve-into-low-beta-equity-play-blackrocks-mitchnik-says"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T08:39:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA["It makes no fundamental sense, and yet when it's repeated enough, it can actually become a little self-fulfilling,” Mitchnik said.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Omkar Godbole</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Is Bitcoin a hedge against inflation in 2025?]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/explained/is-bitcoin-a-hedge-against-inflation</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/explained/is-bitcoin-a-hedge-against-inflation?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T08:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Understanding inflation and the need for hedges            
            
                
Bitcoin’s supply-and-demand dynamics, in addition to growing institutional adoption, position it as a potential hedge against inflation in 2025. However, its high volatility and centralization concerns mean it remains a speculative asset rather than a guaranteed safeguard against inflation.
What is inflation? 
Inflation refers to the general increase in the prices of goods and services in an economy over time, leading to a decrease in the purchasing power of money. As prices rise, each unit of currency buys fewer goods and services. Inflation is typically measured by indexes such as the Consumer Price Index (CPI), which tracks the average change in the prices paid by consumers for a basket of goods an…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Dilip Kumar Patairya</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trump Administration Could Alter Biden-Era AI Chip Rule]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=350146</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/350146/trump-administration-could-alter-biden-era-ai-chip-rule/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T08:24:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[US President Trump and his administration could be looking to bring back a Biden-era rule regarding the export of AI chips to other countries. Supposedly, it’s planning on making a few tweaks to the rule and, in conjunction, do away with its current way of segregating recipient countries into three tiers. According to sources close […]
The post Trump Administration Could Alter Biden-Era AI Chip Rule appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John Law</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Where and how to sell Pi Coin: A step-by-step guide]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/where-and-how-to-sell-pi-coin</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/where-and-how-to-sell-pi-coin?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T08:21:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Key takeaways

Set up your Pi Wallet and secure it with a 24-word seed phrase before transferring your coins.

KYC is often required on both CEXs and P2P platforms to transfer and sell Pi Coins.

You can sell Pi through CEXs or P2P platforms, each offering different security, speed and control.

Always do your own research (DYOR) before selling or holding, as expert opinions on Pi’s future vary.

If you’re here, you probably already know what Pi Coin is and just want to figure out how to sell it. However, a recap awaits, in case you need one. 
While the project pitches itself as a way to democratize crypto access through mobile mining, there are some major concerns that have been hard to ignore:

Pi claims over 60 million users, but blockchain explorers show only about 9.11 million wallets…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Bradley Peak</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Apple Watch SE 3 Display Leaked, May Come In Two Sizes]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=350132</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/350132/apple-watch-se-3-display-leaked-two-sizes/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T08:13:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There is a chance that Apple might be releasing its Watch SE 3 soon, possibly this year, as reported by 9to5Mac. The original model of the watch was released back in 2020, with the 2nd generation being launched two years later in 2022. Like the two preceding models, the third generation may also come in […]
The post Apple Watch SE 3 Display Leaked, May Come In Two Sizes appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ian Chee</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Leaderboard Illusion]]></title>
        <id>https://arxiv.org/abs/2504.20879</id>
        <link href="https://arxiv.org/abs/2504.20879"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T07:58:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Is Bitcoin price going to crash again?]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/is-bitcoin-price-going-to-crash-again</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/is-bitcoin-price-going-to-crash-again?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T07:56:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Key takeaways:

Bitcoin's 28% rebound from $75,000 faces resistance at $95,000, risking a bull trap.

Strong spot price momentum and ETF inflows support a potential $100,000 push.

Bull flag pattern suggests a $108,300 target if BTC breaks the $95,000 resistance.

Bitcoin (BTC) price has rebounded by 28% from its five-month low below $75,000 reached on April 9. However, its failure to break above the $95,000 resistance level decisively has sparked concerns that the latest recovery may trap bulls.
BTC/USD daily price chart. Source: Cointelegraph/TradingView
Bitcoin ETF flows provide a “more solid foundation”
But another big crash may be averted as BTC price momentum is backed by elevated spot Bitcoin ETF inflows in recent days. 
This provides Bitcoin a “more solid foundation” to surge forwa…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Nancy Lubale</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Banks must adopt crypto or be extinct in 10 years, Eric Trump says]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/bank-must-adopt-crypto-or-be-extinct-eric-trump</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/bank-must-adopt-crypto-or-be-extinct-eric-trump?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T07:51:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Eric Trump, executive vice president of the Trump Organization and son of US President Donald Trump, has delivered a warning to global banks regarding cryptocurrency adoption.
“The modern financial system is broken, it’s slow, it’s expensive,” Trump said in a CNBC interview on April 30, adding that the existing banking system “favors the ultra-wealthy.”
“It forced me into the crypto world,” he continued, adding: “And I’m telling you, if the banks don’t watch what’s coming, they’re going to be extinct in 10 years.”
SWIFT is an “absolute disaster”
While emphasizing the need for banks to closely monitor developments in the crypto industry, Trump highlighted the benefits of cryptocurrency’s underlying blockchain technology for the financial system.
He slammed the existing cross-border transact…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Helen Partz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[realme 14T Set To Land In Malaysia On 16 May]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=350149</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/350149/realme-14t-16-may/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T07:51:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hot on the heels of its recent launch of the 14 series, realme has revealed that it will be launching the 14T next month. The upcoming device has been listed on the brand’s official Shopee page with an arrival date of 16 May 2025. Aside from the first sale date, the listing also reveals that […]
The post realme 14T Set To Land In Malaysia On 16 May appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ikmal Rozlan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[I created Perfect Wiki and reached $250k in annual revenue without investors]]></title>
        <id>https://habr.com/en/articles/905812/</id>
        <link href="https://habr.com/en/articles/905812/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T07:45:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TON’s Broxus launches blockchain app scalability platform TON Factory]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/telegram-ton-factory-scalability-launch</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/telegram-ton-factory-scalability-launch?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T06:16:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Open Network (TON) ecosystem participant Broxus has unveiled TON Factory, a new platform designed to accelerate the development and scalability of high-throughput applications like decentralized exchanges (DEXs) and blockchain-based games.
In an April 30 post on Telegram, the project said TON Factory aims to help developers rapidly build and scale projects with modular components, integration tools, and hands-on expert support.
“For OGs already building on TON, TON Factory helps you scale further,” the announcement stated.
The initiative is backed by a team of over 150 engineers with experience delivering production-ready infrastructure in the TON ecosystem, per the announcement. 
Source: TON
“TON Factory will help developers focusing on L2/appchains with TVM tech and ensuring connecti…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Amin Haqshanas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BlackRock Looking to Tokenize Shares of Its $150B Treasury Trust Fund, SEC Filing Shows]]></title>
        <id>c3e9da3d-b1ba-4d10-99bf-07ac25dd1351</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/04/30/sec-filing-shows-blackrock-preparing-150-billion-tokenized-treasury-trust-offering"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T06:15:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BlackRock will work with BNY Mellon in creating a new class of Distributed Ledger Technology shares for the fund.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sam Reynolds</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Samsung To Add Direct Access To Gemini For Galaxy A Series]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=350134</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/350134/samsung-adds-direct-access-gemini-for-galaxy-a-series/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T06:10:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Samsung has announced that it is adding a feature to select Galaxy A series devices that allows users to directly access Gemini using the side button. With this feature, which is already available on the company’s Galaxy S series, users can simply press and hold the side button to activate the AI assistant. The upcoming […]
The post Samsung To Add Direct Access To Gemini For Galaxy A Series appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nurul Kamil</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum ETF staking will have little impact without multimonth rally: Analyst]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/ether-etf-staking-impact-on-inflows-little-price-rally-eric-balchunas</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/ether-etf-staking-impact-on-inflows-little-price-rally-eric-balchunas?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T06:04:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Key takeaways

Approving staking for spot Ether exchange-traded funds (ETFs) in the US may have a minimal impact on inflows unless Ether sees a sustained rally, says Eric Balchunas

ETH dropped significantly in price after the launch of the ETFs last year, unlike spot Bitcoin ETFs, which saw new all-time highs just two months after launching.

Balchunas said that for inflows to increase again, ETH would need a multimonth run and a strong narrative.

Spot Ethereum ETFs being able to stake a portion of the tokens under their control may not help garner inflows without a more sustained rally in the token’s price, says Bloomberg ETF analyst Eric Balchunas.
Balchunas said on an April 29 episode of the New Era Finance Podcast that staking being approved for Ether (ETH) ETFs would have “a little”…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Ciaran Lyons</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Telegram’s TON Takes On Real World Assets With Libre’s $500M Tokenized Bond Fund]]></title>
        <id>ebe6875e-7c61-4b31-9f2e-03a0d9648aa6</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2025/04/30/telegram-s-ton-takes-on-real-world-assets-with-libre-s-usd500m-tokenized-bond-fund"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T06:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Libre’s Telegram Bond Fund ($TBF) will offer accredited investors institutional-grade yield products that will also be available as collateral for on-chain borrowing and product development on TON,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ian Allison</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google’s “Audio Overviews” Feature For NotebookLM Now Supports Bahasa Malaysia]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=350138</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/350138/google-audio-overviews-now-supports-bahasa-malaysia/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T05:59:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google has updated its AI-powered learning tool, NotebookLM, by introducing support for more than 50 languages in its Audio Overviews feature. With this update, users can now generate podcast-style summaries of their submitted content in languages beyond English — including Bahasa Malaysia. According to a recent blog post, Google says the expansion is part of […]
The post Google’s “Audio Overviews” Feature For NotebookLM Now Supports Bahasa Malaysia appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Heirul Kamel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SEC drops investigation into PayPal’s stablecoin]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/sec-drops-investigation-into-paypal-s-stablecoin</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/sec-drops-investigation-into-paypal-s-stablecoin?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T05:46:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[PayPal says the US Securities and Exchange Commission has abandoned its investigation into the payment giant’s US-dollar stablecoin.
PayPal said in an April 29 regulatory filing that the SEC concluded its investigation into PayPal USD (PYUSD) and wouldn’t be taking any action.
The company said it received a subpoena from the SEC’s Division of Enforcement over its stablecoin in November 2023. 
“The subpoena requests the production of documents. We are cooperating with the SEC in connection with this request,” PayPal stated at the time.
In its latest filing, the firm said the SEC notified it in February that the agency “was closing this inquiry without enforcement action.”
PayPal has said its stablecoin is 100% redeemable for US dollars and “fully backed” by dollar deposits, including short-…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Martin Young</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FTX sues NFT Stars and Kurosemi in push to recover tokens]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/ftx-sues-nft-stars-and-kurosemi-in-push-to-recover-tokens</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/ftx-sues-nft-stars-and-kurosemi-in-push-to-recover-tokens?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T05:31:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bankrupt crypto exchange FTX has filed lawsuits against the non-fungible token marketplace NFT Stars and the blockchain gaming firm Kurosemi, which operates as Delysium, accusing them of withholding tokens they owed.
The lawsuits, both filed in the Delaware bankruptcy court, alleged that NFT Stars and Delysium failed to deliver all the tokens paid for by FTX despite repeated attempts to resolve the matter.
FTX claimed in an April 28 statement that it made “numerous unanswered attempts” to engage with both firms, and it would be “contacting numerous other token and coin issuers regarding FTX assets and will be filing additional suits against non-responsive parties.”
Source: FTX
As part of the complaint against Delysium, FTX claimed its defunct trading arm, Alameda Research, paid $1 million …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Stephen Katte</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SEC Delays Dogecoin and XRP ETF Decisions]]></title>
        <id>6bb80abf-8034-42d9-991c-6a51ab9ce9a3</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/04/30/sec-delays-dogecoin-and-xrp-etf-decisions"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T05:25:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The delays are expected as most ETF filings have final deadlines in October or beyond, one analyst pointed out.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shaurya Malwa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BlackRock files to create digital shares tracking one of its money market funds]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/blackrock-files-digital-shares-money-market-fund</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/blackrock-files-digital-shares-money-market-fund?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T05:18:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Asset manager BlackRock has filed to create digital ledger technology shares from one of the firm’s money market funds, which will leverage blockchain technology to maintain a mirror record of share ownership for investors.
The DLT shares will track BlackRock’s BLF Treasury Trust Fund (TTTXX), which may only be purchased from BlackRock Advisors and The Bank of New York Mellon (BNY), the firm said in its April 29 Form N-1A filing with the Securities and Exchange Commission.
The money market fund holds over $150 million worth of assets, invested almost entirely in US Treasury bills and cash.
BlackRock said that the shares “are expected to be purchased and held through BNY, which intends to use blockchain technology to maintain a mirror record of share ownership for its customers.”
Unlike the…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Brayden Lindrea</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[US Treasury’s OFAC can’t restore Tornado Cash sanctions, judge rules]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/us-treasury-ofac-cant-restore-tornado-cash-sanctions</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/us-treasury-ofac-cant-restore-tornado-cash-sanctions?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T04:14:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The US Treasury Department’s Office of Foreign Assets Control can’t restore or reimpose sanctions against the crypto mixing service Tornado Cash, a US federal court has ruled.
Austin federal court judge Robert Pitman said in an April 28 judgment that OFAC’s sanctions on Tornado Cash were unlawful and that the agency was “permanently enjoined from enforcing” sanctions.
Tornado Cash users led by Joseph Van Loon had sued the Treasury, arguing that OFAC’s addition of the platform’s smart contract addresses to its Specially Designated Nationals and Blocked Persons (SDN) list was “not in accordance with law.” 
OFAC had sanctioned Tornado Cash in August 2022, accusing the protocol of helping launder crypto stolen by the North Korean hacking collective, the Lazarus Group.
The agency dropped the pl…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Martin Young</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Strategy’s Bitcoin buys should be ‘super careless’ to pump price — Exec]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/michael-saylor-strategy-bitcoin-buying-approach-super-careless-idea-richard-byworth</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/michael-saylor-strategy-bitcoin-buying-approach-super-careless-idea-richard-byworth?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T03:48:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Key takeaways:

Richard Byworth says Michael Saylor’s Strategy could ramp up its Bitcoin buys by acquiring cash-rich companies and converting their cash into Bitcoin.

He says that Strategy should consider accelerating purchases as the Bitcoin supply on exchanges continues to decline.

Byworth argues that aggressively increasing Bitcoin holdings would boost Strategy’s mNAV, benefiting shareholders.

Michael Saylor’s Strategy should take a more aggressive approach to buying Bitcoin by acquiring companies to use their cash holdings to fund purchases and do away with over-the-counter buys, a crypto executive says.
“Saylor’s strategy so far has been the right one,” Syz Capital partner and Jan3 adviser Richard Byworth said on an April 29 podcast.
Strategy should try “super aggressive” buying
Ho…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Ciaran Lyons</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Linux in Excel]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/NSG650/LinuxInExcel</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/NSG650/LinuxInExcel"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T03:08:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sycophancy in GPT-4o]]></title>
        <id>https://openai.com/index/sycophancy-in-gpt-4o/</id>
        <link href="https://openai.com/index/sycophancy-in-gpt-4o/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T03:06:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What It Takes to Defend a Cybersecurity Company from Today's Adversaries]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sentinelone.com/labs/top-tier-target-what-it-takes-to-defend-a-cybersecurity-company-from-todays-adversaries/</id>
        <link href="https://www.sentinelone.com/labs/top-tier-target-what-it-takes-to-defend-a-cybersecurity-company-from-todays-adversaries/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T02:53:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Malaysia attracts US$3.7 billion in digital investments, solidifying]]></title>
        <id>b95e1bfb983c9cc102bc4266d362a8c2</id>
        <link href="https://www.digitalnewsasia.com/digital-economy/malaysia-attracts-us37-billion-digital-investments-solidifying-position-aseans-tech"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T02:31:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Malaysia’s digital economy continues to go from strength to strength, emerging as a strategic engine of growth that creates jobs, opens new opportunities, and fosters local innovation for businesses]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>@DigitalNewsAsia</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Australia’s finance watchdog to crack down on dormant crypto exchanges]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/australia-finance-agency-austrac-dormant-crypto-exchange-blitz</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/australia-finance-agency-austrac-dormant-crypto-exchange-blitz?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T02:24:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Australia’s financial intelligence agency has told inactive registered crypto exchanges to withdraw their registrations or risk having them canceled over fears that the dormant firms could be used for scams.
There are currently 427 crypto exchanges registered with the Australian Transaction Reports and Analysis Centre (AUSTRAC), but the agency said on April 29 that it suspects a significant number are inactive and possibly vulnerable to being bought and co-opted by criminals.
The agency is contacting any so-called digital currency exchanges (DCEs) that appear to no longer be trading, and AUSTRAC CEO Brendan Thomas said they’ll be told to “use it or lose it.”
“Businesses registered with AUSTRAC are required to keep their details up to date; this includes details about services that are no l…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Stephen Katte</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MDV powers Malaysia's tech innovation with over RM13bil financing]]></title>
        <id>d3f5fdc4ea236d719dc3a9d352d4620c</id>
        <link href="https://www.nst.com.my/business/corporate/2025/04/1209375/mdv-powers-malaysias-tech-innovation-over-rm13bil-financing"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T01:56:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[KUALA LUMPUR: Malaysia Debt Ventures Bhd (MDV) has emerged as a key enabler of the nation’s innovation and digital transformation agenda, with more than RM13 billion channelled into over 1,000 high-impact, technology-driven projects.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bernama</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ledger scammers are sending letters to steal seed phrases]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/ledger-scammers-send-letters-steal-recovery-seed-phrases</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/ledger-scammers-send-letters-steal-recovery-seed-phrases?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T01:50:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Scammers are mailing physical letters to the owners of Ledger crypto hardware wallets asking them to validate their private seed phrases in a bid to access the wallets to clean them out.
In an April 29 X post, tech commentator Jacob Canfield shared a scam letter sent to his home via post that appeared to be from Ledger claiming he needed to immediately perform a “critical security update” on his device. 
The letter, which uses Ledger’s logo, business address, and a reference number to feign legitimacy, asks to scan a QR code and enter the wallet’s private recovery phrase under the guise of validating the device.
The letter threatens that “failure to complete this mandatory validation process may result in restricted access to your wallet and funds.”
Source: Jacob Canfield
A seed phrase, or…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Brayden Lindrea</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[You Wouldn't Download a Hacker News]]></title>
        <id>https://www.jasonthorsness.com/25</id>
        <link href="https://www.jasonthorsness.com/25"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T01:26:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trump Media considers crypto token and wallet for streaming arm]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/trump-media-exploring-crypto-token-digital-wallet</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/trump-media-exploring-crypto-token-digital-wallet?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T23:56:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Trump Media and Technology Group, the social media conglomerate backed by US President Donald Trump, is considering integrating a crypto token and wallet into its video streaming site, Truth+.
"We're exploring the introduction of a utility token within a Truth digital wallet that can initially be used to pay for Truth+ subscription costs, and later be applied to other products and services in the Truth ecosphere," Trump Media CEO Devin Nunes wrote in an April 29 letter to shareholders.
He added that the crypto token and wallet would be part of a rewards program that Trump Media is exploring across its services, which include the social media platform Truth Social and the financial services platform Truth.Fi.
Trump Media first signaled plans for a potential crypto payments venture last Nove…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Brayden Lindrea</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Labor pain, crypto gain — How weak JOLTS data sets path for Bitcoin price to rally]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/labor-pain-crypto-gain-how-weak-jolts-data-sets-path-for-bitcoin-price-to-rally</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/labor-pain-crypto-gain-how-weak-jolts-data-sets-path-for-bitcoin-price-to-rally?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T23:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Key points:

Weak labor and consumer data often precede Bitcoin rallies, leading some analysts to anticipate future economic stimulus programs.

Job openings fell to 7.2 million in March versus the 7.5 million forecast and consumer confidence hit its lowest level since January 2021.

If past patterns hold, Bitcoin could rally by mid-July and possibly reach $140,000 by October 2025.

Macroeconomic conditions have long been seen as a major influence on cryptocurrency prices. Generally, Bitcoin (BTC) and altcoins perform poorly when investors fear that employment and consumer data are weakening. 
According to a US Labor Department JOLTS report released on April 29, job openings in March approached their lowest levels in four years. US employers posted 7.2 million vacancies in March, below the…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Marcel Pechman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Betting markets’ Q1 US GDP forecast flips negative amid tariff turmoil]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/betting-markets-q1-us-gdp-forecast-flips-negative-amid-tariff-turmoil</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/betting-markets-q1-us-gdp-forecast-flips-negative-amid-tariff-turmoil?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T22:58:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bettors on prediction platforms Polymarket and Kalshi are flipping bearish on the US economy. As of April 29, both platforms are predicting that the US will log an economic contraction during the first quarter of 2025 in an upcoming economic data release. 
The US has logged positive growth figures every quarter since 2022, and a reversal in that trend could mark the start of a recession.
The pessimistic outlook marks a stark sentiment shift for prediction markets, which had recently anticipated a positive US growth report. On April 29, consensus Q1 US growth estimates on Kalshi, a US derivatives exchange, plunged from around 0.5% to -0.4% in less than 24 hours. 
Meanwhile, Polymarket bettors are setting the odds of a US economic contraction in Q1 at around 70%. On April 28, they still had …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Alex O’Donnell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Author of Crypto Bills Now Being Rehashed Predicts 'Wicked Hot Summer' in Congress]]></title>
        <id>efd65f86-4255-4797-861a-23f03284b564</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2025/04/29/author-of-crypto-bills-now-being-rehashed-predicts-wicked-hot-summer-in-congress"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T22:49:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Patrick McHenry, the ex-lawmaker who championed last year's crypto legislation, also said he expects a role to be found for Tether in the U.S. stablecoin field.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jesse Hamilton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[No more window switching: Mastercard’s Agent Pay transforms how enterprises use AI search]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3005997</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/no-more-window-switching-mastercards-agent-pay-transforms-how-enterprises-use-ai-search/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T22:24:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mastercard is working with AI companies and banks to allow AI platforms and agents to facilitate transactions.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Emilia David</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trump's Truth Social Mulls Launching Token for Subscriptions in Latest Crypto Push]]></title>
        <id>38806852-3f69-4584-a468-6c835ffce78f</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2025/04/29/trump-s-truth-social-mulls-launching-token-for-subscriptions-in-further-crypto-push"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T21:39:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The company also plans to forge ahead with its ETFs, which will include cryptocurrencies.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tom Carreras</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Edges Above $95K, U.S. Stocks Remain Strong as Analyst Warns of 'Blind' Market]]></title>
        <id>0b77b062-fd9e-4a51-9e8c-b2f07d34ab15</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/04/29/bitcoin-edges-up-to-usd95k-u-s-stocks-remain-strong-as-analyst-warns-of-blind-market"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T20:11:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Secretary of Commerce Howard Lutnick announced that the White House was finalizing a trade deal with an unnamed country.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tom Carreras</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meta unleashes Llama API running 18x faster than OpenAI: Cerebras partnership delivers 2,600 tokens per second]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3005976</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/meta-unleashes-llama-api-running-18x-faster-than-openai-cerebras-partnership-delivers-2600-tokens-per-second/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T20:02:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Meta partners with Cerebras to launch its new Llama API, offering developers AI inference speeds up to 18 times faster than traditional GPU solutions, challenging OpenAI and Google in the fast-growing AI services market.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Nuñez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Researchers are studying how to minimize human impact on public lands]]></title>
        <id>https://undark.org/2025/04/28/keep-wild-places-wild/</id>
        <link href="https://undark.org/2025/04/28/keep-wild-places-wild/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T19:45:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SoFi Plans Major Push Into Crypto Amid New Regulatory Environment]]></title>
        <id>2f3ada3b-e97d-4f16-8191-76362479c063</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2025/04/29/sofi-will-allow-clients-to-invest-in-crypto-again-after-suspending-service-in-2023-plans-major-push"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T19:11:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There's been a “fundamental shift” in the crypto landscape in the U.S., CEO Anthony Noto said on Wednesday.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Helene Braun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tornado Cash Can’t Be Sanctioned Again, Texas Judge Rules]]></title>
        <id>fc5b1370-af53-43a5-b5da-ec4d7b6197e9</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2025/04/29/tornado-cash-can-t-be-sanctioned-again-texas-judge-rules"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T18:43:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In December, a U.S. appeals court ruled that the U.S. Treasury’s Office of Foreign Asset Control (OFAC) exceeded its statutory authority in sanctioning Tornado Cash.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cheyenne Ligon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meta’s first dedicated AI app is here with Llama 4 — but it’s more consumer than productivity or business oriented]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3005961</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/metas-first-dedicated-ai-app-is-here-with-llama-4-but-its-more-consumer-than-productivity-or-business-oriented/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T18:19:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This mainstream exposure will likely accelerate a shift in what people expect not just from consumer apps, but from workplaces...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carl Franzen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Show HN: Beatsync – perfect audio sync across multiple devices]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/freeman-jiang/beatsync</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/freeman-jiang/beatsync"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T17:32:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bamba: An open-source LLM that crosses a transformer with an SSM]]></title>
        <id>https://research.ibm.com/blog/bamba-ssm-transformer-model</id>
        <link href="https://research.ibm.com/blog/bamba-ssm-transformer-model"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T17:24:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chain of Recursive Thoughts: Make AI think harder by making it argue with itself]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/PhialsBasement/Chain-of-Recursive-Thoughts</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/PhialsBasement/Chain-of-Recursive-Thoughts"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T17:19:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Samourai Wallet Prosecutors Are Considering Dropping Charges Under New DOJ Crypto Enforcement Priorities: Filing]]></title>
        <id>9b36b910-d4ee-462e-9886-3535208b8bf1</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2025/04/29/samourai-wallet-prosecutors-are-considering-dropping-charges-under-new-doj-crypto-enforcement-priorities-filing"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T16:46:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The co-founders are each facing up to 25 years in prison for alleged money laundering and unlicensed money transmitting.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cheyenne Ligon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WonderFi’s Dean Skurka on Bringing Users Onchain and Canada's Crypto Evolution]]></title>
        <id>a385b7d2-bf6b-439c-ac1f-788c4e93eea3</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/consensus-toronto-2025-coverage/2025/04/29/wonderfis-dean-skurka-on-bringing-users-onchain-and-canadas-crypto-evolution"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T16:26:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[WonderFi's CEO, a speaker at Consensus 2025, outlines the firm’s Layer-2 ambitions, Australia expansion, regulatory hopes for Canada, and how volatility impacts the industry.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Aoyon Ashraf</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Will Arizona Become the First State to Join Feds in Planning a Bitcoin Reserve?]]></title>
        <id>d9063668-1142-442c-8cc1-b523c9bc1b60</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2025/04/29/will-arizona-become-the-first-state-to-join-feds-in-planning-a-bitcoin-reserve"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T16:11:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new approval from Arizona lawmakers to form a digital assets stockpile must still survive a veto potential from the Democratic governor.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jesse Hamilton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase’s Base Network Achieves ‘Stage 1’ Status, Reducing Centralization Risk]]></title>
        <id>7d072d24-3f60-421a-a920-8e95c984d5c0</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/tech/2025/04/29/coinbases-base-network-achieves-stage-1-status-reducing-centralization-risk"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T16:00:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The move means that Base will now have a security council which will  help approve certain network upgrades if needed.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Margaux Nijkerk</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Create Accessible and User-Friendly Forms in React]]></title>
        <id>6810f59e8deee87383c1bc46</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-create-accessible-and-user-friendly-forms-in-react/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T15:51:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When designing web applications, you’ll often be asked the age old question “How accessible is your website” and “Does it offer the best user experience?”. These are both very valid questions, but they are often overlooked in favour of rich or fancy ...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Grant Riordan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn College Calculus and Implement with Python]]></title>
        <id>6810eebd43aa3d16a14700eb</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-college-calculus-and-implement-with-python/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T15:22:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Calculus is one of the cornerstones of higher mathematics and a powerful tool for understanding change, motion, and growth across countless disciplines. But for many students, Calculus can seem intimidating or abstract. What if you could learn it ste...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Robinhood Crypto Revenue Expected to Fall in Q1 After Record Late 2024 Gain: JPMorgan]]></title>
        <id>566c9f9c-b936-42b1-a04e-184afe5d0f85</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/04/29/robinhood-crypto-revenue-expected-to-fall-in-q1-after-record-late-2024-gain-jpmorgan"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T15:12:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After a 700% surge in Q4 crypto revenue, analysts now expect a pullback in Q1 as trading activity slows.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Helene Braun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Register Models in Django Admin]]></title>
        <id>6810e5a2dc9845a2ab207f06</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-register-models-in-django-admin/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T14:43:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When you're building a website or an app with Django, one of the most exciting moments is when your database models finally come to life. But to manage your data easily – adding, editing, or deleting entries – you need Django’s Admin panel. Now, here...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Udemezue John</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Jepsen: Amazon RDS for PostgreSQL 17.4]]></title>
        <id>https://jepsen.io/analyses/amazon-rds-for-postgresql-17.4</id>
        <link href="https://jepsen.io/analyses/amazon-rds-for-postgresql-17.4"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T14:30:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[UK Government Targets Exchanges and Stablecoins With New Draft Crypto Rules]]></title>
        <id>fcb85fd8-4f27-4591-b2f0-903dd0f5a661</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2025/04/29/uk-government-releases-draft-crypto-rules"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T14:00:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The statutory instruments will see the creation of new regulated activities such as operating a cryptoasset trading exchange and stablecoin issuance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Camomile Shumba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How $330M BTC Hacker May Have Doubled Down on Monero Derivatives]]></title>
        <id>c860b182-cbd2-4443-a40e-0c334598597a</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2025/04/29/did-the-usd330m-btc-hacker-deliberatley-pump-monero-to-make-even-more-money"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T13:56:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Monero rose by 45% after a flurry of spot buys, but open interest increased by 107%.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Oliver Knight</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mission Impossible: Managing AI Agents in the Real World]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/gitconnected/mission-impossible-managing-ai-agents-in-the-real-world-f8e7834833af</id>
        <link href="https://medium.com/gitconnected/mission-impossible-managing-ai-agents-in-the-real-world-f8e7834833af"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T13:54:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tripp launches Kōkua AI as mental wellness coach across multiple platforms]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3005798</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/games/tripp-launches-kokua-ai-as-mental-wellness-coach-across-multiple-platforms/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T13:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tripp launched Kōkua AI, a mental wellness guide designed to deliver real-time, personalized emotional support across multiple platforms.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dean Takahashi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[xMEMS extends micro cooling fan-on-a-chip tech to AI data centers]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3005879</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/game-development/xmems-extends-micro-cooling-fan-on-a-chip-tech-to-ai-data-centers/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[xMEMS Labs, a pioneer of MEMS-based chips, announced that its innovative µCooling fan-on-a-chip tech will be expanded to AI data centers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dean Takahashi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New atomic fountain clock joins group that keeps the world on time]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nist.gov/news-events/news/2025/04/new-atomic-fountain-clock-joins-elite-group-keeps-world-time</id>
        <link href="https://www.nist.gov/news-events/news/2025/04/new-atomic-fountain-clock-joins-elite-group-keeps-world-time"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T12:39:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Download: the AI Hype Index, and “normal” AI]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1115932</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/04/29/1115932/the-download-the-ai-hype-index-and-normal-ai/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T12:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is today’s edition of The Download, our weekday newsletter that provides a daily dose of what’s going on in the world of technology. The AI Hype Index: AI agent cyberattacks, racing robots, and musical models Separating AI reality from hyped-up fiction isn’t always easy. That’s why we’ve created the AI Hype Index—a simple, at-a-glance summary of…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rhiannon Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The AI Hype Index: AI agent cyberattacks, racing robots, and musical models]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1115918</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/04/29/1115918/the-ai-hype-index-ai-agent-cyberattacks-racing-robots-and-musical-models/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Separating AI reality from hyped-up fiction isn’t always easy. That’s why we’ve created the AI Hype Index—a simple, at-a-glance summary of everything you need to know about the state of the industry. AI agents are the AI industry’s hypiest new product—intelligent assistants capable of completing tasks without human supervision. But while they can be theoretically…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Editors</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Web3j Six Month Project Update]]></title>
        <id>68109495670a1300013504c2</id>
        <link href="https://blog.web3labs.com/web3j-six-month-project-update/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T09:10:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[November 2024 - April 2025
This report summarizes the activities and accomplishments of Web3j, an LF Decentralized Trust project, from November 2024 to April 2025. During this period, the project made significant strides in improving the framework’s functionality, enhancing user engagement, and bolstering overall community interaction. 
Key]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>George Tebrean</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[We need to start thinking of AI as “normal”]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1115928</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/04/29/1115928/is-ai-normal/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Right now, despite its ubiquity, AI is seen as anything but a normal technology. There is talk of AI systems that will soon merit the term “superintelligence,” and the former CEO of Google recently suggested we control AI models the way we control uranium and other nuclear weapons materials. Anthropic is dedicating time and money…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>James O'Donnell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[My sourdough starter has twins]]></title>
        <id>https://brainbaking.com/post/2025/04/my-sourdough-starter-has-twins/</id>
        <link href="https://brainbaking.com/post/2025/04/my-sourdough-starter-has-twins/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T08:20:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[An illustrated guide to automatic sparse differentiation]]></title>
        <id>https://iclr-blogposts.github.io/2025/blog/sparse-autodiff/</id>
        <link href="https://iclr-blogposts.github.io/2025/blog/sparse-autodiff/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T03:18:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Alibaba launches open source Qwen3 model that surpasses OpenAI o1 and DeepSeek R1]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3005880</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/alibaba-launches-open-source-qwen3-model-that-surpasses-openai-o1-and-deepseek-r1/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-28T23:56:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Qwen3’s open-weight release under an accessible license marks an important milestone, lowering barriers for developers and organizations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carl Franzen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[I use zip bombs to protect my server]]></title>
        <id>https://idiallo.com/blog/zipbomb-protection</id>
        <link href="https://idiallo.com/blog/zipbomb-protection"/>
        <updated>2025-04-28T22:28:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ex-OpenAI CEO and power users sound alarm over AI sycophancy and flattery of users]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3005850</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/ex-openai-ceo-and-power-users-sound-alarm-over-ai-sycophancy-and-flattery-of-users/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-28T21:49:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crucially, the turbulence also nudges many organizations to explore open-source models they can host, monitor, and fine-tune themselves.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carl Franzen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Beyond A2A and MCP: How LOKA’s Universal Agent Identity Layer changes the game]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3005824</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/beyond-a2a-and-mcp-how-lokas-universal-agent-identity-layer-changes-the-game/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-28T20:35:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The LOKA protocol, a proposed standard for AI agents from Carnegie Mellon University researchers, will give identities and intentions to agents.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Emilia David</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build a Production-Ready DevOps Pipeline with Free Tools]]></title>
        <id>680fe1e69418a1165cb184a2</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-build-a-production-ready-devops-pipeline-with-free-tools/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-28T20:15:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A few months ago, I dove into DevOps, expecting it to be an expensive journey requiring costly tools and infrastructure. But I discovered you can build professional-grade pipelines using entirely free resources. If DevOps feels out of reach because y...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Opaluwa Emidowojo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[30 seconds vs. 3: The d1 reasoning framework that’s slashing AI response times]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3005393</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/30-seconds-vs-3-the-d1-reasoning-framework-thats-slashing-ai-response-times/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-28T19:31:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[d1 framework changes boosts diffusion LLMs with novel reinforcement learning, unlocking efficient, problem-solving AI possibilities.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ben Dickson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build a Website from Scratch – Start to Finish Walkthrough]]></title>
        <id>680fd51ef631538076304a73</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-build-a-website-from-scratch-start-to-finish-walkthrough/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-28T19:21:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, fellow developers! Building a website can feel overwhelming at first – especially when you're staring at a blank HTML file, wondering how it ever turns into a real website on the internet. If you're new to web development, you've probably asked y...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kunal Nalawade</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WorldGen: Open-source 3D scene generator for Game/VR/XR]]></title>
        <id>https://worldgen.github.io/</id>
        <link href="https://worldgen.github.io/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-28T18:39:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Writer releases Palmyra X5, delivers near GPT-4.1 performance at 75% lower cost]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3005734</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/writer-releases-palmyra-x5-delivers-near-gpt-4-performance-at-75-lower-cost/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-28T17:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Writer unveils Palmyra X5: The enterprise AI model that processes 1,500 pages at once, costs 75% less than GPT-4, and enables affordable autonomous agents for businesses seeking automation ROI.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Nuñez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[QuickNode: Building the Infrastructure for the Next Generation of Blockchain]]></title>
        <id>6807d5787fb8500001c39b99</id>
        <link href="https://blog.quicknode.com/quicknode-building-the-infrastructure-for-the-next-generation-of-blockchain/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-28T16:02:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Join QuickNode co-founder Dmitry Shklovsky as he discusses blockchain infrastructure, building decentralized applications, and the future of Web3 development on TheCube's Crypto Trailblazer Series.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>QuickNode</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Enable CORS in Django]]></title>
        <id>680fa40e9096ceb5eeedd90e</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-enable-cors-in-django/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-28T15:51:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you've ever tried to connect your frontend app to your Django backend and suddenly hit an error that looks something like "has been blocked by CORS policy", you're not alone. It’s frustrating, especially when your code seems fine. So what’s going ...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Udemezue John</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Turn Ubuntu 24.04 into a KVM Hypervisor – Quick Setup with Web Management]]></title>
        <id>680fa285102a9fb019d4fa34</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/turn-ubuntu-2404-into-a-kvm-hypervisor/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-28T15:45:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Virtualization lets you run multiple operating systems on one machine. It’s perfect for testing apps, hosting servers, or learning DevOps. A hypervisor is the software that lets you run multiple virtual machines on a single physical machine, and the ...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shamsuddoha Ranju</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Automate Mobile Testing: Strategies for Reliable, Scalable Tests]]></title>
        <id>680fa2440e43e5b002c3c7f4</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-automate-mobile-testing-strategies/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-28T15:44:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mobile test automation uses tools and frameworks to test mobile applications automatically. It replicates user interactions to evaluate the app's functions and detect possible issues early on. This automated approach is helpful since it accelerates t...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nazneen Ahmad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Download: China’s manufacturers’ viral moment, and how AI is changing creativity]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1115909</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/04/28/1115909/the-download-chinas-manufacturers-viral-moment-and-how-ai-is-changing-creativity/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-28T12:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is today’s edition of The Download, our weekday newsletter that provides a daily dose of what’s going on in the world of technology. Why Chinese manufacturers are going viral on TikTok Since the video was posted earlier this month, millions of TikTok users have watched as a young Chinese man in a blue T-shirt sits beside…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rhiannon Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Does RAG make LLMs less safe?  Bloomberg research reveals hidden dangers]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3005592</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/does-rag-make-llms-less-safe-bloomberg-research-reveals-hidden-dangers/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-28T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[RAG is supposed to make enterprise AI more accurate, but it could potentially also make it less safe according to new research.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sean Michael Kerner</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Chinese manufacturers are going viral on TikTok]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1115876</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/04/28/1115876/why-chinese-manufacturers-are-going-viral-on-tiktok/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-28T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Since the video was posted earlier this month, millions of TikTok users have watched as a young Chinese man in a blue T-shirt sits beside a traditional tea set and speaks directly to the camera in accented English: “Let’s expose luxury’s biggest secret.”  He stands and lifts what looks like an Hermès Birkin bag, one…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Caiwei Chen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[UPDATED] Malaysia and Maldives explore new ties in solar, defence, and digital tech [WATCH]]]></title>
        <id>2ff00997f9c35cff9b55bf1c234d9fd9</id>
        <link href="https://www.nst.com.my/news/nation/2025/04/1208426/updated-malaysia-and-maldives-explore-new-ties-solar-defence-and-digital"/>
        <updated>2025-04-28T04:17:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[PUTRAJAYA: Malaysia is eager to explore new avenues of cooperation with the Maldives, including floating solar energy, defence, and digital technology, says Datuk Seri Anwar Ibrahim.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hakim Mahari</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The missteps that led to a fatal plane crash at Reagan National Airport]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nytimes.com/2025/04/27/business/dc-plane-crash-reagan-airport.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.nytimes.com/2025/04/27/business/dc-plane-crash-reagan-airport.html"/>
        <updated>2025-04-28T02:33:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Retail & E-Commerce Innovation Marketing & Tech Summit: Malaysia 2025]]></title>
        <id>cd2a0d19be53d9723fc0475f09d0da2d</id>
        <link href="https://marketech-apac.com/conference/retail-e-commerce-innovation-marketing-tech-summit-malaysia-2025/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-28T01:58:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Retail & E-Commerce Innovation Marketing & Tech Summit: Malaysia 2025]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Zyra Kate Capilastique</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Is your AI product actually working? How to develop the right metric system]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3005642</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/is-your-ai-product-actually-working-how-to-develop-the-right-metric-system/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-27T19:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Metrics are critical for determining AI product performance. But where to begin? Here's a framework to apply across various use cases.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sharanya Rao, Intuit</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bits + Bytes: A Miscellany Of Technology]]></title>
        <id>92c9e6ae0de9449f2a2cd9808d52c95a</id>
        <link href="https://theedgemalaysia.com/node/752832"/>
        <updated>2025-04-27T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[NEWS

Malaysia sees tech salary surge in 2025, led by system engineers

Tech salaries in Malaysia have risen significantly this year, with system engineers recording the highest increase at 8%, according to NodeFlair’s Tech Salary Report 2...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Edge Malaysia</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FORKLIFTACTION, B2B news service and business platform about forklifts and materials handling]]></title>
        <id>20065c212264065b824a3328d06be4fc</id>
        <link href="https://www.forkliftaction.com/pagenotfound.aspx"/>
        <updated>2025-04-27T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[FORKLIFTACTION, B2B news service and business platform about forklifts and materials handling]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Forkliftaction</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DeepSeek’s success shows why motivation is key to AI innovation]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3005636</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/deepseeks-success-shows-why-motivation-is-key-to-ai-innovation/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-26T19:55:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How did DeepSeek attain such cost-savings while American companies could not? Let's dive into the technical details.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Debasish Ray Chawdhuri, Talentica Software</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The True Size Of]]></title>
        <id>https://thetruesize.com/</id>
        <link href="https://thetruesize.com/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-26T15:41:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Malaysia remains 9th largest global exporter of high-tech products]]></title>
        <id>ec83e12fc9489689eba3a736f7c0fd4e</id>
        <link href="https://e.vnexpress.net/news/tech/tech-news/malaysia-remains-9th-largest-global-exporter-of-high-tech-products-4878750.html"/>
        <updated>2025-04-26T02:41:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Malaysia successfully maintained its position as the ninth-largest exporter of high-tech goods out of 143 economies in 2023, the highest recognition it has achieved in the past decade, Bernama has reported.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>VnExpress</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Liquid AI is revolutionizing LLMs to work on edge devices like smartphones with new ‘Hyena Edge’ model]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3005611</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/liquid-ai-is-revolutionizing-llms-to-work-on-edge-devices-like-smartphones-with-new-hyena-edge-model/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-25T22:02:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hyena Edge’s success positions Liquid AI as one of the emerging players to watch in the evolving AI model landscape.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carl Franzen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The new AI calculus: Google’s 80% cost edge vs. OpenAI’s ecosystem]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3005571</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/the-new-ai-calculus-googles-80-cost-edge-vs-openais-ecosystem/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-25T20:26:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Explore the Google vs OpenAI AI ecosystem battle post-o3. Deep dive into Google's huge cost advantage (TPU vs GPU), agent strategies & model risks for enterprise]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matt Marshall</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Create Models in Your Django Project]]></title>
        <id>680be6e3dfe4e9c64b6b0997</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-create-models-in-your-django-project/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-25T19:47:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you're building something with Django, there's one thing you can't skip: creating models. Models are the heart of any Django app. They define how your data is structured, how it's stored in the database, and how Django can interact with it. Now, i...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Udemezue John</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Malaysia remains 9th largest global exporter of high-tech products]]></title>
        <id>e1054193ac5220fd5f3cf3fb0ac3fcbd</id>
        <link href="https://en.vietnamplus.vn/malaysia-remains-9th-largest-global-exporter-of-high-tech-products-post318075.vnp"/>
        <updated>2025-04-25T18:11:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Malaysia’s high-tech exports increased by 2 billion USD to reach 127 billion USD in 2023. He said high-tech exports comprised 58.69% of total manufacturing exports in 2023, up from 52.48% recorded in 2022.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Vietnam+ (VietnamPlus)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Harden Your Node.js APIs – Security Best Practices]]></title>
        <id>680bb2b3917896a550779bcb</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-harden-your-nodejs-apis-security-best-practices/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-25T16:05:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you’ve built an API with Node.js, chances are you’ve thought about security – at least a little. Maybe you’ve heard about SQL injection, brute force attacks, or data leaks. But here’s the thing: it’s not just about big hacks. Even small gaps in yo...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Manish Shivanandhan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[UK agrees to assist Malaysia in technology, new energy]]></title>
        <id>9bba1ab03b6cc59e6474a313d3bc9d9c</id>
        <link href="https://theedgemalaysia.com/node/753068"/>
        <updated>2025-04-25T15:31:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The UK has agreed to collaborate with Malaysia in various fields, including technology and new energy management, said Deputy Prime Minister Datuk Seri Fadillah Yusof.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Edge Malaysia</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Download: how Trump’s tariffs will affect US manufacturing, and AI architecture]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1115868</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/04/25/1115868/the-download-how-trumps-tariffs-will-affect-us-manufacturing-and-ai-architecture/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-25T12:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is today’s edition of The Download, our weekday newsletter that provides a daily dose of what’s going on in the world of technology. Sweeping tariffs could threaten the US manufacturing rebound Despite the geopolitical chaos and market collapses triggered by President Trump’s announcement of broad tariffs on international goods, some supporters still hope the strategy will…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rhiannon Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Need to embrace technological advancements, sustainable practices discussed at country's premier real estate event]]></title>
        <id>13ba8e804fd9567fa951b4f7cc51bead</id>
        <link href="https://theedgemalaysia.com/node/753073"/>
        <updated>2025-04-25T12:00:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Industry leaders, policymakers, investors and experts explored the future of Malaysia's real estate landscape at the National Real Estate Convention (NREC) 2025 held here recently.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Edge Malaysia</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sweeping tariffs could threaten the US manufacturing rebound]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1115827</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/04/25/1115827/sweeping-tariffs-could-threaten-the-us-manufacturing-rebound/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-25T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Despite the geopolitical chaos and market collapses triggered by President Trump’s announcement of broad tariffs on international goods, some supporters still hope the strategy will produce a “golden age” of American industry. Trump himself insists, “Jobs and factories will come roaring back into our country.” While it’s possible that very targeted tariffs could help protect…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Rotman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Is that really your boss calling? Jericho Security raises $15M to stop deepfake fraud that’s cost businesses $200M in 2025 alone]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3005473</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/is-that-really-your-boss-calling-jericho-security-raises-15m-to-stop-deepfake-fraud-thats-cost-businesses-200m-in-2025-alone/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-24T22:18:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Pentagon-backed Jericho Security raises $15 million to combat deepfake fraud that has already cost North American businesses $200 million in 2025, using AI to detect increasingly convincing voice and video impersonations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Nuñez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Intel’s new CEO signals streamlining efforts but does not spell out exact layoff numbers]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3005456</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/games/intels-new-ceo-signals-streamlining-efforts-but-does-not-spell-out-exact-layoff-numbers/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-24T21:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Lip-Bu Tan, the new CEO of Intel, sent out a blunt message to employees saying the company has to reorganize to be more efficient.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dean Takahashi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Zencoder buys Machinet to challenge GitHub Copilot as AI coding assistant consolidation accelerates]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3005445</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/zencoder-buys-machinet-to-challenge-github-copilot-as-ai-coding-assistant-consolidation-accelerates/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-24T20:36:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Zencoder acquires Machinet to strengthen its position in the rapidly consolidating AI coding assistant market, expanding its JetBrains ecosystem integration while outperforming competitors like GitHub Copilot with innovative features such as Repo Grokking and Coffee Mode.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Nuñez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethically trained AI startup Pleias releases new small reasoning models optimized for RAG with built-in citations]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3005435</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/ethically-trained-ai-startup-pleias-releases-new-small-reasoning-models-optimized-for-rag-with-built-in-citations/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-24T17:03:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Pleias emphasizes the models’ suitability for integration into search-augmented assistants, educational tools, and user support systems.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carl Franzen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Evil Geniuses and Theta Labs launch AI chatbot based on esports mascot Meesh]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3005327</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/games/evil-geniuses-and-theta-labs-launch-ai-chatbot-based-on-esports-mascot-meesh/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-24T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Evil Geniuses, the well-known esports organization and brand, has launched its Meesh AI chatbot in a partnership with Theta Labs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dean Takahashi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Driving business value by optimizing the cloud]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1115716</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/04/24/1115716/driving-business-value-by-optimizing-the-cloud/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-24T13:56:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Organizations are deepening their cloud investments at an unprecedented pace, recognizing its fundamental role in driving business agility and innovation. Synergy Research Group reports that companies spent $84 billion worldwide on cloud infrastructure services in the third quarter of 2024, a 23% rise over the third quarter of 2023 and the fourth consecutive quarter in…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>MIT Technology Review Insights</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google adds more AI tools to its Workspace productivity apps]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3005313</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/google-adds-more-ai-tools-to-its-workspace-productivity-apps/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-23T22:43:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google expanded Gemini's features, adding the popular podcast-style feature Audio Overviews to the platform.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Emilia David</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Former DeepSeeker and collaborators release new method for training reliable AI agents: RAGEN]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3005302</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/former-deepseeker-and-collaborators-release-new-method-for-training-reliable-ai-agents-ragen/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-23T20:04:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[RAGEN stands out not just as a technical contribution but as a conceptual step toward more autonomous, reasoning-capable AI agents.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carl Franzen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon’s SWE-PolyBench just exposed the dirty secret about your AI coding assistant]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3005166</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/amazon-swe-polybench-just-exposed-the-dirty-secret-about-your-ai-coding-assistant/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-23T19:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon launches SWE-PolyBench, a groundbreaking multi-language benchmark that exposes critical limitations in AI coding assistants across Python, JavaScript, TypeScript, and Java while introducing new metrics beyond simple pass rates for real-world development tasks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Nuñez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OpenAI makes ChatGPT’s image generation available as API]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3005253</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/openai-makes-chatgpts-image-generation-available-as-api/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-23T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Enterprises can now make Studio Ghibli-inspired images through OpenAI's API.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Emilia David</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[From friction to flow: Why Swissport scrapped its VPN maze for Cato’s SASE platform]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3004830</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/security/from-friction-to-flow-why-swissport-scrapped-its-vpn-maze-for-catos-sase-platform/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-23T16:53:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Swissport ditches legacy tech, deploying a global SASE architecture with Cato Networks securing 26,000 users, unlocking real-time control.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Louis Columbus</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft just launched powerful AI ‘agents’ that could completely transform your workday — and challenge Google’s workplace dominance]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3005118</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/microsoft-just-launched-powerful-ai-agents-that-could-completely-transform-your-workday-and-challenge-googles-workplace-dominance/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-23T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft unveils new AI reasoning agents and Copilot features to transform workplace productivity, with Chief Product Officer Aparna Chennapragada sharing exclusive insights on the company's vision for human-agent collaboration.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Nuñez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cooperations with China continue to drive Malaysia's tech ambitions: experts]]></title>
        <id>7cf31983f27357e33a7e7403d769042c</id>
        <link href="https://english.news.cn/20250423/23952d602d384abe9a3be2f40797fa2d/c.html"/>
        <updated>2025-04-23T09:33:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cooperations with China continue to drive Malaysia's tech ambitions: experts-]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>english.news.cn</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[IBM Tech Innovation Summit]]></title>
        <id>eb7b875c351e513c2d4750bb29a0ab40</id>
        <link href="https://www.malaysiakini.com/news/741130"/>
        <updated>2025-04-23T02:44:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Seats are limited. Register now!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Malaysiakini Team</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[$42.1 million poured into startup offering energy-efficient solutions for costly and unwieldy operational data and AI workloads]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3005163</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/data-infrastructure/42-1-million-poured-into-startup-offering-energy-efficient-solutions-for-costly-and-unwieldy-operational-data-and-ai-workloads/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-23T02:28:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The funding infusion sharpens a mission to make hyperscale analytics radically cheaper and greener at the very moment enterprises fear ballooning data‑center power bills.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ujas Patel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[More accurate coding: Researchers adapt Sequential Monte Carlo for AI-generated code]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3005146</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/more-accurate-coding-researchers-adapt-sequential-monte-carlo-for-ai-generated-code/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-23T00:09:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Researchers from MIT, Yale, McGill University and others found that adapting the Sequential Monte Carlo algorithm can make AI-generated code better.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Emilia David</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SWiRL: The business case for AI that thinks like your best problem-solvers]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3004781</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/swirl-the-business-case-for-ai-that-thinks-like-your-best-problem-solvers/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-22T23:53:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Training LLMs on trajectories of reasoning and tool use makes them superior at multi-step reasoning tasks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ben Dickson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Alabama’s Pursell Agri-Tech teams with Wastech on fertilizer venture in Malaysia]]></title>
        <id>af0a46cec4f3cf8c521e3bd5a58cb6d6</id>
        <link href="https://www.madeinalabama.com/2025/04/alabamas-pursell-agri-tech-teams-with-wastech-on-fertilizer-venture-in-malaysia/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-21T18:21:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Pursell and Wastech Group are establishing a state-of-the-art facility in Malaysia to producte advanced controlled release fertilizers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jerry Underwood</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>