<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2025-05-19T08:51:11.201Z</id>
    <title>AngJianming RSS Feed</title>
    <updated>2025-05-19T08:51:11.201Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Apple KYC glitch on Bybit draws swift executive response to recover $100K]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/bybit-fixes-kyc-glitch-100-k-crypto-recovery</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/bybit-fixes-kyc-glitch-100-k-crypto-recovery?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T08:46:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency exchange Bybit said it had involved team members, including an executive, to fix a glitch that affected a single user who could not go through an Apple-based know-your-client (KYC) system.
In a May 18 X post, the Bybit China Team said it received reports about users experiencing withdrawal restrictions on the Bybit platform due to a KYC verification anomaly when logging in with an Apple ID. The team claimed to have immediately responded and taken action involving multiple departments, including the firm’s chief operating officer, Helen Liu.
Other people involved in the operation were the heads of customer service, risk control, the Chinese-language division, product managers and the technical team. The exchange coordinated its actions with the user.
After an internal investi…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Adrian Zmudzinski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AI News Q1 2025: Is AI Transforming Society or Facing Limits?]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/bobcars/ai-news-q1-2025-is-ai-transforming-society-or-facing-limits-4g71</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/bobcars/ai-news-q1-2025-is-ai-transforming-society-or-facing-limits-4g71"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T08:37:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Abstract


In this post, we dive deep into AI News Q1 2025 to explore the dual narratives of transformation and limitation. We examine breakthrough trends, landmark projects, and the evolving regulatory and technological landscape in AI and machine learning. From Hollywood innovations and personalized retail experiences to hardware challenges and ethical debates, we discuss how AI is reshaping society and the hurdles it faces on its transformative journey. This technical yet accessible exploration leverages insights, tables, and bullet lists, linking to authoritative resources like About Amazon, GOV.UK, MIT News, and Blockchain and Cybersecurity. For the original article, visit AI News Q1 2025.
Artificial Intelligence is in the spotlight as Q1 2025 unfolds with groundbreaking developments …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bob Cars(on)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Certified Cloud Practitioner]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/dhaval_mojidra_63b4734990/aws-certified-cloud-practitioner-516o</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/dhaval_mojidra_63b4734990/aws-certified-cloud-practitioner-516o"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T08:35:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Certification Overview
The AWS Certified Cloud Practitioner is the perfect entry‑level credential for anyone looking to validate their foundational understanding of AWS Cloud. It covers the core concepts of cloud computing, AWS services, pricing models, security best practices, and the shared responsibility model—without requiring any hands‑on technical experience.
Who Should Pursue This?
Non‑technical professionals (e.g., sales, marketing, project managers) seeking to speak the “language of the cloud”
Technical staff new to AWS (developers, sysadmins, architects) looking for a broad, vendor‑neutral grounding before diving deeper
Decision‑makers and stakeholders who need to understand cloud economics and basic architecture patterns
Exam Details
Format: Multiple choice and multiple response…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dhaval Mojidra</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin bulls should &#039;be careful with longs&#039; as BTC price risks $100K breakdown]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-bulls-careful-with-longs-btc-price-risks-100k-breakdown</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-bulls-careful-with-longs-btc-price-risks-100k-breakdown?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T08:29:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Key takeaways:

Bitcoin dropped over 4.5% on May 19, confirming a bearish divergence and threatening a break below $100,000.

Analysts highlight $97,000–$98,500 as key support that the bulls must hold. 

A potential inverse head-and-shoulders pattern points to a retest of $91,000 before any bullish continuation.

Bitcoin (BTC) is down over 4.5% from its intraday high on May 19, falling to around $102,000 in its worst daily drop in over a month.
BTC/USD daily price chart. Source: TradingView
BTC’s drop accompanied downside moves elsewhere in the risk market, prompted by Moody’s latest downgrade of the US government due to a rising budget deficit and the lack of a credible fiscal consolidation plan.
The decline confirms a bearish divergence and, combined with other technical factors, raises …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Yashu Gola</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[#The Chronicles of Sam: 10,000 Hours to Say “Hi” Automatically 💬]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/aws-builders/the-chronicles-of-sam-10000-hours-to-say-hi-automatically-1fi</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/aws-builders/the-chronicles-of-sam-10000-hours-to-say-hi-automatically-1fi"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T08:28:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A Tale of Probot, Lambda, and a Bot Called Rupert 🤖


Meet Sam, our fictional senior developer. You may remember them from their first adventure exploring AWS S3 storage classes ☁️ or their reluctant encounter with AWS Cognito 🔐.
Sam had just closed their fifth GitHub issue of the morning, all of them some variation of “Thanks for reporting!” or “We’ll look into it soon 🫣.” Copy, paste, rephrase, repeat — across three different repositories. It was the kind of thing that made them question their life choices — and wonder if they should’ve just opened that dog daycare center instead. Somewhere in the middle of googling “automate GitHub issue responses without losing your soul” 😩, they found it: Probot. A framework for building GitHub Apps.
It lets you hook into GitHub events — like issu…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jagoda11</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is Multimodal RAG]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/voltagent/what-is-multimodal-rag-pf8</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/voltagent/what-is-multimodal-rag-pf8"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T08:27:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There's a term out there in the AI community today that everybody's using: Multimodal RAG.

Let's get this "RAG" out of the way before we dive into Multimodal RAG. RAG stands for Retrieval-Augmented Generation. Think of it like this: "Go find some helpful info, mix it with what you know, and then give me a smart answer."
Here's the deal - you know those AI chatbots like ChatGPT that seem super smart?
Well, they've learned tons of stuff, but they have some problems. Sometimes their knowledge is outdated, or when you ask about something really specific, they just shrug and say "Sorry, no idea." That's where RAG comes to the rescue. Before the AI answers you, it acts like a detective.
It searches through fresh databases, company documents, maybe even the internet, to find the most up-to-date …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Necati Özmen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[realme GT 7, GT 7T Listed By Local Retailer Ahead Of Global Launch]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=352151</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/352151/realme-gt-7-gt-7t-price/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T08:25:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[realme will be launching more affordable models of the GT 7 lineup this month, following the release of the Pro model. The brand will have a global debut for both the vanilla GT 7 and 7T on 27 May 2025, but it is unclear when exactly it will be landing in Malaysia. While the company […]
The post realme GT 7, GT 7T Listed By Local Retailer Ahead Of Global Launch appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ikmal Rozlan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Announcing Appwrite Sites: The open source Vercel alternative]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/appwrite/announcing-appwrite-sites-the-open-source-vercel-alternative-35af</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/appwrite/announcing-appwrite-sites-the-open-source-vercel-alternative-35af"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T08:24:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You love using Appwrite to power your backend, but when it’s time to actually ship your website, you’re bouncing between tools, platforms, and extra accounts. That ends today.
Introducing Appwrite Sites. 
A new Appwrite product that lets you deploy and host your websites and web apps right inside Appwrite. No more juggling services. No more gluing things together. No more multiple subscriptions. Just build, deploy, and go live. All in one place, and it's 100% open source, the kind that lets you (really) self-host and (really) own your data.
Appwrite has always been about giving you the tools you need to build fast, secure, and modern apps. However, while Appwrite has always worked hard to deliver a great backend experience, one big piece was missing: web hosting.
Until now, you had to rely…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matej Bačo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[🚀 DevOps Journey: Week 2 – Deep Dive into Cloud, SSH, CLI, and Team Dynamics]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/azmat_awan_7d95fae89005de/devops-journey-week-2-deep-dive-into-cloud-ssh-cli-and-team-dynamics-4937</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/azmat_awan_7d95fae89005de/devops-journey-week-2-deep-dive-into-cloud-ssh-cli-and-team-dynamics-4937"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T08:23:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello DevOps community! 👋
☁️ Cloud Platforms – AWS and Azure
✅ Key Accomplishments:
✅ Launched and configured virtual machines (instances) on AWS.
✅ Learned to create EC2 instances on AWS and manage key configurations.
✅ Successfully connected to AWS instances using SSH via private .pem key files.
⚠️ Major Challenge (And Proud Moment):
To solve this:
I shared the .pem file from Windows to Ubuntu.
Used Add Location via file manager, input the system IP, and securely moved the .pem file.
In VirtualBox, I used Shared Folders to manage file access between host and VM.
This took almost 2 days of research and troubleshooting, but I cracked it! 💪
🔐 SSH, Linux, and Shell Scripting
💻 Linux Commands Mastered:
ls -ltr, cat, touch, cd, pwd – navigation and file handling
nproc – check CPU cores
chm…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Azmat Awan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Social Media Affects Our Mental Health?]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/krishanvijay/how-social-media-affects-our-mental-health-1a97</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/krishanvijay/how-social-media-affects-our-mental-health-1a97"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T08:22:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction: Rise Of Social Media


Have you ever thought of scrolling for just 15 minutes but ended up wasting your whole afternoon? If yes, then you are not the only one. At some point, all of us have felt submissive to social media. It’s so addictive that once you start, there is no end to it.
Social media is now part of our routine. Before, people would begin their day with a walk or some quiet time, but now, the first thing most do is look at their phone. There are 5.24 billion active social media users across the globe, which makes up approximately 64% of the world population.
Social Media is a great source of entertainment, it has made connecting with people so easy. But everything has pros and cons; apart from enjoyment, it also affects the mental health of the users. Especially t…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Skillwaala Krishan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[.NET Learning Notes: Unit Test(Castle Dynamic Proxy)]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/alexleeeeeeeeee/net-learning-notes-unit-testcastle-dynamic-proxy-21p8</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/alexleeeeeeeeee/net-learning-notes-unit-testcastle-dynamic-proxy-21p8"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T08:19:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Castle Dynamic Proxy: github
Castle Dynamic Proxy is a powerful library for generating dynamic proxy objects at runtime in .NET. It is widely used in mocking frameworks like Moq to simulate and intercept the behavior of objects during testing.
In mocking scenarios, Dynamic Proxy allows developers to create fake implementations of interfaces or virtual methods. These proxy objects can:
By enabling such features, Castle Dynamic Proxy plays a key role in unit testing, dependency isolation and aspect-oriented programming(AOP) in the .NET ecosystem.
What's a proxy?
What is an interception pipeline?
A simple example for Dynamic Proxy:
Note: If you implement an interceptor and handle the method, the method is handled. If you don't handle it, nothing happens and it may return null.
public interfac…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alex</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Samsung Galaxy Z Fold7, G Fold May Feature Titanium Backplate]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=352134</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/352134/samsung-galaxy-z-fold7-g-fold-may-feature-titanium-backplate/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T08:16:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A report from The Elec has emerged, claiming that Samsung will be equipping its upcoming Galaxy Z Fold7 and Galaxy G Fold with titanium back plates. The latter phone is slated to be the brand’s first tri-fold model. As per the report, Samsung will be using titanium for the Galaxy Z Fold7 and G Fold […]
The post Samsung Galaxy Z Fold7, G Fold May Feature Titanium Backplate appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Newsdesk</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fast API Request Handling]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/hiteshchawla/fast-api-request-handling-39be</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/hiteshchawla/fast-api-request-handling-39be"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T08:08:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In FastAPI, how route handlers (endpoints) behave in terms of parallelism and concurrency depends on whether they are defined using async def or def, and whether the work inside them is I/O-bound or CPU-bound.

Here are the four combinations of route handlers and how they affect parallel or concurrent handling of requests:
async def with async I/O-bound work (e.g., await asyncio.sleep, database calls)





@router.get("/async-io")
async def async_io_route():
    await asyncio.sleep(2)
    return {"status": "async io"}

Handled concurrently
Non-blocking — multiple such requests can be handled at the same time.
Best performance for I/O tasks like DB queries, network calls, file access.
async def with CPU-bound work (e.g., heavy computation, no await)





@router.get("/async-cpu")
async def …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hitesh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Copyleft Licenses: A Comprehensive Guide for Open Source and Commercial Success]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/rachellovestowrite/copyleft-licenses-a-comprehensive-guide-for-open-source-and-commercial-success-31np</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/rachellovestowrite/copyleft-licenses-a-comprehensive-guide-for-open-source-and-commercial-success-31np"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T08:06:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Abstract:

Copyleft licenses have long served as an essential tool for ensuring software freedom while enabling commercial innovation. In this comprehensive guide, we explore the history, core principles, and mechanisms of copyleft licenses, detailing how they empower both open source communities and profit-driven businesses. We cover the evolution from the GNU GPL to modern commercial models like the Open Compensation Token License (OCTL), discuss legal and technical challenges, and predict future trends. With practical use cases, tables, and bullet lists that break down key points, this post provides a holistic view of how copyleft licenses continue to shape the software ecosystem. Read the original article here.
Copyleft licenses are more than just legal instruments—they represent a bri…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rachel Duncan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Zenith of Art Design School Courses in Jaipur]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/zenithofart/zenith-of-art-design-school-courses-in-jaipur-57ae</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/zenithofart/zenith-of-art-design-school-courses-in-jaipur-57ae"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T08:03:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Zenith of Art is a school dedicated to art education. The main objective of providing art and design education is to help people of all ages smile, explore their imaginations and express themselves. And also to maximize the individual’s potential. We love all kinds of crafts, from knitting and jewellery making to clay work and painting. Whether it's through Art & Craft, Mehandi, Fashion Designing, or another creative outlet. So brush up on your skills or discover a new passion! Zenith of Art's comprehensive art program offers a variety of art forms.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>zenithofart</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why is Ethereum (ETH) price down today?]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/why-is-ethereum-eth-price-down-today</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/why-is-ethereum-eth-price-down-today?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T08:03:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Key takeaways:

Ether’s price fell over 5% to $2,380 on May 19, mirroring similar downward moves across the wider cryptocurrency market.

Long liquidations accompanied ETH’s price drop.

Below $2,400 could be a buy-the-dip opportunity.

Ether (ETH) price declined by over 4.5% in the last 24 hours to around $2,380 on May 19. 
Data from Cointelegraph Markets Pro and TradingView shows ETH lost as much as 10% of its value, dropping to an intraday low of $2,353 on May 19 from a high of $2,587 on May 18. Its daily trading volume has jumped by 110% over the last 24 hours to $30.4 billion, reinforcing the intensity of the sell-side activity.
ETH/USD hourly chart. Source: Cointelegraph/TradingView
Let’s look at the factors behind Ether’s losses today.
Ethereum leads crypto market sell-off
ETH’s dro…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Nancy Lubale</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Alert Validation - Lambda]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/aws-builders/aws-alert-validation-lambda-243l</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/aws-builders/aws-alert-validation-lambda-243l"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T08:02:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We are continuing the blog series about testing your AWS alarms. The first part of the series, which looked at CloudWatch actions and EC2 alarms, can be found here.
An untested alarm is not one you can trust.
This time we will look at alarms for your Lambda functions. As before, we will test the alarms by ”breaking” the Lambda so you get the same outcome as when a real issue would occur.
Since this is Lambda, we will add code (or entire Lambdas) to make the Lambda act as we want. I will use Python, but the logic works for all the other supported languages.
I have an examples repo where you can find Terraform code to deploy Lambas and required resources to AWS to test the alarms. You will need to connect your alarms to the Lambda functions, though.
Remember to lower the thresholds on your a…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jens Båvenmark</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JPJ Halts Conversion Of Foreign Driving Licence]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=352118</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/352118/jpj-halts-conversion-of-foreign-driving-licence/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T07:57:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Road Transport Department (JPJ) will stop taking applications for converting foreign driving licence to Malaysian licence from today onwards (19 May 2025). This was confirmed by the JPJ Director-General Datuk Aedy Fadly Ramli through a press statement. Moving forward, foreigners are required to go through the same process as Malaysians to acquire a driving […]
The post JPJ Halts Conversion Of Foreign Driving Licence appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Keran</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vitalik Buterin proposes partially stateless nodes for Ethereum scaling]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/vitalik-buterin-partially-stateless-nodes-ethereum-scaling-privacy</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/vitalik-buterin-partially-stateless-nodes-ethereum-scaling-privacy?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T07:55:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum co-founder Vitalik Buterin unveiled a proposal to preserve trustless, censorship-resistant access to Ethereum, even as the network scales. 
On May 19, Buterin shared a post outlining how to make Ethereum’s layer-1 scaling “more friendly” to users running local nodes for personal use. The Ethereum co-founder highlighted the importance of independent users running nodes, saying that a market dominated by a few Remote Procedure Call (RPC) providers risks censorship. 
RPC providers let wallets, users and apps interact with the blockchain without running their own nodes. Crypto wallets are usually connected to an RPC provider behind the scenes. Buterin said there are risks to this setup. 
“A market structure dominated by a few RPC providers is one that will face strong pressure to depl…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Ezra Reguerra</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[U.S. 30-Year Treasury Yield Breaches 5% Amid Moody's Rating Downgrade, Fiscal Concerns]]></title>
        <id>7b3bb411-34bf-447e-8808-3dd87f427ff8</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/19/us-30-year-treasury-yield-breaches-5-amid-moodys-rating-downgrade-fiscal-concerns"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T07:53:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Rising deficits, reduced foreign demand, and investor unease over trade policy drive bond market turbulence and broader risk aversion.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>James Van Straten</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ripple Signs Two More Payment System Customers in UAE Expansion]]></title>
        <id>2ecfb1df-2865-4b44-9c43-de8eb030ba90</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2025/05/19/ripple-signs-two-more-payment-system-customers-in-uae-expansion"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T07:42:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The agreements follow Ripple securing a license from the Dubai Financial Services Authority (DFSA) in March.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shaurya Malwa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What does the end of mathematics look like?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.awanderingmind.blog/posts/2025-05-18-what-does-the-end-of-mathematics-look-like.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.awanderingmind.blog/posts/2025-05-18-what-does-the-end-of-mathematics-look-like.html"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T07:40:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to read a Bitcoin liquidation map (without getting liquidated)]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/how-to-read-a-bitcoin-liquidation-map-without-getting-liquidated</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/how-to-read-a-bitcoin-liquidation-map-without-getting-liquidated?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T07:38:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Understanding a Bitcoin liquidation map is imperative in dealing with the inherent volatility of the crypto market. The visual tool showcases probable liquidation levels, indicating where large orders may cause cascading price changes. 
This post explores how to interpret a Bitcoin liquidation map, allowing you to trade smarter in the volatile world of cryptocurrency.
What is liquidation in crypto trading?
In cryptocurrency trading, liquidation happens when an exchange forcefully closes a trader's leveraged position due to insufficient margin to pay losses. This usually occurs when the market moves sharply against the position. 
Long liquidations occur when prices fall, affecting traders who bet on an uptrend. Short liquidations happen when prices unexpectedly rise, impacting those who bet…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Dilip Kumar Patairya</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Foxconn builds AI factory in partnership with Taiwan and Nvidia]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008261</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/games/foxconn-builds-ai-factory-in-partnership-with-taiwan-and-nvidia/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T07:14:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nvidia and Foxconn announced they are working with the Taiwan government to build an AI factory supercomputer.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dean Takahashi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nvidia launches AI-first DGX Personal Computing Systems]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008256</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/games/nvidia-launches-ai-first-dgx-personal-computing-systems/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T07:06:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nvidia announced that Taiwan’s leading system manufacturers are set to build Nvidia DGX Spark and DGX Station systems.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dean Takahashi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nvidia-powered supercomputer to enable quantum leap for Taiwan’s research]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008257</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/games/nvidia-powered-supercomputer-to-enable-quantum-leap-for-taiwans-research/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T06:58:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nvidia is powering a supercomputer at Taiwan’s National Center for High-Performance Computing that’s set to deliver over eight times more AI performance than before.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dean Takahashi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nvidia powers world’s largest quantum research supercomputer]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008248</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/games/nvidia-powers-worlds-largest-quantum-research-supercomputer/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T06:48:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nvidia announced the opening of the Global Research and Development Center for Business by Quantum-AI Technology.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dean Takahashi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Metaplanet Buys Another 1,004 Bitcoin, Lifts Holdings to Over $800M Worth of BTC]]></title>
        <id>65261613-9f36-4ccf-982b-6a9ca1b304ce</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/19/metaplanet-buys-another-1004-bitcoin-lifts-holdings-to-over-800m-worth-of-btc"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T06:46:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The average purchase price for this latest tranche was $103,873 per bitcoin, according to a Monday disclosure.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shaurya Malwa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nvidia provides Omniverse Blueprint for AI factory digital twins]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008243</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/games/nvidia-provides-omniverse-blueprint-for-ai-factory-digital-twins/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T06:34:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nvidia today announced a significant expansion of the Nvidia Omniverse Blueprint for AI factory digital twins, now available as a preview.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dean Takahashi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Bull Case for Galaxy Digital is AI Data Centers Not Bitcoin Mining, Research Firm Says]]></title>
        <id>32ad31f0-2549-4827-8de5-23fb4f649096</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/19/the-bull-case-for-galaxy-digital-is-ai-data-centers-not-bitcoin-mining-research-firm-says"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T06:16:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Rittenhouse Research, a new firm covering fintech, AI, and crypto, is giving GLXY a strong buy rating because of its BTC mining to AI transition]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sam Reynolds</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CUKTECH Launches Three New Power Banks From RM179]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=352108</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/352108/cuktech-launches-three-new-power-banks-from-rm179/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T06:13:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CUKTECH is expanding its product line in Malaysia with the addition of three new power banks. The company, which is named after the Cuk DC-to-DC conversion circuit, claims to leverage over a decade of expertise and its close ties with Xiaomi to offer high-performing products for an affordable price. The first of the lineup is […]
The post CUKTECH Launches Three New Power Banks From RM179 appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nurul Kamil</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Metaplanet scoops 1,004 Bitcoin in 2nd-biggest buy ever]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/metaplanet-scoops-1004-bitcoin-second-largest-buy</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/metaplanet-scoops-1004-bitcoin-second-largest-buy?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T06:12:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Japanese investment firm Metaplanet has made its second-largest single Bitcoin purchase ever, scooping up more than 1,000 Bitcoin as the cryptocurrency came within 3% of its all-time high.
Metaplanet said on May 19 that it purchased 1,004 Bitcoin (BTC) for a total cost of around 15.2 billion yen ($104.6 million), bringing its total holdings to 7,800 Bitcoin worth around $807 million at current market prices.
It is the second-largest purchase the firm has made following its buy of 1,241 BTC for $129 million on May 12 in a move that pushed its Bitcoin holdings above that of El Salvador.
Metaplanet has the largest Bitcoin holdings of a public company in Asia and has the tenth largest holdings among public firms globally, according to BiTBO data.
The firm reported a first-quarter BTC Yield of …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Martin Young</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase hit with wave of lawsuits over customer data breaches]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/coinbase-wave-of-lawsuits-over-customer-data-breaches</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/coinbase-wave-of-lawsuits-over-customer-data-breaches?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T06:01:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase has been hit with a flood of lawsuits after it recently disclosed its user data was breached, with users accusing the crypto exchange of mishandling the incident.
At least six lawsuits were filed against Coinbase between May 15 and May 16, which all made various claims that the exchange failed to keep stringent security protocols to protect user data and handled the data breach aftermath poorly.
In one of the lawsuits, filed in a New York federal court on May 16, plaintiff Paul Bender argued that Coinbase failed to protect the sensitive personal information of millions of users during the data breach. 
Users are suing Coinbase, alleging the exchange failed to protect their sensitive data. Source: PACER
Coinbase reported on May 15 that four days earlier it had been hit with a $20 m…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Stephen Katte</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NVIDIA GeForce RTX 5060 Now Available For Desktop And Laptops]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=352076</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/352076/nvidia-geforce-rtx-5060-now-available-for-desktop-and-laptops/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T06:00:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Per its promise, NVIDIA has officially launched the GeForce RTX 5060, the base model and new entry-level GPU of the current Blackwell architecture. More to the point, it’s arriving for both desktop PCs and laptops. As a quick primer, the RTX 5060 is based on the 5nm GB206 GPU, made using TSMC’s 4N process node, […]
The post NVIDIA GeForce RTX 5060 Now Available For Desktop And Laptops appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John Law</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nvidia charges ahead with humanoid robotics aided by the cloud]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008144</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/games/nvidia-charges-ahead-with-humanoid-robotics-aided-by-the-cloud/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T06:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nvidia said it is racing ahead with humanoid robotics technology, providing more Blackwell systems to accelerate humanoid robot development.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dean Takahashi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Show HN: Goboscript, text-based programming language, compiles to Scratch]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/aspizu/goboscript</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/aspizu/goboscript"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T05:51:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘Sats’ vs ‘bits’ debate reignites amid proposal to change Bitcoin base unit]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/sats-vs-bits-debate-bitcoin-adoption-amid-base-unit-change-bip</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/sats-vs-bits-debate-bitcoin-adoption-amid-base-unit-change-bip?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T05:42:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A recent proposal that aims to change Bitcoin’s base unit to make it easier to understand as a payment tool has run into opposition, with critics saying Bitcoin’s satoshis are no more confusing than the dollar’s cents. 
Bitcoin developer John Carvalho introduced Bitcoin Improvement Proposal-177 on April 23, which seeks to eliminate the concept of satoshis, of which there are 100,000,000 in 1 Bitcoin (BTC), and effectively split Bitcoin’s fixed supply of 21 million into 21 quadrillion units.
It follows a 2017 proposal from Bitcoin developer Jimmy Song to create “bits,” representing one-millionth of 1 Bitcoin. However, Carvalho said Song’s approach would still require Bitcoin users to think about decimals and “shifts complexity rather than eliminating it.”
Block Inc. CEO Jack Dorsey is among…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Brayden Lindrea</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nintendo Switch 2 Can Help You Find Lost Joy-Con Controllers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=352114</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/352114/nintendo-switch-2-can-help-you-find-lost-joy-con-controllers/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T05:17:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If TV remotes can slip through the gaps of a sofa, then it’s probably no surprise that the Joy-Con controllers for the Nintendo Switch can. And the Switch 2 may be able to help you with its new Joy-Con controllers in a similar way as the first handheld console hybrid, but with one major improvement. […]
The post Nintendo Switch 2 Can Help You Find Lost Joy-Con Controllers appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ian Chee</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Binance, Kraken Thwarted Social Engineering Attacks Similar to Coinbase Hack]]></title>
        <id>ab41e8eb-40c4-483d-9cef-6519c9206f19</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/web3/2025/05/19/binance-kraken-thwarted-social-engineering-attacks-similar-to-coinbase-hack"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T05:15:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Attackers reportedly tried bribing support agents, but Binance and Kraken’s internal systems blocked the attempts.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Francisco Rodrigues</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase faces lawsuit over alleged breaches of Illinois biometric privacy law]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/coinbase-sued-alleged-breaches-illinois-biometric-privacy-law</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/coinbase-sued-alleged-breaches-illinois-biometric-privacy-law?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T05:06:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A group of Coinbase users from Illinois have filed a class-action lawsuit against the crypto exchange, alleging that its identity checks violate the state’s Biometric Information Privacy Act (BIPA).
Plaintiffs Scott Bernstein, Gina Greeder and James Lonergan claimed in the May 13 lawsuit filed in a federal court that Coinbase’s “wholesale collection” of faceprints for its Know Your Customer requirements violates BIPA, as they weren’t notified.
The group claimed Coinbase failed to notify users in writing of the collection, storage, or sharing of their biometric data and the purpose and retention schedule for their data.
“Coinbase does not publicly provide a retention schedule or guidelines for permanently destroying Plaintiffs’ biometric identifiers as specified by BIPA,” they alleged. 
The…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Martin Young</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Infinix XPAD GT To Be Unveiled In Malaysia On 21 May]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=352127</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/352127/infinix-pad-gt-21-may/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T05:04:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Infinix is set to launch its next entry-level gaming smartphone, the GT 30 Pro, later this week and alongside it, the brand has confirmed that it will unveil its first gaming tablet, the XPAD GT. The tablet has yet to be officially released anywhere, so its arrival on 21 May 2025 is its global debut. […]
The post Infinix XPAD GT To Be Unveiled In Malaysia On 21 May appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ikmal Rozlan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nothing Confirms Making Its Own Over-Ear Headphones]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=352105</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/352105/nothing-confirms-making-over-ear-headphones/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T04:09:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Earlier in the year, Nothing teased the possibility that it was working on its first over-ear headphones, by giving an official-sounding name to a fan design. Over the weekend, the brand posted a video on YouTube confirming that it is in fact working on such an audio product. The video itself is a discussion of […]
The post Nothing Confirms Making Its Own Over-Ear Headphones appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ian Chee</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Samsung Galaxy S25 FE May Have 8MP Telephoto Camera]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=352100</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/352100/samsung-galaxy-s25-fe-may-have-8mp-telephoto-camera/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T03:41:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Samsung is reportedly working on its Galaxy S25 FE, with some of its alleged specs having already been leaked, such as the chipset it may come equipped with. Now, Dutch news site Galaxy Club claims that the phone may sport an 8MP telephoto lens, as per a machine translation of their report. According to the […]
The post Samsung Galaxy S25 FE May Have 8MP Telephoto Camera appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Newsdesk</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin notches record weekly close after highest-ever daily close candle]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-highest-weekly-close-after-largest-daily-candle-close</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-highest-weekly-close-after-largest-daily-candle-close?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T03:19:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin has notched its highest-ever weekly close as crypto market momentum continues and the cryptocurrency is again nearing its all-time high.
Bitcoin (BTC) has closed at a weekly gain for the past six weeks in a row, and its most recent close at midnight UTC on May 18 was its highest weekly close ever at just below $106,500, according to TradingView.
Its last highest weekly close was in December when it reached $104,400. It later went on to reach an all-time high of $109,358 on Jan. 20, according to TradingView. 
Bitcoin is now less than 3% away from its peak price and has gained 2% over the past 24 hours to trade around $104,730 at the time of writing.
Bitcoin also posted its highest-ever close in a 24-hour period on May 18. However, this is not the largest daily gain Bitcoin has made.…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Martin Young</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Malaysia Airlines, AirAsia Update Name Rules For Bookings]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=352092</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/352092/malaysia-airlines-airasia-name-booking/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T03:09:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Malaysia Airlines and AirAsia have updated their respective name entry guidelines for flight bookings. These changes seem to be better accommodate Southeast Asian passengers whose names do not confirm to conventional Western naming conventions, clearing up any confusion. The national airline splits names into “First & Middle Name” and “Last name/Surname”, while the AirAsia uses […]
The post Malaysia Airlines, AirAsia Update Name Rules For Bookings appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ikmal Rozlan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The principles of database design, or, the Truth is out there]]></title>
        <id>https://ebellani.github.io/blog/2025/the-principles-of-database-design-or-the-truth-is-out-there/</id>
        <link href="https://ebellani.github.io/blog/2025/the-principles-of-database-design-or-the-truth-is-out-there/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T02:58:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Layers All the Way Down: The Untold Story of Shader Compilation]]></title>
        <id>https://moonside.games/posts/layers-all-the-way-down/</id>
        <link href="https://moonside.games/posts/layers-all-the-way-down/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T02:49:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Australian feds seize mansion, Bitcoin allegedly linked to crypto exchange hack]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/australia-seize-mansion-bitcoin-tied-2013-crypto-exchange-hack</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/australia-seize-mansion-bitcoin-tied-2013-crypto-exchange-hack?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T02:42:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An Australian man from the state of Queensland has forfeited Bitcoin, a waterfront mansion and a Mercedes-Benz car after Australian Federal Police claimed the assets could be linked to the proceeds of crime.
The AFP-led Criminal Assets Confiscation Taskforce (CACT) said in a May 18 statement that it seized nearly 25 Bitcoin (BTC), alongside the mansion and car, which are together worth a total of 4.5 million Australian dollars ($2.88 million).
The AFP said its investigation began in September 2018 after law enforcement in Luxembourg shared information about suspicious Bitcoin transactions that the agency claimed were connected to the Queensland man, who was previously convicted of hacking a US gaming company.
A waterfront mansion in Queensland was confiscated under the allegation that it's…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Stephen Katte</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Show HN: Job board aggregator for best paying remote SWE jobs in the U.S.]]></title>
        <id>https://www.remoteswe.fyi/</id>
        <link href="https://www.remoteswe.fyi/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T00:38:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[“There are people who can see and others who cannot even look”]]></title>
        <id>https://worldhistory.substack.com/p/there-are-people-who-can-see-and</id>
        <link href="https://worldhistory.substack.com/p/there-are-people-who-can-see-and"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T00:31:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Russia arrests Blum co-founder Vladimir Smerkis on fraud charges]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/blum-co-founder-arrested-moscow-fraud-resigns-blum</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/blum-co-founder-arrested-moscow-fraud-resigns-blum?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T00:29:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Vladimir Smerkis, a co-founder of the Telegram-based crypto project Blum, has reportedly been arrested in Moscow, Russia, on fraud allegations, amid Blum confirming he is no longer affiliated with the project.
The Zamoskvoretsky District Court of Moscow approved a request from investigators to keep Smerkis in custody while he is being investigated, Russian state-owned news outlet TASS reported on May 18.
Smerkis — who previously ran operations for Binance in Russia — is suspected of committing fraud on a “large scale,” pursuant to Article 159 of the Criminal Code of the Russian Federation, violations of which can result in imprisonment ranging from two to 12 years.
It isn’t clear if charges have been filed against Smerkis.
Russian news outlet Mash tied the fraud allegations against Smerkis…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Brayden Lindrea</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin impulse move toward new highs sets a fire under HYPE, ETH, XMR and AAVE]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-impulse-move-toward-new-highs-sets-a-fire-under-hype-eth-xmr-and-aave</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-impulse-move-toward-new-highs-sets-a-fire-under-hype-eth-xmr-and-aave?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-18T23:40:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Key points:

Bitcoin’s rally to $105,980 has traders predicting new all-time highs this week. 

Traders lift their end-of-year Bitcoin price targets to $200,000 based on technical factors and institutional investor adoption. 

Bitcoin (BTC) has been stuck in a narrow range for the past few days, but the rally above $105,500 on May 18 increases the possibility of an upside breakout. Popular trader Alan said in a post on X that Bitcoin could soar to $116,000 early next week.
Another bullish voice was that of Bitwise chief investment officer Matt Hougan. While speaking to Cointelegraph, Hougan said that a supply shock due to increased institutional demand could propel Bitcoin to $200,000 by the end of 2025. He expects seller exhaustion to occur at the $100,000 level.
Crypto market data daily …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Rakesh Upadhyay</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[France Endorses UN Open Source Principles]]></title>
        <id>https://social.numerique.gouv.fr/@codegouvfr/114529954373492878</id>
        <link href="https://social.numerique.gouv.fr/@codegouvfr/114529954373492878"/>
        <updated>2025-05-18T22:27:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Here’s what happened in crypto today]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/what-happened-in-crypto-today</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/what-happened-in-crypto-today?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-18T22:00:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today in crypto, Bitcoin has notched its highest-ever weekly close, Telegram co-founder Pavel Durov said he rejected pressure from France to censor Romanian election content, and retired artist Ed Suman lost over $2 million in crypto after falling victim to a Coinbase impersonation scam.
Bitcoin notches record weekly close as it reaches back toward peak price
Bitcoin (BTC) notched its highest-ever weekly close at just below $106,500 on midnight UTC on Sunday, May 18, as the cryptocurrency is again nearing its all-time high.
Its last highest weekly close was in December when it reached $104,400. It later went on to reach an all-time high of $109,358 on Jan. 20, according to TradingView.
Bitcoin also posted its highest-ever close in a 24-hour period on May 18. However, this is not the larges…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Cointelegraph</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tornado Cash dev&#039;s attorneys say prosecutors hid exculpatory evidence]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/tornado-cash-dev-attorney-say-prosecutors-hid-evidence</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/tornado-cash-dev-attorney-say-prosecutors-hid-evidence?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-18T21:46:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Attorneys for Tornado Cash developer Roman Storm filed a motion asking the court to reconsider the motion to dismiss the case due to the prosecution withholding exculpatory evidence in the form of communications with the Financial Crimes Enforcement Network (FinCEN) dating back to 2023.
According to a May 16 letter from Storm's attorneys to Judge Katherine Polk Failla, the FinCEN documents show that non-custodial crypto mixers do not fall under the legal definition of a "money transmitting business" and that prosecutors have known this since at least 2023.
Despite having knowledge of the FinCEN guidance on crypto mixers, state prosecutors still proceeded with cases against the Samourai Wallet developers and Tornado Cash, the attorneys alleged.
Letter sent by Roman Storm’s attorneys to Judg…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Vince Quill</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hyper Typing]]></title>
        <id>https://pscanf.com/s/341/</id>
        <link href="https://pscanf.com/s/341/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-18T20:41:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Show HN: Python Simulator of David Deutsch’s “Constructor Theory of Time”]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/gvelesandro/constructor-theory-simulator</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/gvelesandro/constructor-theory-simulator"/>
        <updated>2025-05-18T20:22:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pavel Durov rejects EU pressure to censor Romanian election content]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/pavel-durov-rejects-eu-pressure-censor-romanian-election</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/pavel-durov-rejects-eu-pressure-censor-romanian-election?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-18T19:22:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Telegram founder Pavel Durov said he rejected pressure from a European Union (EU) country to censor political content on the social media platform ahead of the May 18 presidential elections in Romania.
According to Durov, a Western European government, which he hinted at with a baguette emoji, approached the platform and requested it censor conservative voices, which he flatly denied. Durov wrote in a May 18 Telegram post:
"You can't 'defend democracy' by destroying democracy. You can’t 'fight election interference' by interfering with elections. You either have freedom of speech and fair elections — or you don’t. And the Romanian people deserve both."
The Telegram founder is an ardent defender of free speech, who is highly regarded in the crypto community for his stances on freedom of exp…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Vince Quill</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[K-Scale Labs: Open-source humanoid robots, built for developers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.kscale.dev/</id>
        <link href="https://www.kscale.dev/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-18T19:16:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Show HN: Sshsync – CLI tool to run shell commands across multiple remote servers]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/Blackmamoth/sshsync</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/Blackmamoth/sshsync"/>
        <updated>2025-05-18T19:10:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[From dot-com to dot-AI: How we can learn from the last tech transformation (and avoid making the same mistakes)]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3007969</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/from-dot-com-to-dot-ai-how-we-can-learn-from-the-last-tech-transformation-and-avoid-making-the-same-mistakes/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-18T19:05:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The AI winners won’t be the ones slapping “AI” on a landing page — they’ll be creating products enterprises can't live without.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kailiang Fu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Fall of Roam (2022)]]></title>
        <id>https://every.to/superorganizers/the-fall-of-roam</id>
        <link href="https://every.to/superorganizers/the-fall-of-roam"/>
        <updated>2025-05-18T18:36:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Show HN: Vaev – A browser engine built from scratch (It renders google.com)]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/skift-org/vaev</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/skift-org/vaev"/>
        <updated>2025-05-18T17:54:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[$30 Homebrew Automated Blinds Opener]]></title>
        <id>https://sifter.org/~simon/journal/20240718.html</id>
        <link href="https://sifter.org/~simon/journal/20240718.html"/>
        <updated>2025-05-18T17:05:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Nears Golden Cross Weeks After 'Trapping Bears' as U.S. Debt Concerns Mount]]></title>
        <id>7c62efb2-7b44-4d03-a19c-75ee592eeafe</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/18/bitcoin-nears-bullish-golden-cross-following-failed-death-cross-echoing-2024-pattern"/>
        <updated>2025-05-18T16:58:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BTC nears golden cross, as Moody's downgrade validates bond markets' concerns about the sustainability of the U.S. fiscal debt.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Omkar Godbole</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto execs beef up security following string of kidnappings: Report]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/crypto-execs-beef-up-security-following-kidnappings</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/crypto-execs-beef-up-security-following-kidnappings?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-18T16:48:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto industry executives are beefing up personal security and demanding more bodyguard services in response to a recent string of kidnapping and ransom attempts worldwide — particularly in France — targeting investors and professionals in the sector.
According to a Bloomberg report, Infinite Risks International, a private security firm based in Amsterdam, Netherlands, is seeing more inquiries into bodyguard services and more long-term clients signing up for a private security detail.
Additionally, French law enforcement officials recently announced enhanced security measures for crypto entrepreneurs and investors, following at least three separate kidnapping incidents so far in 2025.

The measures include security briefings and expedited access to police lines in the case of emergencies …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Vince Quill</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ditching Obsidian and building my own]]></title>
        <id>https://amberwilliams.io/blogs/building-my-own-pkms</id>
        <link href="https://amberwilliams.io/blogs/building-my-own-pkms"/>
        <updated>2025-05-18T16:21:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Show HN: I modeled the Voynich Manuscript with SBERT to test for structure]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/brianmg/voynich-nlp-analysis</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/brianmg/voynich-nlp-analysis"/>
        <updated>2025-05-18T16:09:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spaced Repetition Memory System]]></title>
        <id>https://notes.andymatuschak.org/Spaced_repetition_memory_system</id>
        <link href="https://notes.andymatuschak.org/Spaced_repetition_memory_system"/>
        <updated>2025-05-18T15:48:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What do wealthy people buy, that ordinary people know nothing about? (2015)]]></title>
        <id>https://old.reddit.com/r/AskReddit/comments/2s9u0s/comment/cnnmca8/</id>
        <link href="https://old.reddit.com/r/AskReddit/comments/2s9u0s/comment/cnnmca8/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-18T15:47:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum back to $3K in May? Latest rebound says ETH price &#039;still has more gas&#039;]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/ethereum-3k-in-may-eth-price-still-more-gas-3k</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/ethereum-3k-in-may-eth-price-still-more-gas-3k?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-18T15:05:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Key points:

Ether price rose 3% to $2,550 on May 18, triggering $22 million in short ETH liquidations.

A bull flag on the chart suggests a $3,700 target, with analysts predicting Bitcoin’s price to go as high as $5,000 in May.

Ether’s (ETH) price was up on May 18, rising more than 2.5% over the last 24 hours to trade at $2,536. This recovery reinforces the optimism among traders that ETH price could hit $3,000 in May, citing strong technicals.
Ether wipes out $7.5 million shorts in an hour
Data from Cointelegraph Markets Pro and Bitsamp shows that ETH rose by more than 4.5% to an intraday high of $2,551 on May 18 from a low of $2,440 the previous day.
ETH/USD daily chart. Source: Cointelegraph/TradingView
Accompanying Ether’s losses today are significant liquidations across the crypto m…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Nancy Lubale</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Don’t believe the noise: There can never be too many L2s]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/there-can-never-be-too-many-l2s</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/there-can-never-be-too-many-l2s?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-18T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Opinion by: Igor Mandrigin, co-founder and CTPO of Gateway.fm
Every couple of weeks, it seems another layer 2 rolls out, much to the chagrin of some Web3 industry commentators who are concerned about fragmentation. A recent Gemini Institutional Insights report actually noted how a new Ethereum L2 solution is launched approximately every 19 days. In response to the seemingly endless conveyor belt of new zkEVMs and optimistic rollups coming to market, the chorus of criticism continues to grow louder: “This is definitely the saturation point, no more chains are needed.”
Some of the most outspoken critics of L2s argue that L2s are redundant, but this is narrow thinking. In many ways, the idea that creating new L2s should be slowed down is like arguing that there were too many websites in 1998.…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Igor Mandrigin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[InventWood is about to mass-produce wood that's stronger than steel]]></title>
        <id>https://techcrunch.com/2025/05/12/inventwood-is-about-to-mass-produce-wood-thats-stronger-than-steel/</id>
        <link href="https://techcrunch.com/2025/05/12/inventwood-is-about-to-mass-produce-wood-thats-stronger-than-steel/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-18T12:22:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spaced repetition systems have gotten better]]></title>
        <id>https://domenic.me/fsrs/</id>
        <link href="https://domenic.me/fsrs/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-18T11:42:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BTC price to $116K next? Bitcoin trader sees &#039;early week&#039; all-time high]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-due-116k-next-trader-early-week-all-time-highs</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-due-116k-next-trader-early-week-all-time-highs?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-18T11:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Key points:

Bitcoin is convincing traders that an upside breakout is around the corner, with all-time highs in sight.

One target demands $116,000 next week, moving BTC/USD firmly out of its narrow range.

A quick dip before continuing higher is among the options for BTC price action into the new week.

Bitcoin (BTC) reduced volatility to a minimum into the May 18 weekly close as traders bet on a fresh breakout.
BTC/USD 4-hour chart. Source: Cointelegraph/TradingView
BTC price brews classic breakout signal
Data from Cointelegraph Markets Pro and TradingView showed the area around $103,000 acting as a BTC price magnet throughout the weekend.
Now barely fluctuating up or down, BTC/USD was primed for a liquidity grab, with $105,000 and $103,000 both targets, data from monitoring resource Coi…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by William Suberg</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘Bitcoin Standard’ author backs funding dev to make spamming Bitcoin costly]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/saifedean-ammous-funds-dev-to-fight-bitcoin-spam</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/saifedean-ammous-funds-dev-to-fight-bitcoin-spam?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-18T09:40:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Economist and author of The Bitcoin Standard, Saifedean Ammous, has weighed in on the ongoing debate over spam inscriptions on the Bitcoin network, suggesting he would “throw in a few sats” to fund a full-time developer focused on making Bitcoin spamming more difficult and expensive.
Ammous made the remarks in response to a thread initiated by the pseudonymous developer GrassFedBitcoin, who called for Bitcoin Core to merge pull request #28408, which would enable node operators to filter inscriptions more easily.
According to GrassFedBitcoin, the lack of inscription filtering tools contributes to unnecessary blockchain bloat and undermines Bitcoin (BTC)’s role as a monetary protocol.
“No one running a node wants to relay inscriptions,” he wrote, arguing that the OP_RETURN limit increases we…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Amin Haqshanas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[XRP Price Surges After V-Shaped Recovery, Targets $3.40]]></title>
        <id>22282d22-1502-416f-8550-b19a4462336d</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/18/xrp-price-surges-after-v-shaped-recovery-targets-usd3-40"/>
        <updated>2025-05-18T08:23:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Institutional buyers step in after sharp sell-off, establishing strong support at critical levels.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>AI Boost</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Retired artist loses $2M in crypto to Coinbase impersonator]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/retired-artist-loses-2m-in-crypto-to-coinbase-impersonator</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/retired-artist-loses-2m-in-crypto-to-coinbase-impersonator?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-18T08:13:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Retired artist Ed Suman lost over $2 million in cryptocurrency earlier this year after falling victim to a scam involving someone posing as a Coinbase support representative.
Suman, 67, spent nearly two decades as a fabricator in the art world, helping build high-profile works such as Jeff Koons’ Balloon Dog sculptures, according to a May 17 report by Bloomberg.
After retiring, he turned to cryptocurrency investing, eventually accumulating 17.5 Bitcoin (BTC) and 225 Ether (ETH) — a portfolio that comprised most of his retirement savings.
He stored the funds in a Trezor Model One, a hardware wallet commonly used by crypto holders to avoid the risks of exchange hacks. But in March, Suman received a text message appearing to be from Coinbase, warning him of unauthorized account access.
After …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Amin Haqshanas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SUI Surges After Finding Strong Support at $3.75 Level]]></title>
        <id>dccf97d1-13bb-47c4-a0c9-78f9636b452b</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/18/sui-surges-after-finding-strong-support-at-usd3-75-level"/>
        <updated>2025-05-18T08:05:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The resilient cryptocurrency shows remarkable recovery amid broader market volatility, establishing higher lows throughout trading session.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>AI Boost</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dogecoin (DOGE) Whales Accumulate 1 Billion DOGE Amid Critical Support Formation]]></title>
        <id>3743ea9c-f473-4e11-8b7e-3b7ad26cafd4</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/18/dogecoin-doge-whales-accumulate-1-billion-doge-amid-critical-support-formation"/>
        <updated>2025-05-18T07:30:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The meme coin shows resilience at $0.212 level despite 4.3% price swings, suggesting potential upside momentum.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>AI Boost</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BNB Trades in Tight Range Amid Decreasing Volatility]]></title>
        <id>15df49e0-9f27-4794-b3d0-59e891fc1bb1</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/18/bnb-trades-in-tight-range-amid-decreasing-volatility"/>
        <updated>2025-05-18T06:50:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Despite trade wars and Middle East conflict, the cryptocurrency shows resilience with higher lows forming.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>AI Boost</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[UK to require crypto firms to report every customer transaction]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/uk-to-mandate-crypto-reporting-on-all-customer-transactions-in-2026</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/uk-to-mandate-crypto-reporting-on-all-customer-transactions-in-2026?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-18T04:57:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[United Kingdom crypto companies will need to collect and report data from every customer trade and transfer beginning Jan. 1, 2026 as part of a broader effort to improve crypto tax reporting, the UK government said.
Everything from the user’s full name, home address and tax identification number will need to be collected and reported for every transaction, including the cryptocurrency used and the amount moved, the UK Revenue and Customs department said in a May 14 statement.
Details of companies, trusts and charities transacting on crypto platforms will also need to be reported.
Failure to comply or inaccurate reporting may incur penalties of up to 300 British pounds ($398.4) per user. The UK Revenue and Customs department said it would inform companies on how to comply with the incoming …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Brayden Lindrea</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hong Kong police busts $15M laundering ring that used crypto, 500 bank accounts]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/hong-kong-police-busts-15-million-dollar-crypto-laundering-ring</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/hong-kong-police-busts-15-million-dollar-crypto-laundering-ring?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-18T00:49:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hong Kong police arrested 12 people involved in a cross-border money laundering scheme that relied on crypto and over 500 stooge bank accounts to launder HK$118 million ($15 million), local news outlets reported.
The syndicate was dismantled on May 15, resulting in the arrest of nine men and three women in mainland China and Hong Kong. 
The suspects allegedly recruited others to open bank accounts to receive proceeds from fraud cases, which were then converted into crypto at crypto exchange shops to launder the illicit funds, Hong Kong Commercial Daily reported on May 17.
The criminal organization rented a residential unit in the Hong Kong neighborhood of Mong Kok to plan and carry out its money laundering activities. Of the $15 million laundered, more than $1.2 million was linked to 58 re…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Brayden Lindrea</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Public internet is a bottleneck for blockchain — DoubleZero CEO]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/public-internet-bottleneck-blockchain-networks-double-zero</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/public-internet-bottleneck-blockchain-networks-double-zero?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-17T22:14:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Public internet infrastructure is the critical speed and performance constraint on high-throughput blockchain networks, according to Austin Federa, co-founder and CEO of DoubleZero, a project developing high-speed fiber optic communication rails for blockchains.
"The downside of the public internet is it was never built for high-performance systems. It was always built for this sort of relationship of one big server talking to one little server," Federa told Cointelegraph in an interview at Consensus 2025. The executive explained:
"We have validators all around the world. Rotating leader schedules all the time. And then they switch from having to be massive consumers of data to extremely massive broadcasters of data. So that means that they need huge amounts of resources both on ingress an…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Vince Quill</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Moody&#039;s downgrades US credit rating due to rising debt]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/moodys-downgrades-us-credit-rating</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/moodys-downgrades-us-credit-rating?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-17T20:40:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Moody's credit rating agency downgraded the credit rating of the United States government from Aaa to Aa1, citing the rising national debt as the primary driver behind the reduction in creditworthiness.
According to the May 16 announcement from the rating agency, US lawmakers have failed to stem annual deficits or reduce spending over the years, leading to a growing national debt. The rating agency wrote:
"We do not believe that material multi-year reductions in mandatory spending and deficits will result from the current fiscal proposals under consideration. Over the next decade, we expect larger deficits as entitlement spending rises while government revenue remains broadly flat."
The credit downgrade is only one degree out of the 21-notch rating scale used by the company to assess the c…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Vince Quill</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Adopting agentic AI? Build AI fluency, redesign workflows, don’t neglect supervision]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3007933</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/adopting-agentic-ai-build-ai-fluency-redesign-workflows-dont-neglect-supervision/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-17T19:05:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How can organizations decide how to use human-in-the-loop mechanisms and collaborative frameworks with AI agents?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Imran Aftab, 10Pearls</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mystical]]></title>
        <id>https://suberic.net/~dmm/projects/mystical/README.html</id>
        <link href="https://suberic.net/~dmm/projects/mystical/README.html"/>
        <updated>2025-05-17T18:21:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[High-speed oracles disrupting $50B finance data industry — Web3 Exec]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/high-speed-oracles-disrupt-50-billion-finance-data-industry</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/high-speed-oracles-disrupt-50-billion-finance-data-industry?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-17T18:05:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Michael James, the head of institutional business development at Douro Labs — the company that developed the Pyth high-speed blockchain oracle network — told Cointelegraph that oracle networks like Pyth are disrupting the $50 billion financial data industry that provides critical price information to exchanges, brokerages, trading firms, and other institutional entities.
In an interview at Consensus 2025, the executive said that Pyth Network's data pull model sets it apart from traditional pricing oracles, allowing customers to pay for data on demand, reducing costs for institutions reliant on real-time market data.
Differences between pull and push models in oracle systems. Source: Pyth Network
According to the executive, the financial data industry is currently monopolized by around eigh…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Vince Quill</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Bitcoiner’s guide to South Africa’s Garden Route]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoiners-guide-south-africa-garden-route</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoiners-guide-south-africa-garden-route?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-17T15:21:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[South Africa’s Garden Route, famed for its lush forests, expansive beaches and charming towns, has become a testbed for Bitcoin adoption.
From Mossel Bay to Witsand and Plettenberg Bay to Knysna, Bitcoin has become popular among shop owners and travelers alike for a multitude of reasons.
“We’re seeing the early signs of a parallel, permissionless economy emerging across an entire region,” James Caw, founder of SimplB — a local crypto asset provider — told Cointelegraph, “where small businesses benefit from faster, lower-cost digital payments and where people have more options to earn, send and receive sound money securely.”
For tourists, the benefits are immediate: no currency exchange hassles, no international card fees, and the ability to pay instantly and securely. For locals, Bitcoin (…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Cath Jenkin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The DeFi mullet — Fintech needs DeFi in the back]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/fintech-needs-de-fi-in-the-back</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/fintech-needs-de-fi-in-the-back?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-17T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Opinion by: Merlin Egalite, co-founder at Morpho Labs
Fintechs in the front, decentralized finance (DeFi) in the back: the DeFi Mullet.
Today’s fintech companies offer excellent user experiences but are constrained by traditional financial infrastructure — siloed, slow, expensive and inflexible. Meanwhile, DeFi provides lightning-fast, cost-effective, interoperable infrastructure but lacks mainstream accessibility.
The solution? Combine fintech’s distribution and user experience with DeFi’s efficient back end.
The mullet is inevitable
Fintech companies heavily rely on traditional financial (TradFi) infrastructure that is siloed, slow to deploy and run, and costly to maintain. This inefficiency limits their control over costs and product offerings and has potential infrastructure risks. Fin…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Merlin Egalite</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Over $5B Pouring into Bitcoin ETFs – Thanks to Bold Directional Bets]]></title>
        <id>4401d046-146d-4fa0-8894-d5d19d1da3d4</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/17/over-usd5b-pouring-into-bitcoin-etfs-thanks-to-bold-directional-bets"/>
        <updated>2025-05-17T14:18:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The 11 spot ETFs have attracted over $5.61 billion since early April, according to SoSoValue.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Omkar Godbole</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Alabama Man Sentenced for Hacking SEC’s Social Media to Post Fake Bitcoin ETF News]]></title>
        <id>aeaa9b88-7474-473a-840f-860d9385fdea</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2025/05/17/alabama-man-sentenced-for-hacking-secs-social-media-to-post-fake-bitcoin-etf-news"/>
        <updated>2025-05-17T13:46:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The hack in January 2024 briefly sent bitcoin’s price surging $1,000 before crashing back down minutes later.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Francisco Rodrigues</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[State of Crypto: Consensus Toronto 2025 Reg Highlights]]></title>
        <id>b55a0395-6cfb-407d-aec0-5ec428425539</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2025/05/17/state-of-crypto-consensus-toronto-2025-reg-highlights"/>
        <updated>2025-05-17T13:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Thousands of crypto folks descended upon Canada to talk shop.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nikhilesh De</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin to $250K in 2025 ‘totally possible’ — crypto analyst Scott Melker]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-250k-2025-melker</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-250k-2025-melker?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-17T12:09:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin’s next explosive move could send the asset to $250,000 by the end of 2025, according to Scott Melker, a crypto analyst and host of The Wolf of All Streets podcast.
Speaking in a recent interview, Melker cited growing institutional interest and diminishing volatility as key factors that could drive the next leg up.
“250K this year, totally possible,” Melker said, adding that Bitcoin (BTC)’s volatility has declined significantly in recent years.
“It used to be about three times as volatile as the S&P. Now it’s less than two times.” He pointed to increased involvement from pension funds and ETF issuers as evidence of a more mature, stable market.
The shift, he argued, reflects a broader trend of institutional adoption. “The more institutional money, the more Wall Street money, the mor…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Amin Haqshanas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Movement Labs and Mantra Scandal Are Shaking up Crypto Market-Making]]></title>
        <id>5ed07d6f-b878-412b-a49e-83c5767a3aae</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/17/movement-labs-and-mantra-scandal-are-shaking-up-crypto-market-making"/>
        <updated>2025-05-17T08:41:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Forced liquidations, hidden contracts, and backchannel deals are prompting a rethink in how liquidity is structured — and who gets trusted.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shaurya Malwa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ETH, DOGE, XRP Down 3% as Moody’s Downgrades U.S. Credit Rating]]></title>
        <id>68e3884d-7677-4876-a72b-ed4090ab21bd</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/17/eth-doge-xrp-down-3-as-moodys-downgrades-the-us-credit-score"/>
        <updated>2025-05-17T07:54:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto markets slipped alongside stocks after Moody’s cut the U.S. sovereign credit score to Aa1, triggering risk-off sentiment and fresh concerns over government debt and macro stability.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shaurya Malwa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Undervalued Ether Catching Eye of ETF Buyers as Rally Inbound: CryptoQuant]]></title>
        <id>0628db75-86a5-40c1-9286-ee9d2c12abbf</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/17/undervalued-ether-catching-eye-of-etf-buyers-as-rally-inbound-cryptoquant"/>
        <updated>2025-05-17T07:25:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ETH's rally is fueling investor expectations for a new 'Alt season', according to a recent CryptoQuant report.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sam Reynolds</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[`This Printer company served you malware for months, called them false positives]]></title>
        <id>https://www.neowin.net/news/this-printer-company-served-you-malware-for-months-and-dismissed-it-as-false-positives/</id>
        <link href="https://www.neowin.net/news/this-printer-company-served-you-malware-for-months-and-dismissed-it-as-false-positives/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-17T05:44:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google’s AlphaEvolve: The AI agent that reclaimed 0.7% of Google’s compute – and how to copy it]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3007997</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/googles-alphaevolve-the-ai-agent-that-reclaimed-0-7-of-googles-compute-and-how-to-copy-it/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-17T00:31:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google's AlphaEvolve is the epitome of a best-practice AI agent orchestration. It offers a lesson in production-grade agent engineering. Discover its architecture & essential takeaways for your enterprise AI strategy.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matt Marshall</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Connoisseur of Desire]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nybooks.com/articles/2025/05/29/the-connoisseur-of-desire-the-annotated-great-gatsby/</id>
        <link href="https://www.nybooks.com/articles/2025/05/29/the-connoisseur-of-desire-the-annotated-great-gatsby/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-16T23:22:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[U.S. Stablecoin Bill Could Clear Senate Next Week, Proponents Say]]></title>
        <id>7ec64662-e09a-41d6-8205-fbb2163558b1</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2025/05/16/u-s-stablecoin-bill-could-clear-senate-next-week-proponents-say"/>
        <updated>2025-05-16T22:37:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Senator Bill Hagerty, who backed the Senate's version of the legislation, predicted the body will "make history" next week by passing the bill.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jesse Hamilton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Font Activations: A Note on the Type]]></title>
        <id>https://robhorning.substack.com/p/font-activations</id>
        <link href="https://robhorning.substack.com/p/font-activations"/>
        <updated>2025-05-16T21:52:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Shrink exploit windows, slash MTTP: Why ring deployment is now a must for enterprise defense]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3007233</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/security/slash-mttp-block-exploits-ring-deployment-now-essential/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-16T20:48:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ring deployment slashes MTTP and legacy CVE risk. Learn how Ivanti and Southstar Bank are modernizing patch strategy with real-time intel.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Louis Columbus</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Alchemy Acquires Solana Developer DexterLab for Undisclosed Sum]]></title>
        <id>6a8013cb-a4d1-44a2-bc18-87fe8012e862</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2025/05/16/alchemy-acquires-solana-developer-dexterlab-for-undisclosed-sum"/>
        <updated>2025-05-16T20:03:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The purchase will accelerate the development of Solana-based Web3 applications to meet growing enterprise demand, Alchemy said]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Crawley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Comparing Parallel Functional Array Languages: Programming and Performance]]></title>
        <id>https://arxiv.org/abs/2505.08906</id>
        <link href="https://arxiv.org/abs/2505.08906"/>
        <updated>2025-05-16T19:50:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Eric Trump: 'The Banks Made The Biggest Mistake of Their Lives']]></title>
        <id>a9ca0953-12da-4b62-9b24-530e29a29d4f</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2025/05/16/eric-trump-the-banks-made-the-biggest-mistake-of-their-lives"/>
        <updated>2025-05-16T19:29:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The son of U.S. President Donald Trump spoke at CoinDesk's Consensus conference in Toronto, Canada on Friday.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Helene Braun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Miners Soar on OpenAI-CoreWeave Deal; Galaxy Jumps in Nasdaq Debut]]></title>
        <id>8f87e76a-1ecf-4267-8d07-73eede657336</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/16/crypto-miners-soar-on-openai-coreweave-deal-galaxy-jumps-in-nasdaq-debut"/>
        <updated>2025-05-16T19:15:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Asset prices across markets largely shrugged off surging Inflation expectations, with crypto prices consolidating sideways.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Krisztian Sandor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum Backers Respond to Critics: ‘Markets Will Catch Up’]]></title>
        <id>642d0287-e945-4e75-bce1-ca35572e0577</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/consensus-toronto-2025-coverage/2025/05/16/ethereum-backers-respond-to-critics-markets-will-catch-up"/>
        <updated>2025-05-16T19:01:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum insiders pushed back on criticism of the network’s leadership and roadmap, arguing that the ecosystem is built for long-term value.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sam Kessler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Canvas App Components: A Crash Course for Power Apps Developers]]></title>
        <id>682779afad5694b25984f6b1</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/powerapps-component-crash-course/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-16T17:45:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you have experience in traditional software development, low-code tools may feel a bit sparse at first. But to many people’s surprise, traditional techniques often translate quite well to low-code development. Not always one-for-one – but usually ...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brandon Wozniewicz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[World Liberty's Stablecoin Now Available on Multiple Networks Via Chainlink]]></title>
        <id>5a8ebe0d-55ac-4548-81cc-54ec9e46cb58</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/16/world-liberty-s-stablecoin-now-available-on-multiple-networks-through-chainlink-s-interoperability-protocol"/>
        <updated>2025-05-16T17:32:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The integration, initially supporting Ethereum and BNB Chain, addresses cross-chain security concerns and aims to expand USD1’s reach, the firms said.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Francisco Rodrigues</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CFTC's Christy Goldsmith Romero to Leave Agency at End of Month]]></title>
        <id>51db3dff-fccb-46c3-bfe4-0f2f6f194e61</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2025/05/16/cftcs-christy-goldsmith-romero-to-leave-agency-at-end-of-month"/>
        <updated>2025-05-16T17:31:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Her departure will leave the CFTC with just two commissioners, at least until new chair Brian Quintenz is confirmed by the Senate and sworn in.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nikhilesh De</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TRX Struggles at $0.278 Resistance as Trade Tensions Weigh on Markets]]></title>
        <id>49596c4f-3b1b-42fd-a2f9-1825ff52d508</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/16/trx-struggles-at-usd0-278-resistance-as-trade-tensions-weigh-on-markets"/>
        <updated>2025-05-16T16:56:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tron's blockchain processes over $1 billion in daily transactions despite price consolidation.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>AI Boost</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DeFi Development Surges 30% on BONK Validator Partnership, More SOL Purchases]]></title>
        <id>45ebf0be-085c-48ca-9591-04be44bab385</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/16/defi-development-surges-30-on-bonk-validator-partnership-more-sol-purchases"/>
        <updated>2025-05-16T16:36:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The real estate tech enterprise turned Solana-focused public company now holds 609,190 SOL tokens worth over $107 million.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Krisztian Sandor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Write Math Equations in Google Docs]]></title>
        <id>68275cf15ed8a1db0cf8769b</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/write-math-equations-in-google-docs/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-16T15:42:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Math equations are a critical part of academic papers, research reports, and technical documentation. While LaTeX is widely used for professional typesetting, Google Docs offers a robust set of features for inserting and formatting math equations and...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Vikram Aruchamy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OpenAI launches research preview of Codex AI software engineering agent for developers — with parallel tasking]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3007915</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/programming-development/openai-launches-research-preview-of-codex-ai-software-engineering-agent-for-developers-with-parallel-tasking/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-16T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Starting today it will be available as a research preview for ChatGPT Pro, Enterprise, and Team users, with support later for Plus and Edu.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carl Franzen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Show HN: A platform to find tech conferences, discounts, and ticket giveaways]]></title>
        <id>https://www.tech.tickets/</id>
        <link href="https://www.tech.tickets/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-16T14:05:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Acer unveils AI-powered wearables at Computex 2025]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3007872</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/games/acer-unveils-ai-powered-wearables-at-computex-2025/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-16T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Acer Gadget, a subsidiary of Acer, unveiled AI-powered wearables at the Computex 2025 trade show in Taiwan.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dean Takahashi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Download: the first personalized gene-editing drug, and Montana’s Right to Try experiment]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1116619</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/05/16/1116619/the-download-the-first-personalized-gene-editing-drug-and-montanas-right-to-try-experiment/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-16T12:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is today’s edition of The Download, our weekday newsletter that provides a daily dose of what’s going on in the world of technology. This baby boy was treated with the first personalized gene-editing drug Doctors say they constructed a bespoke gene-editing treatment in less than seven months and used it to treat a baby with a…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rhiannon Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to make Developer Friends When You Don't Live in Silicon Valley, with Iraqi Engineer Code;Life [Podcast #172]]]></title>
        <id>68271ae2c90fa4a071c44a2b</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-make-developer-friends-when-you-dont-live-in-silicon-valley-with-iraqi-engineer-codelife-podcast-172/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-16T11:00:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On this week's episode of the podcast, freeCodeCamp founder Quincy Larson interviews software engineer and live coding streamer Code;Life.   For those of you watching the video version of this interview, she lives in Iraq and she uses a 3D avatar to ...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Access to experimental medical treatments is expanding across the US]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1116526</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/05/16/1116526/access-to-experimental-medical-treatments-expanding-us/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-16T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A couple of weeks ago I was in Washington, DC, for a gathering of scientists, policymakers, and longevity enthusiasts. They had come together to discuss ways to speed along the development of drugs and other treatments that might extend the human lifespan. One approach that came up was to simply make experimental drugs more easily…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jessica Hamzelou</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elon Musk’s xAI tries to explain Grok’s South African race relations freakout the other day]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3007876</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/elon-musks-xai-tries-to-explain-groks-south-african-race-relations-freakout-the-other-day/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-16T02:47:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With its prompts now public and a team of human babysitters on call, Grok is supposedly back on script. But the incident underscores...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carl Franzen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn A1 Level Spanish]]></title>
        <id>68269a8eb0cc91a6c87a682d</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-a1-level-spanish/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-16T01:53:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learning a new language can open doors to new cultures, connections, and opportunities, and Spanish is one of the most widely spoken languages in the world. Whether you're dreaming of traveling to Spanish-speaking countries, connecting with Spanish-s...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Software engineering-native AI models have arrived: What Windsurf’s SWE-1 means for technical decision-makers]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3007851</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/software-engineering-native-ai-models-have-arrived-what-windsurfs-swe-1-means-for-technical-decision-makers/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-16T00:30:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Windsurf's new SWE-1 AI models tackle the complete software engineering workflow, potentially reducing development cycles and technical debt.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sean Michael Kerner</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is Sui: A Comprehensive Guide to Web3 Scalability]]></title>
        <id>6823533984101f00013a5ca4</id>
        <link href="https://blog.quicknode.com/what-is-sui-a-comprehensive-guide-to-web3-scalability/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-15T23:34:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Explore how Sui Network achieves 300,000 TPS through parallel processing, and its applications in gaming, DeFi, and supply chain management.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>QuickNode</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AI Meets Blockchain: Transforming Technology for the Next Era]]></title>
        <id>682354c584101f00013a5cb9</id>
        <link href="https://blog.quicknode.com/ai-and-blockchain-transforming-technology-together/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-15T23:34:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discover how AI and blockchain integration enhances security, efficiency, and innovation in healthcare, supply chains, and financial services.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>QuickNode</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Reduce model integration costs while scaling AI: LangChain’s open ecosystem delivers where closed vendors can’t]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3007838</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/reduce-model-integration-costs-while-scaling-ai-langchains-open-ecosystem-delivers-where-closed-vendors-cant/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-15T23:16:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Through the LangGraph Platform, organizations can deploy agents with one-click deployment, horizontal scaling to handle “bursty, long-running traffic."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Emilia David</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The $1 Billion database bet: What Databricks’ Neon acquisition means for your AI strategy]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3007813</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/data-infrastructure/the-1-billion-database-bet-what-databricks-neon-acquisition-means-for-your-ai-strategy/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-15T22:54:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Databricks' $1 billion acquisition of Neon highlights how serverless PostgreSQL has become essential for agentic AI development.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sean Michael Kerner</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[In Memoriam: John L. Young, Cryptome Co-Founder]]></title>
        <id>https://www.eff.org/deeplinks/2025/05/memoriam-john-l-young-cryptome-co-founder</id>
        <link href="https://www.eff.org/deeplinks/2025/05/memoriam-john-l-young-cryptome-co-founder"/>
        <updated>2025-05-15T22:16:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[From OAuth bottleneck to AI acceleration: How CIAM solutions are removing the top integration barrier in enterprise AI agent deployment]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3007718</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/from-oauth-bottleneck-to-ai-acceleration-how-ciam-solutions-are-removing-the-top-integration-barrier-in-enterprise-ai-agent-deployment/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-15T21:43:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New CIAM platforms are addressing a significant barrier to enterprise AI adoption: identity management for autonomous agents.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Chen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This baby boy was treated with the first personalized gene-editing drug]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1116524</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/05/15/1116524/this-baby-boy-was-treated-with-the-first-personalized-gene-editing-drug/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-15T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Doctors say they constructed a bespoke gene-editing treatment in less than seven months and used it to treat a baby with a deadly metabolic condition. The rapid-fire attempt to rewrite the child’s DNA marks the first time gene editing has been tailored to treat a single individual, according to a report published in the New…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Antonio Regalado</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Arm is rebranding its system-on-a-chip product designs to showcase power savings for AI workloads, targeting a surprising sector]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3007796</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/arm-is-rebranding-its-system-on-a-chip-product-designs-to-showcase-power-savings-for-ai-workloads-targeting-a-surprising-sector/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-15T16:17:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For engineers orchestrating AI pipelines across environments, the modularity and performance tiering within Arm’s new architecture...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carl Franzen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Show HN: I reinvented PHP in TypeScript (demo)]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/vseplet/morph</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/vseplet/morph"/>
        <updated>2025-05-15T16:04:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New research reveals the strongest solar event ever detected, in 12350 BC]]></title>
        <id>https://phys.org/news/2025-05-reveals-strongest-solar-event-bc.html</id>
        <link href="https://phys.org/news/2025-05-reveals-strongest-solar-event-bc.html"/>
        <updated>2025-05-15T13:48:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[You.com’s ARI Enterprise crushes OpenAI in head-to-head tests, aims at deep research market]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3007729</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/you-coms-ari-enterprise-crushes-openai-in-head-to-head-tests-aims-at-deep-research-market/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-15T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You.com launches ARI Enterprise, an AI research platform that outperforms OpenAI in 76% of head-to-head tests and integrates with enterprise data sources to transform business intelligence with 400+ source analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Nuñez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Download: Montana’s experimental treatments, and Google DeepMind’s new AI agent]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1116516</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/05/15/1116516/the-download-montanas-experimental-treatments-and-google-deepminds-new-ai-agent/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-15T12:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is today’s edition of The Download, our weekday newsletter that provides a daily dose of what’s going on in the world of technology. The first US hub for experimental medical treatments is coming The news: A bill that allows clinics to sell unproven treatments has been passed in Montana. Under the legislation, doctors can apply for…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rhiannon Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Adventure Layer: AI Native Onchain Games, Unleashed]]></title>
        <id>6824c55abf73460001094973</id>
        <link href="https://blog.quicknode.com/adventure-layer-launches-on-quicknode-raas/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-15T12:04:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Adventure Layer launches layer-2 chain leveraging QuickNode's Rollup-as-a-Service (RaaS) product.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>QuickNode</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Llama from scratch (2023)]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.briankitano.com/llama-from-scratch/</id>
        <link href="https://blog.briankitano.com/llama-from-scratch/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-15T09:34:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How US research cuts are threatening crucial climate data]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1116485</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/05/15/1116485/climate-data/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-15T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Over the last few months, and especially the last few weeks, there’s been an explosion of news about proposed budget cuts to science in the US. One trend I’ve noticed: Researchers and civil servants are sounding the alarm that those cuts mean we might lose key data that helps us understand our world and how…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Casey Crownhart</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OpenAI brings GPT-4.1 and 4.1 mini to ChatGPT — what enterprises should know]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3007689</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/openai-brings-gpt-4-1-and-4-1-mini-to-chatgpt-what-enterprises-should-know/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-14T23:46:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As OpenAI continues to evolve its model offerings, GPT-4.1 represents a step forward in democratizing advanced AI for enterprise environments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carl Franzen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Beyond sycophancy: DarkBench exposes six hidden ‘dark patterns’ lurking in today’s top LLMs]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3007681</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/darkness-rising-the-hidden-dangers-of-ai-sycophancy-and-dark-patterns/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-14T23:14:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Without a strong push from AI companies to combat sycophancy and other dark patterns, the default trajectory is more engagement optimization, more manipulation and fewer checks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Leon Yen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How DNS Works: A Guide to Understanding the Internet's Address Book]]></title>
        <id>6824f1ac04a60b4a58654ddc</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-dns-works-the-internets-address-book/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-14T19:40:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Domain Name System (DNS) translates domain names (like example.com) into IP addresses (like 192.0.2.1) so we can easily access websites. In this guide, you’ll learn how DNS resolution starts, its step-by-step process, how caching works, and the r...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dhruv Prajapati</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Load Balancing with Azure Application Gateway and Azure Load Balancer – When to Use Each One]]></title>
        <id>6824f10a7d203c180e5ea4b2</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/load-balancing-with-azure-application-gateway-and-azure-load-balancer/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-14T19:37:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You’ve probably heard someone mention load balancing when talking about cloud apps. Maybe even names like Azure Load Balancer, Azure Application Gateway, or something about Virtual Machines and Scale Sets. 😵‍💫 It all sounds important...but also a l...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Prince Onukwili</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elon Musk’s Grok AI is spamming X users about South African race relations now, for some reason]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3007646</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/elon-musks-grok-ai-is-spamming-x-users-about-south-african-race-relations-now-for-some-reason/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-14T19:08:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Grok was caught earlier this year censoring results critical of President Trump and Musk himself, sowing more doubt of its factual integrity.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carl Franzen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build Slim and Fast Docker Images with Multi-Stage Builds]]></title>
        <id>6824b1638a2b26e9d2d0fe86</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-slim-fast-docker-images-with-multi-stage-builds/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-14T15:06:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Apps don’t stay simple forever. More features mean more dependencies, slower builds, and heavier Docker images. That’s where things start to hurt. Docker helps, but without the right setup, your builds can quickly get bloated. Multi-stage builds make...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniel Adeboye</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google DeepMind’s new AI agent cracks real-world problems better than humans can]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1116438</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/05/14/1116438/google-deepminds-new-ai-uses-large-language-models-to-crack-real-world-problems/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-14T15:00:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google DeepMind has once again used large language models to discover new solutions to long-standing problems in math and computer science. This time the firm has shown that its approach can not only tackle unsolved theoretical puzzles, but improve a range of important real-world processes as well. Google DeepMind’s new tool, called AlphaEvolve, uses the…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Will Douglas Heaven</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meet AlphaEvolve, the Google AI that writes its own code—and just saved millions in computing costs]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3007538</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/meet-alphaevolve-the-google-ai-that-writes-its-own-code-and-just-saved-millions-in-computing-costs/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-14T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google DeepMind's AlphaEvolve AI system breaks a 56-year-old mathematical record by discovering a more efficient matrix multiplication algorithm that had eluded human mathematicians since Strassen's 1969 breakthrough.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Nuñez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn Vite for a Better Web Development Workflow]]></title>
        <id>6824ae178a2b26e9d2d0fe4c</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-vite-for-a-better-web-development-workflow/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-14T14:52:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Speed and simplicity are at the heart of modern web development. As applications grow more complex and the demand for rapid iteration increases, developers are constantly searching for tools that minimize friction and maximize productivity. Tradition...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Web Services Work – The Unseen Engines of the Connected World]]></title>
        <id>6824ad336ea9fe84cfb4d0c4</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-web-services-work-with-examples/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-14T14:48:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Have you ever wondered how your weather app instantly knows the forecast, how you can book flights from multiple airlines on one travel site, or how logging into one service can magically log you into another? The answer often lies in a powerful, yet...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kumar Anand</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Master Kotlin & Android 60-Hour Course]]></title>
        <id>6824aba7be2c002301d59188</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/master-kotlin-and-android-60-hour-course/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-14T14:41:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Do you want to create the next groundbreaking mobile app? Kotlin, a modern and powerful language officially backed by Google, not only makes Android development more efficient and enjoyable but also opens doors to diverse programming opportunities be...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[QuickLee V2: An Improved Transparent Look into RPC Provider Latency]]></title>
        <id>680fc8e1f8ae810001969b47</id>
        <link href="https://blog.quicknode.com/quicklee-v2/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-14T13:57:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[View public and real-time dashboards to better understand latency and speed when evaluating RPC providers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>QuickNode</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Patronus AI debuts Percival to help enterprises monitor failing AI agents at scale]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3007592</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/patronus-ai-debuts-percival-to-help-enterprises-monitor-failing-ai-agents-at-scale/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-14T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Patronus AI introduces Percival, a real-time monitoring platform that helps enterprises detect, debug, and prevent failures in autonomous AI agents to improve reliability, safety, and scalability.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Nuñez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The first US hub for experimental medical treatments is coming]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1116428</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/05/14/1116428/first-us-hub-for-experimental-medical-treatments/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-14T12:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A bill that allows medical clinics to sell unproven treatments has been passed in Montana.  Under the legislation, doctors can apply for a license to open an experimental treatment clinic and recommend and sell therapies not approved by the Food and Drug Administration (FDA) to their patients. Once it’s signed by the governor, the law…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jessica Hamzelou</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The VentureBeat AI survey is back: Are you ready for the agentic AI future?]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3007483</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/the-venturebeat-ai-survey-is-back-are-you-ready-for-the-agentic-ai-future/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-14T12:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AI is a critical competitive advantage — and it’s time to find out how your company stacks up. The annual VentureBeat AI survey is back. The survey is brought to you by ActiveFence, a leader in expert-driven gen AI safety and security solutions, and returns alongside Transform 2025 in SF this June 24 and 25. […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>VB Staff</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Download: taking the temperature of snow, and the future of privacy]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1116426</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/05/14/1116426/the-download-taking-the-temperature-of-snow-and-the-future-of-privacy/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-14T12:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is today’s edition of The Download, our weekday newsletter that provides a daily dose of what’s going on in the world of technology. Why climate researchers are taking the temperature of mountain snow The Sierra’s frozen reservoir provides about a third of California’s water and most of what comes out of the faucets, shower heads, and…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rhiannon Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why climate researchers are taking the temperature of mountain snow]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1116395</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/05/14/1116395/why-climate-researchers-are-taking-the-temperature-of-mountain-snow/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-14T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On a crisp morning in early April, Dan McEvoy and Bjoern Bingham cut clean lines down a wide run at the Heavenly Ski Resort in South Lake Tahoe, then ducked under a rope line cordoning off a patch of untouched snow.  They side-stepped up a small incline, poled past a row of Jeffrey pines, then…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>James Temple</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Notion bets big on integrated LLMs, adds GPT-4.1 and Claude 3.7 to platform]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3007515</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/notion-bets-big-on-integrated-llms-adds-gpt-4-1-and-claude-3-7-to-platform/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-13T22:18:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Notion used OpenAI's GPT-4.1 and Anthropic's Claude 3.7 for its new AI features for enterprises, moving away from reasoning models.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Emilia David</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What your tools miss at 2:13 AM: How gen AI attack chains exploit telemetry lag – Part 2]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3005726</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/what-your-tools-miss-at-213-am-how-gen-ai-attack-chains-exploit-telemetry-lag-part-2/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-13T22:05:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Explore a strategic 2025 roadmap for cybersecurity leaders to tackle GenAI, insider risks, and team burnout with actionable guidance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Louis Columbus</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AI power rankings upended: OpenAI, Google rise as Anthropic falls, Poe report finds]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3007490</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/ai-power-rankings-upended-openai-google-rise-as-anthropic-falls-poe-report-finds/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-13T19:13:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New Poe data reveals major shifts in AI market share as OpenAI and Google gain ground while specialized reasoning models surge to 10% of usage in 2025.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Nuñez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SimilarWeb’s new AI usage report reveals 5 surprising findings, including explosive growth in coding tools]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3007475</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/similarwebs-new-ai-usage-report-reveals-5-surprising-findings-including-explosive-growth-in-coding-tools/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-13T17:22:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The signs point to early-stage AI disruption beginning to erode the utility of some legacy platforms. It also offers a hint to enterprises...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carl Franzen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The interoperability breakthrough: How MCP is becoming enterprise AI’s universal language]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3007355</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/the-interoperability-breakthrough-how-mcp-is-becoming-enterprise-ais-universal-language/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-13T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Just a few months after it's release, MCP adoption is growing. VentureBeat spoke to some enterprises asking why MCP is winning the standards race.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Emilia David</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Download: CRISPR in court, and the police’s ban-skirting AI]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1116357</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/05/13/1116357/the-download-crispr-in-court-and-the-polices-ban-skirting-ai/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-13T12:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is today’s edition of The Download, our weekday newsletter that provides a daily dose of what’s going on in the world of technology. A US court just put ownership of CRISPR back in play The CRISPR patents are back in play. Yesterday, the US Court of Appeals for the Federal Circuit said scientists Jennifer Doudna and…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rhiannon Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Breathe lands $21M Series B to predict battery performance]]></title>
        <id>https://techcrunch.com/?p=3003769</id>
        <link href="https://techcrunch.com/2025/05/07/breathe-lands-21m-series-b-to-predict-battery-performance/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-07T12:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Breathe has developed a suite of tools that it says helps automakers and others get the most out of their batteries.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tim De Chant</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Join the 2025 Web3j Mentorships: Build the Future of Ethereum on the JVM]]></title>
        <id>6819c8dc41eeeb000183d37b</id>
        <link href="https://blog.web3labs.com/join-the-2025-web3j-mentorships-build-the-future-of-ethereum-on-the-jvm/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T08:32:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Linux Foundation’s Decentralized Trust (LFDT) mentorship program is back in 2025 with two exciting opportunities for developers passionate about Ethereum, Android, and the Java Virtual Machine (JVM). Whether you’re a seasoned blockchain developer or an Android enthusiast eager to dive into Web3, these mentorships offer]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>George Tebrean</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>