<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2025-05-09T14:13:37.217Z</id>
    <title>AngJianming RSS Feed</title>
    <updated>2025-05-09T14:13:37.217Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Itter.sh – Micro-Blogging via Terminal]]></title>
        <id>https://www.itter.sh/</id>
        <link href="https://www.itter.sh/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-09T14:02:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[I Just Wanted to Code. Now I'm a CTO]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/bobysf12/i-just-wanted-to-code-now-im-a-cto-25jj</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/bobysf12/i-just-wanted-to-code-now-im-a-cto-25jj"/>
        <updated>2025-05-09T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I never planned to be a CTO. I just wanted to build cool things and solve real world problems.
Today, I lead a small team, manage our infrastructure, make technical decisions, and still write a lot of code every day.
My younger self would have never imagined this path.
My first programming job came during my second year of college. I joined as a junior programmer building a school management system using ASP.NET Web Forms. The codebase followed a clean structure with multi-layer architecture, MVC, and solid naming conventions. It was my first exposure to how real software was built, and I loved it.
But I was curious about more. Web Forms felt outdated, and I kept wondering how modern web apps were built. That curiosity led me to discover AngularJS and React. It completely changed how I saw…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Boby Santoso</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[My Wins of the Week! ⭐]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/anitaolsen/my-wins-of-the-week-31ak</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/anitaolsen/my-wins-of-the-week-31ak"/>
        <updated>2025-05-09T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[📰 I published a new post on DEV! ✨
What Qualities Make a Great Software Developer?
Anita Olsen ・ May 6
#discuss
      
💡 I can now make a button in Markdown! ✨
🎮 Visit my web page
 

 
💻 I completed 28 singleplayer levels and I played multiplayer levels daily on CodeCombat! ✨

 

🔥 I hit a 17 days streak on W3Schools! ✨
 
 

🎯 I met my weekly target on Codecademy! ✨
 
 


The will to win, the desire to succeed, the urge to reach your full potential… these are the keys that will unlock the door to personal excellence. – Confucius  
Thank you for reading! ♡]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Anita Olsen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Show HN: Hyper – Standards first React alternative]]></title>
        <id>https://nuejs.org/blog/standards-first-react-alternative/</id>
        <link href="https://nuejs.org/blog/standards-first-react-alternative/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-09T13:59:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PiGEF: A GPU-accelerated open-source Graphics Extension]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/pixloro/pigef-a-gpu-accelerated-open-source-graphics-extension-20p0</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/pixloro/pigef-a-gpu-accelerated-open-source-graphics-extension-20p0"/>
        <updated>2025-05-09T13:58:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is a library and rendering engine, it's efficient, faster, and doesn't need overkill hardware.
So here How it work:
We use a grade system from black (darker) to white (lighter) is identify and rendered by number 0 = black to 255 = white, if is more lighter we do the white (125-255) and if not lighter but darker we do dark (000-124) Why? Because if we do traditional strategy it will lose performances and slow down it but if we do like 20s that will use like 128mb of VRAM place of GB, then we combine the grade with color set grade.
A color set it's who take care of color and with two category the cool one blue and purple, and the warm one red and yellow. For blinding is should be at the exact pixel and  make different plate for optimize the first one red then the yellow... When is stick between them the grade make the emissions red be more white or be pink.
Then the final part material set it's care about quality and rending and is heavy, for that we use reference for M001 is steel if is in the view of the player is called than execute but how is work when is called we use data more Grey is hard...
Advice: Please don't delete folder in library if you delete color set say goodbyes to color stuck in black and white.
For the nest post is performance, more detail, how work material, light, reference, and free.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>sami ourrak</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pope Art, Pop Culture, and AI vs. "Authentic" Artwork]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/ingosteinke/pope-art-pop-culture-and-ai-vs-authentic-artwork-6ac</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/ingosteinke/pope-art-pop-culture-and-ai-vs-authentic-artwork-6ac"/>
        <updated>2025-05-09T13:56:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Thoughts and observations about viral AI art, fake popes, Berlin's "Sellerie Weekend", dreams and experimental processes in real life, originally posted as Pope Art, Pop Culture, and Analog Authenticity at Open Mind Culture and published on my Substack.
Last month I wrote about alternatives to mainstream social media. I still use Instagram and LinkedIn to connect with new people and share some short and short time information and inspiration. However, I prefer blog posts as more in-depth and less short-lived medium.
The late Pope Francis was celebrated as a popular fighter against poverty and for peace, but perhaps the most famous image of Francis was invented by AI artists: in 2023, an image went viral showing the Pope in a white Balenciaga puffer jacket, an outfit that the modest Pope wo…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ingo Steinke, web developer</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dasung Paperlike 13K is a 13.3 inch E Ink color monitor]]></title>
        <id>https://liliputing.com/dasung-paperlike-13k-is-a-13-3-inch-e-ink-color-monitor-crowdfunding/</id>
        <link href="https://liliputing.com/dasung-paperlike-13k-is-a-13-3-inch-e-ink-color-monitor-crowdfunding/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-09T13:56:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mastering Kubernetes Deployments: A Step-by-Step Guide to Managing Containers at Scale]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/cliffordisaboke/mastering-kubernetes-deployments-a-step-by-step-guide-to-managing-containers-at-scale-2dg</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/cliffordisaboke/mastering-kubernetes-deployments-a-step-by-step-guide-to-managing-containers-at-scale-2dg"/>
        <updated>2025-05-09T13:48:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction
What is Kubernetes?
Why Use Kubernetes?
Scalability: 
High Availability:
Service Discovery and Load Balancing: 
Automated Rollouts and Rollbacks:
Key Kubernetes Concepts
Pods: 
Nodes: 
Clusters: 
Deployments: 
Getting Started with Kubernetes
Install Minikube: Minikube is a tool that makes it easy to run Kubernetes clusters locally.
minikube start
Create Your First Deployment
kubectl create deployment nginx --image=nginx
Expose Your Deployment
kubectl expose deployment nginx --port=80 --type=LoadBalancer
Scaling the Application
kubectl scale deployment nginx --replicas=3
Check Pod Status
kubectl get pods
Best Practices for Managing Kubernetes Applications
Use Namespaces: 
Use Helm for Package Management: 
Monitor with Prometheus and Grafana: 
Set Resource Requests and Limits: 
Conclusion
Call to Action:
If you’re starting with Kubernetes or looking to optimize your workflow, try deploying your own app and share your experience in the comments.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CliffordIsaboke</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Institutional investors continue to scoop up Bitcoin above $100K]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/institutional-investors-continue-to-scoop-up-bitcoin-above-100-k</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/institutional-investors-continue-to-scoop-up-bitcoin-above-100-k?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-09T13:46:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin crossed the $100,000 mark again on May 8 as institutional investors continue stacking sats.
Farside Investors’ data shows that spot Bitcoin (BTC) exchange-traded funds (ETFs) recorded cumulative net inflows of $142.3 million on May 7, in a sign of “sustained institutional interest,” according to the founder of Obchakevich Research, Alex Obchakevich.
“These inflows indicate the activity of institutional investors, including hedge funds and asset managers, who continue to accumulate BTC through regulated instruments,“ he said.
The ARK 21Shares Bitcoin ETF (ARKB) led with $54 million in inflows, followed by Fidelity’s Wise Origin Bitcoin Fund (FBTC) at $39 million and BlackRock’s iShares Bitcoin Trust (IBIT) at $37 million. Data from Arkham Intelligence shows BlackRock acquired more t…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Adrian Zmudzinski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Set Scrollbar Thumb Height in CSS?]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/generatecodedev/how-to-set-scrollbar-thumb-height-in-css-3coi</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/generatecodedev/how-to-set-scrollbar-thumb-height-in-css-3coi"/>
        <updated>2025-05-09T13:45:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When working with scrollable areas in web development, you might find yourself wondering about the default behavior of the scrollbar thumb. Specifically, is the height of the scroll thumb automatically set based on the scrollable area? If not, how can you customize its height through CSS? In this article, we'll tackle these questions and provide a clear solution.
Understanding the Scroll Thumb Behavior
The scrollbar thumb is a UI element that allows users to scroll through a container with content that overflows its bounds. By default, the height of the scrollbar thumb is not a fixed size and varies based on the amount of scrollable content. CSS gives you the ability to control various aspects of the scrollbar, but there are some limitations to be aware of.
What You Should Know About Scrol…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Generatecode</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Build an Inventory Management System Using MongoDB Atlas]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/mongodb/build-an-inventory-management-system-using-mongodb-atlas-4526</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/mongodb/build-an-inventory-management-system-using-mongodb-atlas-4526"/>
        <updated>2025-05-09T13:44:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This tutorial was written by Rami Pinto.
In the competitive retail landscape, having the right stock in the right place at the right time is crucial. Too little inventory when and where it’s needed can create unhappy customers. However, a large inventory can increase costs and risks associated with its storage. Companies of all sizes struggle with inventory management. Solutions such as a single view of inventory, real-time analytics, and event-driven architectures can help your businesses overcome these challenges and take your inventory management to the next level. By the end of this guide, you'll have inventory management up and running, capable of all the solutions mentioned above. 
We will walk you through the process of configuring and using MongoDB Atlas as your back end for your N…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>MongoDB Guests</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Understanding Promises and Coroutines in JavaScript]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/this-is-learning/understanding-promises-and-coroutines-in-javascript-50gd</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/this-is-learning/understanding-promises-and-coroutines-in-javascript-50gd"/>
        <updated>2025-05-09T13:42:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Think of a Promise as a placeholder for a value that you’ll get later.
const pizzaOrder = new Promise((resolve, reject) => {
  setTimeout(() => {
    const isPizzaReady = true;
    if (isPizzaReady) {
      resolve("Pizza is ready!");
    } else {
      reject("Sorry, no pizza today.");
    }
  }, 3000);
});

pizzaOrder
  .then((message) => console.log(message))
  .catch((error) => console.error(error));

Here, .then() is like, “What do I do when the pizza arrives?” and .catch() is, “What if it doesn’t?”
JavaScript is single-threaded — it can do one thing at a time. Promises help us avoid blocking things while waiting for slower tasks (like API calls or timers).
Instead of freezing the app, Promises let JavaScript say, “I’ll come back to this when it’s ready,” and keep moving.
Dealing with…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hayk Sargsyan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Story of Building a Storage-Agnostic Message Queue]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/fahimfaisaal/a-story-of-building-a-storage-agnostic-message-queue-3lo4</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/fahimfaisaal/a-story-of-building-a-storage-agnostic-message-queue-3lo4"/>
        <updated>2025-05-09T13:41:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A year ago, I was knee-deep in Golang, trying to build a simple concurrent queue as a learning project. Coming from a Node.js background, where I’d spent years working with tools like BullMQ and RabbitMQ, Go’s concurrency model felt like a puzzle. My first attempt—a minimal queue with round-robin channel selection—was, well, buggy. Let’s just say it worked until it didn’t.
But that’s how learning goes, right?
In my professional work, I’ve used tools like BullMQ and RabbitMQ for event-driven solutions, and p-queue and p-limit for handling concurrency. Naturally, I began wondering if there were similar tools in Go. I found packages like asynq, ants, and various worker pools—solid, battle-tested options. But suddenly, a thought struck me: what if I built something different? A package with ze…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Fahim Faisaal</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[uniapp跨平台开发HarmonyOS NEXT应用初体验]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/youlanjihua/uniappkua-ping-tai-kai-fa-harmonyos-nextying-yong-chu-ti-yan-6ob</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/youlanjihua/uniappkua-ping-tai-kai-fa-harmonyos-nextying-yong-chu-ti-yan-6ob"/>
        <updated>2025-05-09T13:40:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[之前写过使用uniapp开发鸿蒙应用的教程，简单介绍了如何配置开发环境和运行项目。那时候的HbuilderX还是4.22版本，小一年过去了HbuilderX的正式版本已经来到4.64，历经了多个版本的更新后，跨平台开发鸿蒙应用的体验大幅提升。今天再次跟大家分享一下使用uniapp开发鸿蒙的使用教程。
这次的开发体验最大的感觉是非常的方便快捷，你甚至不需要打开DevEco studio，直接使用Hbuilder就可以连接真机进行调试，还有自动的实时编译更新，非常友好。
首先，你需要去AppGallery Connect创建一个新的应用，填写应用名称和包名之后创建应用，包名我们一会需要用到。

接下来下载安装最新版本的HbuilderX，目前是4.64版本

创建项目之后，电脑连接真机，或者打开DevEco studio的模拟器也可以。然后再HbuilderX的运行菜单下找到运行到鸿蒙，第一次可能会有下载真机插件的步骤，还有配置调试证书的弹窗，真机插件是自动下载的，配置证书需要填写第一步创建应用时的包名，然后我推荐大家使用自动申请调试证书，信息自动填写完成后点击保存。

再次运行，会弹出检测到的设备列表：

选择设备就可以将应用运行到设备上：

这时候尝试修改一些内容，程序会自动编译更新，非常方便。
以上就是最新的uniapp开发鸿蒙应用的使用体验，以后也会持续深入的跟大家分享使用uniapp跨平台开发鸿蒙应用的教程，也打算把跨平台开发这部分做成一个合集，方便大家持续学习，欢迎大家关注。]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>wei chang</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Looking for Developers to Collaborate on an Ambulance Inventory Management System]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/mehmet_cansandal_90dceef/looking-for-developers-to-collaborate-on-an-ambulance-inventory-management-system-ak3</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/mehmet_cansandal_90dceef/looking-for-developers-to-collaborate-on-an-ambulance-inventory-management-system-ak3"/>
        <updated>2025-05-09T13:40:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi there,
As an entrepreneur, my goal is to move this project forward and bring innovation to the healthcare sector using the latest technologies. That’s why I’m looking for a developer who is solution-driven, open to using modern tools, and ready to grow with a dynamic and motivated team.
🎯 Project Vision
Monitor live locations via an interactive map
Assign tasks, manage users, and track low-stock alerts
Digitize operations for efficiency and transparency
✅ What’s Already Done
Functional mockups based on real ambulance workflows
Direct access to ambulance companies for testing and feedback
👥 Who I’m Looking For
Backend Developer (Node.js, Django, Laravel): to build the core system logic
Database Engineer (PostgreSQL, MongoDB): to design scalable ambulance-inventory relations
DevOps / Server Expert: to deploy the system to a cloud server (Hetzner or similar)
💡 What I Offer
Clear roadmap toward a monetizable MVP
A collaborative, entrepreneurial mindset and work environment
If this sounds like something you’d like to be a part of, feel free to reach out.
https://app.tempo.new/canvases/9c366815-914b-4e2a-8781-7c9165aaeced/editor]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mehmet can Sandal</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[21 GB/s CSV Parsing Using SIMD on AMD 9950X]]></title>
        <id>https://nietras.com/2025/05/09/sep-0-10-0/</id>
        <link href="https://nietras.com/2025/05/09/sep-0-10-0/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-09T13:38:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[It wasn’t the idea that failed: it was the execution]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/whitep4nth3r/it-wasnt-the-idea-that-failed-it-was-the-execution-406l</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/whitep4nth3r/it-wasnt-the-idea-that-failed-it-was-the-execution-406l"/>
        <updated>2025-05-09T13:37:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Since writing my new talk, An Introduction to the World Wide Web for Very Senior Programmers, in which I transport the audience back to the year 1995, I’ve become somewhat of a proud and nerdy Internet historian. So much happened on the web in 1995. HTML 2.0 was released in September and saw the introduction of the HTML  tag, transitioning the online experience from something that resembled reading books and formal documents, to flicking through colorful magazines or photo albums. JavaScript was released in December 1995, which moved the web from a read-only medium to an interactive experience. Multimedia tools like Macromedia Shockwave Player and FutureWave FutureSplash Animator were created in 1995 out of a desire to bring exciting and interactive CD-ROM-like experiences to the browser.
…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Salma Alam-Naylor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why crypto’s next breakthrough could start in the classroom — Animoca’s Yat Siu]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/why-cryptos-next-breakthrough-could-start-in-classroom-animoca-yat-siu</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/why-cryptos-next-breakthrough-could-start-in-classroom-animoca-yat-siu?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-09T13:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ripple’s $25 million donation to a crypto education fund has reignited conversations about how blockchain projects are building influence through academia—but in the latest episode of Byte-Sized Insight, Animoca Brands’ co-founder Yat Siu says that money alone isn’t enough. 
Instead, real-world use cases like student loans backed by DeFi may be crypto’s most convincing value proposition to date.

DeFi student loans
On April 30th, Pencil Finance, a project supported by Animoca Brands and its education arm Open Campus, announced a $10 million student loan financing initiative aimed at providing cheaper, blockchain-backed loans. Siu believes this type of infrastructure investment goes further than symbolic funding.
“What our industry needs a lot more is these kinds of positive-sum use cases t…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Savannah Fortis</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hollow Core Fiber (HCF)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.holightoptic.com/what-is-hollow-core-fiber-hcf%ef%bc%9f/</id>
        <link href="https://www.holightoptic.com/what-is-hollow-core-fiber-hcf%ef%bc%9f/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-09T13:25:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Reconstructing illusory camouflage patterns on moth wings using computer vision]]></title>
        <id>https://royalsocietypublishing.org/doi/10.1098/rsif.2024.0757</id>
        <link href="https://royalsocietypublishing.org/doi/10.1098/rsif.2024.0757"/>
        <updated>2025-05-09T13:24:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sofie: open-source web based system for automating live TV news production]]></title>
        <id>https://nrkno.github.io/sofie-core/</id>
        <link href="https://nrkno.github.io/sofie-core/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-09T13:18:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CoinDesk 20 Performance Update: Uniswap (UNI) Surges 13.5% as Index Trades Higher]]></title>
        <id>7f3ae31a-9643-4c79-9f04-6e4b7dc1096d</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/coindesk-indices/2025/05/09/coindesk-20-performance-update-uniswap-uni-surges-13-5-as-index-trades-higher"/>
        <updated>2025-05-09T13:11:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[NEAR Protocol (NEAR) joined Uniswap (UNI) as a top performer, gaining 11.7%.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CoinDesk Indices</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Here’s what happened in crypto today]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/what-happened-in-crypto-today</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/what-happened-in-crypto-today?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-09T13:09:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today in crypto, German authorities seized $38 million of digital assets from an exchange linked to the Bybit hack in February, US Securities and Exchange Commission Commissioner Caroline Crenshaw blasted a settlement agreement between the SEC and Ripple, which she says could erode SEC lawyers’ credibility in the court, and Democrats in the US block the GENIUS stablecoin bill from advancing.
Germany seizes $38 million in crypto from Bybit hack-linked eXch exchange
German law enforcement seized 34 million euros ($38 million) in cryptocurrency from eXch, a cryptocurrency platform allegedly used to launder funds stolen after Bybit’s record-breaking $1.4 billion hack.
The seizure, announced on May 9 by Germany’s Federal Criminal Police Office (BKA) and Frankfurt’s main prosecutor’s office, inv…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Cointelegraph</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Zencoder launches Zen Agents, ushering in a new era of team-based AI for software development]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3007152</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/zencoder-launches-zen-agents-ushering-in-a-new-era-of-team-based-ai-for-software-development/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-09T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Zencoder launches Zen Agents, the first AI platform enabling teams to create, share, and leverage custom development assistants organization-wide, plus an open-source marketplace for enterprise-grade AI tools.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Nuñez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Market Maker Flowdesk Expands Capital Market Offerings With New Institutional Credit Desk]]></title>
        <id>5d3865d7-b01e-420e-995f-9a98d0fb0a14</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/09/market-maker-flowdesk-expands-capital-market-offerings-with-new-institutional-credit-desk"/>
        <updated>2025-05-09T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Institutions trading crypto need more than fast execution, they need tools to unlock capital and build precise strategies says Flowdesk’s U.S. CEO.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sam Reynolds</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum Foundation distributed $32.6M grants to ecosystem in Q1]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/ethereum-foundation-spent-32-6-m-on-education-community-initiatives-in-q1</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/ethereum-foundation-spent-32-6-m-on-education-community-initiatives-in-q1?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-09T12:58:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Ethereum Foundation, the nonprofit that supports development across the Ethereum blockchain, distributed $32.6 million in grants in the first quarter of 2025. 
In an allocation update, the organization reported spending on various initiatives through its Ecosystem Support Program (ESP). 
Categories included community and educational grants, zero-knowledge and cryptography. Other allocations included execution layers, developer experience and tools, layer-2 networks and overall ecosystem growth and support. 

Ethereum Foundation focuses on education and community
Of the 101 grants awarded, 32 went to community and education-focused initiatives. Recipients included educational content creators, conference organizers, bootcamps and hackathons such as ETHPrague and ETHiopia.  
Sixteen proj…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Ezra Reguerra</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gemini to launch crypto derivatives in Europe with new license]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/gemini-launches-crypto-derivatives-europe-new-license</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/gemini-launches-crypto-derivatives-europe-new-license?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-09T12:51:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Gemini, the cryptocurrency exchange founded by Cameron and Tyler Winklevoss, has received regulatory approval to expand crypto derivatives trading across Europe.
Gemini secured a Markets in Financial Instruments Directive II (MiFID II) license from the Malta Financial Services Authority (MFSA), allowing the exchange to offer crypto derivatives in the European Union, it announced on May 9.
“Once we commence business activities, we will be able to offer regulated derivatives throughout the EU and EEA [European Economic Area] under MiFID II,” said Gemini’s head of Europe, Mark Jennings.
According to the exec, the MiFID II license is a big milestone in Gemini’s European expansion, putting it one step closer to offering derivatives to both retail and institutional users.
Advanced traders will g…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Helen Partz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TapSwap on Telegram: Is it legit or a scam?]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/explained/tapswap-on-telegram-is-it-legit-or-a-scam</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/explained/tapswap-on-telegram-is-it-legit-or-a-scam?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-09T12:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What is TapSwap on Telegram?            
            
                
TapSwap is a tap-to-earn Web3 application that lives inside Telegram — no separate download required.
Are your crypto friends obsessed with tapping their phones all the time? Welcome to the world of TapSwap. TapSwap is a tap-to-earn game released in mid-2024 in the Telegram Mini Apps ecosystem. The game quickly catches your attention: one minute you’re just curious… the next, you’re tapping away at 2 am trying to squeeze out one more energy boost. 
At its core, TapSwap is simple:

You tap your screen.
You earn TAPS tokens.
Repeat.


It’s built as a Mini App inside Telegram, which means no downloading or setting up complicated wallets just to play. Just hit “Start” and you’re in. Launched in early 2024, it quickly amasse…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Shailey Singh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Show HN: Aberdeen – An elegant approach to reactive UIs]]></title>
        <id>https://aberdeenjs.org/</id>
        <link href="https://aberdeenjs.org/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-09T12:42:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Senator Tim Scott slams partisan politics for failed stablecoin bill]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/senator-tim-scott-blames-politics-for-failed-stablecoin-bill</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/senator-tim-scott-blames-politics-for-failed-stablecoin-bill?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-09T12:14:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Senate Banking Committee Chairman Tim Scott blamed the Guiding and Establishing National Innovation for US Stablecoins (GENIUS) Act’s failure on partisan politics during a Senate speech on May 8.
Scott said the vote, which failed to reach cloture in the Senate, was expected to mark a step toward greater affordability and innovation. Instead, he said, political divisions took precedence.  
“Instead, we witnessed a disappointing display of political gamesmanship that puts partisan politics above policy, and obstruction above innovation, “Scott said.
The bill had previously undergone multiple amendments to address concerns raised by Democrats, including stricter requirements for stablecoin issuers and further provisions for Anti-Money Laundering.
Related: Trump tricked into pushing XRP for cr…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Adrian Zmudzinski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NSF faces shake-up as officials abolish its 37 divisions]]></title>
        <id>https://www.science.org/content/article/exclusive-nsf-faces-radical-shake-officials-abolish-its-37-divisions</id>
        <link href="https://www.science.org/content/article/exclusive-nsf-faces-radical-shake-officials-abolish-its-37-divisions"/>
        <updated>2025-05-09T12:13:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Download: AI headphone translation, and the link between microbes and our behavior]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1116247</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/05/09/1116247/the-download-ai-headphone-translation-and-the-link-between-microbes-and-our-behavior/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-09T12:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is today’s edition of The Download, our weekday newsletter that provides a daily dose of what’s going on in the world of technology. A new AI translation system for headphones clones multiple voices simultaneously What’s new: Imagine going for dinner with a group of friends who switch in and out of different languages you don’t speak,…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rhiannon Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DOGE, XRP, ETH, SOL Follow Bitcoin Through the Cloud as Altcoin Momentum Builds]]></title>
        <id>0ca98f70-71bc-4c09-a422-052459fdfcd6</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/09/from-bitcoin-topping-cloud-to-doge-xrp-eth-sol-catching-up-momentum-builds-in-the-altcoin-sector"/>
        <updated>2025-05-09T11:57:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Top altcoins are mimicking BTC's late April bullish breakout that set the stage for a rally to $100,000.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Omkar Godbole</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Taiwan lawmaker calls for Bitcoin reserve at national conference]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/taiwan-lawmaker-pushes-bitcoin-reserve-national-conference</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/taiwan-lawmaker-pushes-bitcoin-reserve-national-conference?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-09T11:45:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Taiwanese lawmaker Ko Ju-Chun has called on the government to consider adding Bitcoin to its national reserves, suggesting it could serve as a hedge against global economic uncertainty.  
Ko, a legislator at-large in Taiwan’s legislative body, the Legislative Yuan, took to X on Friday to report that he had advocated Bitcoin (BTC) investment by the Taiwanese government at the National Conference on May 9.
In his remarks, Ko cited Bitcoin’s potential to become a hedge amid global economic risks and urged Taiwan to recognize the cryptocurrency alongside gold and foreign exchange reserves to boost its financial resilience.
Source: Ko Ju-Chun
Ko’s announcement came shortly after the legislator held talks with Samson Mow, who advocates for Bitcoin adoption by states like El Salvador at his BTC t…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Helen Partz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chery Teases Omoda C7 Crossover In Malaysia]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=351298</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/351298/chery-teases-omoda-c7-crossover-in-malaysia/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-09T11:23:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Chinese automaker Chery has unveiled its upcoming crossover SUV, the C7, at MAS 2025 yesterday. It will also be one of the first vehicles to be marketed under a major rebrand, Omoda | Jaecoo, which merges two of its sub-brands together. However, there was not much information that was given about the C7 during the […]
The post Chery Teases Omoda C7 Crossover In Malaysia appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Keran</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Data manipulations alleged in study that paved way for Microsoft's quantum chip]]></title>
        <id>https://www.science.org/content/article/data-manipulations-alleged-study-paved-way-microsoft-s-quantum-chip</id>
        <link href="https://www.science.org/content/article/data-manipulations-alleged-study-paved-way-microsoft-s-quantum-chip"/>
        <updated>2025-05-09T11:23:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Daybook Americas: PEPE Signals Altcoin Frenzy as Rampant Ether Outpaces Bitcoin]]></title>
        <id>e9e54d6f-1e79-4b41-8435-b7418c61e638</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/daybook-us/2025/05/09/crypto-daybook-americas-pepe-signals-altcoin-frenzy-as-rampant-ether-outpaces-bitcoin"/>
        <updated>2025-05-09T11:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Your day-ahead look for May 9, 2025]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Omkar Godbole</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Implementing a Struct of Arrays]]></title>
        <id>https://brevzin.github.io/c++/2025/05/02/soa/</id>
        <link href="https://brevzin.github.io/c++/2025/05/02/soa/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-09T10:52:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Show HN: Hyvector – A fast and modern SVG editor]]></title>
        <id>https://www.hyvector.com/</id>
        <link href="https://www.hyvector.com/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-09T10:45:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Linux Kernel's PGP Web of Trust]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.kleine-koenig.org/ukl/the-linux-kernels-pgp-web-of-trust.html</id>
        <link href="https://blog.kleine-koenig.org/ukl/the-linux-kernels-pgp-web-of-trust.html"/>
        <updated>2025-05-09T10:39:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin eyes sub-$100K liquidity — Watch these BTC price levels next]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-eyes-sub-100k-liquidity-watch-these-btc-price-levels-next</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-eyes-sub-100k-liquidity-watch-these-btc-price-levels-next?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-09T10:05:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Key points:

Bitcoin (BTC) is at its highest levels since January, and traders are eyeing key levels to watch for what’s next.

After hitting $104,000, BTC/USD is retracing to establish support, but the fate of $100,000 is among the concerns for market participants.

Current price action represents an important battleground, as measured from the $75,000 lows this year.


” Headline driven” BTC price gains draw scrutiny
Just $6,000 from new all-time highs, per data from Cointelegraph Markets Pro and TradingView, BTC price action has stunned the market by jumping 10% in days.
The pace of the BTC price gains has come as a surprise for many, but longer-term perspectives show where the most difficult battleground lies.
“Since this current impulse was primarily headline driven again this puts ma…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by William Suberg</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Move To iOS App Upgrade Allows Faster Cabled Data Transfers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=351289</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/351289/move-to-ios-app-upgrade-allows-faster-cabled-data-transfers/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-09T09:50:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Move to iOS, an Apple-made app for Android phones, has received an update, as noted by MacRumors. New features have been added to make the process of switching from an Android phone to an iPhone easier, one of them being faster cabled data transfers between the two phones. You can either use a USB-C cable […]
The post Move To iOS App Upgrade Allows Faster Cabled Data Transfers appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Newsdesk</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Germany Seizes $38M From Crypto Platform Suspected of Laundering Bybit, Genesis Hack Proceeds]]></title>
        <id>170d81ba-4ee1-4b8d-a10d-af6d64f1de87</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/09/germany-seizes-38m-from-crypto-platform-suspected-of-laundering-bybit-genesis-hack-proceeds"/>
        <updated>2025-05-09T09:42:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[EXch served as a hub for over $1.9 billion in illicit crypto transfers, authorities said, with funds tied to both high-profile hacks and phishing operations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shaurya Malwa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Life in Startup Pivot Hell with Ex-Microsoft Lonewolf Engineer Sam Crombie [Podcast #171]]]></title>
        <id>681dc8d07dcd2a77c4bbe048</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/life-in-startup-pivot-hell-with-ex-microsoft-lonewolf-engineer-sam-crombie-podcast-171/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-09T09:20:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On this week's episode of the podcast, freeCodeCamp founder Quincy Larson interviews Sam Crombie. He's a software engineer and prolific open source contributor to freeCodeCamp. He abandon his job at Microsoft, got into Y Combinator, and is currently ...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[iCAUR 03 To Locally Launch In Q3 At A Starting Price Of RM145,000]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=351225</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/351225/icaur-03-to-locally-launch-in-q3/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-09T09:20:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Chery’s sub-brand, the iCAUR (iCAR in China), has made its official debut at the Malaysian Autoshow 2025. The automaker previewed three fully electric SUVs – the iCAUR 03, iCAUR 03T and iCAUR V23, with the 03 leading the charge as the first model slated to go on sale within Q3 2025. The iCAUR 03 features […]
The post iCAUR 03 To Locally Launch In Q3 At A Starting Price Of RM145,000 appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Keran</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Sees Surge in Institutional Confidence, Deribit-Listed BTC Options Market Reveals]]></title>
        <id>76188f7b-5e88-4548-9776-ff529c6c12ae</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/09/bitcoin-sees-surge-in-institutional-confidence-deribit-listed-btc-options-market-reveals"/>
        <updated>2025-05-09T09:19:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Panning out over just the last week shows a much bigger sign of institutional positioning on BTC, Deribit said.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Omkar Godbole</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google Rolls To Use AI To Fight Scams On Chrome]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=351264</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/351264/google-rolls-to-use-ai-to-fight-scams-on-chrome/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-09T09:15:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google has announced that it will be using AI to both identify and also protect you from “the latest scams” while you are using its Chrome browser. The internet search giant says that the desktop version of said browser will be getting Gemini Nano which works on-device, with the goal of making this also available […]
The post Google Rolls To Use AI To Fight Scams On Chrome appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ian Chee</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lenovo Announces 18-Inch Legion 9i Gaming Laptop With Enthusiast-Level Hardware]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=351260</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/351260/lenovo-announces-18-inch-legion-9i-gaming-laptop-with-enthusiast-level-hardware/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-09T09:11:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Lenovo officially announced a new Legion 9i (18″, 10) gaming laptop. The machine was launched at Tech World Shanghai 2025 event and boasts some flagship hardware. The new Legion 9i comes with an 18-inch 16:10 LCD display with two resolution options: 4K 240Hz with 3ms GTG response time, and another with Lenovo’s own version of […]
The post Lenovo Announces 18-Inch Legion 9i Gaming Laptop With Enthusiast-Level Hardware appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John Law</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How high can Bitcoin price go?]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/how-high-can-bitcoin-price-go</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/how-high-can-bitcoin-price-go?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-09T09:03:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Key takeaways:

Bitcoin was up 4.3% on May 9, after breaking $100,000  for the first time since February.

BTC price gains trigger $800 million in short liquidations, the largest since 2021.

A bull flag on the weekly chart suggests a $182,200 target, with analysts predicting Bitcoin’s price can go as high as $1 million in 2025.

Bitcoin’s (BTC) price is up 4.3% on May 9 as a fresh liquidity cascade sent BTC price soaring above $100,000 for the first time in over 90 days.
BTC/USD pair trades above $100K for the first time since Feb. 4. Source: Cointelegraph/TradingView
Bitcoin wipes out liquidity in return to 6-figures
BTC/USD rose as high as $104,150 during the late New York trading session on May 8, according to data from Cointelegraph Markets Pro and Bitstamp. Crypto market sentiment, a…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Nancy Lubale</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Your gut microbes might encourage criminal behavior]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1116211</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/05/09/1116211/gut-microbes-criminal-behavior/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-09T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A few years ago, a Belgian man in his 30s drove into a lamppost. Twice. Local authorities found that his blood alcohol level was four times the legal limit. Over the space of a few years, the man was apprehended for drunk driving three times. And on all three occasions, he insisted he hadn’t been…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jessica Hamzelou</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A new AI translation system for headphones clones multiple voices simultaneously]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1116215</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/05/09/1116215/a-new-ai-translation-system-for-headphones-clones-multiple-voices-simultaneously/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-09T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Imagine going for dinner with a group of friends who switch in and out of different languages you don’t speak, but still being able to understand what they’re saying. This scenario is the inspiration for a new AI headphone system that translates the speech of multiple speakers simultaneously, in real time. The system, called Spatial…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rhiannon Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Malaysia’s Halal Certification Now Fully Digital]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=351241</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/351241/malaysia-halal-certification-is-now-fully-digital/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-09T08:59:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As of Monday, 5 May, all applications for the Malaysian Halal Certification are being processed electronically. This shift to a digital process is part of efforts by the government to meet a growing industry demand. According to Department of Islamic Development Malaysia (JAKIM) director general Datuk Dr Sirajuddin Suhaimee, successful applications will receive digital certificates […]
The post Malaysia’s Halal Certification Now Fully Digital appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nurul Kamil</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Linear Programming for Fun and Profit]]></title>
        <id>https://modal.com/blog/resource-solver</id>
        <link href="https://modal.com/blog/resource-solver"/>
        <updated>2025-05-09T08:48:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Metaplanet Plans a Further $21M Bond Sale to Buy More BTC]]></title>
        <id>0238e622-5f17-455c-83d5-93aa48a3869b</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/09/metaplanet-plans-a-further-21m-bond-sale-to-buy-more-btc"/>
        <updated>2025-05-09T08:40:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Metaplanet has the largest BTC stash among publicly-traded companies outside North America]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Crawley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Germany seizes $38M in crypto from Bybit hack-linked eXch exchange]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/germany-seizes-38-million-crypto-bybit-hack-linked-exch</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/germany-seizes-38-million-crypto-bybit-hack-linked-exch?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-09T08:24:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[German law enforcement seized 34 million euros ($38 million) in cryptocurrency from eXch, a cryptocurrency platform allegedly used to launder funds stolen after Bybit’s record-breaking $1.4 billion hack.
The seizure, announced on May 9 by Germany’s Federal Criminal Police Office (BKA) and Frankfurt’s main prosecutor’s office, involved multiple crypto assets, including Bitcoin (BTC), Ether (ETH), Litecoin (LTC) and Dash (DASH). The move marks the third-largest crypto confiscation in the BKA’s history.
The authorities also seized eXch’s German server infrastructure with over eight terabytes of data and shut down the platform, the announcement added.
eXch exchanged crypto without AML
In the statement, the BKA described eXch as a “swapping” service that allowed users to exchange various crypto…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Helen Partz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[APAD Orders inDrive, Maxim To Cease Operations Starting 24 July 2025]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=351269</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/351269/apad-orders-indrive-maxim-to-cease-operations-starting-24-july-2025/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-09T08:22:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Land Public Transport Agency (APAD) has issued cease-and-desist letters to two e-hailing platforms, inDrive and Maxim, for allegedly operating without proper authorisation in Malaysia. This was revealed by Transport Minister Anthony Loke during the reopening of the track for cargo service operations for the Kempas Baru-Pasir Gudang route today. “Effective 24 July, inDrive and […]
The post APAD Orders inDrive, Maxim To Cease Operations Starting 24 July 2025 appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Heirul Kamel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Is Pi Network dead? What really went wrong behind the hype]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/explained/is-pi-network-dead-what-really-went-wrong-behind-the-hype</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/explained/is-pi-network-dead-what-really-went-wrong-behind-the-hype?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-09T08:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What Pi Network promised            
            
                
When Pi Network first hit the scene in 2019, it had a simple but compelling pitch: What if you could mine cryptocurrency straight from your phone — no expensive gear, no massive electricity bills, just a tap a day on an app?
It caught fire. Millions of people jumped on board, lured by the idea of “free” mobile mining and a chance to get in early on the next big thing. The app made it easy: You signed up, invited a few friends, tapped a button every 24 hours, and watched your Pi (PI) balance slowly grow. With the social referral model fueling growth, it wasn’t long before over 70 million users had signed up worldwide.

Did you know? Pi Network utilizes the Stellar Consensus Protocol (SCP), which aims for energy efficiency an…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Bradley Peak</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[vivo X Fold5 Global Specs Leak; May Pack 6,000 mAh Battery]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=351205</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/351205/vivo-x-fold5-global-specs-leak-may-pack-6000-mah-battery/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-09T08:01:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[vivo released its X Fold3 series last year, and is now reported to be launching the X Fold5. While the Pro version of last year’s series received a limited global release, the base model was only launched in China. However, only foldable from the brand will reportedly be released in the Chinese market. As per […]
The post vivo X Fold5 Global Specs Leak; May Pack 6,000 mAh Battery appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Newsdesk</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WASM 2.0]]></title>
        <id>https://www.w3.org/TR/wasm-core-2/</id>
        <link href="https://www.w3.org/TR/wasm-core-2/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-09T08:01:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Sony WH-1000XM6 Renders Confirm Foldable Design]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=351209</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/351209/new-sony-wh-1000xm6-renders-confirms-foldable-design/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-09T07:55:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It looks like the Sony WH-1000XM6 headphones have been outed in all their glory. Product renders of the headphones were obtained by The Walkman Blog, and shows the products in three colour schemes and more importantly, sporting a foldable design. It’s safe to say that the leaked renders fully confirm that Sony is reverting to […]
The post New Sony WH-1000XM6 Renders Confirm Foldable Design appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John Law</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Grab Reportedly Aiming To Finalise GoTo Acquisition Deal By Q2 2025]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=351239</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/351239/grab-finalising-goto-acquisition-within-q2-2025/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-09T07:43:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Grab is aiming to finalise the acquisition of its Indonesian competitor GoTo in the second quarter of this year, according to a Reuters report. The proposed deal, which could be worth around US$7 billion (~RM30.2 billion), would mark a significant consolidation in Southeast Asia’s tech and mobility landscape. Reuters adds that Grab has hired advisors […]
The post Grab Reportedly Aiming To Finalise GoTo Acquisition Deal By Q2 2025 appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Heirul Kamel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Florida Pharma Firm Will Use XRP for Real-Time Payments in $50M Financing Deal]]></title>
        <id>3bea0223-cb59-4560-bc12-d0767714ca4b</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/09/florida-pharma-firm-will-use-xrp-for-real-time-payments-in-usd50m-financing-deal"/>
        <updated>2025-05-09T07:26:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“We believe that there are certain advantages to integrating XRP and its related infrastructure into its healthcare ecosystem,” the firm said in the release.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shaurya Malwa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Solana lacks ‘convincing signs’ of besting Ethereum: Sygnum]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/solana-no-convincing-signs-besting-ethereum-memecoin-bias</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/solana-no-convincing-signs-besting-ethereum-memecoin-bias?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-09T06:22:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Solana has yet to show convincing signs that it could surpass Ethereum as the preferred blockchain for institutions, as its revenue, heavily reliant on memecoins, is considered unstable, according to crypto bank group Sygnum.
In a May 8 blog post, Sygnum said that the current sentiment around Ethereum “remains poor,” with the market focused on Solana’s “transaction volumes and its recent dominance in fee generation.”
However, Sygnum said “the medium-term outlook will primarily be shaped by traditional financial institutions’ platform choices to bring their product offerings,” not by sentiment.
“We do not yet see convincing signs that Solana would be the preferred choice as Ethereum’s security, stability and longevity are highly prized,” it added.
Sygnum argued that institutions could choos…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Jesse Coghlan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin accepted at fast food chain Steak ’n Shake from May 16]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/steak-n-sats-bitcoin-accepted-steak-n-shake-locations-may-16</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/steak-n-sats-bitcoin-accepted-steak-n-shake-locations-may-16?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-09T06:19:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[American fast food outlet Steak ‘n Shake has announced it will begin accepting Bitcoin as payment at all locations starting on May 16.
The firm said on X on May 9 that it was making the cryptocurrency available to more than 100 million customers, adding that “the movement is just beginning,” before signing off as “Steaktoshi.” 
The fast food chain initially hinted at accepting Bitcoin (BTC) in March when it posted “Should Steak ‘n Shake accept Bitcoin?” on social media. 
The tweet drew the attention of the crypto community and Bitcoin proponents such as Jack Dorsey, who rapidly replied with a “yes.” 
The firm has built momentum since then with Bitcoin-themed marketing, Tesla promotions, and visual hints on its social media feeds.
“The future is bright,” said the firm in April. Source: Stak…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Martin Young</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Metaplanet is raising another $21M through bonds to buy more Bitcoin]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/metaplanet-raising-another-21m-buy-more-bitcoin</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/metaplanet-raising-another-21m-buy-more-bitcoin?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-09T06:18:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fresh off its most recent Bitcoin purchase, Japanese investment firm Metaplanet is raising more funds through another bond issue to expand its growing crypto treasury.
Through a $21.25 million issue of “0% Ordinary Bonds,”  all the “funds raised will be allocated to the purchase of Bitcoin,” the firm said in a May 9 statement. 
Zero-coupon bonds don’t offer any interest to the holder. Most of the time, they are issued at a steep discount from their normal value, and when they mature, the holder receives the full value.
After its most recent May 9 board of directors meeting, the firm said it will issue a 14th Stock Acquisition Rights to EVO Fund, an investment management firm in the Cayman Islands, with a redemption date of Nov. 7.
Source: Metaplanet
At current prices, Metaplanet could buy …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Stephen Katte</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ether clocks ‘insane’ 20% candle post Pectra — A turning point?]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/ether-price-insane-candle-pectra-upgrade-turning-point-crypto-traders</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/ether-price-insane-candle-pectra-upgrade-turning-point-crypto-traders?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-09T06:01:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ether surged 20% in the past 24 hours following the launch of the Pectra upgrade, with some crypto traders suggesting the growing number of ETH long positions could mark a “turning point” for the asset that has faced uncertain sentiment throughout most of 2025.
At the time of publication, Ether (ETH) is trading at $2,230, up 19.6% over the past 24 hours, according to CoinMarketCap data. Pseudonymous crypto trader Daan Crypto Trades said it was a “pretty insane candle.” Over the same 24 hours, Ether Open Interest (OI) spiked 21%. 
Ether price pump caught traders offside
The surge followed the long-awaited Pectra Upgrade, which went live on May 7, introducing new wallet features, increased staking limits and scalability improvements to Ethereum. 
Popular crypto trader Alex Kruger said on May…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Ciaran Lyons</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AI decentralized apps are coming for the Web3 throne: DappRadar]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/ai-decentralized-appscoming-for-web3-throne-dappradar</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/ai-decentralized-appscoming-for-web3-throne-dappradar?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-09T05:27:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AI decentralized apps (DApps) have seen a spike in user activity and could soon challenge gaming and DeFi for the top spot in the DApp ecosystem, according to blockchain analytics platform DappRadar.
Gaming and DeFi are both sitting on 21% dominance in April, judged by percentage of unique active wallets, while AI has climbed to 16%, up from the 11% recorded in the February report, data in DappRadar’s April industry report shows.
“As user interest in artificial intelligence tools grows across industries, AI-powered DApps are steadily carving out their place in the decentralized ecosystem,” DappRadar analyst Sara Gherghelas said. 
“If this trend continues, AI could soon challenge the traditional dominance of DeFi and Gaming, signaling a new era in the DApp landscape.”
AI DApps have seen a j…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Stephen Katte</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Apple makes progress toward its first pair of smart glasses: Report]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/apple-makes-progress-first-smart-glasses-bloomberg</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/apple-makes-progress-first-smart-glasses-bloomberg?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-09T05:13:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Apple is reportedly working on its own microchips across multiple product categories, including smart glasses and artificial intelligence — a hint at what’s next for the massive Silicon Valley-based tech giant. 
A May 8 report from Bloomberg, citing people familiar with the matter, said the company is working on new processors to power its future devices, including its first smart glasses to rival Meta’s Ray-Bans, more powerful Macs, and artificial intelligence servers.
The smart glasses — a first for Apple — would rely on a specialized chip codenamed N401. The processor is based on Apple Watch chips but is further optimized for power efficiency and designed to control multiple cameras planned for the glasses, the sources said. 
Apple’s smart glasses will initially be non-augmented reality…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Martin Young</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Zerebro dev is reportedly alive and at parents’ house: Report]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/zerebro-dev-jeffy-yu-reported-alive-after-being-spotted-parents-house</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/zerebro-dev-jeffy-yu-reported-alive-after-being-spotted-parents-house?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-09T04:56:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The 22-year-old developer of Zerebro, who apparently committed suicide during a livestream on May 4, is actually alive, according to a San Francisco news outlet that claims they spoke to Yu outside his family home. 
The San Francisco Standard reporter George Kelly claimed on May 8 that he briefly spoke with Yu outside of his family’s two-story home, where the crypto influencer refused to discuss the suicide allegations and whether he had financially benefited from it. 
Instead, Yu reportedly said: “You can see the PTSD in my eyes, right?” before asking the reporter to leave.
He was reportedly wearing a T-shirt, shorts, flip-flops and wire-rimmed glasses, possibly similar to the ones he had on while appearing to shoot himself to death during the livestream.
Jeffy Yu speaking about the futur…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Brayden Lindrea</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[LegoGPT: Generating Physically Stable and Buildable Lego]]></title>
        <id>https://avalovelace1.github.io/LegoGPT/</id>
        <link href="https://avalovelace1.github.io/LegoGPT/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-09T04:55:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin's Price Surge to $104K Liquidates Nearly $400M in Bearish BTC Bets, Opening Doors to Further Gains]]></title>
        <id>91319329-e8ec-4f3d-a334-191b0a4a0737</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/09/bitcoin-s-price-surge-to-usd104k-liquidates-nearly-usd400m-in-bearish-btc-bets-opening-doors-to-further-gains"/>
        <updated>2025-05-09T04:03:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The rally followed a U.K. trade deal announcement and record ETF inflows exceeding $40 billion.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Omkar Godbole</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[US man who sent crypto to ISIS could remain in prison until age 65]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/man-funded-isis-crypto-gets-over-30-years-prison</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/man-funded-isis-crypto-gets-over-30-years-prison?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-09T03:57:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A man from the US state of Virginia will spend over three decades behind bars after being convicted of sending crypto to the terrorist organization commonly known as the Islamic State of Iraq and Syria.
Federal Judge David Novak sentenced Mohammed Azharuddin Chhipa to 30 years and four months in prison on May 7 for sending over $185,000 to the Islamic State, the Department of Justice said on May 8.
Prosecutors said that from around October 2019 until October 2022, the 35-year-old Chhipa collected and sent money to female Islamic State members in Syria, which helped them escape prison camps and funded fighting.
The Justice Department said Chhipa raised funds for the United Nations-designated terror organization through social media, receiving money online or traveling hundreds of miles to a…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Jesse Coghlan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rumble CEO confirms Tether-collab crypto wallet to launch in Q3]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/rumble-launch-bitcoin-stablecoin-wallet-q3</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/rumble-launch-bitcoin-stablecoin-wallet-q3?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-09T03:49:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Rumble’s pro-crypto founder and CEO has confirmed that the firm will launch its Bitcoin and stablecoin wallet in the third quarter of this year, aimed at giving the Coinbase Wallet a run for its money. 
The Rumble Wallet will be launched in partnership with stablecoin issuer Tether and compete directly with Coinbase, Chris Pavlovski said in a May 9 X post.
“Our goal is to become the most prominent non-custodial Bitcoin and stablecoin wallet, powering the creator economy,” he added. 
He continued to state that the Rumble Wallet will be the “vehicle to help monetize creators better than most advertisers, especially in international markets,” though he did not provide further details other than it may support Tether Gold (XAUT) as well. 
Rumble Wallet. Source: Chris Pavlovski
The video stream…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Martin Young</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dead Reckoning]]></title>
        <id>https://www.damninteresting.com/dead-reckoning/</id>
        <link href="https://www.damninteresting.com/dead-reckoning/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-09T03:46:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin at $103K hurtles MARA stack toward $5B, holdings triple]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/mara-holdings-bitcoin-holdings-value-surge-price-btc-q1-results</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/mara-holdings-bitcoin-holdings-value-surge-price-btc-q1-results?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-09T03:46:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin mining firm MARA Holdings (MARA) nearly tripled its Bitcoin holdings over 12 months, according to its newly released Q1 results.
However, its Bitcoin production fell, and total earnings slightly missed Wall Street estimates in Q1.
MARA, formerly Marathon Digital, saw its Bitcoin (BTC) holdings increase to 47,531 BTC, up 175% from the 17,320 BTC the firm was holding at the end of Q1 2024.
MARA holdings inch closer to $5B after Bitcoin pump
MARA holds the second-largest amount of Bitcoin among all publicly traded companies, according to CoinGecko data. Strategy (MSTR) holds the number one spot with 555,450 Bitcoin.
The holdings represent a total value of approximately $4.9 billion, based on Bitcoin’s current price of $102,660 at the time of publication, according to CoinMarketCap dat…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Ciaran Lyons</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Explosive ETH, ADA, DOGE Moves Spur $800M in Short Liquidations, Highest Since 2023]]></title>
        <id>d394948b-2ef5-42b4-8378-4271a83b3bb0</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/09/explosive-eth-ada-doge-moves-spur-800m-in-short-liquidations-highest-since-2023"/>
        <updated>2025-05-09T03:32:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bears are nursing their highest losses over two years as majors surged as much as 20%.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shaurya Malwa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Usenix ATC Announcement]]></title>
        <id>https://www.usenix.org/blog/usenix-atc-announcement</id>
        <link href="https://www.usenix.org/blog/usenix-atc-announcement"/>
        <updated>2025-05-09T03:18:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Starlink User Terminal Teardown]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darknavy.org/blog/a_first_glimpse_of_the_starlink_user_ternimal/</id>
        <link href="https://www.darknavy.org/blog/a_first_glimpse_of_the_starlink_user_ternimal/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-09T03:03:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Audiobookshelf: Self-hosted audiobook and podcast server]]></title>
        <id>https://www.audiobookshelf.org/</id>
        <link href="https://www.audiobookshelf.org/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-09T02:17:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ETH Surges 20%, Biggest Gain Since 2021 as Pectra Upgrade Helps Restore 'Confidence']]></title>
        <id>cea68a93-be89-4882-b355-6a0820a26fb0</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/08/eth-surges-20-biggest-gain-since-2021-as-pectra-upgrade-helps-restore-confidence"/>
        <updated>2025-05-09T01:51:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ETH outperforms CoinDesk 20 Index, as bulls comes back while BTC surges above $100k.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sam Reynolds</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OpenAI, Microsoft tell Senate ‘no one country can win AI’]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3007056</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/openai-microsoft-tell-senate-no-one-country-can-win-ai/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-09T01:02:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Executives like OpenAI's Sam Altman said US support for infrastructure would make it easier for AI companies to meet demand.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Emilia David</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SEC’s Crenshaw slams Ripple settlement, warns of ‘regulatory vacuum’]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/sec-commissioner-slams-proposed-settlement-ripple</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/sec-commissioner-slams-proposed-settlement-ripple?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-09T00:44:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A crypto-skeptical commissioner at the US Securities and Exchange Commission has blasted her agency over its settlement letter that could finally end the Ripple legal saga. 
The SEC and Ripple filed a joint settlement letter in a New York court asking for the August 2024 injunction against Ripple to be dissolved and $75 million of the $125 million in civil penalties held in escrow to be returned to the crypto firm, according to a May 8 statement from the SEC.
SEC Commissioner Caroline Crenshaw blasted the pending deal in a May 8 statement, saying it would damage the regulators’ ability to keep crypto firms in line and undermine the court’s ruling.
Source: James Filan
“This settlement, alongside the programmatic disassembly of the SEC’s crypto enforcement program, does a tremendous disservi…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Stephen Katte</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase revenue falls 10% in Q1, missing industry estimates]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/coinbase-revenue-falls-double-digits-q1-earnings-miss</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/coinbase-revenue-falls-double-digits-q1-earnings-miss?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-09T00:19:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto exchange Coinbase’s total revenue fell 10% quarter-over-quarter to $2 billion in Q1, missing industry estimates by 4.1% as trading activity slowed across the market.
Coinbase’s net income was sliced by 95% from a near-company record $1.29 billion in Q4 to $66 million, in a large part due to Coinbase marking a $596 million paper loss on its crypto holdings. 
The firm’s earnings per share of $1.94, however, managed to beat the Zacks Consensus Estimate of $1.85 for the quarter.
Coinbase’s May 8 results also showed that transaction revenue fell 18.9% quarter-on-quarter to $1.26 billion, as did trading volumes, which dipped 10.5% to $393 billion as crypto market cap dropped by double digits over the quarter, partly attributed to the Trump administration’s tariffs. 
In contrast, US Presid…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Brayden Lindrea</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[You can now fine-tune your enterprise’s own version of OpenAI’s o4-mini reasoning model with reinforcement learning]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3007091</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/you-can-now-fine-tune-your-enterprises-own-version-of-openais-o4-mini-reasoning-model-with-reinforcement-learning/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-09T00:07:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For organizations with clearly defined problems and verifiable answers, RFT offers a compelling way to align models.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carl Franzen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How The Ottawa Hospital uses AI ambient voice capture to reduce physician burnout by 70%, achieve 97% patient satisfaction]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3007069</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/how-the-ottawa-hospital-uses-ai-ambient-voice-capture-to-reduce-physician-burnout-by-70-achieve-97-patient-satisfaction/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-08T23:57:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[TOH is using Microsoft’s DAX Copilot to capture physician-patient conversations and generate draft clinical notes in real time.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Taryn Plumb</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[5 strategies that separate AI leaders from the 92% still stuck in pilot mode]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3007013</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/5-strategies-that-separate-ai-leaders-from-the-92-still-stuck-in-pilot-mode/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-08T23:09:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Accenture's new research reveals the critical strategies that separate the companies successfully scaling AI from the 92% stuck in perpetual pilot mode, providing enterprise leaders with actionable insights to accelerate their AI transformation journey.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sean Michael Kerner</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fui: C library for interacting with the framebuffer in a TTY context]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/martinfama/fui</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/martinfama/fui"/>
        <updated>2025-05-08T22:05:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meta exploring stablecoin integration for payouts: Report]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/meta-exploring-stablecoin-integration-payouts</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/meta-exploring-stablecoin-integration-payouts?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-08T21:59:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tech company Meta is reportedly exploring integrating stablecoin payments into its platforms after a three-year hiatus from cryptocurrencies, Fortune reported, citing sources familiar with the matter.
The Facebook parent held talks with several crypto infrastructure firms in consultation but has not chosen a decisive course of action, according to the report.
One source said the company may take a multi-token approach and integrate support for popular stablecoins such as Tether's USDt (USDT), Circle's USD Coin (USDC) and others.
Meta is the latest tech firm to integrate or explore the use of stablecoins for payments, as they increasingly attract institutional interest and investment, causing the stablecoin market capitalization to soar past $230 billion.
An overview of the stablecoin marke…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Vince Quill</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SEC, Ripple Ink $50M Settlement Agreement, Ask NY Judge for Green Light]]></title>
        <id>98a8d705-82b6-4ec1-8a93-9aa501a370d9</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2025/05/08/sec-ripple-ink-usd50m-settlement-agreement-ask-ny-judge-for-green-light"/>
        <updated>2025-05-08T21:26:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[District Judge Analisa Torres ordered Ripple to pay the SEC a $125 million fine last year. Under the new settlement agreement, Ripple will get the majority of that money back.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cheyenne Ligon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Wellgistics Health to integrate XRP into payment infrastructure]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/wellgistics-health-integrate-xrp-payment-infrastructure</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/wellgistics-health-integrate-xrp-payment-infrastructure?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-08T21:18:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Wellgistics Health, a healthcare infrastructure company, will integrate XRP (XRP) and related technologies into its payment network to streamline transactions between pharmacies, medical suppliers and prescription medication manufacturers, the company said in an announcement on May 8. 
Wellgistics cited the finality time of XRP transactions and reduced transaction costs, which are fractions of a penny, compared to legacy financial architecture like automated clearinghouse (ACH) payments or wire transfers, as reasons for using XRP. Brian Norton, CEO of Wellgistics Health, said in the announcement:
"I believe that the future winners in healthcare will not be the companies with the biggest buildings, they will be those with the fastest rails, cleanest data, and most efficient platforms. We ar…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Vince Quill</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Anna Kazlauskas: Data Ownership in the Age of AI]]></title>
        <id>a8d0abb4-9e20-4df5-9d90-2097344dbc7d</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/consensus-toronto-2025-coverage/2025/05/08/anna-kazlauskas-data-ownership-in-the-age-of-ai"/>
        <updated>2025-05-08T21:13:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The co-founder of Vana is building data DAOs and decentralized marketplaces to create an ecosystem of user-owned data. She will give the keynote at the AI Summit at Consensus May 16.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeff Wilser</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A flat pricing subscription for Claude Code]]></title>
        <id>https://support.anthropic.com/en/articles/11145838-using-claude-code-with-your-max-plan</id>
        <link href="https://support.anthropic.com/en/articles/11145838-using-claude-code-with-your-max-plan"/>
        <updated>2025-05-08T21:12:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Prepare for your iOS interview]]></title>
        <id>681d1bbfb1018a470d0d8a02</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/prepare-for-your-ios-interview/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-08T21:01:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Preparing for an iOS developer interview can be a daunting task, especially when you're trying to master both conceptual questions and practical coding challenges. Whether you're just starting your iOS development journey or gearing up for your next ...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase’s Deribit buy shows growing derivatives market]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/coinbase-s-deribit-buy-shows-growing-importance-of-crypto-derivatives</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/coinbase-s-deribit-buy-shows-growing-importance-of-crypto-derivatives?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-08T20:50:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase’s agreement to buy Deribit highlights the increasing importance of financial derivatives for cryptocurrency exchanges, according to industry executives. 
On May 8, Coinbase, the US’s largest crypto exchange by trading volume, agreed to acquire crypto derivatives platform Deribit for $2.9 billion in the crypto industry’s largest corporate acquisition to date.  
The deal reflects increasing competition among digital asset exchanges and brokerages — including Coinbase, Kraken and Robinhood — to dominate the burgeoning crypto derivatives market. 
"Global derivatives trading is a key driver of growth for Coinbase,” Spencer Yang, co-founder of Fractal Bitcoin, a Bitcoin scaling solution, told Cointelegraph.
Coinbase agreed to buy Deribit on May 8. Source: Coinbase
The merger established…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Alex O’Donnell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The walled garden cracks: Nadella bets Microsoft’s Copilots—and Azure’s next act—on A2A/MCP interoperability]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3006872</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/the-walled-garden-cracks-nadella-bets-microsofts-copilots-and-azures-next-act-on-a2a-mcp-interoperability/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-08T20:47:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft CEO Satya Nadella’s endorsement of Google DeepMind‘s A2A open protocol and Anthropic's MCP is huge sign the industry is moving to an open garden.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Louis Columbus</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin options could pave the path for new BTC price highs — Here is how]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-options-could-pave-the-path-for-new-btc-price-highs-here-is-how</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-options-could-pave-the-path-for-new-btc-price-highs-here-is-how?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-08T20:38:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Key takeaways:

97% of the $8.3 billion in Bitcoin put options expire worthless at a $102,000 BTC price.

Short covering above $105,000 could trigger a Bitcoin price rally to new highs.

Bitcoin (BTC) soared above $101,000 on May 8, reaching its highest level in over three months. The 4.6% daily BTC price gain triggered $205 million in liquidations of bearish futures positions and eroded the value of nearly every put (sell) option. Traders now question whether Bitcoin is poised to break its $109,354 all-time high in the near term.
Bitcoin put (sell) options open interest for May-June-July, USD notional. Source: Laevitas.ch
The aggregate Bitcoin put (sell) option open interest for the next three months stands at $8.3 billion, but 97% of those have been placed below $101,000 and will likely …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Marcel Pechman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase Stock Falls After Earnings Disappoints Wall Street on Market Volatility]]></title>
        <id>cd4cf5e1-f454-429f-9b58-53f2635f5b47</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/08/coinbase-earnings-sales-disappoints-wall-street-as-trading-volume-drops-10-amid-market-turmoil"/>
        <updated>2025-05-08T20:27:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The crypto exchange cited a drop in crypto prices as a result of U.S. President Donald Trump’s tariff policy and macroeconomic uncertainty as the reason behind the weak quarter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Helene Braun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Former FTX exec&#039;s wife says gov&#039;t ‘induced a guilty plea’]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/michelle-bond-ftx-exec-dismissal-guilty-plea</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/michelle-bond-ftx-exec-dismissal-guilty-plea?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-08T20:26:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Michelle Bond, the wife of former FTX Digital Markets co-CEO Ryan Salame, who faces federal campaign finance charges, is pushing for dismissal on the grounds that US prosecutors deceived her husband in a plea deal.
In a May 7 filing in the US District Court for the Southern District of New York, Bond’s lawyers reiterated some of the claims Salame made in opposing his plea deal with the government, which ultimately still led to him serving time in prison. She claimed that prosecutors obtained a deal with Salame through “stealth and deception” by allegedly agreeing they would not file charges against Bond. 
“Mr. Salame and Ms. Bond’s attorneys were advised that the agreement to cease investigating Ms. Bond could not be placed within the four corners of the Salame plea or other written agreem…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Turner Wright</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase's $2.9B Deribit Deal a 'Legitimate Threat' for Peers, Wall Street Analysts Say]]></title>
        <id>6137f109-2311-41c0-81cb-93091f32f4a0</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/08/coinbase-buying-deribit-for-usd2-9b-a-legitimate-threat-for-peers-wall-street-analysts-say"/>
        <updated>2025-05-08T20:13:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The acquisition makes Coinbase the largest crypto derivatives platform and a credible rival to Binance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Helene Braun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meta Is Looking to Enter Red-Hot Stablecoin Market: Fortune]]></title>
        <id>32425793-fd6d-47b5-9dad-189ef40688aa</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2025/05/08/meta-is-looking-to-deploy-stablecoin-to-manage-payouts-fortune"/>
        <updated>2025-05-08T19:58:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The tech giant reportedly also hired a vice president of product with crypto experience to help with the stablecoin efforts.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Aoyon Ashraf</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celsius Founder Alex Mashinsky Sentenced to 12 Years in Prison for Fraud]]></title>
        <id>f0c99361-53ad-4428-b976-1843ee03127e</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2025/05/08/celsius-founder-alex-mashinsky-sentenced-to-12-years-in-prison-for-fraud"/>
        <updated>2025-05-08T19:42:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mashinsky pled guilty to securities and commodities fraud charges last December.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cheyenne Ligon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mashinsky’s 12-year sentence sets tone of enforcement in Trump era]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/mashinksy-enforcement-sentence-court</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/mashinksy-enforcement-sentence-court?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-08T19:35:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The US federal court for the Southern District of New York has sentenced former Celsius CEO Alex Mashinsky to 12 years in prison for fraud. 
Mashinsky’s legal team sought a light sentence. They highlighted his spotless record before the Celsius incident, along with his military service and willingness to plead guilty. But US prosecutors were less inclined to leniency, suggesting on April 28 that the judge deliver a 20-year sentence for his actions.
Betting markets predicted a light sentence ahead of the May 8 hearing. Polymarket showed only 11% odds for a 20-year sentence or higher.
Source: Polymarket
President Donald Trump began his second term with high-profile pardons of crypto executives, signalling that his administration may bring leniency to crypto fraudsters like Mashinsky. His sen…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Aaron Wood</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Alibaba’s ‘ZeroSearch’ lets AI learn to google itself — slashing training costs by 88 percent]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3007024</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/alibabas-zerosearch-lets-ai-learn-to-google-itself-slashing-training-costs-by-88-percent/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-08T19:15:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Alibaba’s ZeroSearch trains large language models to beat Google Search and slash API costs by 88%, redefining how AI learns to retrieve information.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Nuñez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mem0’s scalable memory promises more reliable AI agents that remembers context across lengthy conversations]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3006826</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/mem0s-scalable-memory-promises-more-reliable-ai-agents-that-remembers-context-across-lengthy-conversations/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-08T19:13:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mem0's architecture is designed to LLM memory and enhance consistency for more reliable agent performance in long conversations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ben Dickson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use Arrow Functions in PHP 7.4+]]></title>
        <id>681cf9062cbe43bee0f4138f</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-arrow-functions-in-php/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-08T18:33:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Arrow functions were introduced in PHP 7.4 to allow devs to write short, anonymous functions. They offer a compact alternative to traditional closures, especially when the function body is small and focused. In this article, you will learn how to use...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Montasser Mossallem</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Senate Votes Against Advancing Stablecoin Bill, Delaying Process as Trump Concerns Fester]]></title>
        <id>39e96b89-58d1-4a04-b735-c7a815099697</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2025/05/08/senate-votes-against-advancing-stablecoin-bill-delaying-process-as-trump-concerns-fester"/>
        <updated>2025-05-08T18:33:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Last-minute Democrat objections led to a failed vote to move into debate on a top crypto industry legislative priority to regulate dollar-based tokens.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jesse Hamilton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Reservoir Sampling]]></title>
        <id>https://samwho.dev/reservoir-sampling/</id>
        <link href="https://samwho.dev/reservoir-sampling/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-08T17:02:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Void: Open-source Cursor alternative]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/voideditor/void</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/voideditor/void"/>
        <updated>2025-05-08T16:35:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin $120K Target for 2Q May Be Too Conservative: Standard Chartered]]></title>
        <id>e94afa61-4a92-4d90-80c3-4bd2fd25c9a4</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/08/bitcoin-120k-target-for-2q-may-be-too-conservative-standard-chartered"/>
        <updated>2025-05-08T16:14:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Spot bitcoin ETF net inflows totaled over $4 billion in the last three weeks, when adjusted for hedge fund basis trades, the bank said.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Will Canny</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Free GenAI 65-Hour Bootcamp]]></title>
        <id>681cd4ea505e2f4aa02206d5</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/free-genai-65-hour-bootcamp/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-08T15:59:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Generative AI is revolutionizing how we create, learn, and interact with digital content. From intelligent chatbots and personalized language tutors to realistic image generation and interactive story engines, the applications are endless. We just pu...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Tops $100K for First Time in 3 Months; Are Upside Targets Too Low?]]></title>
        <id>3caf7639-a5b3-40db-87a5-ecfb096e2838</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/02/bitcoin-tops-usd100k-for-first-time-in-3-months-are-upside-targets-too-low"/>
        <updated>2025-05-08T15:38:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The price has jumped 33% in a few weeks after plunging to $75,000 in the days following President Trump's early April Liberation Day tariff announcement.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephen Alpher</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Brief Introduction to Web Components]]></title>
        <id>681cce7f505e2f4aa022069b</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/a-brief-introduction-to-web-components/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-08T15:32:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a previous article, I gave a brief introduction to React. This tutorial introduces an alternative approach to building a component-based frontend. It covers the fundamentals of Web Components to build modular, reusable elements for your web applic...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mark Mahoney</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OpenAI names Instacart leader Fidji Simo as new CEO of Applications]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3006978</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/openai-names-instacart-leader-fidji-simo-as-new-ceo-of-applications/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-08T15:25:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Simo’s appointment may also hint at a broader productization push within OpenAI. Her background at Facebook and Instacart underscores...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carl Franzen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Senate Republicans Making Plea to Get on With Stablecoin Debate]]></title>
        <id>f0785da5-57a1-4ecf-99a9-1f64bb84ac8f</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2025/05/08/senate-republicans-making-plea-to-get-on-with-stablecoin-debate"/>
        <updated>2025-05-08T15:08:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Once-allied Democrats continue to drag their heels on the first big crypto bill, leaving a key vote in doubt as GOP Majority Leader Thune calls for action.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jesse Hamilton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto for Advisors: Trends in Tokenizing Real-World Assets]]></title>
        <id>b842342d-8b85-40e5-a277-0d942aa00390</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/coindesk-indices/2025/05/07/crypto-for-advisors-trends-in-tokenizing-real-world-assets"/>
        <updated>2025-05-08T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tokenization turns real-world assets into blockchain tokens, boosting efficiency, liquidity and accessibility. Learn about why Ethereum is the current leader in this space.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tedd Strazimiri</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Breakout Alert: Ether, Bitcoin Cash-Bitcoin Ratio Break Downtrends as DOGE, SHIB Bottom Out]]></title>
        <id>47d52b24-b2a0-49d4-97e9-7912e7196447</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/08/breakout-alert-ether-bitcoin-cash-bitcoin-ratio-break-downtrends-doge-shib-bottom-out"/>
        <updated>2025-05-08T14:42:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ETH, BCH and top memecoins are flashing bullish chart patterns.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Omkar Godbole</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GSR’s Josh Riezman on Regulation, Risk, and Readying Crypto for the Next Phase]]></title>
        <id>07207794-a009-461a-839b-c1e82dc89e52</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/consensus-toronto-2025-coverage/2025/05/08/gsrs-josh-riezman-on-regulation-risk-and-readying-crypto-for-the-next-phase"/>
        <updated>2025-05-08T14:11:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The market-maker, investor and asset manager aims to be a “one-stop shop for market participants,” says its Chief Strategy Officer. Riezman is a speaker at Consensus 2025 May 14-16.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Francisco Rodrigues</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Superstate Expands Into Tokenized Equities; SOL Strategies to Be First Listing]]></title>
        <id>6b1ea7b7-1c49-4659-84bd-828e67ef0d0f</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2025/05/08/superstate-expands-into-tokenized-equities-sol-strategies-to-be-first-listing"/>
        <updated>2025-05-08T14:00:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The company's "Opening Bell" platform lets SEC-registered shares trade on-chain, bridging crypto and public equity markets.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Krisztian Sandor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Download: AI benchmarks, and Spain’s grid blackout]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1116202</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/05/08/1116202/the-download-ai-benchmarks-and-spains-grid-blackout/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-08T12:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is today’s edition of The Download, our weekday newsletter that provides a daily dose of what’s going on in the world of technology. How to build a better AI benchmark It’s not easy being one of Silicon Valley’s favorite benchmarks.  SWE-Bench (pronounced “swee bench”) launched in November 2024 as a way to evaluate an AI model’s…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rhiannon Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Did solar power cause Spain’s blackout?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1116166</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/05/08/1116166/spain-blackout-grid/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-08T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At roughly midday on Monday, April 28, the lights went out in Spain. The grid blackout, which extended into parts of Portugal and France, affected tens of millions of people—flights were grounded, cell networks went down, and businesses closed for the day. Over a week later, officials still aren’t entirely sure what happened, but some…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Casey Crownhart</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to build a better AI benchmark]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1116192</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/05/08/1116192/how-to-build-a-better-ai-benchmark/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-08T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s not easy being one of Silicon Valley’s favorite benchmarks.  SWE-Bench (pronounced “swee bench”) launched in November 2024 to evaluate an AI model’s coding skill, using more than 2,000 real-world programming problems pulled from the public GitHub repositories of 12 different Python-based projects.  In the months since then, it’s quickly become one of the most…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Russell Brandom</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Imagination unveils E-Series GPUs for graphics and AI at the edge]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3006922</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/games/imagination-unveils-e-series-gpus-for-graphics-and-ai-at-the-edge/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-08T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Imagination Technologies is unveiling its E-Series graphics processing units (GPUs) for graphics and AI processing at the edge.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dean Takahashi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nvidia welcomes Trump’s proposal to rescind global chip restrictions]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3006921</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/gaming-business/nvidia-welcomes-trumps-proposal-to-rescind-global-chip-restrictions/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-08T06:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Donald Trump's administration is expected to rescind Joe Biden's curbs on AI chip sales as part of a broader effort to revise semiconductor restrictions, Bloomberg reported.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dean Takahashi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Anthropic launches Claude web search API, betting on the future of post-Google information access]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3006849</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/anthropic-launches-claude-web-search-api-betting-on-the-future-of-post-google-information-access/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-07T22:01:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Anthropic launches web search API for Claude as Apple considers AI search alternatives to Google, signaling a major shift in how users discover information online.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Nuñez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn Next.js by Coding Your Own Dropbox Clone – Full Course]]></title>
        <id>681b80ee1a1a4e16cffa1a50</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/code-a-dropbox-clone-with-nextjs/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-07T15:49:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Building modern full-stack applications requires a strong grasp of various interconnected technologies. And what better way to learn than by creating a real-world project that mimics a widely used tool like Dropbox? That’s exactly what this new cours...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mistral comes out swinging for enterprise AI customers with new Le Chat Enterprise, Medium 3 model]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3006803</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/mistral-comes-out-swinging-for-enterprise-ai-customers-with-new-le-chat-enterprise-medium-3-model/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-07T15:13:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mistral AI is making a concerted push to lower the barriers to scalable, privacy-respecting AI adoption for modern enterprises.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carl Franzen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Recursive Types in TypeScript: A Brief Exploration]]></title>
        <id>681b77a47396438eaee0c5ce</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/recursive-types-in-typescript-a-brief-exploration/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-07T15:09:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It is said that there are two different worlds in TypeScript that exist side by side: the type world and the value world. Consider this line of code: const firstName: string = 'Maynard'; While firstName and 'Maynard' live in the value world, string ...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eda Eren</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The business of the future is adaptive]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1116098</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/05/07/1116098/the-business-of-the-future-is-adaptive/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-07T14:14:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Manufacturing is in a state of flux. From supply chain disruptions to rising costs, tougher environmental regulations, and a changing consumer market, the sector faces a series of competing challenges. But a new way of operating offers a way to tackle complexities head-on: adaptive production hardwires flexibility and resilience into the enterprise, drawing on powerful…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>MIT Technology Review Insights</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Front-End Performance Optimization Handbook – Tips and Strategies for Devs]]></title>
        <id>681b5e61b1ed0b90facd0adf</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/the-front-end-performance-optimization-handbook/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-07T13:21:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When you’re building a website, you’ll want it to be responsive, fast, and efficient. This means making sure the site loads quickly, runs smoothly, and provides a seamless experience for your users, among other things. So as you build, you’ll want to...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gordan Tan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Breathe lands $21M Series B to predict battery performance]]></title>
        <id>https://techcrunch.com/?p=3003769</id>
        <link href="https://techcrunch.com/2025/05/07/breathe-lands-21m-series-b-to-predict-battery-performance/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-07T12:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Breathe has developed a suite of tools that it says helps automakers and others get the most out of their batteries.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tim De Chant</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Netflix unveils new TV experience with GenAI search and AI-based recommendations]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3006789</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/games/netflix-unveils-new-tv-experience-with-genai-search-and-ai-based-recommendations/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-07T12:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Netflix unveiled its new TV experience that features generative AI search, AI-based recommendations and an enhanced design.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dean Takahashi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Download: Neuralink’s AI boost, and Trump’s tariffs]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1116147</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/05/07/1116147/the-download-neuralinks-ai-boost-and-trumps-tariffs/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-07T12:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is today’s edition of The Download, our weekday newsletter that provides a daily dose of what’s going on in the world of technology. This patient’s Neuralink brain implant gets a boost from generative AI Last November, Bradford G. Smith got a brain implant from Elon Musk’s company Neuralink. The device, a set of thin wires attached…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rhiannon Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This patient’s Neuralink brain implant gets a boost from generative AI]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1116139</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/05/07/1116139/this-brain-implant-gets-a-boost-from-generative-ai/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-07T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Last November, Bradford G. Smith got a brain implant from Elon Musk’s company Neuralink. The device, a set of thin wires attached to a computer about the thickness of a few quarters that sits in his skull, lets him use his thoughts to move a computer pointer on a screen.  And by last week he…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Antonio Regalado</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS report: Generative AI overtakes security in global tech budgets for 2025]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3006670</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/aws-report-generative-ai-overtakes-security-in-global-tech-budgets-for-2025/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T21:33:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New AWS report reveals 45% of global IT leaders now prioritize generative AI over cybersecurity in 2025 tech budgets as companies race to hire AI talent and implement AI strategies despite persistent skills shortages.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Nuñez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Secure Mobile APIs in Flutter]]></title>
        <id>681a707658599a397b11b418</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-secure-mobile-apis-in-flutter/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T20:26:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As mobile applications continue to evolve in functionality and scope, securing the APIs that power these apps has become more critical than ever. In the context of Flutter, a framework that enables cross-platform development, understanding how to sec...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Atuoha Anthony</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How "Night of the Living Dead" Accidentally Became Public Domain]]></title>
        <id>https://screenrant.com/night-living-dead-movie-public-domain-copyright-accident/</id>
        <link href="https://screenrant.com/night-living-dead-movie-public-domain-copyright-accident/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T20:14:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meet the new king of AI coding: Google’s Gemini 2.5 Pro I/O Edition dethrones Claude 3.7 Sonnet]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3006623</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/meet-the-new-king-of-ai-coding-googles-gemini-2-5-pro-i-o-edition-dethrones-claude-3-7-sonnet/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T18:39:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One of the standout features of the update is its ability to build full, interactive web apps or simulations from a single prompt.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carl Franzen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Create Documentation with docs.page – A Beginner's Tutorial]]></title>
        <id>681a558b9791d0e469b84519</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-create-documentation-with-docspage/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T18:31:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One of the most tedious tasks for every startup, company, and open-source project is often building and managing documentation – especially for medium to large-scale documentation websites. docs.page is an open-source documentation tool that helps yo...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rajdeep Singh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lightricks just made AI video generation 30x faster — and you won’t need a $10,000 GPU]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3006613</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/lightricks-just-made-ai-video-generation-30x-faster-and-you-wont-need-a-10000-gpu/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T17:56:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Lightricks unveils groundbreaking LTXV-13B AI video model that runs 30X faster than competitors on consumer hardware through innovative "multiscale rendering" technology.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Nuñez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ServiceNow lets users see more of their AI]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3006589</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/servicenow-lets-users-see-more-of-their-ai/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ServiceNow also announced a way for agents to communicate with others along with its new observability platform.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Emilia David</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Report: OpenAI is buying AI-powered developer platform Windsurf — what happens to its support for rival LLMs?]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3006587</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/report-openai-is-buying-ai-powered-developer-platform-windsurf-what-happens-to-its-support-for-rival-llms/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T14:37:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[OpenAI could see which types of developers use rival models such as the Meta Llama variants and Anthropic's Claude, and for what purposes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carl Franzen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Startup Korl unveils multimodal, multi-agent tool for custom communication across disparate systems]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3006451</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/how-openai-gemini-and-anthropic-help-korl-prepare-customer-materials-in-minutes/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Korl's platform works across multiple systems, using multi-agent and multimodal AI to create highly-customized customer messaging.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Taryn Plumb</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ōura adds AI-driven meal and glucose tracking features with Stelo by Dexcom]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3006449</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/games/oura-adds-ai-driven-meal-and-glucose-tracking-features-with-stelo-by-dexcom/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ōura, maker of a health-monitoring smart ring, announced that it will use AI to track and analyze two new metabolic health features: meals and glucose.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dean Takahashi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Malaya's Timeless Design]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linyangchen.com/Philately</id>
        <link href="https://www.linyangchen.com/Philately"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T12:54:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Download: a longevity influencer’s new religion, and humanoid robots’ shortcomings]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1116114</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/05/06/1116114/the-download-a-longevity-influencers-new-religion-and-humanoid-robots-shortcomings/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T12:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is today’s edition of The Download, our weekday newsletter that provides a daily dose of what’s going on in the world of technology. Bryan Johnson wants to start a new religion in which “the body is God” Bryan Johnson is on a mission to not die. The 47-year-old multimillionaire has already applied his slogan “Don’t Die”…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rhiannon Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Join the 2025 Web3j Mentorships: Build the Future of Ethereum on the JVM]]></title>
        <id>6819c8dc41eeeb000183d37b</id>
        <link href="https://blog.web3labs.com/join-the-2025-web3j-mentorships-build-the-future-of-ethereum-on-the-jvm/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T08:32:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Linux Foundation’s Decentralized Trust (LFDT) mentorship program is back in 2025 with two exciting opportunities for developers passionate about Ethereum, Android, and the Java Virtual Machine (JVM). Whether you’re a seasoned blockchain developer or an Android enthusiast eager to dive into Web3, these mentorships offer]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>George Tebrean</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[IBM thinks that over a billion new applications will be built with gen AI : Here’s how they’re going to help that happen with agentic AI]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3006455</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/agents-are-key-to-enterprise-ai-success-heres-ibms-plan-on-how-to-make-it-happen/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T04:01:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[IBM details its plans to help enterprises to actually do more with AI, with an expanded set of agentic AI capabilities.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sean Michael Kerner</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meta, Cisco put open-source LLMs at the core of next-gen SOC workflows]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3006384</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/rsac-2025-cisco-and-meta-put-open-source-ai-at-the-heart-of-enterprise-threat-defense/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T00:08:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cisco’s Foundation-sec-8B LLM & Meta’s AI Defenders redefine cybersecurity with open-source AI for scalable SOCs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Louis Columbus</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nvidia launches fully open source transcription AI model Parakeet-TDT-0.6B-V2 on Hugging Face]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3006438</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/nvidia-launches-fully-open-source-transcription-ai-model-parakeet-tdt-0-6b-v2-on-hugging-face/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-05T19:17:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An attractive proposition for commercial enterprises and indie developers looking to build speech recognition and transcription services...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carl Franzen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Zombieverter: Open source VCU for reusing salvage EV components]]></title>
        <id>https://openinverter.org/wiki/ZombieVerter_VCU</id>
        <link href="https://openinverter.org/wiki/ZombieVerter_VCU"/>
        <updated>2025-05-05T19:00:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Visa launches ‘Intelligent Commerce’ platform, letting AI agents swipe your card—safely, it says]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3006416</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/visa-launches-intelligent-commerce-platform-letting-ai-agents-swipe-your-card-safely-it-says/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-05T18:01:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Visa launches Intelligent Commerce platform enabling AI assistants to make secure purchases with your credit card, transforming online shopping with personalized automation and consumer-controlled spending limits.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Nuñez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Structuring Competency-Based Courses Through Skill Trees]]></title>
        <id>https://arxiv.org/abs/2504.16966</id>
        <link href="https://arxiv.org/abs/2504.16966"/>
        <updated>2025-05-05T13:34:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Full Control.xyz Freeform Gcode]]></title>
        <id>https://fullcontrol.xyz/#/models</id>
        <link href="https://fullcontrol.xyz/#/models"/>
        <updated>2025-05-05T11:51:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Robotics meets the culinary arts]]></title>
        <id>https://actu.epfl.ch/news/robotics-meets-the-culinary-arts/</id>
        <link href="https://actu.epfl.ch/news/robotics-meets-the-culinary-arts/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-05T08:45:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The great cognitive migration: How AI is reshaping human purpose, work and meaning]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3006326</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/the-great-cognitive-migration-ai-will-win-at-intelligence-but-only-we-can-make-it-matter/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-04T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Humans need to embrace domains where AI still falters, and where human creativity, ethics and emotion emain indispensable.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gary Grossman, Edelman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Not everything needs an LLM: A framework for evaluating when AI makes sense]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3006312</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/not-everything-needs-an-llm-a-framework-for-evaluating-when-ai-makes-sense/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-03T19:35:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The answer to 'What customer needs requires an AI solution?' isn’t always 'Yes.' LLMs are still expensive and not always accurate.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sharanya Rao</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[RSAC 2025: Why the AI agent era means more demand for CISOs]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3006066</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/security/rsac-2025-why-the-ai-agent-era-means-more-demand-for-cisos/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-02T23:02:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[RSAC 2025 made one thing clear: AI agents are entering security workflows, but boards want proof they work.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Louis Columbus</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OpenAI overrode concerns of expert testers to release sycophantic GPT-4o]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3006276</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/openai-overrode-concerns-of-expert-testers-to-release-sycophantic-gpt-4o/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-02T17:57:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Once again, it shows the importance of incorporating more domains beyond the traditional math and computer science into AI development.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carl Franzen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Web3j Six Month Project Update]]></title>
        <id>68109495670a1300013504c2</id>
        <link href="https://blog.web3labs.com/web3j-six-month-project-update/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T09:10:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[November 2024 - April 2025
This report summarizes the activities and accomplishments of Web3j, an LF Decentralized Trust project, from November 2024 to April 2025. During this period, the project made significant strides in improving the framework’s functionality, enhancing user engagement, and bolstering overall community interaction. 
Key]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>George Tebrean</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[QuickNode: Building the Infrastructure for the Next Generation of Blockchain]]></title>
        <id>6807d5787fb8500001c39b99</id>
        <link href="https://blog.quicknode.com/quicknode-building-the-infrastructure-for-the-next-generation-of-blockchain/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-28T16:02:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Join QuickNode co-founder Dmitry Shklovsky as he discusses blockchain infrastructure, building decentralized applications, and the future of Web3 development on TheCube's Crypto Trailblazer Series.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>QuickNode</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>