<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2025-05-09T08:18:35.714Z</id>
    <title>AngJianming RSS Feed</title>
    <updated>2025-05-09T08:18:35.714Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Is Pi Network dead? What really went wrong behind the hype]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/explained/is-pi-network-dead-what-really-went-wrong-behind-the-hype</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/explained/is-pi-network-dead-what-really-went-wrong-behind-the-hype?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-09T08:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What Pi Network promised            
            
                
When Pi Network first hit the scene in 2019, it had a simple but compelling pitch: What if you could mine cryptocurrency straight from your phone — no expensive gear, no massive electricity bills, just a tap a day on an app?
It caught fire. Millions of people jumped on board, lured by the idea of “free” mobile mining and a chance to get in early on the next big thing. The app made it easy: You signed up, invited a few friends, tapped a button every 24 hours, and watched your Pi (PI) balance slowly grow. With the social referral model fueling growth, it wasn’t long before over 70 million users had signed up worldwide.

Did you know? Pi Network utilizes the Stellar Consensus Protocol (SCP), which aims for energy efficiency an…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Bradley Peak</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trading Competitions: Why Emotional Discipline Matters More Than Strategy]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/philip_crypto92/trading-competitions-why-emotional-discipline-matters-more-than-strategy-4i6c</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/philip_crypto92/trading-competitions-why-emotional-discipline-matters-more-than-strategy-4i6c"/>
        <updated>2025-05-09T08:08:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The common perception of trading often revolves around technical analysis, algorithms, and advanced strategies. While these components are essential, they only represent part of the picture. Trading, particularly in competitive environments, also demands psychological resilience and emotional control.
This becomes particularly evident in trading tournaments, where pressure, time limits, and direct competition create a behavioral environment that tests more than just market knowledge. Success in such scenarios is not determined solely by the depth of one's strategy, but by the ability to execute under stress.
In trading competitions, participants aren't just battling the market—they're also contending with one another. Public leaderboards, predefined timelines, and fixed capital allocations…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Philip Laurens</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[React or Next.js]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/kumar_mrigank_f0a7b50be09/react-or-nextjs-2c19</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/kumar_mrigank_f0a7b50be09/react-or-nextjs-2c19"/>
        <updated>2025-05-09T08:08:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I’m building a web app for Restaurant Reservations which will have dedicated URLs and pages with rich text, heavy images, for each outlet. 
My main goal is to achieve faster webpage speed and performance, along with a strong user experience so that ad campaigns work well and we can retain the customer to book through us.
I’m deciding between using React or Next.js, and I’d like to understand which one would be more suitable for me and why it would be better?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>kumar mrigank</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why obsidian wins the second brain war and notion just can’t keep up]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/devlinktips/why-obsidian-wins-the-second-brain-war-and-notion-just-cant-keep-up-3p9f</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/devlinktips/why-obsidian-wins-the-second-brain-war-and-notion-just-cant-keep-up-3p9f"/>
        <updated>2025-05-09T08:07:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[the markdown-powered beast that turned my cluttered mind into a structured wiki with backlinks and magic
Section 1: introduction the brain fog problem
Let’s be real for a sec most of us are drowning in digital clutter.
You open Notion to “organize” your notes and suddenly spend 45 minutes tweaking page aesthetics like you’re designing a landing page for a failed SaaS. You try Craft and get distracted by the beautiful UI because it’s basically Apple Notes with a Gatsby filter. Capacities? Promising, but slow. And you still can’t remember where you wrote that idea about “building an indie dev SaaS for LLM-powered cats.”
We’re knowledge workers in the age of information overload, and ironically, all our shiny productivity tools are making us feel… less productive.
Here’s the core problem: the…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Devlink Tips</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[6 Game-Changing Postman Alternatives That Will Revolutionize Your API Development in 2025]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/rihpig/6-game-changing-postman-alternatives-that-will-revolutionize-your-api-development-in-2025-4fll</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/rihpig/6-game-changing-postman-alternatives-that-will-revolutionize-your-api-development-in-2025-4fll"/>
        <updated>2025-05-09T08:06:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Let's face it – we've all been there. You're in the middle of an API testing marathon, your team is growing, and suddenly you hit that dreaded Postman free plan limit. Whether it's the 3-API cap, the measly 25 collection runs per month, or the collaboration restrictions that only allow 3 team members, these barriers can bring your development workflow to a screeching halt.
Postman has been the industry standard for years, but the API development landscape has evolved dramatically. Today's teams need tools that scale with their projects, offer robust collaboration features, and don't force you into premium plans just to handle basic workflows.
In this deep dive, we'll explore seven powerful Postman alternatives that are changing the game for API development teams in 2025. And spoiler alert …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rihpig</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Is Next.js falling off? why some devs are bailing, and what they’re building instead]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/devlinktips/is-nextjs-falling-off-why-some-devs-are-bailing-and-what-theyre-building-instead-28f9</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/devlinktips/is-nextjs-falling-off-why-some-devs-are-bailing-and-what-theyre-building-instead-28f9"/>
        <updated>2025-05-09T08:05:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[next.js was once the golden child of react frameworks. now? not so much. here’s why the hype is fading and what’s replacing it.
Section 1: Intro the fall of a frontend darling
Once upon a time, every React dev and their dog was shipping sites with Next.js. It was clean. It was fast. It made static generation cool again. You threw your .mdx files into a pages/ directory, ran next build, and went on with your life. Need some SSR? BoomgetServerSideProps() had your back. Need an image optimizer? Already built-in. Life was good.
Then came the App Router.
 Then came React Server Components.
 Then came Middleware.
 Then came… existential dread.
Suddenly, what used to be a dev-friendly framework started feeling like a PhD thesis in distributed systems. Next.js started promising everything, but del…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Devlink Tips</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why devs are quitting aws and what they’re choosing instead]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/devlinktips/why-devs-are-quitting-aws-and-what-theyre-choosing-instead-4hea</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/devlinktips/why-devs-are-quitting-aws-and-what-theyre-choosing-instead-4hea"/>
        <updated>2025-05-09T08:01:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The cloud giant isn’t invincible here’s why some engineers are ditching AWS for leaner, meaner setups
Introduction: rage quitting the cloud boss battle
If AWS were a video game boss, it would be the one with 27 different attack modes, a second health bar, and a $437 surprise invoice when you respawn. For years, Amazon Web Services was the obvious choice for developers powerful, scalable, and used by the big leagues. But now? A growing number of devs are hitting the eject button and exploring new terrain.
This article isn’t a salty rant from someone who got burned by CloudWatch fees (okay, maybe a little). It’s a real look at how AWS, once the darling of cloud infrastructure, is becoming less attractive especially for indie hackers, startups, and lean dev teams.
We’ll break down why develop…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Devlink Tips</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[vivo X Fold5 Global Specs Leak; May Pack 6,000 mAh Battery]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=351205</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/351205/vivo-x-fold5-global-specs-leak-may-pack-6000-mah-battery/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-09T08:01:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[vivo released its X Fold3 series last year, and is now reported to be launching the X Fold5. While the Pro version of last year’s series received a limited global release, the base model was only launched in China. However, only foldable from the brand will reportedly be released in the Chinese market. As per […]
The post vivo X Fold5 Global Specs Leak; May Pack 6,000 mAh Battery appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Newsdesk</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to mass convert TIFF to JPG (Tutorial)]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/idrsolutions/how-to-mass-convert-tiff-to-jpg-tutorial-1gio</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/idrsolutions/how-to-mass-convert-tiff-to-jpg-tutorial-1gio"/>
        <updated>2025-05-09T08:01:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[TIFF (Tagged Image File Format) is a versatile image format known for its high-quality and lossless compression. It is often widely used across various devices and platforms, particularly in professional photography, publishing, and graphic design.
Converting a lot of TIFF images to JPG can significantly reduce file size, making them easier to store and share without compromising too much on quality.
In this article, I’ll guide you through the process of using Java to convert TIFF files to JPG format with JDeli, ensuring your images are accessible.  JDeli is the best enterprise-level Java image library for quick development.
Download the JDeli trial jar.
Process image if needed (scale, sharpen, lighten, watermark, etc)
Write out BufferedImage as JPG image file




BufferedImage bufferedImage = JDeli.read(new File("tiffImageFile.tiff"));
// Read TIFF image into Java

bufferedImage = operations.apply(BufferedImage bufferedImage);
// Process TIFF image (Optional)

JDeli.write(bufferedImage, "jpg", new File("jpgImageFile.jpg"));
// Write out BufferedImage as JPEG image file

With the JDeli.convert() method you can save TIFF as JPG in just one line of code.
JDeli.convert(File inFile, File outFile);

JDeli.convert(InputStream inputStream, OutputStream outputStream, "jpg");

byte[] outputData = JDeli.convert(byte[] inputData, "jpg");

You can specify an EncoderOptions object with this option to configure output settings like image compression.
JDeli.convert(File inFile, EncoderOptions outputOptions, File outfile);

Command line or bash, bat, and PowerShell scripts can be used to mass convert TIFF to JPG. This method also allows JDeli to be invoked from any programming language that supports creating a child process.
java -jar jdeli.jar –convert jpg "inputFileOrDir" "outputDir"

In this tutorial you learned how to bulk convert TIFF to JPG in bulk, our Java Image library JDeli also has TIFF support for reading and writing, which you can learn more about on our support site.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>IDRSolutions</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Building AI Voice Agents for Production]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/brains_behind_bots/building-ai-voice-agents-for-production-16ig</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/brains_behind_bots/building-ai-voice-agents-for-production-16ig"/>
        <updated>2025-05-09T08:00:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A post by Chanchal Singh]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chanchal Singh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Fix Flutter Run Command Errors on Mac?]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/generatecodedev/how-to-fix-flutter-run-command-errors-on-mac-9oo</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/generatecodedev/how-to-fix-flutter-run-command-errors-on-mac-9oo"/>
        <updated>2025-05-09T08:00:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction
Building a Flutter app on a Mac can be a delightful experience if everything goes smoothly. However, it’s not uncommon to encounter errors while running the flutter run command, which can halt your development process. In this guide, we will address how to resolve common Flutter run command errors you might face during setup, particularly on macOS.
Understanding the Issue
When you encounter an error running the flutter run command, it's often due to several potential issues. This includes misconfigured Flutter SDK paths, missing dependencies, or issues with your iOS or Android emulators. The error message displayed in your terminal can provide insight into what went wrong.
Some possible errors might include:
Flutter SDK not found.
Problems with the iOS Simulator or Android Emu…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Generatecode</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ecto for Elixir: A Beginner's Guide to Database Interactions]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/actor-dev/ecto-for-elixir-a-beginners-guide-to-database-interactions-4l7k</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/actor-dev/ecto-for-elixir-a-beginners-guide-to-database-interactions-4l7k"/>
        <updated>2025-05-09T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction


During my journey learning Elixir, I discovered Ecto, a powerful database wrapper and query generator that enables seamless interaction with SQL databases. While often compared to ORMs like Entity Framework Core or Ruby on Rails' ActiveRecord, Ecto diverges by avoiding automatic state tracking, requiring developers to manage changes explicitly. This article explores Ecto's core concepts, including repositories, schemas, migrations, and CRUD operations. For advanced features, refer to Ecto’s official documentation.
Ecto is a database wrapper and query generator for Elixir, designed to work with relational databases like PostgreSQL and MySQL. It provides:
Map database tables to Elixir structs (via schemas).
Generate type-safe queries using Elixir syntax.
Validate data before p…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rafael Andrade</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[C# How to ambient transaction work under the hood]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/eveissim/how-to-ambient-transaction-work-under-the-hood-5e55</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/eveissim/how-to-ambient-transaction-work-under-the-hood-5e55"/>
        <updated>2025-05-09T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In previous article, we looked at how  TransactionScope (ambient transaction) simplifies transactional consistency. But how does it do this? How does such a simple and convenient mechanism solve this problem? How exactly is a transaction passed between threads is asynchronous communication? And how does the process of rollback and commit work?
 TransactionScope and Transaction.Current

How exactly does ExecutionContext 'know' about ContextKey through AsyncLocal and what happens when await occurs
How Transaction is passed to Npgsql

How do Commit() and Rollback() work
Conclusion
sources:
transaction scope class - source

System.Transaction class - source 
The TransactionScope class in .NET is used to automatically manage transactions through the ambient transactions mechanism. You can read …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>EveIsSim</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ecto para Elixir: Guia para Iniciantes sobre Interações com Banco de Dados]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/actor-dev/ecto-para-elixir-guia-para-iniciantes-sobre-interacoes-com-banco-de-dados-1ng6</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/actor-dev/ecto-para-elixir-guia-para-iniciantes-sobre-interacoes-com-banco-de-dados-1ng6"/>
        <updated>2025-05-09T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introdução ao Ecto com Elixir: Configuração e Operações Básicas


Durante minha jornada de aprendizado em Elixir, descobri o Ecto, uma poderosa camada de abstração para bancos de dados e gerador de consultas que permite interagir com bancos SQL de forma intuitiva. Embora frequentemente comparado a ORMs como o Entity Framework Core ou o ActiveRecord do Ruby on Rails, o Ecto se diferencia por não rastrear automaticamente estados de entidades, exigindo que os desenvolvedores gerenciem mudanças de forma explícita. Este artigo explora conceitos fundamentais do Ecto, incluindo repositórios, schemas, migrações e operações CRUD. Para recursos avançados, consulte a documentação oficial do Ecto.  
O Ecto é uma camada de abstração para bancos de dados projetada para trabalhar com bancos relacionais c…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rafael Andrade</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Sony WH-1000XM6 Renders Confirm Foldable Design]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=351209</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/351209/new-sony-wh-1000xm6-renders-confirms-foldable-design/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-09T07:55:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It looks like the Sony WH-1000XM6 headphones have been outed in all their glory. Product renders of the headphones were obtained by The Walkman Blog, and shows the products in three colour schemes and more importantly, sporting a foldable design. It’s safe to say that the leaked renders fully confirm that Sony is reverting to […]
The post New Sony WH-1000XM6 Renders Confirm Foldable Design appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John Law</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Grab Reportedly Aiming To Finalise GoTo Acquisition Deal By Q2 2025]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=351239</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/351239/grab-finalising-goto-acquisition-within-q2-2025/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-09T07:43:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Grab is aiming to finalise the acquisition of its Indonesian competitor GoTo in the second quarter of this year, according to a Reuters report. The proposed deal, which could be worth around US$7 billion (~RM30.2 billion), would mark a significant consolidation in Southeast Asia’s tech and mobility landscape. Reuters adds that Grab has hired advisors […]
The post Grab Reportedly Aiming To Finalise GoTo Acquisition Deal By Q2 2025 appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Heirul Kamel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Florida Pharma Firm Will Use XRP for Real-Time Payments in $50M Financing Deal]]></title>
        <id>3bea0223-cb59-4560-bc12-d0767714ca4b</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/09/florida-pharma-firm-will-use-xrp-for-real-time-payments-in-usd50m-financing-deal"/>
        <updated>2025-05-09T07:26:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“We believe that there are certain advantages to integrating XRP and its related infrastructure into its healthcare ecosystem,” the firm said in the release.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shaurya Malwa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Boy Accidentally Orders 70k Lollipops on Amazon. Panic Ensues.]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nytimes.com/2025/05/08/business/dum-dums-amazon-order-kentucky.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.nytimes.com/2025/05/08/business/dum-dums-amazon-order-kentucky.html"/>
        <updated>2025-05-09T07:23:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Doge software engineer's computer infected by info-stealing malware]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/security/2025/05/doge-software-engineers-computer-infected-by-info-stealing-malware/</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/security/2025/05/doge-software-engineers-computer-infected-by-info-stealing-malware/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-09T07:22:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Smart #5 Debuts In Malaysia Alongside Smart #1 Brabus Edition]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=351125</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/351125/smart-5-debuts-in-malaysia-alongside-smart-1-brabus-edition/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-09T06:55:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Smart, a well-known name in Malaysia’s electric vehicle industry, previewed its Smart #5 and Smart #1 Brabus edition yesterday at the Malaysia Auto Show (MAS 2025). The #5 is offered as a mid-size electric SUV and the Brabus #1 is only limited to 20 units in Malaysia. Now, let us see what these models have […]
The post Smart #5 Debuts In Malaysia Alongside Smart #1 Brabus Edition appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Keran</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Solana lacks ‘convincing signs’ of besting Ethereum: Sygnum]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/solana-no-convincing-signs-besting-ethereum-memecoin-bias</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/solana-no-convincing-signs-besting-ethereum-memecoin-bias?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-09T06:22:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Solana does not yet have “convincing signs” that it could overtake Ethereum as the blockchain of choice for institutions, as its revenue is seen as unstable due to its memecoin concentration, according to crypto bank group Sygnum.
In a May 8 blog post, Sygnum said that the current sentiment around Ethereum “remains poor,” with the market focused on Solana’s “transaction volumes and its recent dominance in fee generation.”
However, Sygnum said “the medium-term outlook will primarily be shaped by traditional financial institutions’ platform choices to bring their product offerings,” not by sentiment.
“We do not yet see convincing signs that Solana would be the preferred choice as Ethereum’s security, stability and longevity are highly prized,” it added.
Sygnum argued that institutions could …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Jesse Coghlan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[6502 Illegal Opcodes in the Siemens PC 100 Assembly Manual (1980)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.pagetable.com/?p=1798</id>
        <link href="https://www.pagetable.com/?p=1798"/>
        <updated>2025-05-09T06:19:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin accepted at fast food chain Steak ’n Shake from May 16]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/steak-n-sats-bitcoin-accepted-steak-n-shake-locations-may-16</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/steak-n-sats-bitcoin-accepted-steak-n-shake-locations-may-16?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-09T06:19:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[American fast food outlet Steak ‘n Shake has announced it will begin accepting Bitcoin as payment at all locations starting on May 16.
The firm said on X on May 9 that it was making the cryptocurrency available to more than 100 million customers, adding that “the movement is just beginning,” before signing off as “Steaktoshi.” 
The fast food chain initially hinted at accepting Bitcoin (BTC) in March when it posted “Should Steak ‘n Shake accept Bitcoin?” on social media. 
The tweet drew the attention of the crypto community and Bitcoin proponents such as Jack Dorsey, who rapidly replied with a “yes.” 
The firm has built momentum since then with Bitcoin-themed marketing, Tesla promotions, and visual hints on its social media feeds.
“The future is bright,” said the firm in April. Source: Stak…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Martin Young</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Metaplanet is raising another $21M through bonds to buy more Bitcoin]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/metaplanet-raising-another-21m-buy-more-bitcoin</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/metaplanet-raising-another-21m-buy-more-bitcoin?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-09T06:18:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fresh off its most recent Bitcoin purchase, Japanese investment firm Metaplanet is raising more funds through another bond issue to expand its growing crypto treasury.
Through a $21.25 million issue of “0% Ordinary Bonds,”  all the “funds raised will be allocated to the purchase of Bitcoin,” the firm said in a May 9 statement. 
Zero-coupon bonds don’t offer any interest to the holder. Most of the time, they are issued at a steep discount from their normal value, and when they mature, the holder receives the full value.
After its most recent May 9 board of directors meeting, the firm said it will issue a 14th Stock Acquisition Rights to EVO Fund, an investment management firm in the Cayman Islands, with a redemption date of Nov. 7.
Source: Metaplanet
At current prices, Metaplanet could buy …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Stephen Katte</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ether clocks ‘insane’ 20% candle post Pectra — a turning point?]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/ether-price-insane-candle-pectra-upgrade-turning-point-crypto-traders</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/ether-price-insane-candle-pectra-upgrade-turning-point-crypto-traders?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-09T06:01:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ether surged 20% in the past 24 hours following the launch of the Pectra upgrade, with some crypto traders suggesting the growing number of ETH long positions could mark a “turning point” for the asset that has faced uncertain sentiment throughout most of 2025.
At the time of publication, Ether (ETH) is trading at $2,230, up 19.6% over the past 24 hours, according to CoinMarketCap data. Pseudonymous crypto trader Daan Crypto Trades said it was a “pretty insane candle.” Over the same 24 hours, Ether Open Interest (OI) spiked 21%. 
Ether price pump caught traders offside
The surge followed the long-awaited Pectra Upgrade, which went live on May 7, introducing new wallet features, increased staking limits and scalability improvements to Ethereum. 
Popular crypto trader Alex Kruger said on May…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Ciaran Lyons</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pipe Leakages Can Be Reported Via Air Selangor 2.0 App]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=351195</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/351195/pipe-leakages-can-be-reported-via-air-selangor-2-0-app/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-09T05:57:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Pengurusan Air Selangor Sdn Bhd (Air Selangor) has launched its upgraded Air Selangor 2.0 app, which will enable users to report pipe leakages. This was announced by the company’s chief executive officer, Adam Saffian Ghazali, who states that the new app feature can be used by the 9.62 million water consumers across Selangor, Kuala Lumpur, […]
The post Pipe Leakages Can Be Reported Via Air Selangor 2.0 App appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Newsdesk</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AI decentralized apps are coming for the Web3 throne: DappRadar]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/ai-decentralized-appscoming-for-web3-throne-dappradar</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/ai-decentralized-appscoming-for-web3-throne-dappradar?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-09T05:27:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AI decentralized apps (DApps) have seen a spike in user activity and could soon challenge gaming and DeFi for the top spot in the DApp ecosystem, according to blockchain analytics platform DappRadar.
Gaming and DeFi are both sitting on 21% dominance in April, judged by percentage of unique active wallets, while AI has climbed to 16%, up from the 11% recorded in the February report, data in DappRadar’s April industry report shows.
“As user interest in artificial intelligence tools grows across industries, AI-powered DApps are steadily carving out their place in the decentralized ecosystem,” DappRadar analyst Sara Gherghelas said. 
“If this trend continues, AI could soon challenge the traditional dominance of DeFi and Gaming, signaling a new era in the DApp landscape.”
AI DApps have seen a j…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Stephen Katte</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Razer Launches Portable Joro Keyboard, Basilisk Mobile Mouse]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=351163</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/351163/razer-portable-joro-keyboard-basilisk-mobile-mouse/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-09T05:17:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Razer has announced new peripherals which it says will be “revolutionise mobile gaming”, but the things being launched are a keyboard and a mouse. Or more specifically, the Joro and the Basilisk Mobile respectively, so maybe the company meant portable rather than mobile. Starting with the new entry, the brand claims that the Razer Joro […]
The post Razer Launches Portable Joro Keyboard, Basilisk Mobile Mouse appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ian Chee</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Apple makes progress toward its first pair of smart glasses: Report]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/apple-makes-progress-first-smart-glasses-bloomberg</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/apple-makes-progress-first-smart-glasses-bloomberg?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-09T05:13:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Apple is reportedly working on its own microchips across multiple product categories, including smart glasses and artificial intelligence — a hint at what’s next for the massive Silicon Valley-based tech giant. 
A May 8 report from Bloomberg, citing people familiar with the matter, said the company is working on new processors to power its future devices, including its first smart glasses to rival Meta’s Ray-Bans, more powerful Macs, and artificial intelligence servers.
The smart glasses — a first for Apple — would rely on a specialized chip codenamed N401. The processor is based on Apple Watch chips but is further optimized for power efficiency and designed to control multiple cameras planned for the glasses, the sources said. 
Apple’s smart glasses will initially be non-augmented reality…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Martin Young</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Verification, the Key to AI (2001)]]></title>
        <id>http://incompleteideas.net/IncIdeas/KeytoAI.html</id>
        <link href="http://incompleteideas.net/IncIdeas/KeytoAI.html"/>
        <updated>2025-05-09T05:10:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Unifi TV x Max: Unlock the Full “The Last of Us” Season 2 Experience]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=351177</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/351177/unifi-tv-x-max-the-full-the-last-of-us/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-09T05:07:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Get ready, “The Last of Us” fans! Season 2 is finally here, and with it comes a whole new chapter of emotional storytelling, heart-stopping action, and the unforgettable world of Joel and Ellie. Whether you’ve been with them since the beginning or are just jumping into the story, now is the perfect time to immerse […]
The post Unifi TV x Max: Unlock the Full “The Last of Us” Season 2 Experience appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Newsdesk</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Zerebro dev is reportedly alive and at parents’ house: Report]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/zerebro-dev-jeffy-yu-reported-alive-after-being-spotted-parents-house</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/zerebro-dev-jeffy-yu-reported-alive-after-being-spotted-parents-house?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-09T04:56:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The 22-year-old developer of Zerebro, who apparently committed suicide during a livestream on May 4, is actually alive, according to a San Francisco news outlet that claims they spoke to Yu outside his family home. 
The San Francisco Standard reporter George Kelly claimed on May 8 that he briefly spoke with Yu outside of his family’s two-story home, where the crypto influencer refused to discuss the suicide allegations and whether he had financially benefited from it. 
Instead, Yu reportedly said: “You can see the PTSD in my eyes, right?” before asking the reporter to leave.
He was reportedly wearing a T-shirt, shorts, flip-flops and wire-rimmed glasses, possibly similar to the ones he had on while appearing to shoot himself to death during the livestream.
Jeffy Yu speaking about the futur…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Brayden Lindrea</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[LegoGPT: Generating Physically Stable and Buildable Lego]]></title>
        <id>https://avalovelace1.github.io/LegoGPT/</id>
        <link href="https://avalovelace1.github.io/LegoGPT/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-09T04:55:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Touch n Go Warns Of Scammers Impersonating Company Agents]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=351145</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/351145/touch-n-go-warns-of-scammers-impersonating-company-agents/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-09T04:53:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Touch n Go is reminding its customers to be wary of scammers pretending to be representatives of the company. In a recent notice issued via Touch n Go’s Facebook page, it stressed that no agent or individual has ever been appointed to collect personal information or identification documents from customers. Additionally, the company emphasised that […]
The post Touch n Go Warns Of Scammers Impersonating Company Agents appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nurul Kamil</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dieshot Of Nintendo Switch 2 T239 Chipset Appears; Based On NVIDIA Ampere Design]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=351152</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/351152/dieshot-of-nintendo-switch-2-t239-chipset-appears-based-on-nvidia-ampere-design/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-09T04:45:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When the Nintendo Switch 2 was announced, many of us knew that NVIDIA had a hand in its creation but the gaming brand was elusive about the specifics of the hardware running it. Now, thanks to a well-known chip analyst, they’ve posted a dieshot of the chipset in question, labelled as a T239. Now, the […]
The post Dieshot Of Nintendo Switch 2 T239 Chipset Appears; Based On NVIDIA Ampere Design appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John Law</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin's Price Surge to $104K Liquidates Nearly $400M in Bearish BTC Bets, Opening Doors to Further Gains]]></title>
        <id>91319329-e8ec-4f3d-a334-191b0a4a0737</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/09/bitcoin-s-price-surge-to-usd104k-liquidates-nearly-usd400m-in-bearish-btc-bets-opening-doors-to-further-gains"/>
        <updated>2025-05-09T04:03:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The rally followed a U.K. trade deal announcement and record ETF inflows exceeding $40 billion.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Omkar Godbole</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[eBPF Mystery: When is IPv4 not IPv4? When it's pretending to be IPv6]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.gripdev.xyz/2025/05/06/ebpf-mystery-when-is-ipv4-not-ipv4-when-its-ipv6/</id>
        <link href="https://blog.gripdev.xyz/2025/05/06/ebpf-mystery-when-is-ipv4-not-ipv4-when-its-ipv6/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-09T03:59:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[US man who sent crypto to ISIS could remain in prison until age 65]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/man-funded-isis-crypto-gets-over-30-years-prison</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/man-funded-isis-crypto-gets-over-30-years-prison?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-09T03:57:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A man from the US state of Virginia will spend over three decades behind bars after being convicted of sending crypto to the terrorist organization commonly known as the Islamic State of Iraq and Syria.
Federal Judge David Novak sentenced Mohammed Azharuddin Chhipa to 30 years and four months in prison on May 7 for sending over $185,000 to the Islamic State, the Department of Justice said on May 8.
Prosecutors said that from around October 2019 until October 2022, the 35-year-old Chhipa collected and sent money to female Islamic State members in Syria, which helped them escape prison camps and funded fighting.
The Justice Department said Chhipa raised funds for the United Nations-designated terror organization through social media, receiving money online or traveling hundreds of miles to a…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Jesse Coghlan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PlayStation Unveils Death Stranding 2 Limited Edition DualSense]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=351143</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/351143/playstation-unveils-death-stranding-2-limited-edition-dualsense/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-09T03:53:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Death Stranding 2: On the Beach got its release date announced, with the game coming on on 26 June. Being a PS5 exclusive, at least initially, PlayStation has taken the opportunity to announce a limited edition DualSense controller to go with it. Though the limited edition nature of it also means a higher than usual […]
The post PlayStation Unveils Death Stranding 2 Limited Edition DualSense appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ian Chee</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rumble CEO confirms Tether-collab crypto wallet to launch in Q3]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/rumble-launch-bitcoin-stablecoin-wallet-q3</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/rumble-launch-bitcoin-stablecoin-wallet-q3?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-09T03:49:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Rumble’s pro-crypto founder and CEO has confirmed that the firm will launch its Bitcoin and stablecoin wallet in the third quarter of this year, aimed at giving the Coinbase Wallet a run for its money. 
The Rumble Wallet will be launched in partnership with stablecoin issuer Tether and compete directly with Coinbase, Chris Pavlovski said in a May 9 X post.
“Our goal is to become the most prominent non-custodial Bitcoin and stablecoin wallet, powering the creator economy,” he added. 
He continued to state that the Rumble Wallet will be the “vehicle to help monetize creators better than most advertisers, especially in international markets,” though he did not provide further details other than it may support Tether Gold (XAUT) as well. 
Rumble Wallet. Source: Chris Pavlovski
The video stream…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Martin Young</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dead Reckoning]]></title>
        <id>https://www.damninteresting.com/dead-reckoning/</id>
        <link href="https://www.damninteresting.com/dead-reckoning/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-09T03:46:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin at $103K hurtles MARA stack toward $5B, holdings triple]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/mara-holdings-bitcoin-holdings-value-surge-price-btc-q1-results</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/mara-holdings-bitcoin-holdings-value-surge-price-btc-q1-results?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-09T03:46:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin mining firm MARA Holdings (MARA) nearly tripled its Bitcoin holdings over 12 months, according to its newly released Q1 results.
However, its Bitcoin production fell, and total earnings slightly missed Wall Street estimates in Q1.
MARA, formerly Marathon Digital, saw its Bitcoin (BTC) holdings increase to 47,531 BTC, up 175% from the 17,320 BTC the firm was holding at the end of Q1 2024.
MARA holdings inch closer to $5B after Bitcoin pump
MARA holds the second-largest amount of Bitcoin among all publicly traded companies, according to CoinGecko data. Strategy (MSTR) holds the number one spot with 555,450 Bitcoin.
The holdings represent a total value of approximately $4.9 billion, based on Bitcoin’s current price of $102,660 at the time of publication, according to CoinMarketCap dat…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Ciaran Lyons</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hill or High Water]]></title>
        <id>https://royalsociety.org/blog/2025/05/hill-or-high-water/</id>
        <link href="https://royalsociety.org/blog/2025/05/hill-or-high-water/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-09T03:41:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Explosive ETH, ADA, DOGE Moves Spur $800M in Short Liquidations, Highest Since 2023]]></title>
        <id>d394948b-2ef5-42b4-8378-4271a83b3bb0</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/09/explosive-eth-ada-doge-moves-spur-800m-in-short-liquidations-highest-since-2023"/>
        <updated>2025-05-09T03:32:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bears are nursing their highest losses over two years as majors surged as much as 20%.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shaurya Malwa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[For better or for worse, the overload (2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://consteval.ca/2024/07/25/overload/</id>
        <link href="https://consteval.ca/2024/07/25/overload/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-09T03:27:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Usenix ATC Announcement]]></title>
        <id>https://www.usenix.org/blog/usenix-atc-announcement</id>
        <link href="https://www.usenix.org/blog/usenix-atc-announcement"/>
        <updated>2025-05-09T03:18:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Starlink User Terminal Teardown]]></title>
        <id>https://www.darknavy.org/blog/a_first_glimpse_of_the_starlink_user_ternimal/</id>
        <link href="https://www.darknavy.org/blog/a_first_glimpse_of_the_starlink_user_ternimal/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-09T03:03:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Formal Analysis of Apple's iMessage PQ3 Protocol [pdf]]]></title>
        <id>https://www.usenix.org/system/files/conference/usenixsecurity25/sec25cycle1-prepub-595-linker.pdf</id>
        <link href="https://www.usenix.org/system/files/conference/usenixsecurity25/sec25cycle1-prepub-595-linker.pdf"/>
        <updated>2025-05-09T02:54:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Audiobookshelf: Self-hosted audiobook and podcast server]]></title>
        <id>https://www.audiobookshelf.org/</id>
        <link href="https://www.audiobookshelf.org/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-09T02:17:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ETH Surges 20%, Biggest Gain Since 2021 as Pectra Upgrade Helps Restore 'Confidence']]></title>
        <id>cea68a93-be89-4882-b355-6a0820a26fb0</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/08/eth-surges-20-biggest-gain-since-2021-as-pectra-upgrade-helps-restore-confidence"/>
        <updated>2025-05-09T01:51:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ETH outperforms CoinDesk 20 Index, as bulls comes back while BTC surges above $100k.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sam Reynolds</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OpenAI, Microsoft tell Senate ‘no one country can win AI’]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3007056</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/openai-microsoft-tell-senate-no-one-country-can-win-ai/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-09T01:02:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Executives like OpenAI's Sam Altman said US support for infrastructure would make it easier for AI companies to meet demand.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Emilia David</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SEC’s Crenshaw slams Ripple settlement, warns of ‘regulatory vacuum’]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/sec-commissioner-slams-proposed-settlement-ripple</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/sec-commissioner-slams-proposed-settlement-ripple?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-09T00:44:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A crypto-skeptical commissioner at the US Securities and Exchange Commission has blasted her agency over its settlement letter that could finally end the Ripple legal saga. 
The SEC and Ripple filed a joint settlement letter in a New York court asking for the August 2024 injunction against Ripple to be dissolved and $75 million of the $125 million in civil penalties held in escrow to be returned to the crypto firm, according to a May 8 statement from the SEC.
SEC Commissioner Caroline Crenshaw blasted the pending deal in a May 8 statement, saying it would damage the regulators’ ability to keep crypto firms in line and undermine the court’s ruling.
Source: James Filan
“This settlement, alongside the programmatic disassembly of the SEC’s crypto enforcement program, does a tremendous disservi…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Stephen Katte</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase revenue falls 10% in Q1, missing industry estimates]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/coinbase-revenue-falls-double-digits-q1-earnings-miss</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/coinbase-revenue-falls-double-digits-q1-earnings-miss?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-09T00:19:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto exchange Coinbase’s total revenue fell 10% quarter-over-quarter to $2 billion in Q1, missing industry estimates by 4.1% as trading activity slowed across the market.
Coinbase’s net income was sliced by 95% from a near-company record $1.29 billion in Q4 to $66 million, in a large part due to Coinbase marking a $596 million paper loss on its crypto holdings. 
The firm’s earnings per share of $1.94, however, managed to beat the Zacks Consensus Estimate of $1.85 for the quarter.
Coinbase’s May 8 results also showed that transaction revenue fell 18.9% quarter-on-quarter to $1.26 billion, as did trading volumes, which dipped 10.5% to $393 billion as crypto market cap dropped by double digits over the quarter, partly attributed to the Trump administration’s tariffs. 
In contrast, US Presid…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Brayden Lindrea</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[You can now fine-tune your enterprise’s own version of OpenAI’s o4-mini reasoning model with reinforcement learning]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3007091</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/you-can-now-fine-tune-your-enterprises-own-version-of-openais-o4-mini-reasoning-model-with-reinforcement-learning/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-09T00:07:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For organizations with clearly defined problems and verifiable answers, RFT offers a compelling way to align models.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carl Franzen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How The Ottawa Hospital uses AI ambient voice capture to reduce physician burnout by 70%, achieve 97% patient satisfaction]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3007069</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/how-the-ottawa-hospital-uses-ai-ambient-voice-capture-to-reduce-physician-burnout-by-70-achieve-97-patient-satisfaction/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-08T23:57:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[TOH is using Microsoft’s DAX Copilot to capture physician-patient conversations and generate draft clinical notes in real time.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Taryn Plumb</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[5 strategies that separate AI leaders from the 92% still stuck in pilot mode]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3007013</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/5-strategies-that-separate-ai-leaders-from-the-92-still-stuck-in-pilot-mode/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-08T23:09:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Accenture's new research reveals the critical strategies that separate the companies successfully scaling AI from the 92% stuck in perpetual pilot mode, providing enterprise leaders with actionable insights to accelerate their AI transformation journey.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sean Michael Kerner</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Podfox: First Container-Aware Browser]]></title>
        <id>https://val.packett.cool/blog/podfox/</id>
        <link href="https://val.packett.cool/blog/podfox/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-08T22:19:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fui: C library for interacting with the framebuffer in a TTY context]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/martinfama/fui</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/martinfama/fui"/>
        <updated>2025-05-08T22:05:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meta exploring stablecoin integration for payouts: Report]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/meta-exploring-stablecoin-integration-payouts</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/meta-exploring-stablecoin-integration-payouts?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-08T21:59:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tech company Meta is reportedly exploring integrating stablecoin payments into its platforms after a three-year hiatus from cryptocurrencies, Fortune reported, citing sources familiar with the matter.
The Facebook parent held talks with several crypto infrastructure firms in consultation but has not chosen a decisive course of action, according to the report.
One source said the company may take a multi-token approach and integrate support for popular stablecoins such as Tether's USDt (USDT), Circle's USD Coin (USDC) and others.
Meta is the latest tech firm to integrate or explore the use of stablecoins for payments, as they increasingly attract institutional interest and investment, causing the stablecoin market capitalization to soar past $230 billion.
An overview of the stablecoin marke…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Vince Quill</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Here’s what happened in crypto today]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/what-happened-in-crypto-today</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/what-happened-in-crypto-today?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-08T21:53:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today in crypto, SEC Commissioner Caroline Crenshaw blasted a settlement agreement between the SEC and Ripple, which she says could erode SEC lawyers’ credibility in the court. Democrats in the United States block the GENIUS stablecoin bill from advancing and Coinbase has agreed to acquire crypto options trading platform Deribit in a deal worth $2.9 billion.
SEC’s Crenshaw slams Ripple settlement, warns of “regulatory vacuum”
A crypto-skeptical commissioner at the US Securities and Exchange Commission has blasted her agency over its settlement letter that could finally end the Ripple legal saga.
The SEC and Ripple filed a joint settlement letter in a New York court asking for the August 2024 injunction against Ripple to be dissolved and $75 million of the $125 million in civil penalties he…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Cointelegraph</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Prepare your apps for Google Play's 16 KB page size compatibility requirement]]></title>
        <id>https://android-developers.googleblog.com/2025/05/prepare-play-apps-for-devices-with-16kb-page-size.html</id>
        <link href="https://android-developers.googleblog.com/2025/05/prepare-play-apps-for-devices-with-16kb-page-size.html"/>
        <updated>2025-05-08T21:46:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SEC, Ripple Ink $50M Settlement Agreement, Ask NY Judge for Green Light]]></title>
        <id>98a8d705-82b6-4ec1-8a93-9aa501a370d9</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2025/05/08/sec-ripple-ink-usd50m-settlement-agreement-ask-ny-judge-for-green-light"/>
        <updated>2025-05-08T21:26:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[District Judge Analisa Torres ordered Ripple to pay the SEC a $125 million fine last year. Under the new settlement agreement, Ripple will get the majority of that money back.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cheyenne Ligon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Wellgistics Health to integrate XRP into payment infrastructure]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/wellgistics-health-integrate-xrp-payment-infrastructure</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/wellgistics-health-integrate-xrp-payment-infrastructure?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-08T21:18:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Wellgistics Health, a healthcare infrastructure company, will integrate XRP (XRP) and related technologies into its payment network to streamline transactions between pharmacies, medical suppliers and prescription medication manufacturers, the company said in an announcement on May 8. 
Wellgistics cited the finality time of XRP transactions and reduced transaction costs, which are fractions of a penny, compared to legacy financial architecture like automated clearinghouse (ACH) payments or wire transfers, as reasons for using XRP. Brian Norton, CEO of Wellgistics Health, said in the announcement:
"I believe that the future winners in healthcare will not be the companies with the biggest buildings, they will be those with the fastest rails, cleanest data, and most efficient platforms. We ar…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Vince Quill</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Anna Kazlauskas: Data Ownership in the Age of AI]]></title>
        <id>a8d0abb4-9e20-4df5-9d90-2097344dbc7d</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/consensus-toronto-2025-coverage/2025/05/08/anna-kazlauskas-data-ownership-in-the-age-of-ai"/>
        <updated>2025-05-08T21:13:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The co-founder of Vana is building data DAOs and decentralized marketplaces to create an ecosystem of user-owned data. She will give the keynote at the AI Summit at Consensus May 16.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeff Wilser</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A flat pricing subscription for Claude Code]]></title>
        <id>https://support.anthropic.com/en/articles/11145838-using-claude-code-with-your-max-plan</id>
        <link href="https://support.anthropic.com/en/articles/11145838-using-claude-code-with-your-max-plan"/>
        <updated>2025-05-08T21:12:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Prepare for your iOS interview]]></title>
        <id>681d1bbfb1018a470d0d8a02</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/prepare-for-your-ios-interview/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-08T21:01:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Preparing for an iOS developer interview can be a daunting task, especially when you're trying to master both conceptual questions and practical coding challenges. Whether you're just starting your iOS development journey or gearing up for your next ...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase’s Deribit buy shows growing derivatives market]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/coinbase-s-deribit-buy-shows-growing-importance-of-crypto-derivatives</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/coinbase-s-deribit-buy-shows-growing-importance-of-crypto-derivatives?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-08T20:50:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase’s agreement to buy Deribit highlights the increasing importance of financial derivatives for cryptocurrency exchanges, according to industry executives. 
On May 8, Coinbase, the US’s largest crypto exchange by trading volume, agreed to acquire crypto derivatives platform Deribit for $2.9 billion in the crypto industry’s largest corporate acquisition to date.  
The deal reflects increasing competition among digital asset exchanges and brokerages — including Coinbase, Kraken and Robinhood — to dominate the burgeoning crypto derivatives market. 
"Global derivatives trading is a key driver of growth for Coinbase,” Spencer Yang, co-founder of Fractal Bitcoin, a Bitcoin scaling solution, told Cointelegraph.
Coinbase agreed to buy Deribit on May 8. Source: Coinbase
The merger established…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Alex O’Donnell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The walled garden cracks: Nadella bets Microsoft’s Copilots—and Azure’s next act—on A2A/MCP interoperability]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3006872</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/the-walled-garden-cracks-nadella-bets-microsofts-copilots-and-azures-next-act-on-a2a-mcp-interoperability/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-08T20:47:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft CEO Satya Nadella’s endorsement of Google DeepMind‘s A2A open protocol and Anthropic's MCP is huge sign the industry is moving to an open garden.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Louis Columbus</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin options could pave the path for new BTC price highs — Here is how]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-options-could-pave-the-path-for-new-btc-price-highs-here-is-how</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-options-could-pave-the-path-for-new-btc-price-highs-here-is-how?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-08T20:38:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Key takeaways:

97% of the $8.3 billion in Bitcoin put options expire worthless at a $102,000 BTC price.

Short covering above $105,000 could trigger a Bitcoin price rally to new highs.

Bitcoin (BTC) soared above $101,000 on May 8, reaching its highest level in over three months. The 4.6% daily BTC price gain triggered $205 million in liquidations of bearish futures positions and eroded the value of nearly every put (sell) option. Traders now question whether Bitcoin is poised to break its $109,354 all-time high in the near term.
Bitcoin put (sell) options open interest for May-June-July, USD notional. Source: Laevitas.ch
The aggregate Bitcoin put (sell) option open interest for the next three months stands at $8.3 billion, but 97% of those have been placed below $101,000 and will likely …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Marcel Pechman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase Stock Falls After Earnings Disappoints Wall Street on Market Volatility]]></title>
        <id>cd4cf5e1-f454-429f-9b58-53f2635f5b47</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/08/coinbase-earnings-sales-disappoints-wall-street-as-trading-volume-drops-10-amid-market-turmoil"/>
        <updated>2025-05-08T20:27:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The crypto exchange cited a drop in crypto prices as a result of U.S. President Donald Trump’s tariff policy and macroeconomic uncertainty as the reason behind the weak quarter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Helene Braun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Former FTX exec&#039;s wife says gov&#039;t ‘induced a guilty plea’]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/michelle-bond-ftx-exec-dismissal-guilty-plea</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/michelle-bond-ftx-exec-dismissal-guilty-plea?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-08T20:26:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Michelle Bond, the wife of former FTX Digital Markets co-CEO Ryan Salame, who faces federal campaign finance charges, is pushing for dismissal on the grounds that US prosecutors deceived her husband in a plea deal.
In a May 7 filing in the US District Court for the Southern District of New York, Bond’s lawyers reiterated some of the claims Salame made in opposing his plea deal with the government, which ultimately still led to him serving time in prison. She claimed that prosecutors obtained a deal with Salame through “stealth and deception” by allegedly agreeing they would not file charges against Bond. 
“Mr. Salame and Ms. Bond’s attorneys were advised that the agreement to cease investigating Ms. Bond could not be placed within the four corners of the Salame plea or other written agreem…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Turner Wright</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase's $2.9B Deribit Deal a 'Legitimate Threat' for Peers, Wall Street Analysts Say]]></title>
        <id>6137f109-2311-41c0-81cb-93091f32f4a0</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/08/coinbase-buying-deribit-for-usd2-9b-a-legitimate-threat-for-peers-wall-street-analysts-say"/>
        <updated>2025-05-08T20:13:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The acquisition makes Coinbase the largest crypto derivatives platform and a credible rival to Binance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Helene Braun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meta Is Looking to Enter Red-Hot Stablecoin Market: Fortune]]></title>
        <id>32425793-fd6d-47b5-9dad-189ef40688aa</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2025/05/08/meta-is-looking-to-deploy-stablecoin-to-manage-payouts-fortune"/>
        <updated>2025-05-08T19:58:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The tech giant reportedly also hired a vice president of product with crypto experience to help with the stablecoin efforts.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Aoyon Ashraf</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Stability by Design]]></title>
        <id>https://potetm.com/devtalk/stability-by-design.html</id>
        <link href="https://potetm.com/devtalk/stability-by-design.html"/>
        <updated>2025-05-08T19:51:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celsius Founder Alex Mashinsky Sentenced to 12 Years in Prison for Fraud]]></title>
        <id>f0c99361-53ad-4428-b976-1843ee03127e</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2025/05/08/celsius-founder-alex-mashinsky-sentenced-to-12-years-in-prison-for-fraud"/>
        <updated>2025-05-08T19:42:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mashinsky pled guilty to securities and commodities fraud charges last December.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cheyenne Ligon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mashinsky’s 12-year sentence sets tone of enforcement in Trump era]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/mashinksy-enforcement-sentence-court</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/mashinksy-enforcement-sentence-court?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-08T19:35:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The US federal court for the Southern District of New York has sentenced former Celsius CEO Alex Mashinsky to 12 years in prison for fraud. 
Mashinsky’s legal team sought a light sentence. They highlighted his spotless record before the Celsius incident, along with his military service and willingness to plead guilty. But US prosecutors were less inclined to leniency, suggesting on April 28 that the judge deliver a 20-year sentence for his actions.
Betting markets predicted a light sentence ahead of the May 8 hearing. Polymarket showed only 11% odds for a 20-year sentence or higher.
Source: Polymarket
President Donald Trump began his second term with high-profile pardons of crypto executives, signalling that his administration may bring leniency to crypto fraudsters like Mashinsky. His sen…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Aaron Wood</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to start a school with your friends]]></title>
        <id>https://prigoose.substack.com/p/how-to-start-a-university</id>
        <link href="https://prigoose.substack.com/p/how-to-start-a-university"/>
        <updated>2025-05-08T19:34:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin hits $101.7K as US strategic reserve bills become law and BTC mass adoption accelerates]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-hits-101-7-k-as-us-strategic-reserve-bills-become-law-and-btc-mass-adoption-accelerates</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-hits-101-7-k-as-us-strategic-reserve-bills-become-law-and-btc-mass-adoption-accelerates?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-08T19:15:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Key takeaways: 

Bitcoin rallies to $101,707 against a backdrop of strong fundamentals in the regulatory and traditional finance space.

Traders are confident that $100,000 will hold as support.

Bitcoin (BTC) price rallied above $100,000 on the heels of US President Donald Trump’s announcement of a “trade deal” with the UK, which could possibly include the removal of the blanket 10% tariff on all imports. 
Frequent social posts from Trump and public comments from White House cabinet members have hinted at a handful of trade deals in negotiation with various countries, and markets have responded positively to the messaging. In addition to the UK trade deal, the US is set to meet with Chinese officials in Switzerland on May 10.
The Dow gained 500 points following the White House announcemen…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Big Smokey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Alibaba’s ‘ZeroSearch’ lets AI learn to google itself — slashing training costs by 88 percent]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3007024</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/alibabas-zerosearch-lets-ai-learn-to-google-itself-slashing-training-costs-by-88-percent/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-08T19:15:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Alibaba’s ZeroSearch trains large language models to beat Google Search and slash API costs by 88%, redefining how AI learns to retrieve information.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Nuñez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why is XRP price up today?]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/why-is-xrp-price-up-today</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/why-is-xrp-price-up-today?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-08T19:15:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Key takeaways:

XRP surged on May 8, boosted by risk-on sentiment following US President Donald Trump’s teased trade deal with the UK.

Whale accumulation continues, with the number of addresses holding 10,000+ XRP rising steadily on price dips.

XRP broke above a key falling wedge resistance, increasing the chances of a rally toward $2.80–$3.66.

XRP’s (XRP) price gained 7.50% on May 8 to reach an intraday high of $2.27, mirroring similar upside moves elsewhere in the cryptocurrency market.
Traders pushed the price higher amid Trump’s tariff threats, increased whale accumulation, and favorable chart technicals.
XRP/USD daily price chart. Source: TradingView
Trump’s tariff tease boosts risk appetite, helping XRP
Trump announced a “major trade deal” in a social media post, announcing an Ova…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Yashu Gola</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mem0’s scalable memory promises more reliable AI agents that remembers context across lengthy conversations]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3006826</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/mem0s-scalable-memory-promises-more-reliable-ai-agents-that-remembers-context-across-lengthy-conversations/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-08T19:13:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mem0's architecture is designed to LLM memory and enhance consistency for more reliable agent performance in long conversations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ben Dickson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[US Stablecoin bill blocked as Democrats withdraw support]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/us-genius-stablecoin-act-fails-to-pass-cloture-by-to-vote</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/us-genius-stablecoin-act-fails-to-pass-cloture-by-to-vote?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-08T18:59:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Guiding and Establishing National Innovation for US Stablecoins of 2025 Act, known as the GENIUS Act, failed to pass cloture in the United States Senate on May 8, dealing a blow to cryptocurrency regulation in the country.
The bill, sponsored by Senator Bill Hagerty and co-sponsored by Senators Tim Scott, Kirsten Gillibrand, Cynthia Lummis and Angela Alsobrooks, received last-minute pushback from Democrats, who took aim at the bill and raised concerns about US President Donald Trump’s cryptocurrency ventures.
To address the concerns of Senate Democrats, the bill had already been amended to include stricter requirements for stablecoin issuers for further provisions for Anti-Money Laundering.
The GENIUS Act was seen as a bipartisan effort to increase regulatory clarity for digital assets…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Christopher Tepedino</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[From: Steve Jobs. "Great idea, thank you."]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.hayman.net/2025/05/06/from-steve-jobs-great-idea.html</id>
        <link href="https://blog.hayman.net/2025/05/06/from-steve-jobs-great-idea.html"/>
        <updated>2025-05-08T18:40:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use Arrow Functions in PHP 7.4+]]></title>
        <id>681cf9062cbe43bee0f4138f</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-arrow-functions-in-php/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-08T18:33:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Arrow functions were introduced in PHP 7.4 to allow devs to write short, anonymous functions. They offer a compact alternative to traditional closures, especially when the function body is small and focused. In this article, you will learn how to use...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Montasser Mossallem</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Senate Votes Against Advancing Stablecoin Bill, Delaying Process as Trump Concerns Fester]]></title>
        <id>39e96b89-58d1-4a04-b735-c7a815099697</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2025/05/08/senate-votes-against-advancing-stablecoin-bill-delaying-process-as-trump-concerns-fester"/>
        <updated>2025-05-08T18:33:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Last-minute Democrat objections led to a failed vote to move into debate on a top crypto industry legislative priority to regulate dollar-based tokens.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jesse Hamilton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trump tricked into pushing XRP for crypto reserve: Report]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/donald-trump-xrp-crypto-reserve-trick</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/donald-trump-xrp-crypto-reserve-trick?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-08T18:32:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[US President Donald Trump was reportedly manipulated by a lobbyist tied to Ripple Labs into announcing the XRP (XRP) token would be part of his plans for a national cryptocurrency reserve.
According to a May 8 Politico report, an employee of pro-Trump lobbyist Brian Ballard gave the president the text to a social media post she recommended he write announcing a US strategic crypto reserve that would include XRP, Solana (SOL), and Cardano (ADA). 
After he posted the message to his social media platform on March 2, Trump learned Ripple was one of Ballard’s clients, infuriating the president, who felt like he’d been used, Politico reported, citing two people familiar with the incident.
“He is not welcome in anything anymore,” said Trump, referencing Ballard, according to the report.
March 2 T…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Turner Wright</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SEC considers new rules easing security token issuance]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/sec-mulls-easing-security-token-issuance</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/sec-mulls-easing-security-token-issuance?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-08T17:59:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Updated to correct that the SEC sent a Wells notice to Uniswap but did not bring charges.
The US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) is considering rule changes to let companies more freely issue tokenized securities, SEC Commissioner Hester Peirce said in a speech published on May 8.
The regulator is “considering a potential exemptive order” for firms using blockchain technology to “issue, trade, and settle securities” that would release them from certain registration requirements, Peirce said in the speech.
For example, decentralized exchanges (DEXs) may no longer need to register “as a broker-dealer, clearing agency, or an exchange,” Peirce said. The SEC has previously sent numerous Wells notices to DEXs such as Uniswap for allegedly failing to register as securities exchanges. 
Fi…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Alex O’Donnell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Reservoir Sampling]]></title>
        <id>https://samwho.dev/reservoir-sampling/</id>
        <link href="https://samwho.dev/reservoir-sampling/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-08T17:02:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Are layer 2s good for Ethereum, or are they ‘extractive?’]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/layer-2s-good-for-ethereum-or-extractive</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/layer-2s-good-for-ethereum-or-extractive?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-08T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Layer 2s have been a great blockchain success story. They’ve reduced congestion on the Ethereum mainnet, driving down gas fees while preserving security.
But maybe they’ve become too successful, drawing chain activity and fee income from the parent that spawned them? At least that’s what some are suggesting lately, most recently at Cornell Tech’s blockchain conference in late April.
Indeed, some think Ethereum should be a little greedier, or at least fight harder for a bigger part of the revenue pie, particularly sequencing fees. 
“People in the Ethereum Foundation [the nonprofit that supports the Ethereum ecosystem] will tell you that, ‘Yes, we effed up by being too ivory tower.’ I have heard that multiple times,” said David Hoffman, an owner at Bankless, during a panel discussion at the …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Andrew Singer</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Missouri bill ending capital gains tax heads to governor for signature]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/missouri-could-become-first-state-eliminate-capital-gains</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/missouri-could-become-first-state-eliminate-capital-gains?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-08T16:55:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Missouri House Bill 594, a bill that would eliminate capital gains tax in the US state, has passed a vote in the state House of Representatives and now heads to Missouri Governor Mike Kehoe's desk for signature.
According to attorney Aaron Brogan, the bill stipulates a 100% income tax deduction for any capital gains income because the Missouri tax code does not explicitly distinguish between capital gains and income tax.
Missouri House Bill 594 proposes exempting capital gains from income taxes. Source: Missouri House of Representatives
Brogan told Cointelegraph that the specific mechanism to exempt capital gains taxes outlined in HB 594 is unique and compared it to a similar income tax deduction in the federal tax code. The attorney explained:
"The most natural comparison is the state and…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Vince Quill</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Void: Open-source Cursor alternative]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/voideditor/void</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/voideditor/void"/>
        <updated>2025-05-08T16:35:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[First American pope elected and will be known as Pope Leo XIV]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cnn.com/world/live-news/new-pope-conclave-day-two-05-08-25</id>
        <link href="https://www.cnn.com/world/live-news/new-pope-conclave-day-two-05-08-25"/>
        <updated>2025-05-08T16:30:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin $120K Target for 2Q May Be Too Conservative: Standard Chartered]]></title>
        <id>e94afa61-4a92-4d90-80c3-4bd2fd25c9a4</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/08/bitcoin-120k-target-for-2q-may-be-too-conservative-standard-chartered"/>
        <updated>2025-05-08T16:14:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Spot bitcoin ETF net inflows totaled over $4 billion in the last three weeks, when adjusted for hedge fund basis trades, the bank said.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Will Canny</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Free GenAI 65-Hour Bootcamp]]></title>
        <id>681cd4ea505e2f4aa02206d5</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/free-genai-65-hour-bootcamp/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-08T15:59:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Generative AI is revolutionizing how we create, learn, and interact with digital content. From intelligent chatbots and personalized language tutors to realistic image generation and interactive story engines, the applications are endless. We just pu...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Progress toward fusion energy gain as measured against the Lawson criteria]]></title>
        <id>https://www.fusionenergybase.com/articles/continuing-progress-toward-fusion-energy-breakeven-and-gain-as-measured-against-the-lawson-criteria</id>
        <link href="https://www.fusionenergybase.com/articles/continuing-progress-toward-fusion-energy-breakeven-and-gain-as-measured-against-the-lawson-criteria"/>
        <updated>2025-05-08T15:49:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Tops $100K for First Time in 3 Months; Are Upside Targets Too Low?]]></title>
        <id>3caf7639-a5b3-40db-87a5-ecfb096e2838</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/02/bitcoin-tops-usd100k-for-first-time-in-3-months-are-upside-targets-too-low"/>
        <updated>2025-05-08T15:38:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The price has jumped 33% in a few weeks after plunging to $75,000 in the days following President Trump's early April Liberation Day tariff announcement.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephen Alpher</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Brief Introduction to Web Components]]></title>
        <id>681cce7f505e2f4aa022069b</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/a-brief-introduction-to-web-components/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-08T15:32:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a previous article, I gave a brief introduction to React. This tutorial introduces an alternative approach to building a component-based frontend. It covers the fundamentals of Web Components to build modular, reusable elements for your web applic...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mark Mahoney</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OpenAI names Instacart leader Fidji Simo as new CEO of Applications]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3006978</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/openai-names-instacart-leader-fidji-simo-as-new-ceo-of-applications/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-08T15:25:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Simo’s appointment may also hint at a broader productization push within OpenAI. Her background at Facebook and Instacart underscores...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carl Franzen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin price reclaims $100K for first time since January]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-hits-100k-first-time-since-january</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-hits-100k-first-time-since-january?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-08T15:22:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin has reclaimed the $100,000 price level for the first time since January, reflecting renewed bullish sentiment among investors.
Bitcoin (BTC) reclaimed the $100,000 mark on May 8 at 3:22 pm UTC, surging 4.2% from the intraday low of $95,967, according to data from CoinGecko.
It marked the third time that BTC has broken through the six-figure level since first achieving it on Dec. 5, 2024. A second all-time high followed on Jan. 20 ahead of US President Donald Trump’s inauguration.
Bitcoin price chart in the past year. Source: CoinGecko
Unlike the previous $100,000 hits, the new price spike came as Bitcoin market dominance surged above 60%, reflecting potential bearish sentiment for altcoins.
Bitcoin dominance below 60% in past $100,000 breakthroughs
Bitcoin dominance — the asset’s s…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Helen Partz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ex-Celsius CEO asks to travel for a wedding after sentencing]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/alex-mashinsky-celsius-sentencing-wedding-travel</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/alex-mashinsky-celsius-sentencing-wedding-travel?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-08T15:17:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Former Celsius CEO Alex Mashinsky will probably be allowed to travel for his daughter’s wedding regardless of the outcome of his May 8 sentencing hearing.
In a May 8 filing in the US District Court for the Southern District of New York, Judge John Koeltl approved an application for Mashinsky to travel from New York to Memphis, Tennessee, between May 26 and May 29 for his daughter’s wedding. The approval was available on the public docket as of May 8, but appeared to have been removed at the time of publication.
Alex Mashinsky’s request to travel for his daughter’s wedding. Source: PACER
Judge Koeltl will determine in a May 8 hearing whether Mashinsky serves prison time following a plea deal with prosecutors.
The former Celsius CEO appeared ready to go to trial in 2024 until his lawyers los…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Turner Wright</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Senate Republicans Making Plea to Get on With Stablecoin Debate]]></title>
        <id>f0785da5-57a1-4ecf-99a9-1f64bb84ac8f</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2025/05/08/senate-republicans-making-plea-to-get-on-with-stablecoin-debate"/>
        <updated>2025-05-08T15:08:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Once-allied Democrats continue to drag their heels on the first big crypto bill, leaving a key vote in doubt as GOP Majority Leader Thune calls for action.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jesse Hamilton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto for Advisors: Trends in Tokenizing Real-World Assets]]></title>
        <id>b842342d-8b85-40e5-a277-0d942aa00390</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/coindesk-indices/2025/05/07/crypto-for-advisors-trends-in-tokenizing-real-world-assets"/>
        <updated>2025-05-08T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tokenization turns real-world assets into blockchain tokens, boosting efficiency, liquidity and accessibility. Learn about why Ethereum is the current leader in this space.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tedd Strazimiri</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[User experience could be crypto’s superpower — or its kryptonite]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/user-experience-crypto-s-superpower</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/user-experience-crypto-s-superpower?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-08T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Opinion by Jonathan Farnell, CEO of Freedx
It’s 2025, and over 560 million people worldwide are already using cryptocurrency — roughly 17 times the population of Tokyo. That’s a vibrant community, yet for every user who’s embraced it, billions more stand on the sidelines, put off by the complicated interactions and clunky interfaces of protocols, platforms, decentralized apps (DApps), and mobile applications. Why? Blockchain technology offers game-changing potential — decentralized ownership, secure trades — but let’s face it: Most people still find it intimidating, risky, and confusing. User experience (UX) might just be the deciding factor in whether cryptocurrency achieves mass adoption or remains a niche segment.
Take complexity. A 2024 Chainalysis report pointed out that 43% of would-…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Jonathan Farnell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Breakout Alert: Ether, Bitcoin Cash-Bitcoin Ratio Break Downtrends as DOGE, SHIB Bottom Out]]></title>
        <id>47d52b24-b2a0-49d4-97e9-7912e7196447</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/08/breakout-alert-ether-bitcoin-cash-bitcoin-ratio-break-downtrends-doge-shib-bottom-out"/>
        <updated>2025-05-08T14:42:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ETH, BCH and top memecoins are flashing bullish chart patterns.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Omkar Godbole</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GSR’s Josh Riezman on Regulation, Risk, and Readying Crypto for the Next Phase]]></title>
        <id>07207794-a009-461a-839b-c1e82dc89e52</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/consensus-toronto-2025-coverage/2025/05/08/gsrs-josh-riezman-on-regulation-risk-and-readying-crypto-for-the-next-phase"/>
        <updated>2025-05-08T14:11:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The market-maker, investor and asset manager aims to be a “one-stop shop for market participants,” says its Chief Strategy Officer. Riezman is a speaker at Consensus 2025 May 14-16.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Francisco Rodrigues</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Superstate Expands Into Tokenized Equities; SOL Strategies to Be First Listing]]></title>
        <id>6b1ea7b7-1c49-4659-84bd-828e67ef0d0f</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2025/05/08/superstate-expands-into-tokenized-equities-sol-strategies-to-be-first-listing"/>
        <updated>2025-05-08T14:00:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The company's "Opening Bell" platform lets SEC-registered shares trade on-chain, bridging crypto and public equity markets.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Krisztian Sandor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How the Democrats’ Path to 2026 Victory Goes Through Decentralized Crypto]]></title>
        <id>d5c765d2-6ca8-4def-bfa3-90b824eacb57</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/opinion/2025/05/08/how-the-democrats-path-to-2026-victory-goes-through-decentralized-crypto"/>
        <updated>2025-05-08T13:41:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The current draft of the GENIUS Act elevates centralized entities in overseeing stablecoins. Democrats should take the right stand against it, says Hermine Wong.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hermine Wong</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[In $2.9B Deal, Coinbase Agrees to Buy Deribit to Expand in U.S. Crypto Options Market]]></title>
        <id>ffc60f4b-07d3-4d1b-9f08-d1a7f0756444</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2025/05/08/coinbase-buys-deribit-for-usd2-9b"/>
        <updated>2025-05-08T13:28:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The deal includes $700 million in cash and 11 million shares of Coinbase Class A common stock.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Helene Braun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Much-Awaited Fed Rate Cut May Not Come Before Q4, ING Says]]></title>
        <id>ac1a01b7-2e50-4379-8bfc-99f09b2c5134</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/08/much-awaited-fed-rate-cut-may-not-come-before-q4-ing-says"/>
        <updated>2025-05-08T13:19:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Delayed rate cuts could be more aggressive when they happen, the investment bank said.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Omkar Godbole</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Stripe Unveils Payments Products Powered by 'Gale-Force Tailwind' Stablecoins]]></title>
        <id>9923b217-87db-4304-b19a-16c50bdbe5c2</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2025/05/08/stripe-unveils-payments-products-powered-by-gale-force-tailwind-stablecoins"/>
        <updated>2025-05-08T13:17:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Stripe has launched a new money management service powered by stablecoins]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Crawley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CoinDesk 20 Performance Update: Index Surges 6.2% as All Assets Trade Higher]]></title>
        <id>a9b0fc2d-06ea-4e1d-a957-2971d71b5c2a</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/coindesk-indices/2025/05/08/coindesk-20-performance-update-index-surges-6-2-as-all-assets-trade-higher"/>
        <updated>2025-05-08T13:13:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sui (SUI) jumped 16.4% and Bitcoin Cash (BCH) gained 15.6%, leading the index higher.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CoinDesk Indices</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[98% of Tokens on Pump.Fun Have Been Rug Pulls or an Act of Fraud, New Report Says]]></title>
        <id>c35992fb-4d61-468c-910b-25590be1b9e5</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2025/05/07/98-of-tokens-on-pump-fun-have-been-rug-pulls-or-an-act-of-fraud-new-report-says"/>
        <updated>2025-05-08T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Seven millions tokens have been launched in pump.fun since its inception in 2024.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Oliver Knight</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ether-Bitcoin Ratio Signals ETH Is 'Extremely Undervalued,' but Headwinds Remain: CryptoQuant]]></title>
        <id>d159c2bf-79a9-41ee-821a-8a7c1ac6973c</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/08/ether-bitcoin-ratio-signals-eth-is-extremely-undervalued-but-headwinds-remain-cryptoquant"/>
        <updated>2025-05-08T12:23:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Undervaluation signals have previously preceded ETH rallies, but surging supply, flat demand, and weakened burn mechanics complicate the outlook.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shaurya Malwa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Download: AI benchmarks, and Spain’s grid blackout]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1116202</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/05/08/1116202/the-download-ai-benchmarks-and-spains-grid-blackout/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-08T12:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is today’s edition of The Download, our weekday newsletter that provides a daily dose of what’s going on in the world of technology. How to build a better AI benchmark It’s not easy being one of Silicon Valley’s favorite benchmarks.  SWE-Bench (pronounced “swee bench”) launched in November 2024 as a way to evaluate an AI model’s…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rhiannon Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Did solar power cause Spain’s blackout?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1116166</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/05/08/1116166/spain-blackout-grid/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-08T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At roughly midday on Monday, April 28, the lights went out in Spain. The grid blackout, which extended into parts of Portugal and France, affected tens of millions of people—flights were grounded, cell networks went down, and businesses closed for the day. Over a week later, officials still aren’t entirely sure what happened, but some…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Casey Crownhart</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to build a better AI benchmark]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1116192</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/05/08/1116192/how-to-build-a-better-ai-benchmark/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-08T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s not easy being one of Silicon Valley’s favorite benchmarks.  SWE-Bench (pronounced “swee bench”) launched in November 2024 to evaluate an AI model’s coding skill, using more than 2,000 real-world programming problems pulled from the public GitHub repositories of 12 different Python-based projects.  In the months since then, it’s quickly become one of the most…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Russell Brandom</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Imagination unveils E-Series GPUs for graphics and AI at the edge]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3006922</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/games/imagination-unveils-e-series-gpus-for-graphics-and-ai-at-the-edge/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-08T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Imagination Technologies is unveiling its E-Series graphics processing units (GPUs) for graphics and AI processing at the edge.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dean Takahashi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nvidia welcomes Trump’s proposal to rescind global chip restrictions]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3006921</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/gaming-business/nvidia-welcomes-trumps-proposal-to-rescind-global-chip-restrictions/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-08T06:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Donald Trump's administration is expected to rescind Joe Biden's curbs on AI chip sales as part of a broader effort to revise semiconductor restrictions, Bloomberg reported.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dean Takahashi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Anthropic launches Claude web search API, betting on the future of post-Google information access]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3006849</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/anthropic-launches-claude-web-search-api-betting-on-the-future-of-post-google-information-access/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-07T22:01:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Anthropic launches web search API for Claude as Apple considers AI search alternatives to Google, signaling a major shift in how users discover information online.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Nuñez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn Next.js by Coding Your Own Dropbox Clone – Full Course]]></title>
        <id>681b80ee1a1a4e16cffa1a50</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/code-a-dropbox-clone-with-nextjs/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-07T15:49:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Building modern full-stack applications requires a strong grasp of various interconnected technologies. And what better way to learn than by creating a real-world project that mimics a widely used tool like Dropbox? That’s exactly what this new cours...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mistral comes out swinging for enterprise AI customers with new Le Chat Enterprise, Medium 3 model]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3006803</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/mistral-comes-out-swinging-for-enterprise-ai-customers-with-new-le-chat-enterprise-medium-3-model/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-07T15:13:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mistral AI is making a concerted push to lower the barriers to scalable, privacy-respecting AI adoption for modern enterprises.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carl Franzen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Recursive Types in TypeScript: A Brief Exploration]]></title>
        <id>681b77a47396438eaee0c5ce</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/recursive-types-in-typescript-a-brief-exploration/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-07T15:09:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It is said that there are two different worlds in TypeScript that exist side by side: the type world and the value world. Consider this line of code: const firstName: string = 'Maynard'; While firstName and 'Maynard' live in the value world, string ...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eda Eren</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The business of the future is adaptive]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1116098</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/05/07/1116098/the-business-of-the-future-is-adaptive/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-07T14:14:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Manufacturing is in a state of flux. From supply chain disruptions to rising costs, tougher environmental regulations, and a changing consumer market, the sector faces a series of competing challenges. But a new way of operating offers a way to tackle complexities head-on: adaptive production hardwires flexibility and resilience into the enterprise, drawing on powerful…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>MIT Technology Review Insights</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Front-End Performance Optimization Handbook – Tips and Strategies for Devs]]></title>
        <id>681b5e61b1ed0b90facd0adf</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/the-front-end-performance-optimization-handbook/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-07T13:21:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When you’re building a website, you’ll want it to be responsive, fast, and efficient. This means making sure the site loads quickly, runs smoothly, and provides a seamless experience for your users, among other things. So as you build, you’ll want to...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gordan Tan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Breathe lands $21M Series B to predict battery performance]]></title>
        <id>https://techcrunch.com/?p=3003769</id>
        <link href="https://techcrunch.com/2025/05/07/breathe-lands-21m-series-b-to-predict-battery-performance/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-07T12:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Breathe has developed a suite of tools that it says helps automakers and others get the most out of their batteries.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tim De Chant</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Netflix unveils new TV experience with GenAI search and AI-based recommendations]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3006789</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/games/netflix-unveils-new-tv-experience-with-genai-search-and-ai-based-recommendations/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-07T12:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Netflix unveiled its new TV experience that features generative AI search, AI-based recommendations and an enhanced design.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dean Takahashi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Download: Neuralink’s AI boost, and Trump’s tariffs]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1116147</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/05/07/1116147/the-download-neuralinks-ai-boost-and-trumps-tariffs/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-07T12:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is today’s edition of The Download, our weekday newsletter that provides a daily dose of what’s going on in the world of technology. This patient’s Neuralink brain implant gets a boost from generative AI Last November, Bradford G. Smith got a brain implant from Elon Musk’s company Neuralink. The device, a set of thin wires attached…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rhiannon Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This patient’s Neuralink brain implant gets a boost from generative AI]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1116139</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/05/07/1116139/this-brain-implant-gets-a-boost-from-generative-ai/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-07T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Last November, Bradford G. Smith got a brain implant from Elon Musk’s company Neuralink. The device, a set of thin wires attached to a computer about the thickness of a few quarters that sits in his skull, lets him use his thoughts to move a computer pointer on a screen.  And by last week he…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Antonio Regalado</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS report: Generative AI overtakes security in global tech budgets for 2025]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3006670</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/aws-report-generative-ai-overtakes-security-in-global-tech-budgets-for-2025/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T21:33:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New AWS report reveals 45% of global IT leaders now prioritize generative AI over cybersecurity in 2025 tech budgets as companies race to hire AI talent and implement AI strategies despite persistent skills shortages.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Nuñez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Secure Mobile APIs in Flutter]]></title>
        <id>681a707658599a397b11b418</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-secure-mobile-apis-in-flutter/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T20:26:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As mobile applications continue to evolve in functionality and scope, securing the APIs that power these apps has become more critical than ever. In the context of Flutter, a framework that enables cross-platform development, understanding how to sec...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Atuoha Anthony</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meet the new king of AI coding: Google’s Gemini 2.5 Pro I/O Edition dethrones Claude 3.7 Sonnet]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3006623</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/meet-the-new-king-of-ai-coding-googles-gemini-2-5-pro-i-o-edition-dethrones-claude-3-7-sonnet/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T18:39:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One of the standout features of the update is its ability to build full, interactive web apps or simulations from a single prompt.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carl Franzen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[When Abandoned Mines Collapse]]></title>
        <id>https://practical.engineering/blog/2025/5/6/when-abandoned-mines-collapse</id>
        <link href="https://practical.engineering/blog/2025/5/6/when-abandoned-mines-collapse"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T18:38:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Create Documentation with docs.page – A Beginner's Tutorial]]></title>
        <id>681a558b9791d0e469b84519</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-create-documentation-with-docspage/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T18:31:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One of the most tedious tasks for every startup, company, and open-source project is often building and managing documentation – especially for medium to large-scale documentation websites. docs.page is an open-source documentation tool that helps yo...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rajdeep Singh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lightricks just made AI video generation 30x faster — and you won’t need a $10,000 GPU]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3006613</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/lightricks-just-made-ai-video-generation-30x-faster-and-you-wont-need-a-10000-gpu/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T17:56:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Lightricks unveils groundbreaking LTXV-13B AI video model that runs 30X faster than competitors on consumer hardware through innovative "multiscale rendering" technology.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Nuñez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ServiceNow lets users see more of their AI]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3006589</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/servicenow-lets-users-see-more-of-their-ai/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ServiceNow also announced a way for agents to communicate with others along with its new observability platform.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Emilia David</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build Your Own Local AI: Create Free RAG and AI Agents with Qwen 3 and Ollama]]></title>
        <id>681a35d4d5da806f5e9467b1</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-a-local-ai/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T16:16:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The landscape of Artificial Intelligence is rapidly evolving, and one of the most exciting trends is the ability to run powerful Large Language Models (LLMs) directly on your local machine. This shift away from reliance on cloud-based APIs offers sig...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chaitanya Rahalkar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Report: OpenAI is buying AI-powered developer platform Windsurf — what happens to its support for rival LLMs?]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3006587</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/report-openai-is-buying-ai-powered-developer-platform-windsurf-what-happens-to-its-support-for-rival-llms/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T14:37:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[OpenAI could see which types of developers use rival models such as the Meta Llama variants and Anthropic's Claude, and for what purposes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carl Franzen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Startup Korl unveils multimodal, multi-agent tool for custom communication across disparate systems]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3006451</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/how-openai-gemini-and-anthropic-help-korl-prepare-customer-materials-in-minutes/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Korl's platform works across multiple systems, using multi-agent and multimodal AI to create highly-customized customer messaging.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Taryn Plumb</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Throwaway Code: Don't recycle, throw it away (2017)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sung.codes/blog/2017/throwaway-code-dont-recycle-throw-away</id>
        <link href="https://www.sung.codes/blog/2017/throwaway-code-dont-recycle-throw-away"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T13:54:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ōura adds AI-driven meal and glucose tracking features with Stelo by Dexcom]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3006449</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/games/oura-adds-ai-driven-meal-and-glucose-tracking-features-with-stelo-by-dexcom/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ōura, maker of a health-monitoring smart ring, announced that it will use AI to track and analyze two new metabolic health features: meals and glucose.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dean Takahashi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Download: a longevity influencer’s new religion, and humanoid robots’ shortcomings]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1116114</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/05/06/1116114/the-download-a-longevity-influencers-new-religion-and-humanoid-robots-shortcomings/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T12:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is today’s edition of The Download, our weekday newsletter that provides a daily dose of what’s going on in the world of technology. Bryan Johnson wants to start a new religion in which “the body is God” Bryan Johnson is on a mission to not die. The 47-year-old multimillionaire has already applied his slogan “Don’t Die”…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rhiannon Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why the humanoid workforce is running late]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1116108</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/05/06/1116108/why-the-humanoid-workforce-is-running-late/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On Thursday I watched Daniela Rus, one of the world’s top experts on AI-powered robots, address a packed room at a Boston robotics expo. Rus spent a portion of her talk busting the notion that giant fleets of humanoids are already making themselves useful in manufacturing and warehouses around the world.  That might come as…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>James O'Donnell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Join the 2025 Web3j Mentorships: Build the Future of Ethereum on the JVM]]></title>
        <id>6819c8dc41eeeb000183d37b</id>
        <link href="https://blog.web3labs.com/join-the-2025-web3j-mentorships-build-the-future-of-ethereum-on-the-jvm/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T08:32:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Linux Foundation’s Decentralized Trust (LFDT) mentorship program is back in 2025 with two exciting opportunities for developers passionate about Ethereum, Android, and the Java Virtual Machine (JVM). Whether you’re a seasoned blockchain developer or an Android enthusiast eager to dive into Web3, these mentorships offer]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>George Tebrean</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[IBM thinks that over a billion new applications will be built with gen AI : Here’s how they’re going to help that happen with agentic AI]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3006455</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/agents-are-key-to-enterprise-ai-success-heres-ibms-plan-on-how-to-make-it-happen/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T04:01:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[IBM details its plans to help enterprises to actually do more with AI, with an expanded set of agentic AI capabilities.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sean Michael Kerner</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meta, Cisco put open-source LLMs at the core of next-gen SOC workflows]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3006384</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/rsac-2025-cisco-and-meta-put-open-source-ai-at-the-heart-of-enterprise-threat-defense/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T00:08:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cisco’s Foundation-sec-8B LLM & Meta’s AI Defenders redefine cybersecurity with open-source AI for scalable SOCs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Louis Columbus</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Phoenician culture spread mainly through cultural exchange]]></title>
        <id>https://www.mpg.de/24574685/0422-evan-phoenician-culture-spread-mainly-through-cultural-exchange-150495-x</id>
        <link href="https://www.mpg.de/24574685/0422-evan-phoenician-culture-spread-mainly-through-cultural-exchange-150495-x"/>
        <updated>2025-05-05T21:06:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nvidia launches fully open source transcription AI model Parakeet-TDT-0.6B-V2 on Hugging Face]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3006438</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/nvidia-launches-fully-open-source-transcription-ai-model-parakeet-tdt-0-6b-v2-on-hugging-face/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-05T19:17:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An attractive proposition for commercial enterprises and indie developers looking to build speech recognition and transcription services...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carl Franzen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Zombieverter: Open source VCU for reusing salvage EV components]]></title>
        <id>https://openinverter.org/wiki/ZombieVerter_VCU</id>
        <link href="https://openinverter.org/wiki/ZombieVerter_VCU"/>
        <updated>2025-05-05T19:00:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Visa launches ‘Intelligent Commerce’ platform, letting AI agents swipe your card—safely, it says]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3006416</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/visa-launches-intelligent-commerce-platform-letting-ai-agents-swipe-your-card-safely-it-says/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-05T18:01:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Visa launches Intelligent Commerce platform enabling AI assistants to make secure purchases with your credit card, transforming online shopping with personalized automation and consumer-controlled spending limits.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Nuñez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Finding a Bug in Chromium]]></title>
        <id>https://bou.ke/blog/chromium-bug/</id>
        <link href="https://bou.ke/blog/chromium-bug/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-05T10:44:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bryan Johnson wants to start a new religion in which “the body is God”]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1116090</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/05/05/1116090/bryan-johnson-new-religion-body-is-god/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-05T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bryan Johnson is on a mission to not die. The 47-year-old multimillionaire has already applied his slogan “Don’t Die” to events, merchandise, and a Netflix documentary. Now he’s founding a Don’t Die religion. Johnson, who famously spends millions of dollars on scans, tests, supplements, and a lifestyle routine designed to slow or reverse the aging…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jessica Hamzelou</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Robotics meets the culinary arts]]></title>
        <id>https://actu.epfl.ch/news/robotics-meets-the-culinary-arts/</id>
        <link href="https://actu.epfl.ch/news/robotics-meets-the-culinary-arts/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-05T08:45:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The great cognitive migration: How AI is reshaping human purpose, work and meaning]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3006326</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/the-great-cognitive-migration-ai-will-win-at-intelligence-but-only-we-can-make-it-matter/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-04T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Humans need to embrace domains where AI still falters, and where human creativity, ethics and emotion emain indispensable.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gary Grossman, Edelman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Not everything needs an LLM: A framework for evaluating when AI makes sense]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3006312</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/not-everything-needs-an-llm-a-framework-for-evaluating-when-ai-makes-sense/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-03T19:35:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The answer to 'What customer needs requires an AI solution?' isn’t always 'Yes.' LLMs are still expensive and not always accurate.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sharanya Rao</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[RSAC 2025: Why the AI agent era means more demand for CISOs]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3006066</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/security/rsac-2025-why-the-ai-agent-era-means-more-demand-for-cisos/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-02T23:02:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[RSAC 2025 made one thing clear: AI agents are entering security workflows, but boards want proof they work.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Louis Columbus</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OpenAI overrode concerns of expert testers to release sycophantic GPT-4o]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3006276</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/openai-overrode-concerns-of-expert-testers-to-release-sycophantic-gpt-4o/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-02T17:57:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Once again, it shows the importance of incorporating more domains beyond the traditional math and computer science into AI development.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carl Franzen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Roblox breaks ground on data center in Brazil for early 2026]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3006251</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/games/roblox-breaks-ground-on-data-center-in-brazil-for-early-2026/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-02T16:55:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At Gamescom Latam, Roblox announced it has broken ground on a new data center in Brazil -- slated to go live in early 2026.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dean Takahashi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Download: foreign disinformation intel, and gene-edited pork]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1116079</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/05/02/1116079/the-download-foreign-disinformation-intel-and-gene-edited-pork/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-02T12:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is today’s edition of The Download, our weekday newsletter that provides a daily dose of what’s going on in the world of technology. A senior State Department official demanded records of communications with journalists, European officials, and Trump critics A previously unreported document distributed by senior US State Department official Darren Beattie reveals a sweeping effort…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rhiannon Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Web3j Six Month Project Update]]></title>
        <id>68109495670a1300013504c2</id>
        <link href="https://blog.web3labs.com/web3j-six-month-project-update/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T09:10:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[November 2024 - April 2025
This report summarizes the activities and accomplishments of Web3j, an LF Decentralized Trust project, from November 2024 to April 2025. During this period, the project made significant strides in improving the framework’s functionality, enhancing user engagement, and bolstering overall community interaction. 
Key]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>George Tebrean</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[QuickNode: Building the Infrastructure for the Next Generation of Blockchain]]></title>
        <id>6807d5787fb8500001c39b99</id>
        <link href="https://blog.quicknode.com/quicknode-building-the-infrastructure-for-the-next-generation-of-blockchain/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-28T16:02:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Join QuickNode co-founder Dmitry Shklovsky as he discusses blockchain infrastructure, building decentralized applications, and the future of Web3 development on TheCube's Crypto Trailblazer Series.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>QuickNode</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>