<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2025-05-21T06:51:56.851Z</id>
    <title>AngJianming RSS Feed</title>
    <updated>2025-05-21T06:51:56.851Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Import Maps: Why Nobody Talks About Them (But Maybe Should)]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/marie_berezhna/import-maps-why-nobody-talks-about-them-but-maybe-should-3ckl</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/marie_berezhna/import-maps-why-nobody-talks-about-them-but-maybe-should-3ckl"/>
        <updated>2025-05-21T06:50:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You know what sucks?
Bundling.
Install react → ends up in node_modules/, goes through Vite/Rollup/webpack, gets transpiled, hashed, minified… just so you can write:

import React from 'react';


But what if you didn’t need a bundler at all?
Import Maps are a native browser feature (yep, no polyfill needed in modern Chromium) that let you map bare module specifiers to real URLs — directly in the browser.
Here’s the magic:
<script type="importmap">
{
  "imports": {
    "react": "https://esm.sh/react@18",
    "react-dom": "https://esm.sh/react-dom@18"
  }
}
</script>


Now, in your <script type="module">, you can write:
import React from "react";

And the browser knows where to get it, no bundler, no build step, no CDN script tags.
No build step: Instant dev workflow
No node_modules/: Zero install, zero bloat
Works with CDNs like Skypack, ESM.sh, JSPM
Great for micro frontends, prototypes, and fast loading islands
Not supported in all browsers yet
→ Mostly just Chromium for now. Firefox is dragging. Safari? Radio silence.
(You can polyfill it, but it kills the whole “zero tooling” idea.)
Tooling momentum is too big
→ Everyone already uses Vite, webpack, etc. Import Maps don’t fit the current “npm install + dev server” mindset.
No ecosystem support
→ Most tutorials, libraries, and docs assume you're bundling. Period.
Import Maps shine when you want:
No build tools at all
To prototype quickly
To ship something truly small
To combine multiple micro-apps without a monolith
They’re especially useful with:
Web components
Vanilla JS apps
Islands architecture setups (Astro, Marko, etc.)
JAMstack sites that want dynamic bits without bundling
Import Maps don’t want to replace your build system.
They’re just saying: "Hey... you might not need one."
They're not mainstream (yet), but they offer a glimpse at a simpler frontend world — one where browsers do more and you ship less.
Worth keeping an eye on.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Marie Berezhna</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microservices simply]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/vjnvisakh/microservices-simply-3dei</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/vjnvisakh/microservices-simply-3dei"/>
        <updated>2025-05-21T06:49:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microservices have been a topic that has been revolving in my mind for some time. I wanted to find out what the big deal is behind all of that.
Microservices is an architecture where we create a system with loosely coupled services each that can be scaled in isolation.
Microservices talk to each other via protocols like HTTP, gRPC etc.
Each MS can be individually deployed and has its own database. So total isolation. But it comes with the overhead of managing each one too. There is also the problem that now databases can't have foreign key relationships.
It is a good way to show separation of concerns as the microservices are totally isolated.
The key component is the API gateway which acts as a proxy to the services. Everything hits the gateway and is then routed.
Last but not the least, it is not meant for small projects. It is best for large teams with each micro-team working on a micro-service.
So I went out to make it happen and get over with the fuss once and for all. Like always I went ahead with my most favourite thing in the world - a todo application.
Here is the architecture
User Domain - a user micro-service that creates and gets users.
Todo Domain - a todo micro-service that adds and fetches todo items for the users
API Gateway - a gateway that acts as a proxy and routes requests.
Here is the code
https://github.com/visakhvjn/microservices-express]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Visakh Vijayan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[URL - what is it?]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/aexol-studio/url-what-is-it-4ja7</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/aexol-studio/url-what-is-it-4ja7"/>
        <updated>2025-05-21T06:48:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Let's start with the basics. A URL (Uniform Resource Locator) is simply a unique address that allows you to find a particular page, file or resource on the web. By typing in a URL in your browser, you end up exactly where you want to go - whether it's to a shop homepage, a blog article or an image. Without URLs, the internet would be a pure chaos, because there would be no way to pinpoint where the content is.
What is a URL and what does it consist of?
If you're wondering: what is a URL and what does it look like, it's worth knowing that each URL is made up of several elements:
a protocol (usually https or http)
domain (e.g. twojastrona.pl)
path (e.g. /blog/what-to-address-url)
sometimes parameters (e.g. ?sort=desc)
excerpt (e.g. #section1)
An example URL might look like this:
https://your…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tomek Poniatowicz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tune Talk Launches In-App Entertainment Hub]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=352519</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/352519/tune-talk-in-app-entertainment-hub/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-21T06:40:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tune Talk has officially launched its in-app entertainment hub, the Games and Drama in Tune Talk App. This feature is the first of its nature to be offered by a telco in Malaysia, and was developed in collaboration with cloud entertainment platform Jolibox. According to Tune Talk, the app offers a selection of over 200 […]
The post Tune Talk Launches In-App Entertainment Hub appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nurul Kamil</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Master AI/ML Infrastructure with Azure]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/rigalpatel001/master-aiml-infrastructure-with-azure-1bcm</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/rigalpatel001/master-aiml-infrastructure-with-azure-1bcm"/>
        <updated>2025-05-21T06:36:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What if you could turn your machine learning (ML) models into production-ready AI solutions that scale effortlessly? That’s the power of mastering AI/ML infrastructure—and in this guide, we’ll explore how Microsoft Azure makes it all possible.
Whether you're just starting with ML or scaling enterprise-level projects, Azure provides a complete ecosystem to build, train, deploy, and monitor your AI models. In this post, I’ll walk you through Azure’s key services, real-world examples, and actionable steps—written simply, with code and clarity.
In simple terms, AI/ML infrastructure refers to the cloud-based tools, services, and compute resources that support the end-to-end lifecycle of a machine learning model—from data ingestion to deployment and maintenance.
Azure offers:
Integrated environm…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rigal Patel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Is This the Best Free WAF in 2025?]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/sharon_42e16b8da44dabde6d/is-this-the-best-free-waf-in-2025-26o7</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/sharon_42e16b8da44dabde6d/is-this-the-best-free-waf-in-2025-26o7"/>
        <updated>2025-05-21T06:34:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you're looking for a free, powerful Web Application Firewall (WAF), SafeLine WAF should be at the top of your list.
Developed by Chaitin Tech, SafeLine has been refined for years, with core technologies like semantic analysis engines and security modules open-sourced since 2016. SafeLine WAF is making waves in the security community — it's powerful, easy to deploy, and completely free to use.

SafeLine is a reverse proxy-based WAF that blocks malicious HTTP traffic before it reaches your web service. Acting as a shield between your site and the internet, it helps you mitigate:
Web attacks like SQL injection and XSS

Automated tools and vulnerability scanners

Malicious bots and scrapers

DDoS attempts via rate limiting and verification



Whether you're running a blog, an API backend, o…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sharon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Know the Endpoint, Understand the Payload]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/ameliax/know-the-endpoint-understand-the-payload-18h4</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/ameliax/know-the-endpoint-understand-the-payload-18h4"/>
        <updated>2025-05-21T06:33:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In today's digital landscape, APIs serve as the fundamental means of communication between systems. They enable data exchange across web, mobile, and cloud platforms, making services interoperable and scalable. Whenever a user performs an action within an app, an API often acts as the conduit through which the app communicates with backend servers.
A payload represents the actual data being transmitted in an API request. For example, when a user signs up for a service, details like their name, email, and password are sent as the payload. It serves as the medium by which the client expresses the intent and content of a request to the server. Understanding how payloads are structured and processed is key to reliable data exchange.
An endpoint is a unique URL path that corresponds to a specif…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amelia</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The AI Hypocrisy: Why We Need to Rethink How We Judge AI Usage]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/sangram_behera_2001/the-ai-hypocrisy-why-we-need-to-rethink-how-we-judge-ai-usage-3h3f</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/sangram_behera_2001/the-ai-hypocrisy-why-we-need-to-rethink-how-we-judge-ai-usage-3h3f"/>
        <updated>2025-05-21T06:33:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“AI is making us dumb.”

“We shouldn’t rely on ChatGPT for everything.”

“Real intelligence comes from struggle, not shortcuts.”
You’ve probably seen these statements across blogs, social media, or even heard them in casual conversations. And truth be told, they’re not entirely wrong. AI should not be a replacement for thinking — it should be an aid, a tool. But here’s where the contradiction creeps in...
Many people talk about limiting AI usage, yet they use AI to write those very posts warning others not to. Irony much?
It’s like saying, “Don’t drink too much coffee” — while sipping a large Americano.
Yes, over-relying on AI can weaken critical thinking, but let’s not act like searching on Google is somehow nobler. Why is using ChatGPT to get answers called "downgrading our brain" while …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sangram Behera</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Share Your Local Next.js App Online Using Pinggy]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/lightningdev123/how-to-share-your-local-nextjs-app-online-using-pinggy-55m8</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/lightningdev123/how-to-share-your-local-nextjs-app-online-using-pinggy-55m8"/>
        <updated>2025-05-21T06:32:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When working on a Next.js application during development, it's common to run the app locally at localhost:3000. However, there are situations where you may need to share your local development environment with others—for example, to collect feedback, debug collaboratively, or demonstrate features in progress. Typically, this requires deploying the app to a staging server or a cloud platform, which can be time-consuming or unnecessary for short-term access. An alternative approach is to use a tunneling tool that creates a secure connection between your local machine and the internet. In this guide, we'll use Pinggy, a simple SSH-based tunneling solution, to make a locally hosted Next.js app accessible from anywhere.
Next.js is a powerful React framework built by Vercel. It offers everything…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lightning Developer</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Schedule on Demand: Building Self-Destructing Dynamically Scheduled Lambda Triggers in AWS]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/abhiyan_khanal_17efc6164b/schedule-on-demand-building-self-destructing-dynamically-scheduled-lambda-triggers-in-aws-5505</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/abhiyan_khanal_17efc6164b/schedule-on-demand-building-self-destructing-dynamically-scheduled-lambda-triggers-in-aws-5505"/>
        <updated>2025-05-21T06:31:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cover image source: Introducing Amazon EventBridge Scheduler - AWS Blog
Dynamic, self-managing schedulers would be valuable in several scenarios:
Custom S3 Object Lifecycle Management

Set flexible, per-object expiration times beyond S3’s standard lifecycle policies:  
Object A needs deletion after 5 minutes


Object B requires retention for 1 day


Object C must be archived after 3 hours but deleted after 30 days
All managed through event-driven, temporary schedulers that clean up after themselves.
Limited-Time Promotional Offers

Schedule promotional code expirations or pricing changes that clean up after themselves.


Trial Period Management

Automatically schedule feature deactivation for users after trial periods.




  
  
  Traditional Approaches & Limitations



  
  
  DynamoDB TT…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Abhiyan Khanal</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Write SEO-Optimized Content with AI]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/dct_technology/how-to-write-seo-optimized-content-with-ai-48e0</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/dct_technology/how-to-write-seo-optimized-content-with-ai-48e0"/>
        <updated>2025-05-21T06:30:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AI-powered writing tools are everywhere, promising to boost your SEO and crank out content faster than ever. 
But here’s the catch—how do you keep your unique voice alive when a machine is doing the writing?
If you want to harness AI for SEO without sounding robotic or losing your personal touch, this post is for you. 
Let’s dive into how you can blend AI’s power with your creativity to craft content that ranks and resonates.

AI tools like ChatGPT or Jasper can generate content quickly, but they often lack emotional depth, personality, and nuance. SEO demands relevance and readability, not just keyword stuffing or robotic phrasing.
If you blindly copy AI outputs, Google’s algorithms might catch on, or worse—your readers won’t connect with your content.
Here’s a practical approach you can …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>DCT Technology Pvt. Ltd.</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Using Iterator Traits to Replace Loops]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/sgchris/using-iterator-traits-to-replace-loops-23ai</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/sgchris/using-iterator-traits-to-replace-loops-23ai"/>
        <updated>2025-05-21T06:30:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Using Iterator Traits to Replace Loops in Rust


Refactor common for loops into expressive iterator chains.  
Rust developers often praise the language for its zero-cost abstractions, safety guarantees, and expressive API design. One of Rust's most powerful and elegant features is its iterator system. Iterators allow us to process collections without explicitly managing loops, enabling concise, readable, and performant code.  
But why bother replacing for loops with iterators? Aren't loops simple enough? Here's the deal:  
Expressiveness: Iterators communicate what you're doing with data rather than how you're doing it.


Composability: You can chain iterator methods like .filter(), .map(), and .collect() to build pipelines that are easy to reason about.


Performance: Iterators are optimi…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gregory Chris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google Wants Gemini To Anticipate And Resolve Your Needs]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=352455</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/352455/google-wants-gemini-anticipate-resolve-your-needs/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-21T06:28:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Since Google first teased Project Astra before last year’s I/O, bits of it has permeated though Gemini Live, leading to the Android AI chatbot we have today. Its uses have expanded to the point of supplanting the old Google Assistant. With that, the internet search giant also wants the new assistant to be pushed further, […]
The post Google Wants Gemini To Anticipate And Resolve Your Needs appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ian Chee</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is LLaMA Factory? LLM Fine-Tuning]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/voltagent/what-is-llama-factory-llm-fine-tuning-1d23</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/voltagent/what-is-llama-factory-llm-fine-tuning-1d23"/>
        <updated>2025-05-21T06:27:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Large Language Models (LLMs) are gigantic AI models which generate text and code for a variety of tasks. Although such models are very powerful, however, they sometimes need to be tailored for specific purposes even more. Fine-tuning an LLM will accomplish this, but the process can be tricky without the right tools.
That's where I came across LLaMA-Factory, which made it much simpler for me to personalize the model.

Basically, LLaMA-Factory is just this totally awesome open-source thing by some great dev dude hiyouga. It's a one-stop-shop for fiddling with data from over 100 different LLMs and even VLMs (those are the ones which get visual). People love this thing. It doesn't surprise me. It takes some serious headache out of fiddling around.
It's also mostly platform-agnostic, meaning it…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Necati Özmen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SEC delays decision on Ether staking and XRP ETFs, as analysts expected]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/sec-delays-ether-staking-xrp-etfs-expected-analyst</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/sec-delays-ether-staking-xrp-etfs-expected-analyst?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-21T06:13:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The US Securities and Exchange Commission has delayed its decision on Bitwise’s application to add staking to its Ether exchange-traded fund and on Grayscale’s XRP ETF bid, which analysts had expected.
The SEC said on May 20 that it needed to extend its decision on Bitwise’s application by 45 days to “consider the proposed rule change and the issues raised therein.” The agency needed to either decide or punt its decision by May 22.
The agency also delayed deciding on Grayscale’s XRP (XRP) tracking ETF and Bitwise’s Solana (SOL) tracking fund while it seeks public comments and begins “proceedings to allow for additional analysis” of the proposals to ensure they meet regulatory standards.
Bloomberg ETF analyst James Seyffart said on X that both delays were expected as the SEC “typically take…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Stephen Katte</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[KindlyMD shareholders OK merger with Trump-linked Bitcoin firm]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/kindlymd-shareholders-ok-merger-with-trump-linked-bitcoin-firm</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/kindlymd-shareholders-ok-merger-with-trump-linked-bitcoin-firm?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-21T06:01:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Shareholders of the healthcare services provider KindlyMD, Inc have approved a proposed merger with Bitcoin holding company Nakamoto Holdings, founded by US President Donald Trump’s crypto adviser, David Bailey.
KindlyMD and Nakamoto Holdings, a newly formed company that focuses on creating a network of Bitcoin-related entities, will both file information statements with the Securities and Exchange Commission, KindlyMD said in a May 20 statement.
The merger is expected to take place 20 days after both companies have shared the information statement with KindlyMD’s shareholders, with the transaction expected to be finalized in the third quarter of 2025.
Google Finance shows shares in KindlyMD (KDLY) closed the May 20 trading session up 9% at $15.22 and gained another 4.8% after the bell as …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Tarang Khaitan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Show HN: Kraa.io – Markdown editor for notes, blogs, chats]]></title>
        <id>https://kraa.io/</id>
        <link href="https://kraa.io/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-21T05:22:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Sets Record Daily Close With $110K as the Next Level to Watch for BTC]]></title>
        <id>77e476d9-5a46-4072-8996-39f0786cb6ed</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/21/bitcoin-sets-record-daily-close-with-usd110k-as-the-next-level-to-watch-for-btc"/>
        <updated>2025-05-21T05:21:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The next significant price level for Bitcoin is $110,000, where market dynamics could amplify price movements.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Omkar Godbole</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blackstone buys $1M worth of Bitcoin ETF in first crypto bet]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/blackstone-buys-1-million-blackrock-bitcoin-etf-ibit</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/blackstone-buys-1-million-blackrock-bitcoin-etf-ibit?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-21T05:16:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Blackstone, which bills itself as the “the world’s largest alternative asset manager,” disclosed its first-ever crypto-related purchase, buying shares in BlackRock’s spot Bitcoin exchange-traded fund.
However, Blackstone’s investment, reported in a May 20 filing with the US Securities and Exchange Commission, only totaled around $1.08 million — a fraction of the asset manager’s $1.2 trillion portfolio.
Blackstone reported holding 23,094 shares of BlackRock’s iShares Bitcoin Trust ETF (IBIT) as of March 31.
The IBIT shares were added to Blackstone’s Alternative Multi-Strategy Fund (BTMIX), which holds $2.63 billion worth of assets, Google Finance data shows.
The filing shows Blackstone also bought 4,300 shares in crypto ATM operator Bitcoin Depot Inc. (BTM) for a total cost of $6,300 and sp…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Brayden Lindrea</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google Introduces AI Pro, AI Ultra Subscriptions; Starts From RM97.99/month]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=352465</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/352465/google-ai-pro-ai-ultra/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-21T05:11:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As leaked earlier this month, Google has introduced two new paid subscription tiers for its AI features called AI Pro and AI Ultra. The former is available now while the latter is limited to the US but will be rolling out to other countries soon. Priced above the regular Google One subscription plans, the AI […]
The post Google Introduces AI Pro, AI Ultra Subscriptions; Starts From RM97.99/month appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ikmal Rozlan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Convolutions, Polynomials and Flipped Kernels]]></title>
        <id>https://eli.thegreenplace.net/2025/convolutions-polynomials-and-flipped-kernels/</id>
        <link href="https://eli.thegreenplace.net/2025/convolutions-polynomials-and-flipped-kernels/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-21T04:35:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google Partners With Gentle Monster; Warby Parker For Android XR Devices]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=352401</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/352401/google-partners-with-gentle-monster-warby-parker-for-android-xr-devices/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-21T04:35:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When the Google Glass was consigned to a life completely outside of the public eye, there was always a hope that it would make a comeback at some point. We saw a glimpse of that last month when the internet search giant demoed an Android XR device at a TED Talk, and following its I/O […]
The post Google Partners With Gentle Monster; Warby Parker For Android XR Devices appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ian Chee</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘Hawk tuah girl’ Haliey Welch says FBI probed her ‘memecoin disaster’]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/hawk-tuah-girl-haliey-welch-fbi-probed-over-hawk-memecoin</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/hawk-tuah-girl-haliey-welch-fbi-probed-over-hawk-memecoin?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-21T04:03:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Haliey Welch, better known as the “Hawk tuah girl,” says the Federal Bureau of Investigation briefly probed her after her “memecoin disaster” — the failed launch of a token in her image that she promoted. 
Welch said in a May 21 episode of her “Talk Tuah” podcast that the FBI showed up at her grandmother’s house looking to speak to her over the Hawk Tuah (HAWK) crypto token, which many crypto commentators have called an exit scam.
“After the coin launch, the feds came to granny’s house and knocked on her door, and she called me, having a heart attack, saying: ‘The FBI is here after you, what have you done?’”
Welch said she handed over her phone to the FBI and met with agents who “interrogated me, asking me questions and everything else related to crypto.”
“They cleared me, I was good to go…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Brayden Lindrea</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AMD Officially Announces Ryzen Threadripper 9000 Series At Computex 2025]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=352380</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/352380/amd-officially-announces-ryzen-threadripper-9000-series-at-computex-2025/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-21T03:55:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In addition to the launch of the Radeon RX 9060 XT, AMD also announced its new Ryzen Threadripper 9000 Series HEDT processors here at Computex 2025. As generational update, the new Threadripper Series, is based on AMD’s 4nm Zen 5 CPU architecture, offers a total of nine SKUs with its top-tier model offering 96-cores, 192-threads, […]
The post AMD Officially Announces Ryzen Threadripper 9000 Series At Computex 2025 appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John Law</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AMD Launches Radeon RX 9060 XT At Computex 2025]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=352369</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/352369/amd-launches-radeon-rx-9060-xt-at-computex-2025/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-21T03:41:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AMD officially announced the Radeon RX 9060 XT at its press conference at Computex 2025. As promised, the GPUs serve as the red chipmaker’s entry-level Navi 44 architecture. The GPU will be available in two graphics memory configurations, 8GB and 16GB GDDR6 graphics memory. Regardless of the memory configuration, the card will feature 32 RDNA4 […]
The post AMD Launches Radeon RX 9060 XT At Computex 2025 appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John Law</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google Launches Flow, An AI Filmmaking Tool]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=352391</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/352391/google-launches-flow-an-ai-filmmaking-tool/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-21T03:21:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google has announced the release of its new AI filmmaking tool, Flow, which is powered by the brand’s latest AI models: Veo, Imagen, and Gemini. As of now, it is currently available exclusively to Google AI Pro and AI Ultra plan users in the US, with “more countries coming soon”. According to Google, Flow has […]
The post Google Launches Flow, An AI Filmmaking Tool appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Newsdesk</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google Starts Rolling Out AI Mode In Search]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=352388</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/352388/google-ai-mode-search/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-21T03:04:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At this year’s Google I/O event, the tech giant announced a major overhaul of its search engine with a wider release of its AI Mode feature. First revealed as an experimental tool earlier this year, the feature will now be rolling it out for all users in the U.S., but it is unknown if or […]
The post Google Starts Rolling Out AI Mode In Search appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ikmal Rozlan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AMD unveils new Threadripper CPUs and Radeon GPUs for gamers at Computex 2025]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008206</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/games/amd-unveils-new-threadripper-cpus-and-radeon-gpus-for-gamers-at-computex-2025/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-21T03:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AMD held a Computex press event to introduce its Radeon RX 9060 XT graphics cards and Threadripper CPUs for next-gen gaming and workstations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dean Takahashi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Disabling kernel functions in your process (2009)]]></title>
        <id>https://chadaustin.me/2009/03/disabling-functions/</id>
        <link href="https://chadaustin.me/2009/03/disabling-functions/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-21T02:22:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Secret Trove of Rare Guitars Heads to the Met]]></title>
        <id>https://www.newyorker.com/magazine/2025/05/26/a-secret-trove-of-rare-guitars-heads-to-the-met</id>
        <link href="https://www.newyorker.com/magazine/2025/05/26/a-secret-trove-of-rare-guitars-heads-to-the-met"/>
        <updated>2025-05-21T02:13:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[realme, Aston Martin F1 Team To Launch GT 7 Dream Edition]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=352310</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/352310/realme-aston-martin-f1-team-gt-7-dream-edition/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-21T02:00:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As realme prepares for the global launch of the GT 7 series, the company seems to have one more surprise up its sleeve: a special Dream Edition of the GT 7. realme revealed in an announcement that it has entered a three-year strategic partnership with the Aston Martin Formula One Team, with the realme GT […]
The post realme, Aston Martin F1 Team To Launch GT 7 Dream Edition appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nurul Kamil</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NYC Mayor Eric Adams launches crypto advisory council]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/nyc-mayor-eric-adams-launches-crypto-taskforce</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/nyc-mayor-eric-adams-launches-crypto-taskforce?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-21T01:37:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New York City Mayor Eric Adams says he will create a digital advisory council to attract jobs and investment to the Big Apple and position it as the “crypto capital of the globe.”
“This is not about chasing memes or trends,” Adams told the inaugural New York City Crypto Summit on May 20. “We want to use the technology of tomorrow to better serve New Yorkers today.”
“We have experts right here, and they are going to help us navigate solutions that serve our city,” he added. “The age of tokenization, which includes crypto and blockchain and other fintech innovations, that age is here, and we’re going to continue to move forward with it.”
Adams didn’t share further details on the advisory group, but said a council chair and key policy recommendations would follow in the next few weeks.

We're…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Stephen Katte</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SEC Charges Unicoin, Top Executives With $100M ‘Massive Securities Fraud’]]></title>
        <id>52b6a53a-ba17-4896-aa11-65abbba3d283</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2025/05/20/sec-charges-unicoin-top-executives-with-100m-massive-securities-fraud"/>
        <updated>2025-05-21T01:29:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Unicoin’s CEO announced last month that he’d rejected the SEC’s offer to negotiate a settlement.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nikhilesh De</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SEC charges Unicoin crypto platform over alleged $100 million fraud]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/sec-charges-unicoin-100-million-fraud</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/sec-charges-unicoin-100-million-fraud?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-21T01:13:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Update May 21, 4:32 am UTC: This article has been updated to add more information from the SEC’s complaint.
The US Securities and Exchange Commission has sued crypto investment platform Unicoin and three of its executives, alleging they made false and misleading statements about their crypto assets that raised over $100 million from investors.
The SEC said on May 20 that it charged Unicoin CEO Alex Konanykhin, board member Silvina Moschini and former investment chief Alex Dominguez with misleading over 5,000 investors about certificates that conveyed rights to receive Unicoin tokens and stock.
SEC Division of Enforcement associate director Mark Cave claimed that starting in 2022, the trio “exploited thousands of investors with fictitious promises that its tokens, when issued, would be back…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Stephen Katte</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Strive targets 75,000 Bitcoin from Mt. Gox claims to build Bitcoin treasury]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/strive-targets-75000-bitcoin-in-mt-gox-claims</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/strive-targets-75000-bitcoin-in-mt-gox-claims?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-21T00:49:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Vivek Ramaswamy’s Strive is looking to build its Bitcoin holdings by purchasing distressed Bitcoin claims at a discount, starting with claims tied to 75,000 Bitcoin at the bankrupt crypto exchange Mt. Gox.
Strive said in a May 20 regulatory filing that it partnered with 117 Castell Advisory Group LLC to target claims to Bitcoin (BTC) that have received definitive legal rulings but are still awaiting distribution.
The company said buying the claims would allow it to purchase Bitcoin at a discount and grow its Bitcoin per share ratio ahead of its planned reverse merger with Asset Entities — which is expected to be completed sometime mid this year.
Strive hasn’t disclosed any Bitcoin holdings but claims it will face fewer restrictions on purchasing Bitcoin than companies going public through …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Brayden Lindrea</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Apple WWDC 2025 Live Stream To Kick Off At 1am Local Time On 10 June]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=352375</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/352375/apple-wwdc-2025-live-stream-to-kick-off-at-1am-local-time-on-10-june/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-21T00:49:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Apple has shared a minor update regarding its upcoming Worldwide Developers Conference (WWDC) 2025 event. Apart from showing off a new graphic and this year’s “On the horizon” slogan, the company confirms that its keynote will be live streamed on its website, Apple TV app, and its official YouTube channel at 1am local time on […]
The post Apple WWDC 2025 Live Stream To Kick Off At 1am Local Time On 10 June appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Heirul Kamel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The value isn't in the code (2022)]]></title>
        <id>https://jonayre.uk/blog/2022/10/30/the-real-value-isnt-in-the-code/</id>
        <link href="https://jonayre.uk/blog/2022/10/30/the-real-value-isnt-in-the-code/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T23:33:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[“ZLinq”, a Zero-Allocation LINQ Library for .NET]]></title>
        <id>https://neuecc.medium.com/zlinq-a-zero-allocation-linq-library-for-net-1bb0a3e5c749</id>
        <link href="https://neuecc.medium.com/zlinq-a-zero-allocation-linq-library-for-net-1bb0a3e5c749"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T22:29:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Here’s what happened in crypto today]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/what-happened-in-crypto-today</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/what-happened-in-crypto-today?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T22:02:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today in crypto, the SEC filed a $100 million fraud suit against Unicoin and its executives, Javier Milei shut down a task force investigating the fallout from LIBRA, and Germany’s summer 2024 Bitcoin sale looks like a $2.3 billion blunder.
SEC sues Unicoin, executives alleging $100 million fraud
The US Securities and Exchange Commission sued Unicoin and three of the crypto platform’s executives on May 20, alleging they made false and misleading statements about crypto assets that raised $100 million from investors.
The SEC charged Unicoin CEO Alex Konanykhin, board member Silvina Moschini, and former investment chief Alex Dominguez with misleading investors about certificates that conveyed rights to receive Unicoin tokens and stock.
A highlighted excerpt of the SEC complaint claims Unicoi…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Cointelegraph</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Apex Group Buys Majority Stake in Tokenization Specialist Tokeny as RWA Trend Soars]]></title>
        <id>dcd8f748-4310-41a1-ad35-ee2944196b19</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2025/05/20/apex-group-buys-majority-stake-in-tokenization-specialist-tokeny-as-rwa-trend-soars"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T22:00:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Apex Group said it plans to fold Tokeny’s team and tech into its services as it pushes tokenized finance to the mainstream.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Krisztian Sandor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Semantic search engine for ArXiv, biorxiv and medrxiv]]></title>
        <id>https://arxivxplorer.com/</id>
        <link href="https://arxivxplorer.com/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T21:49:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Justin Sun to attend Trump&#039;s dinner with memecoin backers]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/justin-sun-attend-trump-dinner-with-memecoin-backers</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/justin-sun-attend-trump-dinner-with-memecoin-backers?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T20:54:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After weeks of speculation among crypto enthusiasts and news outlets, Tron founder Justin Sun has claimed he owns the wallet that purchased the largest amount of Donald Trump’s memecoin, allowing him to qualify for a dinner and reception with the US president.
In a May 19 X post, Sun said he had received an invitation to attend Trump’s dinner at his golf club outside Washington, DC, as part of a reward for the top 220 memecoin holders. The Tron founder claimed he controlled the top wallet on the TRUMP token leaderboard under the username “Sun,” which held roughly $19 million worth of the memecoin at a price of $13.20.
According to Sun, he plans to network at the May 22 memecoin dinner, “talk crypto,” and “discuss the future” of the industry. It’s unclear why the Tron founder chose to annou…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Turner Wright</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sell in May? Bitcoin Tops $107K, Could Hit Record Highs This Summer Say Analysts]]></title>
        <id>42110d25-971e-4561-b01b-abc1c39cb570</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/20/sell-in-may-bitcoin-tops-107k-could-hit-record-highs-this-summer-say-analysts"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T20:43:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Regulatory tailwinds, persistent ETF and corporate buying, Fed rate decisions and Trump's looming tariff deadline are setting the crypto market up for an eventful next few months.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Krisztian Sandor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin open interest hits record high as bulls stampede toward new BTC price highs]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-open-interest-hits-record-high-as-bulls-stampede-toward-new-btc-price-highs</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-open-interest-hits-record-high-as-bulls-stampede-toward-new-btc-price-highs?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T20:32:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Key takeaways:

Bitcoin futures open interest hit a record $72 billion, signaling rising use of leverage among institutional investors.

$1.2 billion in shorts at $107,000 to $108,000 are at risk of liquidation, boosting BTC’s breakout odds.

The aggregate open interest in Bitcoin (BTC) futures surged to a record high on May 20, raising questions about whether bearish positions are now at risk. Despite repeated failures to break above the $107,000 level since May 18, the sheer volume of leveraged positions could propel Bitcoin to a new all-time high.
Bitcoin futures aggregate open interest, USD. Source: CoinGlass
The total open interest in BTC futures climbed to $72 billion on May 20, marking an 8% increase from $66.6 billion just a week earlier. Institutional demand continues to be a majo…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Marcel Pechman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Litestream: Revamped]]></title>
        <id>https://fly.io/blog/litestream-revamped/</id>
        <link href="https://fly.io/blog/litestream-revamped/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T19:58:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum price gained 90% the last time this indicator turned bullish]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/ethereum-price-gained-90-the-last-time-this-indicator-turned-bullish</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/ethereum-price-gained-90-the-last-time-this-indicator-turned-bullish?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T19:44:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Key Takeaways:

Ethereum is forming a bull flag on the daily chart, with a potential breakout above $3,600.

If ETH reclaims the 2-week Gaussian Channel mid-line, a 90% rally could occur.

Ethereum (ETH) price is consolidating between $2,400 and $2,750 on its daily chart, forming a bull flag pattern with sights on the $3,000 to $3,100 resistance zone. A bull flag is a continuation pattern that follows a sharp rally (black flagpole) to $2,730 from $1,900, with the current range forming the flag. 
Ethereum 1-day chart. Source: Cointelegraph/TradingView
A bullish breakout above $2,600 could target $3,600, which is calculated by adding the flagpole height to the breakout point, but the immediate key area of interest remains between the resistance range at $3,100-$3,000. 
The 200-day exponentia…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Biraajmaan Tamuly</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NYC Mayor Eric Adams Is Creating a Crypto Advisory Council]]></title>
        <id>266b251b-2d78-4859-822b-d03736b6ea13</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2025/05/20/nyc-mayor-eric-adams-creating-crypto-advisory-council"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T19:38:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA["We want to use technology of tomorrow to better serve New Yorkers today," said the mayor at a summit on Tuesday.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cheyenne Ligon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google finally launches NotebookLM mobile app at I/O: hands-on, first impressions]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008400</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/google-finally-launches-notebooklm-mobile-app-at-i-o-hands-on-first-impressions/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T19:29:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As NotebookLM matures, its emerging business-tier capabilities suggest growing alignment with the productivity and compliance...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carl Franzen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bancor files patent infringement lawsuit against Uniswap over DEX tech]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/bancor-files-patent-infringement-lawsuit-against-uniswap-over-dex-tech</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/bancor-files-patent-infringement-lawsuit-against-uniswap-over-dex-tech?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T19:20:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bancor, the creator of a smart contract-based automated market maker, is suing Uniswap for patent infringement, alleging the decentralized finance exchange has used its technology without permission and profited significantly from it.
According to the May 20 announcement of the lawsuit, Bancor designed the technology in 2016 and patented it in January 2017. The technology underpins the “constant product automated market maker,” which involves using mathematics to add or withdraw resources from a liquidity pool. The application subsequently led to two issued patents.
Bancor alleges that Uniswap used the invention to create its protocol, launched in November 2018. The two organizations are considered competitors in the sector of decentralized finance (DeFi).
“When an organization continuousl…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Christopher Tepedino</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Securitize’s Tokenized Credit Fund Set for Solana DeFi Debut as RWA Trend Expands]]></title>
        <id>dd6c31b9-61fb-4c38-a037-82c330292bb5</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2025/05/20/apollos-tokenized-credit-fund-set-for-solana-defi-debut-as-rwa-trend-expands"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T18:52:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kamino Finance and Steakhouse Financial are teaming up to bring Securitize's ACRED token to the fast-growing Solana DeFi ecosystem.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Krisztian Sandor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The NSA Selector]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/wenzellabs/the_NSA_selector</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/wenzellabs/the_NSA_selector"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T18:30:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Red Programming Language]]></title>
        <id>https://www.red-lang.org/p/about.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.red-lang.org/p/about.html"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T18:14:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin ready to ‘vaporize’ shorts once price discovery above $110K begins]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-ready-to-vaporize-shorts-once-price-discovery-above-110k-begins</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-ready-to-vaporize-shorts-once-price-discovery-above-110k-begins?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T18:05:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Key takeaways:

An end-of-month Bitcoin price close above $102,400 would set the highest monthly close ever, proving the bull market continues at a rapid pace.

Over $3 billion in Bitcoin short positions are vulnerable above $107,000, creating a “liquidation magnet” that could send BTC price to new highs.

Bitcoin (BTC) is 11 days from potentially setting its highest monthly candle close in history. After achieving a record weekly close of $106,407 on May 18, BTC could secure a new monthly high by closing above $102,400 this month.
Bitcoin 1-month chart. Source: Cointelegraph/TradingView
With respect to its current market trend, Bitcoin is inches away from a “price discovery” period, as noted by crypto trader Jelle.
Price discovery in this context refers to the process where buyers and sel…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Biraajmaan Tamuly</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gemma 3n preview: Mobile-first AI]]></title>
        <id>https://developers.googleblog.com/en/introducing-gemma-3n/</id>
        <link href="https://developers.googleblog.com/en/introducing-gemma-3n/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T18:03:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase CEO&#039;s journey from no &#039;political causes&#039; to hiring DOGE staff]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/brian-armstrong-coinbase-political-journey</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/brian-armstrong-coinbase-political-journey?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Five years ago, Brian Armstrong wanted employees of his cryptocurrency exchange to refrain from expressing political views at work. Now, the Coinbase CEO seems to be open to involvement with Republican figures, including members of US President Donald Trump’s inner circle.
In a May 13 X post, Armstrong said members of the Department of Government Efficiency (DOGE) team, spearheaded by Elon Musk, though not set up as an actual department, would be welcome to implement cost-cutting changes at Coinbase after leaving the US government. 
Armstrong offered to set up an accelerated onboarding process with the exchange, responding to an interview in which at least one DOGE staffer felt ostracized from Harvard University, where he had been enrolled.
“If you are looking for your next mission after s…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Turner Wright</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Veo 3 and Imagen 4, and a new tool for filmmaking called Flow]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.google/technology/ai/generative-media-models-io-2025/</id>
        <link href="https://blog.google/technology/ai/generative-media-models-io-2025/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T17:46:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google just leapfrogged every competitor with mind-blowing AI that can think deeper, shop smarter, and create videos with dialogue]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008346</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/google-just-leapfrogged-every-competitor-with-mind-blowing-ai-that-can-think-deeper-shop-smarter-and-create-videos-with-dialogue/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T17:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google unveiled major AI advancements at I/O 2025, including Gemini 2.5 with Deep Think, AI Mode in Search, Veo 3 for video with audio, and a $249 Ultra plan aimed at power users and enterprises.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Nuñez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google’s Jules aims to out-code Codex in battle for the AI developer stack]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008361</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/googles-jules-aims-to-out-code-codex-in-battle-for-the-ai-developer-stack/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T17:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google released Jules, its coding agent, into beta as autonomous coding agents are quickly gaining market share.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Emilia David</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Inside Google’s AI leap: Gemini 2.5 thinks deeper, speaks smarter and codes faster]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008366</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/inside-google-ai-leap-gemini-2-5-thinks-deeper-speaks-smarter-codes-faster/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T17:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google is moving closer to its goal of autonomous agentic AI with a series of enhancements to Gemini 2.5 Pro and Flash.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Taryn Plumb</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Dawn of Nvidia's Technology]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.dshr.org/2025/05/the-dawn-of-nvidias-technology.html</id>
        <link href="https://blog.dshr.org/2025/05/the-dawn-of-nvidias-technology.html"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T17:04:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Validation Cloud Debuts Mavrik-1 AI Engine on Hedera to Democratize DeFi Data Analysis and Web3]]></title>
        <id>aa892120-4788-4a32-b30a-3103c605d77a</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/press-release/2025/05/20/emb-13-00-est-validation-cloud-debuts-mavrik-1-ai-engine-on-hedera-to-democratize-defi-data-analysis-and-web3"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T17:00:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mavrik-1 aims to lower the barrier to DeFi adoption by allowing users to access complex data without technical expertise.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Omkar Godbole</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Validation Cloud deploys Web3 AI engine on Hedera]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/validation-cloud-deploys-web3-ai-engine-hedera</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/validation-cloud-deploys-web3-ai-engine-hedera?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Artificial intelligence platform Validation Cloud has launched a new large language model on the Hedera network, potentially giving decentralized finance users the ability to reach blockchain data in a more accessible way.
The Mavrik-1 AI engine has been deployed on Hedera, with several other planned integrations expected during a public rollout later this year, Validation Cloud’s team told Cointelegraph. 
The AI engine is designed to allow users to interact with DeFi protocols and access blockchain data through natural language queries without needing technical expertise or knowledge. 
Mavrik-1 uses live onchain data trained for DeFi, stablecoins and other blockchain applications. 
Hedera DeFi metrics, including total value locked (TVL), decentralized exchange volume and stablecoin activi…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Sam Bourgi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SEC crypto task force to release first report &#039;in the next few months&#039;]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/sec-chair-paul-atkins-report-crypto-months</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/sec-chair-paul-atkins-report-crypto-months?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T16:49:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) Chair Paul Atkins appeared before lawmakers in one of his first hearings since taking the reins at the financial regulator, addressing questions about his plans for the cryptocurrency industry.
In a May 20 hearing discussing oversight of the SEC, Atkins reiterated his pledge to make regulating digital assets a “key priority” while chair. In response to questions from North Carolina Representative Chuck Edwards, the SEC chair did not directly answer how much of the regulator’s funds were used to support the crypto task force headed by Commissioner Hester Peirce, and said its findings were “still under development.”
“We should be having something here in the next few months with proposed steps forward,” said Atkins, referring to the task force’s fi…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Turner Wright</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Genesis Files Suits Against DCG to Recover Billions Worth of Allegedly Fraudulent Transfers]]></title>
        <id>803a60d0-2728-4650-a0fd-9ea08b8c46c4</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2025/05/20/genesis-files-suits-against-dcg-to-recover-billions-worth-of-allegedly-fraudulent-transfers"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T16:43:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[DCG, CEO Barry Silbert and others withdrew billions of dollars from the company they knew was failing while keeping customers in the dark, according to the lawsuits.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Camomile Shumba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SocGen’s Crypto Arm to Launch Dollar Denominated Stablecoin on Ethereum, Reports Say]]></title>
        <id>2ea339d8-43ab-4408-85cd-371da0407ef5</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/20/socgen-s-crypto-arm-to-launch-dollar-denominated-stablecoin-on-ethereum-reports-say"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T16:38:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The stablecoin, initially for institutional investors, follows the launch of SG Forge’s euro stablecoin, EURCV.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Francisco Rodrigues</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Robin: A multi-agent system for automating scientific discovery]]></title>
        <id>https://arxiv.org/abs/2505.13400</id>
        <link href="https://arxiv.org/abs/2505.13400"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T16:21:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Falters Near Record, but 'Realized Price' Analysis Suggests Optimistic Outlook]]></title>
        <id>58f97b38-7391-489b-9f47-684c4066f3b7</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/20/bitcoin-falters-near-record-but-realized-price-analysis-suggests-optimistic-outlook"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T16:20:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tracking average exchange withdrawal prices reveals signs of capitulation and a shift toward recovery.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>James Van Straten</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Argentina&#039;s Milei shuts down task force investigating LIBRA scandal]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/javier-milei-shuts-down-task-force-investigating-libra-scandal</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/javier-milei-shuts-down-task-force-investigating-libra-scandal?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T16:19:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Argentine President Javier Milei has dissolved a task force established to investigate the fallout from LIBRA, the scandalous cryptocurrency project the head of state promoted on his social media channel before it crashed to zero. 
The Investigative Task Force (ITU) was dissolved via a May 19 decree signed by Milei and Justice Minister Mariano Cúneo Libarona, government documents revealed. 
“The Research Task Unit is dissolved” after completing its mandate, the translated version of the decree read.
The task force is being dissolved despite pressure from opposition groups, which are seeking to activate an investigative commission as soon as May 20, local media outlet Clarin reported. 
A screenshot of Milei’s tweet endorsing LIBRA. Source: TRM Labs
Government officials established the UTI o…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Sam Bourgi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[XRP Price Slips as Bearish Chart Pattern Points to $2.00 Target]]></title>
        <id>fc28eaf2-9990-4b2e-88da-771f0d8cdce8</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/20/xrp-price-slips-as-bearish-chart-pattern-points-to-usd2-00-target"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T16:13:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Market sentiment shifts as XRP faces critical support test amid global economic uncertainties and upcoming token unlock.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>AI Boost</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why is Ethereum (ETH) price up today?]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/why-is-ethereum-eth-price-up-today</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/why-is-ethereum-eth-price-up-today?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T16:00:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Key takeaways:

Ether’s price rose over 5% to $2,520 on May 20, mirroring similar upward moves across the wider cryptocurrency market.

Ethereum’s record open interest, rising funding rates and a significant short squeeze fuel the rally.

A classic recovery pattern suggests a potential 92% rally toward $4,800 as ETH holds key support.

Ether (ETH) price rose by over 5% in the last 24 hours to around $2,520 on May 20 amid increasing futures open interest. 
Data from Cointelegraph Markets Pro and TradingView shows ETH gained as much as 10%, rising to an intraday high of $2,590 on May 20 from a low of $2,350 on May 19. 
ETHUSD daily chart. Source: Cointelegraph/TradingView
Ether price move mirrors marketwide recovery
ETH’s price rise on May 20 mirrors the bullish sentiment in the market that …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Yashu Gola</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GPU-Driven Clustered Forward Renderer]]></title>
        <id>https://logdahl.net/p/gpu-driven</id>
        <link href="https://logdahl.net/p/gpu-driven"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T15:57:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Milei Closes Down LIBRA Investigative Unit After It Shares Findings With Prosecutors]]></title>
        <id>9effbd9a-c483-40c0-be94-d99247e8713f</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2025/05/20/milei-closes-down-libra-investigative-unit-after-it-shares-findings-with-prosecutors"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T15:54:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The country's Department of Justice claims the investigative unit has fulfilled its purpose.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tom Carreras</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blazing-fast Solana data via gRPC: access the freshest Solana data from Shredstream leaders]]></title>
        <id>68273f14bf73460001094b35</id>
        <link href="https://blog.quicknode.com/yellowstone-grpc/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T15:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Access the fastest Solana data with the Yellowstone Geyser gRPC self-serve add-on or with the premium hybrid dedicated gRPC node.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>QuickNode</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn LangGraph and Build Conversational AI with Python]]></title>
        <id>682ca2c574938e5428551845</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-langgraph-and-build-conversational-ai-with-python/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T15:41:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you're building conversational AI and tired of messy logic or hard-to-scale workflows, LangGraph makes it easier. It uses graphs to manage dialogue flow, so your bots stay organized even as they get more complex. Great for anything from support ag...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Show HN: A Tiling Window Manager for Windows, Written in Janet]]></title>
        <id>https://agent-kilo.github.io/jwno/</id>
        <link href="https://agent-kilo.github.io/jwno/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T15:08:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The crypto market values chains more than standalone applications]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/the-crypto-market-values-chains</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/the-crypto-market-values-chains?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Opinion by: Hatu Sheikh, founder of Coin Terminal
Although blockchains and DApps are critical, crypto industry stakeholders often prioritize applications based on adoption principles and revenue distribution. DApps won't function without their underlying chains. The markets must uphold blockchains for long-term value generation.
The value perspective is wrong 
Blockchains and DApps should work collaboratively to coordinate their functions for better usability. Instead, analysts create a binary between chains and DApps based on Web2's structural frameworks.
In “Fat Protocols,” Joel Monegro argued that value within the internet stack comprises "thin" protocols and "fat" applications. In other words, investing in the underlying protocol technologies like TCP/IP, HTTP, and SMTP gives lower ret…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Hatu Sheikh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Show HN: 90s.dev – Game maker that runs on the web]]></title>
        <id>https://90s.dev/blog/finally-releasing-90s-dev.html</id>
        <link href="https://90s.dev/blog/finally-releasing-90s-dev.html"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T14:58:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[True Markets Raises $11M in Series A, Launches Mobile-First DeFi Trading App on Solana]]></title>
        <id>ff9c816c-ae17-4868-9afd-1398aa7de635</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2025/05/20/true-markets-raises-11m-in-series-a-launches-mobile-first-defi-trading-app-on-solana"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The funding round was co-led by Accomplice and RRE Ventures, with participation from Reciprocal Ventures, Variant Fund and PayPal Ventures.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Will Canny</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Senate stablecoin vote splits Democrats amid concerns over corruption]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/senate-stablecoin-vote-democrats-corruption</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/senate-stablecoin-vote-democrats-corruption?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T13:59:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[US Senate Democrats are getting flak after they helped move stablecoin legislation ahead for discussion on the Senate floor.
On May 19, 16 Democratic senators broke from the party line to pass a motion to invoke cloture, which will now set the bill up for debate on the Senate floor. Some of the same Democrats had held up the bill in early May when they withdrew support, citing corruption concerns over President Donald Trump’s cryptocurrency dealings.
The bill’s opponents hailed lawmakers’ refusal to support it but were soon taken aback when the senators reversed their position. The lightly amended legislation contained no provisions regarding World Liberty Financial, the Trump family’s crypto venture.
Some activists have said that the Democrats supporting the bill should be ousted in the u…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Aaron Wood</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Deep Learning Is Applied Topology]]></title>
        <id>https://theahura.substack.com/p/deep-learning-is-applied-topology</id>
        <link href="https://theahura.substack.com/p/deep-learning-is-applied-topology"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T13:54:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Robinhood proposes SEC rules for tokenized real-world assets]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/robinhood-sec-tokenized-rwa-framework-proposal</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/robinhood-sec-tokenized-rwa-framework-proposal?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T13:50:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Robinhood submitted a 42-page proposal to the US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC), calling for a national framework to regulate tokenized real-world assets (RWAs).
The brokerage is seeking to modernize financial infrastructure by making tokenized assets legally equivalent to their traditional counterparts and enabling compliant onchain settlement, Forbes reported on May 20.
In the proposal, Robinhood also revealed plans for creating the Real World Asset Exchange (RRE), a trading platform offering offchain trade matching and onchain settlement for efficiency and transparency.
Robinhood is advocating for uniform federal standards to replace the patchwork of state-level securities regulations that currently apply. The platform would also integrate Know Your Customer (KYC) and Anti-Mon…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Amin Haqshanas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kraken expands in Europe with regulated crypto derivatives]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/kraken-launches-regulated-crypto-derivatives-europe</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/kraken-launches-regulated-crypto-derivatives-europe?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T13:46:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency exchange Kraken announced the launch of regulated derivatives trading on its platform under the European Union’s Markets in Financial Instruments Directive (MiFID II).
According to a May 20 announcement, Kraken’s perpetual and fixed maturity crypto futures contracts will be available for trading by retail and institutional customers in the European Economic Area (EEA). The announcement follows the exchange acquiring an MiFID license in early February through the acquisition of a Cypriot investment firm, approved by the Cyprus Securities and Exchange Commission.
Kraken’s head of exchange, Shannon Kurtas, said, “Europe is one of the fastest-growing regions for digital asset trading and investment, with some of the most sophisticated and demanding clients and institutions.” 
He…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Adrian Zmudzinski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CoinDesk 20 Performance Update: Litecoin (LTC) Drops 6.1%, Leading Index Lower]]></title>
        <id>c2c714df-3207-4be7-badd-50c5dd6f050e</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/coindesk-indices/2025/05/20/coindesk-20-performance-update-litecoin-ltc-drops-6-1-leading-index-lower"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T13:29:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Filecoin (FIL) was also among the underperformers, declining 2.9% from Monday.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CoinDesk Indices</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Circle co-founder to create ‘AI-native’ bank after $18M raise]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/catena-labs-raises-18m-ai-native-financial-institution</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/catena-labs-raises-18m-ai-native-financial-institution?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T13:25:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Circle co-founder and Catena Labs CEO Sean Neville has launched a project that aims to develop a financial institution that natively leverages artificial intelligence. 
On May 20, Catena Labs, the company building an “AI-native financial institution,” announced that it secured $18 million in a funding round led by Andreessen Horowitz (a16z) Crypto, a16z’s crypto and Web3 venture capital arm. 
Led by Neville, the company aims to realize its vision of a fully regulated financial institution for the AI economy. The company said it will be built for AI agents and human collaborators and will be operated by AI workers with human oversight and AI-specific risk management and compliance approaches. 
Cointelegraph contacted Catena Labs to get more information about the project but received no resp…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Ezra Reguerra</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[German gov’t missed out on $2.3B profit after selling Bitcoin at $57K]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/german-gov-t-missed-2-3b-bitcoin-profit-sold-btc-57k</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/german-gov-t-missed-2-3b-bitcoin-profit-sold-btc-57k?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T13:17:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The German government missed out on more than $2 billion worth of Bitcoin profit after selling its holdings in 2024, according to blockchain intelligence firm Arkham.
A “German Government (BKA)” labeled cryptocurrency wallet sold 49,858 Bitcoin (BTC) worth over $2.89 billion at an average price of $57,900 across multiple transactions during June and July in 2024.
The decision to sell the Bitcoin early cost the German government over $2.35 billion, according to crypto intelligence platform Arkham.
Source: Arkham 

“If they had held it, their BTC would now be worth $5.24B,” Arkham said in a May 19 X post, noting that Bitcoin has risen more than 80% since the sale.
At the time of publication, Bitcoin was trading at more than $104,700, according to CoinMarketCap data.  
Related: Justin Sun off…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Zoltan Vardai</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Clojuring the web application stack: Meditation One]]></title>
        <id>https://www.evalapply.org/posts/clojure-web-app-from-scratch/index.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.evalapply.org/posts/clojure-web-app-from-scratch/index.html"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T13:15:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[KULR Boosts Bitcoin Treasury to 800 BTC With $9M Purchase]]></title>
        <id>d964e4f0-9c2b-4078-a3c0-bdd8725c29eb</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/20/kulr-boosts-bitcoin-treasury-to-800-btc-with-usd9m-purchase"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T13:06:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This latest acquisition was made at an average purchase price of $103,234 per bitcoin.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Francisco Rodrigues</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Government-Backed Funds Expanding MSTR Holdings Show Rising BTC Demand: Standard Chartered]]></title>
        <id>d3bcbe9c-bbb5-4cac-9821-7ea53bff1716</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/20/widening-government-strategy-holdings-suggest-increased-structural-demand-for-btc-stanchart"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T13:03:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Holdings of the stock by government bodies reflects a desire to gain bitcoin exposure where in some cases local regulators do not allow direct ownership, the report said.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Will Canny</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Avalanche-backed Fusion launches with $100M to boost blockchain adoption]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/fusion-blockchain-initiative-100m-modular-sector-networks</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/fusion-blockchain-initiative-100m-modular-sector-networks?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T12:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Avalanche, Helix and Faculty Group have launched Fusion,  a new blockchain ecosystem aimed at driving real-world adoption through modular infrastructure tailored to specific industries.
Built on Avalanche, Fusion features a two-layer architecture that includes composers, customizable layer-1 networks and modules, which offer plug-and-play services like compute, identity and data oracles. 
The team said this approach would be the answer for mainstream adoption, as they attempt to deliver “outcome-driven, domain-specific” blockchain-based economies. 
“In order to achieve widespread adoption, our industry needs to shift from selling blockspace to delivering business value,” a Fusion spokesperson told Cointelegraph. They added that Fusion integrates economic alignment, network design and compo…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Ezra Reguerra</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[India’s Supreme Court urges government to regulate cryptocurrency]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/india-s-surpeme-court-asks-government-for-clearer-crypto-stance</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/india-s-surpeme-court-asks-government-for-clearer-crypto-stance?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T12:18:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[India’s Supreme Court questioned the government’s lack of regulatory clarity on cryptocurrencies despite imposing taxes on digital assets like Bitcoin.
According to the Indian legal news outlet LawChakra, the country’s Supreme Court expressed concern over the increasing use of Bitcoin (BTC) and other cryptocurrencies, which remain largely unregulated.
“This is a whole parallel economy running with such coins, and it is a danger to the economy of the country,” Justice Surya Kant reportedly said during a recent hearing related to an ongoing investigation into a Bitcoin transaction.
Kant said that while the government has implemented crypto taxation, it has failed to regulate the space.
“If you can tax it at 30%, also please regulate it as you have recognised it by taxing it,” the judge said.…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Adrian Zmudzinski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Download: introducing the AI energy package]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1117051</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/05/20/1117051/the-download-introducing-the-ai-energy-package/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T12:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is today’s edition of The Download, our weekday newsletter that provides a daily dose of what’s going on in the world of technology. We did the math on AI’s energy footprint. Here’s the story you haven’t heard. It’s well documented that AI is a power-hungry technology. But there has been far less reporting on the extent…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rhiannon Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Strategy's STRK Hits Record Proceeds, Has Outperformed Bitcoin, S&P 500 Since Debut]]></title>
        <id>d59329ed-578b-4a33-b319-74edc3bcf18e</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/20/strategys-strk-hits-record-proceeds-has-outperformed-bitcoin-sp-500-since-debut"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T12:08:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[STRK has risen more than bitcoin and the S&P 500 index while offering an attractive yield and differentiated market exposure.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>James Van Straten</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kraken Rolls Out Regulated Crypto Derivatives in Europe]]></title>
        <id>a5b7fe63-c0e0-47db-8626-931da7ef3431</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2025/05/20/kraken-rolls-out-regulated-crypto-derivatives-in-europe"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kraken is offering derivatives trading in digital assets, compliant with Europe's Markets in Financial Instruments Directive (MiFIDII).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ian Allison</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ether Is Set to Explode as Traders Pump Millions Into $6K ETH Bets]]></title>
        <id>7c0eb330-38c9-46bb-9054-521ee57be70f</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/20/ether-is-set-to-explode-as-traders-pump-millions-into-usd6k-eth-bets"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T11:45:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto traders are betting on Ethereum's ether to reach $6,000 by Dec. 26 through bull call spreads.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Omkar Godbole</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why does the U.S. always run a trade deficit?]]></title>
        <id>https://libertystreeteconomics.newyorkfed.org/2025/05/why-does-the-u-s-always-run-a-trade-deficit/</id>
        <link href="https://libertystreeteconomics.newyorkfed.org/2025/05/why-does-the-u-s-always-run-a-trade-deficit/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T11:42:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Can't India Draft a Clear Cut Crypto Policy? Country's Supreme Court Raps Government]]></title>
        <id>caadec88-a528-4a6b-9a2f-1b8c183cf631</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2025/05/20/why-cant-india-draft-a-clear-cut-crypto-policy-countrys-supreme-court-raps-government"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T11:32:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Supreme court justice Surya Kant and N Kotiswar Singh said that there is "parallel under-market" for crypto that can affect the economy.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Crawley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Daybook Americas: Bitcoin Stability Above $100K Is Cementing New Psychological Floor]]></title>
        <id>a69bb9a3-a3fb-4369-ae61-7c736d3efee7</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/daybook-us/2025/05/20/crypto-daybook-americas-bitcoin-stability-above-100k-is-cementing-new-psychological-floor"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T11:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Your day-ahead look for May 20, 2025]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Omkar Godbole</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Binance seeks to dismiss $1.76B FTX lawsuit, blames SBF for collapse]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/binance-seeks-dismissal-ftx-1-76b-lawsuit</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/binance-seeks-dismissal-ftx-1-76b-lawsuit?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T11:12:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Binance has filed a motion to dismiss a $1.76 billion lawsuit brought by the FTX estate, accusing the defunct crypto exchange of trying to deflect blame for its own failure.
Filed on May 16 in the Delaware Bankruptcy Court, Binance’s legal team called the suit “legally deficient,” stating that FTX’s collapse was not triggered by market manipulation or hostile action but by internal misconduct.
“Plaintiffs are pretending that FTX did not collapse as the result of one of the most massive corporate frauds in history,” the filing said, pointing to Sam “SBF” Bankman-Fried’s conviction on seven counts of fraud and conspiracy.
FTX’s estate alleges that Binance received billions in crypto during a 2021 buyback deal, funded improperly with customer assets.
Binance rejects this claim, stating that “…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Amin Haqshanas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin privacy tool Payjoin receives $100K grant from Maelstrom]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-payjoin-privacy-grant-maelstrom</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-payjoin-privacy-grant-maelstrom?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T10:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin developer Ben Allen has received a $100,000 grant from investment firm Maelstrom to support the development of Payjoin, a privacy-focused tool aimed at improving Bitcoin’s scalability and privacy.
According to a May 20 announcement shared with Cointelegraph, Maelstrom will finance Allen’s work on his Payjoin devkit alongside Dan Gould. The system allows Bitcoin (BTC) senders and receivers to use batched transactions, with positive implications for scalability and privacy.
Payjoin Developer Kit’s website. Source: Payjoin Dev Kit
Payjoin was first proposed by Nicolas Dorier in 2019 in Bitcoin improvement proposal (BIP) 78. The core principle behind the system is that both senders and receivers may contribute inputs to a transaction.
“Namely that privacy is enhanced and improved conso…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Adrian Zmudzinski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin is signaling a golden cross — What does it mean for BTC price?]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-golden-cross-what-does-it-mean-for-btc-price</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-golden-cross-what-does-it-mean-for-btc-price?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T10:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Key takeaways:

Bitcoin is nearing a golden cross that has led to 45%–60% price rallies in the recent past.

Fundamentals like rising M2 supply and easing trade tensions support a bullish outlook.

Bearish divergence and overbought conditions show there’s still a risk of BTC falling below $100,000.

Bitcoin (BTC) will likely confirm a “golden cross” on its daily chart by the end of May, a technical pattern whose occurrences in recent years often preceded rallies.
Source: Benjamin Cowen
Previous golden crosses led to 45%-60% BTC price rallies
As of May 20, Bitcoin’s 50-day simple moving average (50-day SMA; the red wave) was eyeing a close above its 200-day SMA (the blue wave) for the first time since October 2024, forming a golden cross.
BTC/USD daily price chart. Source: TradingView
Previ…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Yashu Gola</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AI's energy footprint]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/05/20/1116327/ai-energy-usage-climate-footprint-big-tech/</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/05/20/1116327/ai-energy-usage-climate-footprint-big-tech/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T10:07:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Solana Surges 6% on Bullish Reversal and DeFi Demand]]></title>
        <id>e2865e87-b973-40cc-84e2-3f56b9aa77ce</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/20/solana-sol-surges-6-on-bullish-reversal-and-defi-activity-toward-usd180"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T10:05:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SOL shows strong momentum with institutional buying signals despite brief correction.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>AI Boost</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Circle Has Explored Potential $5B Sale to Coinbase or Ripple Instead of IPO: Report]]></title>
        <id>7c37af0e-4b3d-4a8b-b779-bacd1af82266</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2025/05/20/circle-has-explored-potential-5b-sale-to-coinbase-or-ripple-instead-of-ipo-report"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T10:02:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The stablecoin issuer took part in informal talks over a potential sale from which it was seeking at least $5 billion.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Crawley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase data leak could put users in physical danger: TechCrunch founder]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/coinbase-breach-physical-crime-techcrunch-founder</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/coinbase-breach-physical-crime-techcrunch-founder?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T10:02:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A recent data breach at crypto exchange Coinbase has raised concerns about user safety after hackers gained access to sensitive information, including home addresses.
Coinbase, the world’s third-largest cryptocurrency exchange, confirmed that less than 1% of its transacting monthly users were affected in an attack that may cost the exchange up to $400 million in reimbursement expenses, Cointelegraph reported on May 15.
However, the “human cost” of this data breach may be much higher for users, according to Michael Arrington, the founder of TechCrunch and Arrington Capital.
“Very disappointed in Coinbase right now. Using the cheapest option for customer service has its price,” Arrington said in a May 20 X post, adding:
“Something that has to be said though - this hack - which includes home …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Zoltan Vardai</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[RWA Platform TokenFi Is Tokenizing the Floki Minibot]]></title>
        <id>f1fda8ea-0df9-4429-8f17-f3e866f4f48a</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/20/rwa-platform-tokenfi-is-tokenizing-the-floki-minibot"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A presale for the Floki Minibot M1 AI robot, made by Rice Robotics, starts May 23, the same day TokenFi’s real-world asset tokenization module goes live.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shaurya Malwa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SHIB Jumps Nearly 7% as Bulls Break Through Resistance on Heavy Buying]]></title>
        <id>81593e19-efce-4331-8328-844c196a2a77</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/20/shib-jumps-nearly-7-as-bulls-break-through-resistance-on-heavy-buying"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T09:47:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The popular meme token shows remarkable resilience despite 80% of holders underwater on their investments.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>AI Boost</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AI could keep us dependent on natural gas for decades to come]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1116272</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/05/20/1116272/ai-natural-gas-data-centers-energy-power-plants/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The thousands of sprawling acres in rural northeast Louisiana had gone unwanted for nearly two decades. Louisiana authorities bought the land in Richland Parish in 2006 to promote economic development in one of the poorest regions in the state. For years, they marketed the former agricultural fields as the Franklin Farm mega site, first to…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Rotman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AI’s energy impact is still small—but how we handle it is huge]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1116274</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/05/20/1116274/opinion-ai-energy-use-data-centers-electricity/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With seemingly no limit to the demand for artificial intelligence, everyone in the energy, AI, and climate fields is justifiably worried. Will there be enough clean electricity to power AI and enough water to cool the data centers that support this technology? These are important questions with serious implications for communities, the economy, and the…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Costa Samaras, Emma Strubell, Ramayya Krishnan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The data center boom in the desert]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1116287</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/05/20/1116287/ai-data-centers-nevada-water-reno-computing-environmental-impact/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the high desert east of Reno, Nevada, construction crews are flattening the golden foothills of the Virginia Range, laying the foundations of a data center city. Google, Tract, Switch, EdgeCore, Novva, Vantage, and PowerHouse are all operating, building, or expanding huge facilities within the Tahoe Reno Industrial Center, a business park bigger than the…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>James Temple</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[We did the math on AI’s energy footprint. Here’s the story you haven’t heard.]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1116327</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/05/20/1116327/ai-energy-usage-climate-footprint-big-tech/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The emissions from individual AI text, image, and video queries seem small—until you add up what the industry isn’t tracking and consider where it’s heading next.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>James O'Donnell, Casey Crownhart</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Everything you need to know about estimating AI’s energy and emissions burden]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1116331</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/05/20/1116331/ai-energy-demand-methodology/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When we set out to write a story on the best available estimates for AI’s energy and emissions burden, we knew there would be caveats and uncertainties to these numbers. But, we quickly discovered, the caveats are the story too.  This story is a part of MIT Technology Review’s series “Power Hungry: AI and our…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>James O'Donnell, Casey Crownhart</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Four reasons to be optimistic about AI’s energy usage]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1116337</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/05/20/1116337/ai-energy-use-optimism/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The day after his inauguration in January, President Donald Trump announced Stargate, a $500 billion initiative to build out AI infrastructure, backed by some of the biggest companies in tech. Stargate aims to accelerate the construction of massive data centers and electricity networks across the US to ensure it keeps its edge over China. This…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Will Douglas Heaven</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Can nuclear power really fuel the rise of AI?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1116339</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/05/20/1116339/ai-nuclear-power-energy-reactors/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the AI arms race, all the major players say they want to go nuclear.   Over the past year, the likes of Meta, Amazon, Microsoft, and Google have sent out a flurry of announcements related to nuclear energy. Some are about agreements to purchase power from existing plants, while others are about investments looking to…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Casey Crownhart</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How AI is introducing errors into courtrooms]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1116823</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/05/20/1116823/how-ai-is-introducing-errors-into-courtrooms/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s been quite a couple weeks for stories about AI in the courtroom. You might have heard about the deceased victim of a road rage incident whose family created an AI avatar of him to show as an impact statement (possibly the first time this has been done in the US). But there’s a bigger,…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>James O'Donnell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft just launched an AI that discovered a new chemical in 200 hours instead of years]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008310</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/microsoft-just-launched-an-ai-that-discovered-a-new-chemical-in-200-hours-instead-of-years/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T18:34:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft launches Discovery platform that uses agentic AI to compress years of scientific research into days, transforming R&D across pharmaceuticals, materials science, and semiconductor industries.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Nuñez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Is your AI app pissing off users or going off-script? Raindrop emerges with AI-native observability platform to monitor performance]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008299</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/is-your-ai-app-pissing-off-users-or-going-off-script-raindrop-emerges-with-ai-native-observability-platform-to-monitor-performance/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T18:09:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With its rebrand and product expansion, Raindrop is betting that the next generation of software observability will be AI-first by design.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carl Franzen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Writing into Uninitialized Buffers in Rust]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.sunfishcode.online/writingintouninitializedbuffersinrust/</id>
        <link href="https://blog.sunfishcode.online/writingintouninitializedbuffersinrust/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T17:56:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft just taught its AI agents to talk to each other—and it could transform how we work]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008254</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/microsoft-just-taught-its-ai-agents-to-talk-to-each-other-and-it-could-transform-how-we-work/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T16:01:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft unveils multi-agent systems, WhatsApp integration, and Python-powered analytics for Copilot Studio at Build 2025, transforming how enterprises build and deploy AI solutions.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Nuñez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Microsoft Fabric has already been adopted by 70% of the Fortune 500 — and what’s next]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3007980</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/70-of-the-fortune-500-already-use-microsoft-fabric-and-its-now-getting-even-more-features-including-cosmosdb-support/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft integrates CosmosDB into Fabric, open sources DiskANN vector search, and unifies its data platforms to eliminate integration complexity that has slowed enterprise AI adoption.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sean Michael Kerner</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub Copilot evolves into autonomous agent with asynchronous code testing]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008231</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/github-copilot-evolves-into-autonomous-agent-with-asynchronous-code-testing/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub adds agentic capabilities to its Copilot coding assistant, competing with other more asynchronous coding platforms.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Emilia David</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft announces over 50 AI tools to build the ‘agentic web’ at Build 2025]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008229</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/microsoft-announces-over-50-ai-tools-to-build-the-agentic-web-at-build-2025/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T15:59:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft reveals its ambitious AI agent strategy, showcasing how multi-agent systems with persistent memory will transform enterprise workflows and accelerate development timelines.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Nuñez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Reddit, Webflow, and Superhuman are already customers—now GrowthX has $12M to grow]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008276</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/reddit-webflow-and-superhuman-are-already-customers-now-growthx-has-12m-to-grow/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[GrowthX secures $12M in funding for its "service-as-software" platform that combines AI with human expertise to boost content marketing results by up to 300%.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Nuñez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AI can do a better job of persuading people than we do]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1116779</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/05/19/1116779/ai-can-do-a-better-job-of-persuading-people-than-we-do/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Millions of people argue with each other online every day, but remarkably few of them change someone’s mind. New research suggests that large language models (LLMs) might do a better job. The finding suggests that AI could become a powerful tool for persuading people, for better or worse.   A multi-university team of researchers found that…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rhiannon Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Cybercriminals Crack Your Passwords (And How to Stay One Step Ahead)]]></title>
        <id>682b3930e99a22ce9f9199c8</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-cybercriminals-crack-your-passwords-and-how-to-stay-one-step-ahead/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T13:59:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Passwords are the keys to your digital life  –  email, bank accounts, social media, and even your workplace systems. Unfortunately, they’re also one of the weakest links in cybersecurity.  Every year, billions of credentials are stolen and sold on th...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Manish Shivanandhan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Quantum Machines launches Qualibrate open source framework to speed quantum computer calibration]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008032</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/games/quantum-machines-launches-qualibrate-open-source-framework-to-speed-quantum-computer-calibration/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Quantum Machines, a provider of advanced hybrid quantum-classical control solutions, announced today the release of Qualibrate.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dean Takahashi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Samsung boosts OLED TV gaming with Nvidia G-Sync compatibility]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008019</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/games/samsung-boosts-oled-tv-gaming-with-nvidia-g-sync-compatibility/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Samsung said its 2025 OLED TV lineup will feature Nvidia G-Sync compatibility, delivering smooth gameplay, low latency, and more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dean Takahashi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Salesforce just unveiled AI ‘digital teammates’ in Slack — and they’re coming for Microsoft Copilot]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008273</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/salesforce-just-unveiled-ai-digital-teammates-in-slack-and-theyre-coming-for-microsoft-copilot/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Salesforce launches Agentforce in Slack, transforming workplace productivity with specialized AI agents that operate as digital teammates, replacing one-size-fits-all AI assistants with purpose-built solutions.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Nuñez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Foxconn builds AI factory in partnership with Taiwan and Nvidia]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008261</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/games/foxconn-builds-ai-factory-in-partnership-with-taiwan-and-nvidia/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T07:14:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nvidia and Foxconn announced they are working with the Taiwan government to build an AI factory supercomputer.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dean Takahashi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nvidia launches AI-first DGX Personal Computing Systems]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008256</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/games/nvidia-launches-ai-first-dgx-personal-computing-systems/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T07:06:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nvidia announced that Taiwan’s leading system manufacturers are set to build Nvidia DGX Spark and DGX Station systems.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dean Takahashi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nvidia-powered supercomputer to enable quantum leap for Taiwan’s research]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008257</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/games/nvidia-powered-supercomputer-to-enable-quantum-leap-for-taiwans-research/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T06:58:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nvidia is powering a supercomputer at Taiwan’s National Center for High-Performance Computing that’s set to deliver over eight times more AI performance than before.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dean Takahashi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nvidia powers world’s largest quantum research supercomputer]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008248</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/games/nvidia-powers-worlds-largest-quantum-research-supercomputer/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T06:48:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nvidia announced the opening of the Global Research and Development Center for Business by Quantum-AI Technology.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dean Takahashi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nvidia provides Omniverse Blueprint for AI factory digital twins]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008243</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/games/nvidia-provides-omniverse-blueprint-for-ai-factory-digital-twins/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T06:34:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nvidia today announced a significant expansion of the Nvidia Omniverse Blueprint for AI factory digital twins, now available as a preview.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dean Takahashi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Linguists find proof of sweeping language pattern once deemed a 'hoax']]></title>
        <id>https://www.scientificamerican.com/article/linguists-find-proof-of-sweeping-language-pattern-once-deemed-a-hoax/</id>
        <link href="https://www.scientificamerican.com/article/linguists-find-proof-of-sweeping-language-pattern-once-deemed-a-hoax/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T06:23:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nvidia charges ahead with humanoid robotics aided by the cloud]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008144</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/games/nvidia-charges-ahead-with-humanoid-robotics-aided-by-the-cloud/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T06:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nvidia said it is racing ahead with humanoid robotics technology, providing more Blackwell systems to accelerate humanoid robot development.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dean Takahashi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Magic of software; what makes a good engineer also makes a good engineering org]]></title>
        <id>https://moxie.org/2024/09/23/a-good-engineer.html</id>
        <link href="https://moxie.org/2024/09/23/a-good-engineer.html"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T05:26:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[From dot-com to dot-AI: How we can learn from the last tech transformation (and avoid making the same mistakes)]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3007969</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/from-dot-com-to-dot-ai-how-we-can-learn-from-the-last-tech-transformation-and-avoid-making-the-same-mistakes/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-18T19:05:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The AI winners won’t be the ones slapping “AI” on a landing page — they’ll be creating products enterprises can't live without.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kailiang Fu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Building my own solar power system]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/@joe_5312/pg-e-sucks-or-how-i-learned-to-stop-worrying-and-love-building-my-own-solar-system-acf0c9f03f3b</id>
        <link href="https://medium.com/@joe_5312/pg-e-sucks-or-how-i-learned-to-stop-worrying-and-love-building-my-own-solar-system-acf0c9f03f3b"/>
        <updated>2025-05-18T18:07:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Taito-tastic: Kiki Kaikai and its Hardware]]></title>
        <id>https://nicole.express/2025/pocky-but-wheres-rocky.html</id>
        <link href="https://nicole.express/2025/pocky-but-wheres-rocky.html"/>
        <updated>2025-05-18T14:55:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gail Wellington, former Commodore executive, has died]]></title>
        <id>https://www.legacy.com/us/obituaries/name/gail-wellington-obituary?id=58418580</id>
        <link href="https://www.legacy.com/us/obituaries/name/gail-wellington-obituary?id=58418580"/>
        <updated>2025-05-17T21:27:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Adopting agentic AI? Build AI fluency, redesign workflows, don’t neglect supervision]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3007933</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/adopting-agentic-ai-build-ai-fluency-redesign-workflows-dont-neglect-supervision/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-17T19:05:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How can organizations decide how to use human-in-the-loop mechanisms and collaborative frameworks with AI agents?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Imran Aftab, 10Pearls</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ask HN: Conversational AI to Learn a Language]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=44012549</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=44012549"/>
        <updated>2025-05-17T07:02:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[My favourite fonts to use with LaTeX (2022)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lfe.pt/latex/fonts/typography/2022/11/21/latex-fonts-part1.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.lfe.pt/latex/fonts/typography/2022/11/21/latex-fonts-part1.html"/>
        <updated>2025-05-17T02:53:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google’s AlphaEvolve: The AI agent that reclaimed 0.7% of Google’s compute – and how to copy it]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3007997</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/googles-alphaevolve-the-ai-agent-that-reclaimed-0-7-of-googles-compute-and-how-to-copy-it/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-17T00:31:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google's AlphaEvolve is the epitome of a best-practice AI agent orchestration. It offers a lesson in production-grade agent engineering. Discover its architecture & essential takeaways for your enterprise AI strategy.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matt Marshall</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New stem cell model sheds light on human amniotic sac development]]></title>
        <id>https://www.crick.ac.uk/news/2025-05-15_new-stem-cell-model-sheds-light-on-human-amniotic-sac-development</id>
        <link href="https://www.crick.ac.uk/news/2025-05-15_new-stem-cell-model-sheds-light-on-human-amniotic-sac-development"/>
        <updated>2025-05-17T00:18:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Shrink exploit windows, slash MTTP: Why ring deployment is now a must for enterprise defense]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3007233</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/security/slash-mttp-block-exploits-ring-deployment-now-essential/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-16T20:48:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ring deployment slashes MTTP and legacy CVE risk. Learn how Ivanti and Southstar Bank are modernizing patch strategy with real-time intel.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Louis Columbus</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Extend Power Apps with Reusable Components]]></title>
        <id>682779afad5694b25984f6b1</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/powerapps-component-crash-course/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-16T17:45:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you have experience in traditional software development, low-code tools may feel a bit sparse at first. But to many people’s surprise, traditional techniques often translate quite well to low-code development. Not always one-for-one – but usually ...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brandon Wozniewicz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Write Math Equations in Google Docs]]></title>
        <id>68275cf15ed8a1db0cf8769b</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/write-math-equations-in-google-docs/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-16T15:42:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Math equations are a critical part of academic papers, research reports, and technical documentation. While LaTeX is widely used for professional typesetting, Google Docs offers a robust set of features for inserting and formatting math equations and...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Vikram Aruchamy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OpenAI launches research preview of Codex AI software engineering agent for developers — with parallel tasking]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3007915</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/programming-development/openai-launches-research-preview-of-codex-ai-software-engineering-agent-for-developers-with-parallel-tasking/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-16T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Starting today it will be available as a research preview for ChatGPT Pro, Enterprise, and Team users, with support later for Plus and Edu.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carl Franzen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Acer unveils AI-powered wearables at Computex 2025]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3007872</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/games/acer-unveils-ai-powered-wearables-at-computex-2025/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-16T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Acer Gadget, a subsidiary of Acer, unveiled AI-powered wearables at the Computex 2025 trade show in Taiwan.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dean Takahashi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to make Developer Friends When You Don't Live in Silicon Valley, with Iraqi Engineer Code;Life [Podcast #172]]]></title>
        <id>68271ae2c90fa4a071c44a2b</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-make-developer-friends-when-you-dont-live-in-silicon-valley-with-iraqi-engineer-codelife-podcast-172/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-16T11:00:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On this week's episode of the podcast, freeCodeCamp founder Quincy Larson interviews software engineer and live coding streamer Code;Life.   For those of you watching the video version of this interview, she lives in Iraq and she uses a 3D avatar to ...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elon Musk’s xAI tries to explain Grok’s South African race relations freakout the other day]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3007876</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/elon-musks-xai-tries-to-explain-groks-south-african-race-relations-freakout-the-other-day/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-16T02:47:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With its prompts now public and a team of human babysitters on call, Grok is supposedly back on script. But the incident underscores...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carl Franzen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn A1 Level Spanish]]></title>
        <id>68269a8eb0cc91a6c87a682d</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-a1-level-spanish/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-16T01:53:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learning a new language can open doors to new cultures, connections, and opportunities, and Spanish is one of the most widely spoken languages in the world. Whether you're dreaming of traveling to Spanish-speaking countries, connecting with Spanish-s...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Software engineering-native AI models have arrived: What Windsurf’s SWE-1 means for technical decision-makers]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3007851</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/software-engineering-native-ai-models-have-arrived-what-windsurfs-swe-1-means-for-technical-decision-makers/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-16T00:30:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Windsurf's new SWE-1 AI models tackle the complete software engineering workflow, potentially reducing development cycles and technical debt.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sean Michael Kerner</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is Sui: A Comprehensive Guide to Web3 Scalability]]></title>
        <id>6823533984101f00013a5ca4</id>
        <link href="https://blog.quicknode.com/what-is-sui-a-comprehensive-guide-to-web3-scalability/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-15T23:34:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Explore how Sui Network achieves 300,000 TPS through parallel processing, and its applications in gaming, DeFi, and supply chain management.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>QuickNode</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AI Meets Blockchain: Transforming Technology for the Next Era]]></title>
        <id>682354c584101f00013a5cb9</id>
        <link href="https://blog.quicknode.com/ai-and-blockchain-transforming-technology-together/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-15T23:34:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discover how AI and blockchain integration enhances security, efficiency, and innovation in healthcare, supply chains, and financial services.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>QuickNode</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Adventure Layer: AI Native Onchain Games, Unleashed]]></title>
        <id>6824c55abf73460001094973</id>
        <link href="https://blog.quicknode.com/adventure-layer-launches-on-quicknode-raas/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-15T12:04:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Adventure Layer launches layer-2 chain leveraging QuickNode's Rollup-as-a-Service (RaaS) product.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>QuickNode</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How DNS Works: A Guide to Understanding the Internet's Address Book]]></title>
        <id>6824f1ac04a60b4a58654ddc</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-dns-works-the-internets-address-book/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-14T19:40:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Domain Name System (DNS) translates domain names (like example.com) into IP addresses (like 192.0.2.1) so we can easily access websites. In this guide, you’ll learn how DNS resolution starts, its step-by-step process, how caching works, and the r...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dhruv Prajapati</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Load Balancing with Azure Application Gateway and Azure Load Balancer – When to Use Each One]]></title>
        <id>6824f10a7d203c180e5ea4b2</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/load-balancing-with-azure-application-gateway-and-azure-load-balancer/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-14T19:37:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You’ve probably heard someone mention load balancing when talking about cloud apps. Maybe even names like Azure Load Balancer, Azure Application Gateway, or something about Virtual Machines and Scale Sets. 😵‍💫 It all sounds important...but also a l...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Prince Onukwili</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build Slim and Fast Docker Images with Multi-Stage Builds]]></title>
        <id>6824b1638a2b26e9d2d0fe86</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-slim-fast-docker-images-with-multi-stage-builds/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-14T15:06:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Apps don’t stay simple forever. More features mean more dependencies, slower builds, and heavier Docker images. That’s where things start to hurt. Docker helps, but without the right setup, your builds can quickly get bloated. Multi-stage builds make...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniel Adeboye</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn Vite for a Better Web Development Workflow]]></title>
        <id>6824ae178a2b26e9d2d0fe4c</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-vite-for-a-better-web-development-workflow/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-14T14:52:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Speed and simplicity are at the heart of modern web development. As applications grow more complex and the demand for rapid iteration increases, developers are constantly searching for tools that minimize friction and maximize productivity. Tradition...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[QuickLee V2: An Improved Transparent Look into RPC Provider Latency]]></title>
        <id>680fc8e1f8ae810001969b47</id>
        <link href="https://blog.quicknode.com/quicklee-v2/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-14T13:57:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[View public and real-time dashboards to better understand latency and speed when evaluating RPC providers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>QuickNode</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Breathe lands $21M Series B to predict battery performance]]></title>
        <id>https://techcrunch.com/?p=3003769</id>
        <link href="https://techcrunch.com/2025/05/07/breathe-lands-21m-series-b-to-predict-battery-performance/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-07T12:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Breathe has developed a suite of tools that it says helps automakers and others get the most out of their batteries.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tim De Chant</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>