<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2025-06-10T23:13:09.918Z</id>
    <title>AngJianming RSS Feed</title>
    <updated>2025-06-10T23:13:09.918Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[quieressermisanvalentin]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/andriwil_590ab7253167fb02/quieressermisanvalentin-4fcc</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/andriwil_590ab7253167fb02/quieressermisanvalentin-4fcc"/>
        <updated>2025-06-10T23:03:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[__Check out this Pen I made!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andriwil</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[QuCode - 21DaysChallenge - Day 10]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/paulobmsousa/qucode-21dayschallenge-day-10-504m</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/paulobmsousa/qucode-21dayschallenge-day-10-504m"/>
        <updated>2025-06-10T23:01:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Day 10 - Quantum Superposition & Interference
Code:
https://github.com/paulobmsousa/QuCode_21DaysChallenge/blob/main/QuCode_Day10_QuantumSuperposition_Interference_Ex1.py]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paulo B.M. Sousa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Check Every Key Exists in a PHP Array with Arr::hasAll()]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/ashallendesign/check-every-key-exists-in-a-php-array-with-arrhasall-4hef</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/ashallendesign/check-every-key-exists-in-a-php-array-with-arrhasall-4hef"/>
        <updated>2025-06-10T23:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction


In Laravel 12.16, a new hasAll method was added to the Illuminate\Support\Arr class. The Arr::hasAll method allows you to check if all specified keys exist in an array, making it easy to validate the presence of multiple keys at once.
The method was contributed by @devajmeireles in PR #55815.
In this Quickfire article, I'm going to show you how to use the Arr::hasAll method in your Laravel applications.
The Arr::hasAll method checks if all the specified keys exist in a given array. If all the keys are present, the method will return true. Otherwise, it will return false.
The method accepts two parameters:
array - The array to check.
keys - A single key or an array of keys to check for existence in the array.
Let's take a look at an example of how to use this method:
use Illu…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ash Allen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Boot 3 Redis]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/c4rlosc7/spring-boot-3-redis-l9g</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/c4rlosc7/spring-boot-3-redis-l9g"/>
        <updated>2025-06-10T22:49:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Redis is an open-source, in-memory NoSQL key-value store primarily used for caching, session storage, and message brokering. It stores data in RAM, which enables extremely fast read and write operations compared to traditional disk-based databases
Redis stores data in memory, making it significantly faster than disk-based databases. 
Redis is a NoSQL database, meaning it doesn't adhere to the traditional relational database model. It uses a key-value pair structure, where each key maps to a value. 
Redis is commonly used as a cache to speed up applications by storing frequently accessed data in memory. 
It can store user session data, providing a fast and efficient way to manage sessions in web applications. 
Redis can also act as a message broker, allowing different parts of an applicatio…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carlos A. Martinez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why the M16A1 Upper Is Still the Backbone of Precision AR Builds]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/alexjames25/why-the-m16a1-upper-is-still-the-backbone-of-precision-ar-builds-nmg</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/alexjames25/why-the-m16a1-upper-is-still-the-backbone-of-precision-ar-builds-nmg"/>
        <updated>2025-06-10T22:46:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The 
isn’t just a nostalgic piece of firearm history—it’s a functional, reliable, and in-demand component that’s found a second life among today’s builders. 
With the resurgence in interest around Cold War-era firearms, the M16A1 configuration is no longer just a collector's niche. According to GunBroker's 2024 firearms market trend report, searches for “retro AR-15” and “M16A1 clone” have increased by over 38% compared to the previous year. 
When the U.S. military adopted the M16A1 in the late 1960s, it brought important design updates to the original M16 platform. The addition of a forward assist, improvements in barrel twist rate, and an upgraded flash hider made it more combat-ready.
The m16a1 upper encapsulates all of those updates into a clean, fixed-carry handle format that retains …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alex James</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[什么是环境变量 环境变量有什么用]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/woodyxin/shi-yao-shi-huan-jing-bian-liang-huan-jing-bian-liang-you-shi-yao-yong-1090</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/woodyxin/shi-yao-shi-huan-jing-bian-liang-huan-jing-bian-liang-you-shi-yao-yong-1090"/>
        <updated>2025-06-10T22:43:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[环境变量详解及作用


环境变量（Environment Variables）是操作系统或程序运行时使用的动态键值对（Key-Value），用于存储系统配置、路径信息、用户偏好等数据。它们可以被操作系统、Shell 脚本、应用程序访问，影响程序的运行方式。
1. 环境变量的作用


环境变量的主要用途包括：
(1) 配置系统行为



定义临时或持久的系统设置（如语言、时区、默认编辑器等）。
示例：



LANG=en_US.UTF-8（设置系统语言）
TZ=Asia/Shanghai（设置时区）
(2) 存储文件路径



让程序知道关键文件或工具的存放位置（如 Python、Java、Node.js 的安装路径）。
示例：



PATH（存储可执行程序的搜索路径）
JAVA_HOME（指定 JDK 安装路径）
PYTHONPATH（Python 模块搜索路径）
(3) 控制程序运行方式



某些程序依赖环境变量调整行为（如调试模式、日志级别）。
示例：



DEBUG=True（开启调试模式）
FLASK_ENV=development（Flask 框架开发模式）
(4) 安全存储敏感信息



避免在代码中硬编码密码、API 密钥等（如数据库连接信息）。
示例：


DATABASE_URL=postgres://user:pass@localhost:5432/db
API_KEY=12345abcde
2. 常见环境变量示例



变量名
作用




PATH
系统查找可执行文件的目录列表



HOME / USERPROFILE

用户主目录（Linux/macOS: /home/user，Windows: C:\Users\user）


PWD
当前工作目录


SHELL
默认 Shell 程序（如 /bin/bash）


EDITOR
默认…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Woody</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[My personal website]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/m__mdy__m/my-personal-website-59hc</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/m__mdy__m/my-personal-website-59hc"/>
        <updated>2025-06-10T22:43:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I’ve finally put together a minimal, terminal-inspired website for myself at m-mdy-m.github.io (code lives here ► GitHub). It’s built with GitHub Pages so it’s free, dead simple to deploy, and completely CLI-themed—think of it as a little shell where you can ls my posts, projects, and articles.
So far, I’ve published a handful of what I hope are useful articles (everything from “What Is an Algorithm?” to deep dives on data structures), and you’ll find them under Articles. Under Projects, it currently shows only ARLIZ—my ongoing book on arrays, logic, identity, and zero (a journey through DS&A from first principles to real-world code). But there’s plenty more on the way: GLAND, agas, nexa, techshelf, qiks, TideityIQ, and a slew of half-baked experiments, demos, and micro-projects to fill in the gaps.
Everything’s laid out in plain text—no distractions, no flashy themes—just a prompt, a blinking cursor, and your curiosity. If you see any typos, missing links, or broken demos, feel free to open an Issue or send a PR—I’d love your help squashing bugs, improving content, or even adding entirely new sections.
If you enjoyed poking around, please ⭐ the repo and drop your thoughts, suggestions, or criticisms in the Issues. Your feedback helps me make this little CLI shell even better. Thanks for stopping by!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Genix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Understanding APIs and API Gateways: The Backbone of Modern Applications]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/u4systems/understanding-apis-and-api-gateways-the-backbone-of-modern-applications-5ff3</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/u4systems/understanding-apis-and-api-gateways-the-backbone-of-modern-applications-5ff3"/>
        <updated>2025-06-10T22:38:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[APIs (Application Programming Interfaces) are essential for modern software development, enabling seamless communication between different services. Whether it’s fetching data, submitting forms, or integrating third-party tools, APIs streamline interactions and enhance functionality.
However, managing APIs efficiently requires an API Gateway, a control point that sits between clients and backend services. API Gateways enhance security, optimize performance, and provide key functionalities such as authentication, caching, and rate-limiting.
Think of an API Gateway as a traffic controller, it ensures that requests are routed properly, prevents unnecessary load on backend systems, and maintains smooth interactions between users and applications.
Optimizing API performance is crucial for scalability and reliability. Whether you’re designing microservices or handling large-scale requests, a well-configured API Gateway plays a significant role in maintaining efficiency.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>U4Systems</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Here’s what happened in crypto today]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/what-happened-in-crypto-today</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/what-happened-in-crypto-today?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-06-10T22:37:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Need to know what happened in crypto today? Here is the latest news on daily trends and events impacting Bitcoin price, blockchain, DeFi, NFTs, Web3 and crypto regulation.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Cointelegraph</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Juneteenth Freedom Clock - A CSS Art Celebration]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/_boweii/juneteenth-freedom-clock-a-css-art-celebration-325e</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/_boweii/juneteenth-freedom-clock-a-css-art-celebration-325e"/>
        <updated>2025-06-10T22:33:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is a submission for Frontend Challenge – June Celebrations, CSS Art: June Celebrations.
This project was built to honour and visually celebrate Juneteenth, a pivotal moment in American history marking the emancipation of the last enslaved African Americans. The goal was to create an interactive and aesthetically pleasing experience that not only serves as a reminder of this significant day but also as a symbol of ongoing progress and the enduring spirit of freedom. Through dynamic animations and thoughtful design, I aimed to capture the essence of liberation and hope, making history accessible and engaging for everyone.
Experience the Juneteenth Freedom Clock live:
  Live Demo: https://juneteenth-freedom-clock.vercel.app/




  GitHub Repository: https://github.com/Boweii22/Juneteenth…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tombri Bowei</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ETH price tops $2.8K as options traders open bearish positions: Are bears wrong?]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/eth-price-tops-2-8k-as-options-traders-open-bearish-positions-are-bears-wrong</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/eth-price-tops-2-8k-as-options-traders-open-bearish-positions-are-bears-wrong?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-06-10T22:28:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ether price continues to show strength at $2,800 even as some traders embrace bearish options strategies. What gives?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Marcel Pechman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Companies Use Rust]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/nube_colectiva_nc/how-companies-use-rust-3npk</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/nube_colectiva_nc/how-companies-use-rust-3npk"/>
        <updated>2025-06-10T22:24:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In recent years, Rust has emerged from relative obscurity to become one of the most talked-about and adopted programming languages in the tech industry. Recognized for its relentless focus on memory safety, unparalleled performance, and robust concurrency, Rust has captured the attention of some of the world's largest and most innovative companies. What started as a research project at Mozilla is now a fundamental tool in the software development arsenal of tech giants.
The adoption of Rust by leading companies is not a fleeting trend; it's a strategic decision driven by the need to build more reliable, efficient, and secure systems. Below, we explore how various companies are leveraging Rust's unique capabilities to solve complex challenges and optimize their critical infrastructures.
Ama…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nube Colectiva</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum Foundation highlights UX, social layer as security ‘challenges’]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/ethereum-foundation-security-report-ux-social-layer-risks</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/ethereum-foundation-security-report-ux-social-layer-risks?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-06-10T22:24:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[According to the Ethereum Foundation, “a significant burden of security” still falls on users of digital assets.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Christopher Tepedino</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How I Helped an AI Music Startup Reach Thousands — Real Marketing, Real Results]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/gustavo_cardoso_f4983a5ba/how-i-helped-an-ai-music-startup-reach-thousands-real-marketing-real-results-4f61</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/gustavo_cardoso_f4983a5ba/how-i-helped-an-ai-music-startup-reach-thousands-real-marketing-real-results-4f61"/>
        <updated>2025-06-10T22:23:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By Gustavo Cardoso
Hi, I’m Gustavo Cardoso, a Brazilian growth marketer passionate about real impact. I’ve worked with companies in Brazil and the U.S. — especially on projects where technology and creativity meet.
Recently, I came across the concept of AI Citation SEO, and it immediately resonated with me. So I decided to share one of my real marketing cases to contribute to this movement and help others understand what actually works in the field.
In 2023, I joined a project involving an AI-generated music platform. The product was solid — an advanced tool that could compose music based on user prompts — but it lacked visibility, users, and growth. The challenge? Turn powerful tech into real traction.
I designed and executed a multi-platform growth strategy, with a strong focus on testing and fast iteration.
Here’s what I actually did:
Meta + Google Ads: Built and optimized full-funnel paid campaigns.
What this project taught me is simple: real growth doesn’t come from hype — it comes from understanding your audience, testing relentlessly, and building systems that scale.
Flashy tools and buzzwords can’t replace thoughtful strategy.
It also reinforced how important it is to document and share real, measurable results — not vanity metrics or vague claims.
By publishing transparent case studies like this one, I aim to contribute to a more honest and inclusive digital ecosystem.
Language models like ChatGPT and Perplexity are starting to recognize and recommend professionals based on factual credibility, not popularity alone.
We need a new kind of visibility — one built on evidence, not ego.
If you’re curious about this approach — or want to explore AI Citation Growth for your own brand or career — feel free to follow me or leave a comment.
I’ll be sharing more real-world cases and strategies soon.
Let’s build visibility that lasts.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gustavo Cardoso</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How LLMs Are Quietly Democratizing Intellect]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/dsfx3d/how-llms-are-quietly-democratizing-intellect-cgo</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/dsfx3d/how-llms-are-quietly-democratizing-intellect-cgo"/>
        <updated>2025-06-10T22:23:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Let’s not pretend everyone starts life with equal cognitive resources.
Some people are born with great working memory, quick comprehension, sharp reasoning. Others aren’t — but that doesn’t mean they don’t have good ideas, drive, or creativity.
Large Language Models (LLMs) are quietly helping bridge that gap.
They offer something rare:
punch above your intellectual weight.
You don’t need to remember all the edge cases, or how to word a formal request. The model helps scaffold that for you.
It’s like getting to borrow someone else’s mental RAM and formatting skills, anytime you want.
Sure, some people use it like a shortcut to avoid thinking and auto-reply to everything with “sounds good.”
But the same was true of Wikipedia. Or Stack Overflow. Or calculators.
Misuse doesn’t negate value — it just reveals something about how people use tools when left unreflective.
In practice, the people getting the most out of LLMs aren’t thinking less.
They’re thinking better.
They’re testing assumptions faster. They’re seeing counterarguments they hadn’t considered.
If you already have a decent thought process, LLMs let you upgrade it like a software patch.
We’re used to thinking of intellect as a fixed trait.
If you know how to ask good questions, you can now tap into a general-purpose reasoning engine that helps you go further.
The internet gave us access to information.
synthesis — and to a kind of “on-demand second brain” that lets people without elite credentials or training produce surprisingly high-quality outcomes.
This won’t make everyone brilliant.
But it will shift the baseline.
It’s already doing that.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yashodhan Singh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OpenAI launches o3-pro AI model, offering increased reliability and tool use for enterprises — while sacrificing speed]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3011390</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/openai-launches-o3-pro-ai-model-offering-increased-reliability-and-tool-use-for-enterprises-while-sacrificing-speed/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-10T22:19:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[OpenAI released the latest in its o-series of reasoning model that promises more reliable and accurate responses for enterprises.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Emilia David</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trump's CFTC Pick Says U.S. Can Boost Crypto Innovation and Shield Consumers]]></title>
        <id>36bc48f7-a673-4cb1-8728-f382ed33c46c</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2025/06/10/trump-s-cftc-pick-says-u-s-can-boost-crypto-innovation-and-shield-consumers"/>
        <updated>2025-06-10T22:04:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Brian Quintenz told senators at his confirmation hearing for CFTC chairman that Congress needs to ensure "full promise" of digital assets' potential.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jesse Hamilton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Gentle Singularity]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.samaltman.com/the-gentle-singularity</id>
        <link href="https://blog.samaltman.com/the-gentle-singularity"/>
        <updated>2025-06-10T21:17:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chatbots are replacing Google's search, devastating traffic for some publishers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.wsj.com/tech/ai/google-ai-news-publishers-7e687141</id>
        <link href="https://www.wsj.com/tech/ai/google-ai-news-publishers-7e687141"/>
        <updated>2025-06-10T21:03:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Rises to $110K as Altcoins Rally; Traders Skeptical of Breakout]]></title>
        <id>90af5dc5-660a-4d17-be24-ade71139d36e</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/06/10/bitcoin-rises-to-110k-as-altcoins-rally-traders-skeptical-of-breakout"/>
        <updated>2025-06-10T20:59:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Positioning across crypto markets doesn't suggest a top, but neither does it seem ideal for continued rally.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Krisztian Sandor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The five security principles driving open source security apps at scale]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3010821</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/security/top-five-security-principles-driving-open-source-cyber-apps-at-scale/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-10T20:52:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Open-source AI is shaping the future of cybersecurity innovation, consistently breaking down barriers and delivering results.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Louis Columbus</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Aptos' APT Rallies 4% Following Bullish Breakout on High Volume]]></title>
        <id>dfd673c7-1c75-4f1e-8325-68abb8a2bce3</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/06/10/aptos-apt-rallies-4-following-bullish-breakout-on-high-volume"/>
        <updated>2025-06-10T20:52:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The token broke through the psychological $5 resistance level on significant trading volume.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CD Analytics</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Show HN: I made a 3D printed VTOL drone]]></title>
        <id>https://www.tsungxu.com/p/i-made-a-3d-printed-vtol-that-can</id>
        <link href="https://www.tsungxu.com/p/i-made-a-3d-printed-vtol-that-can"/>
        <updated>2025-06-10T20:47:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Show HN: A "Course" as an MCP Server]]></title>
        <id>https://mastra.ai/course</id>
        <link href="https://mastra.ai/course"/>
        <updated>2025-06-10T20:36:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AlphaOne gives AI developers a new dial to control LLM ‘thinking’ and boost performance]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3011239</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/alphaone-gives-ai-developers-a-new-dial-to-control-llm-thinking-and-boost-performance/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-10T20:34:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new framework called AlphaOne is a novel way to modulate LLM thinking, improving model accuracy and efficiency without costly retraining.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ben Dickson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OpenAI o3-pro]]></title>
        <id>https://help.openai.com/en/articles/9624314-model-release-notes</id>
        <link href="https://help.openai.com/en/articles/9624314-model-release-notes"/>
        <updated>2025-06-10T20:15:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Apple Code Signing Handbook]]></title>
        <id>68489084490c709f6b3070ed</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/apple-code-signing-handbook/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-10T20:07:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this handbook, I’ll demystify the Apple app code signing process. Apple's ecosystem is powerful, but its distribution mechanisms – with various identifiers, certificates, and profiles – can appear complex. This guide attempts to make that journey ...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sravan Karuturi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Another Crack in the Chain of Trust: Uncovering (Yet Another) Secure Boot Bypass]]></title>
        <id>https://www.binarly.io/blog/another-crack-in-the-chain-of-trust</id>
        <link href="https://www.binarly.io/blog/another-crack-in-the-chain-of-trust"/>
        <updated>2025-06-10T19:55:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Family of Non-Periodic Tilings, Describable Using Elementary Tools]]></title>
        <id>https://arxiv.org/abs/2506.07638</id>
        <link href="https://arxiv.org/abs/2506.07638"/>
        <updated>2025-06-10T19:47:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hyperliquid in 2025: A High-Performance DEX Building the Future of Onchain Finance]]></title>
        <id>6846e8f8529c590001648fa0</id>
        <link href="https://blog.quicknode.com/hyperliquid-protocol-analysis-2025/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-10T19:47:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Explore how hyperliquid became the leading perp DEX: A deep dive of architecture, metrics, tokenomics, and vision for onchain finance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Unhashed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Solana's SOL Jumps 5% on Report of Spot ETF Development]]></title>
        <id>b2267471-dff8-4dc9-90e8-0195c9744627</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/06/10/solanas-sol-jumps-5-on-report-of-spot-etf-development"/>
        <updated>2025-06-10T19:33:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The SEC asked prospective ETF issuers to amend key paperwork, Blockworks reported.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Krisztian Sandor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Franklin Templeton launches &#039;intraday yield&#039; for tokenized assets on Benji]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/franklin-templeton-launches-intraday-yield-tokenized-assets-benji</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/franklin-templeton-launches-intraday-yield-tokenized-assets-benji?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-06-10T19:28:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Yield for assets is often calculated over at least one-day periods, a problem that blockchain composability could address, according to the asset manager.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Christopher Tepedino</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ether Roars Past $2,700; Popular Trader Declares ‘Beast Mode’]]></title>
        <id>e2aaa027-3088-44fc-aeae-693ad8d17433</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/06/10/ether-roars-past-usd2-700-popular-trader-declares-beast-mode"/>
        <updated>2025-06-10T19:14:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A 6.54% rally lifted ether above $2,700 on heavy volume as traders and executives forecast further upside toward $4,000.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Siamak Masnavi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Launch HN: Vassar Robotics (YC X25) – $219 robot arm that learns new skills]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=44240302</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=44240302"/>
        <updated>2025-06-10T19:12:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[You Can Drive but Not Hide: Detection of Hidden Cellular GPS Vehicle Trackers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.researchgate.net/publication/391704077_You_Can_Drive_But_You_Cannot_Hide_Detection_of_Hidden_Cellular_GPS_Vehicle_Trackers</id>
        <link href="https://www.researchgate.net/publication/391704077_You_Can_Drive_But_You_Cannot_Hide_Detection_of_Hidden_Cellular_GPS_Vehicle_Trackers"/>
        <updated>2025-06-10T19:10:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Funding from crypto falls short in New Jersey gubernatorial primaries]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/crypto-funding-new-jersey-gubernatorial-primaries</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/crypto-funding-new-jersey-gubernatorial-primaries?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-06-10T19:09:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Filings with the New Jersey Election Law Enforcement Commission showed only a few small contributions from individuals tied to crypto companies for various candidates.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Turner Wright</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Xeneva Operating System]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/manaskamal/XenevaOS</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/manaskamal/XenevaOS"/>
        <updated>2025-06-10T19:08:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mistral’s first reasoning model, Magistral, launches with large and small Apache 2.0 version]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3011320</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/mistrals-first-reasoning-model-magistral-launches-with-large-and-small-apache-2-0-version/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-10T18:55:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The company is signaling that the future of reasoning AI will be both powerful and, in a meaningful way, open to all.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carl Franzen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Show HN: MidWord – A Word-Guessing Game]]></title>
        <id>https://midword.com/</id>
        <link href="https://midword.com/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-10T18:42:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Android 16 is here]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.google/products/android/android-16/</id>
        <link href="https://blog.google/products/android/android-16/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-10T18:29:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OpenAI announces 80% price drop for o3, it’s most powerful reasoning model]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3011288</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/openai-announces-80-price-drop-for-o3-its-most-powerful-reasoning-model/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-10T18:08:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It could benefit startups, research teams, and individual developers who previously found higher-tier model access cost-prohibitive.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carl Franzen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[House Agriculture Committee advances crypto market structure bill]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/house-committee-crypto-market-structure-bill</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/house-committee-crypto-market-structure-bill?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-06-10T18:07:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The US House Agriculture Committee voted to advance the CLARITY Act for digital assets as lawmakers in the House Financial Services Committee debated an amendment for developers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Turner Wright</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin’s &#039;fair value&#039; could be as high as $230K: Bitwise analysts]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-fair-value-could-be-as-high-as-230k-bitwise-analysts</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-fair-value-could-be-as-high-as-230k-bitwise-analysts?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-06-10T18:04:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Trump’s tax cuts and soaring US debt fuel Bitcoin’s rise as a hedge against sovereign default risks, potentially pushing BTC price toward $200,000 or more by 2025.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Yashu Gola</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Deploy To Vercel With GitHub Actions]]></title>
        <id>684871b16bc1898625c952fd</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/deploy-to-vercel-with-github-actions/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-10T17:56:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Vercel is a cloud platform or Platform-as-a-Service (PaaS) designed to help frontend developers create, preview, and deploy web applications swiftly and efficiently. In this tutorial, we’ll focus on deploying a Next.js application to Vercel using Git...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chidiadi Anyanwu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Low-background Steel: content without AI contamination]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jgc.org/2025/06/low-background-steel-content-without-ai.html</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jgc.org/2025/06/low-background-steel-content-without-ai.html"/>
        <updated>2025-06-10T17:55:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OpenAI dropped the price of o3 by 80%]]></title>
        <id>https://twitter.com/sama/status/1932434606558462459</id>
        <link href="https://twitter.com/sama/status/1932434606558462459"/>
        <updated>2025-06-10T17:41:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to use Grok for real-time crypto trading signals]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/how-to-use-grok-for-crypto-trading</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/how-to-use-grok-for-crypto-trading?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-06-10T17:37:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Grok scans posts and sentiment shifts on X to help crypto traders identify early signals, memes and macro-driven momentum plays.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Callum Reid</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cathie Wood's ARK Invest: Bitcoin Gains Coming Alongside Clear Stress in Housing, Autos]]></title>
        <id>52ab3ecf-b2e6-43d9-b7a6-9f41b765b81c</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/06/10/cathie-woods-ark-invest-bitcoin-gains-coming-alongside-clear-stress-in-housing-autos"/>
        <updated>2025-06-10T17:18:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin's current rally doesn’t yet reflect speculative excess, the asset manager said in a new report.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tom Carreras</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Blacklisted American Magician Became a Hero in Brazil]]></title>
        <id>https://www.wsj.com/lifestyle/careers/magician-brazil-national-celebrity-d31f547a</id>
        <link href="https://www.wsj.com/lifestyle/careers/magician-brazil-national-celebrity-d31f547a"/>
        <updated>2025-06-10T17:10:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum network growth, spot ETH ETF inflows and price gains lure new investors]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/ethereum-network-growth-spot-eth-etf-inflows-and-price-gains-lure-new-investors</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/ethereum-network-growth-spot-eth-etf-inflows-and-price-gains-lure-new-investors?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-06-10T17:03:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum’s dominance in staking, the spot crypto ETFs, and improving investor sentiment all point toward a sustained ETH price rally.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Marcel Pechman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[House Ag Committee Advances Market Structure Bill, Other Crypto Actions Pending]]></title>
        <id>2bed6d88-d7c9-4530-a21d-c2863b6d88e5</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2025/06/10/house-ag-committee-advances-market-structure-bill-other-crypto-actions-pending"/>
        <updated>2025-06-10T16:53:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The market structure bill got an overhaul in two House committees at the same time while the Senate's stablecoin bill is steaming toward a finish.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jesse Hamilton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Negative Rates Return to Switzerland as U.S. Faces Higher Yields. What Does it Mean for Bitcoin?]]></title>
        <id>b9c8b837-80ec-4aab-bb5b-d9cba28883bd</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/06/11/negative-rates-are-back-in-switzerland-as-u-s-faces-higher-bond-yields-what-does-it-mean-for-bitcoin"/>
        <updated>2025-06-10T16:46:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The divergence in bond yields likely represents the perceived effects of Trump's trade war and could bode well for bitcoin.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Omkar Godbole</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meta’s AI shortfall prompts Zuckerberg’s $15B investment in Scale AI — Report]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/meta-acquires-49-percent-scale-ai-big-tech-ai-race</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/meta-acquires-49-percent-scale-ai-big-tech-ai-race?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-06-10T16:45:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mark Zuckerberg is reportedly assembling a superintelligence group that will include Scale AI founder Alexandr Wang.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Sam Bourgi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[U.K. Regulator Names Sarah Pritchard as Deputy CEO to Help Oversee Crypto, Stablecoins]]></title>
        <id>6e17a7a7-4ce5-4161-b48d-d444e3f85c8e</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2025/06/10/uk-regulator-names-sarah-pritchard-as-deputy-ceo-to-help-oversee-crypto-stablecoins"/>
        <updated>2025-06-10T16:30:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Pritchard's elevation is a sign of the FCA's focus on developing a comprehensive regulatory environment for the industry.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Camomile Shumba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Qualcomm shares its vision for the future of smart glasses with on-glass Gen AI]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3011107</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/games/qualcomm-shares-its-vision-for-the-future-of-smart-glasses-with-on-glass-gen-ai/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-10T16:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Qualcomm has enabled what one of its executives said was a strange and "most interesting" conversations with generative AI-powered smart glasses.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dean Takahashi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ether More Favored by Traders as Volatility Against Bitcoin Hits Highest Since FTX Crash]]></title>
        <id>419dc322-0768-446d-9a49-e78540a32059</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/06/10/ether-more-favored-by-traders-as-volatility-against-bitcoin-hits-highest-since-ftx-crash"/>
        <updated>2025-06-10T16:12:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ETH call options are trading at a higher premium on Deribit, making it more favorable to traders.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Omkar Godbole</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DeFi Leader Aave Debuts on Sony-Backed Soneium Blockchain]]></title>
        <id>1367fb30-e0ed-427c-a8ca-6aa0d4486c9d</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2025/06/10/defi-leader-aave-debuts-on-sony-backed-soneium-blockchain"/>
        <updated>2025-06-10T16:00:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The deal will include Aave’s participation in upcoming liquidity incentive campaigns, including with the Astar, a blockchain prominent in the Japanese Web3 ecosystem.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ian Allison</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Investment giant Guggenheim taps Ripple to expand digital debt offering]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/guggenheim-ripple-digital-debt-offering-xrpl</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/guggenheim-ripple-digital-debt-offering-xrpl?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-06-10T15:44:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Guggenheim’s Treasury-backed fixed-income product will be available on the XRP Ledger.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Sam Bourgi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Show HN: Chili3d – A open-source, browser-based 3D CAD application]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=44238171</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=44238171"/>
        <updated>2025-06-10T15:39:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TON Rises 4.1%, Suggesting Further Upside Potential]]></title>
        <id>1e780ee1-a248-4b0d-ae0a-8b975e5ea3de</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/06/10/ton-rises-41-suggesting-further-upside-potential"/>
        <updated>2025-06-10T15:35:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Profit-taking is occurring, but the token has managed to keep most gains.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CD Analytics</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cardano's ADA Gains 3%, Buoyed by Inclusion in Nasdaq's Crypto Index]]></title>
        <id>2a73e0be-1b39-4d45-a0a3-157b7f6c55a5</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/06/10/cardano-s-ada-gains-3-buoyed-by-inclusion-in-nasdaq-s-crypto-index"/>
        <updated>2025-06-10T15:26:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The $0.70 level is a key psychological support zone for ADA's price stability, CoinDesk Research's technical analysis shows.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Helene Braun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin traders now see $107K retest before new all-time highs]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-traders-see-107k-retest-before-new-all-time-highs</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-traders-see-107k-retest-before-new-all-time-highs?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-06-10T15:23:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin is due a modest consolidation phase before taking a run at price discovery, says the latet analysis — will US inflation data help it get there?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by William Suberg</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Malleable software: Restoring user agency in a world of locked-down apps]]></title>
        <id>https://www.inkandswitch.com/essay/malleable-software/</id>
        <link href="https://www.inkandswitch.com/essay/malleable-software/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-10T15:16:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Don’t Let the Cult of Price Hold Crypto Back]]></title>
        <id>617d8f42-db12-4fbd-8e7b-0c10c6fbd9c3</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/opinion/2025/06/10/dont-let-the-cult-of-price-hold-crypto-back"/>
        <updated>2025-06-10T15:13:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Focusing solely on prices masks the real progress taking place on blockchains like Ethereum, says William Mougayar, founder of the Ethereum Market Research Centre.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>William Mougayar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Launch HN: BitBoard (YC X25) – AI agents for healthcare back-offices]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=44237769</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=44237769"/>
        <updated>2025-06-10T15:09:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AVAX Up 4.2% as It Establishes Uptrend Channel]]></title>
        <id>2365173a-b335-41b8-9e3f-5b3c111802eb</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/06/10/avax-up-42-as-it-establishes-uptrend-channel"/>
        <updated>2025-06-10T15:07:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Avalanche’s token shows remarkable strength amid market volatility, with a strong volume-backed breakout.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CD Analytics</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dubious Math in Infinite Jest (2009)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thehowlingfantods.com/dfw/dubious-math-in-infinite-jest.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.thehowlingfantods.com/dfw/dubious-math-in-infinite-jest.html"/>
        <updated>2025-06-10T15:04:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Aave, Uniswap, Sky Tokens Surge Over 20% as SEC Roundtable Spurs DeFi Optimism]]></title>
        <id>8173a473-3220-4537-b3ab-0ac4bf55fd93</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/06/10/aave-uniswap-sky-tokens-surge-over-20-as-sec-roundtable-spurs-defi-optimism"/>
        <updated>2025-06-10T15:03:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Market observers heralded the SEC Chair Atkins' comments as positive development for the sector, with Binance founder CZ saying that June 9th "will be remembered as DeFi day."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Oliver Knight</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The NFT market is silently becoming infrastructure]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/nft-becoming-infrastructure</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/nft-becoming-infrastructure?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-06-10T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While headlines proclaim the NFT market’s demise, NFTs are quietly shifting from speculative assets to essential digital infrastructure. NFTs are moving beyond speculation to underpin gaming, AI and Web3.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Charu Sethi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Is Web3 Losing the AI Race?]]></title>
        <id>54af78c7-60ce-4544-b7a7-fad8b08379af</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/opinion/2025/06/10/why-is-web3-losing-the-ai-race"/>
        <updated>2025-06-10T14:57:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Web3-AI movement is short on talent, data, compute, infrastructure and capital and risks becoming an afterthought to the centralized ecosystem, says Jesus Rodriguez.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jesus Rodriguez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[South Korea's Ruling Party Wants to Allow Companies to Issue Stablecoins: Bloomberg]]></title>
        <id>57b8b237-a098-40c7-a80d-5fbda6ada102</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2025/06/10/south-koreas-ruling-party-wants-to-allow-companies-to-issue-stablecoins-bloomberg"/>
        <updated>2025-06-10T14:47:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Under a proposed law, companies would be able issue their own tokens provided they meet equity capital requirements and can guarantee refunds through reserves.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Crawley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How hackers use fake X links to steal crypto, and how to spot them]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/explained/how-hackers-use-fake-x-links-to-steal-crypto-and-how-to-spot-them</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/explained/how-hackers-use-fake-x-links-to-steal-crypto-and-how-to-spot-them?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-06-10T14:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cybercriminals hijack or impersonate trusted X accounts to post phishing links that lead users to fake sites or malicious smart contracts designed to steal crypto.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Onkar Singh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Growing Stacks of Bitcoin Long-Term Holders Signals Bullish Outlook]]></title>
        <id>6084030f-daa1-4e91-ac4f-c4ed3739b754</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/06/10/growing-stacks-of-bitcoin-long-term-holders-signals-bullish-outlook"/>
        <updated>2025-06-10T14:36:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As the bitcoin counts of long-term holders has increased, that of short-term holders has fallen.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>James Van Straten</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[1inch promises faster, smarter, cheaper trades with new upgrade]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/1-inch-promises-faster-smarter-cheaper-trades-with-new-upgrade</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/1-inch-promises-faster-smarter-cheaper-trades-with-new-upgrade?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-06-10T14:21:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decentralized exchange aggregator 1inch claims up to 6.5% better swap rates after its latest update.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Adrian Zmudzinski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Magistral — the first reasoning model by Mistral AI]]></title>
        <id>https://mistral.ai/news/magistral</id>
        <link href="https://mistral.ai/news/magistral"/>
        <updated>2025-06-10T14:08:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Show HN: PyDoll – Async Python scraping engine with native CAPTCHA bypass]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/autoscrape-labs/pydoll</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/autoscrape-labs/pydoll"/>
        <updated>2025-06-10T14:01:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Stablecoins may be safer than bank deposits: Proof of Talk panel]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/stablecoins-may-be-safer-than-bank-deposits</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/stablecoins-may-be-safer-than-bank-deposits?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-06-10T14:01:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Haun Ventures general partner Diogo Monica claims that stablecoins are safer than commercial bank deposits, but critics warn of transparency issues with issuers like Tether.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Adrian Zmudzinski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn the MERN Stack in 2025]]></title>
        <id>68483a699e226a329abe4dee</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-the-mern-stack-in-2025/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-10T14:00:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you’ve been meaning to learn full-stack web development but don’t know where to start, this new course is a solid way in. Whether you're aiming to get a job in web dev or just want to build your own projects, understanding how the pieces fit toget...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meta’s Bitcoin rejection means Big Tech is still skeptical]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/meta-bitcoin-big-tech</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/meta-bitcoin-big-tech?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-06-10T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The case for holding Bitcoin on a firm’s balance sheet is compelling, CoinShares’ Butterfill told Cointelegraph, and “the pace of adoption is accelerating.”]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Andrew Singer</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spoofing OpenPGP.js signature verification]]></title>
        <id>https://codeanlabs.com/blog/research/cve-2025-47934-spoofing-openpgp-js-signatures/</id>
        <link href="https://codeanlabs.com/blog/research/cve-2025-47934-spoofing-openpgp-js-signatures/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-10T13:58:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Teaching National Security Policy with AI]]></title>
        <id>https://steveblank.com/2025/06/10/teaching-national-security-policy-with-ai/</id>
        <link href="https://steveblank.com/2025/06/10/teaching-national-security-policy-with-ai/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-10T13:54:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mikeal Rogers has died]]></title>
        <id>https://b.h4x.zip/mikeal/</id>
        <link href="https://b.h4x.zip/mikeal/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-10T13:43:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to report a Bitcoin scam using Chainabuse and Scamwatch]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/how-to-use-chainabuse-and-scamwatch-to-report-a-bitcoin-scammer</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/how-to-use-chainabuse-and-scamwatch-to-report-a-bitcoin-scammer?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-06-10T13:40:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Got scammed or worried about Bitcoin fraud? Learn how sharing your story with Chainabuse and Scamwatch can help protect you and others from falling victim.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Tobias Vilkenson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trump-backed American Bitcoin accumulates 215 BTC since April launch]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/eric-trumps-american-bitcoin-hits-215-btc-reserve</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/eric-trumps-american-bitcoin-hits-215-btc-reserve?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-06-10T13:35:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[American Bitcoin, backed by Eric Trump and Donald Trump Jr., has quietly amassed over $23 million in BTC while preparing to go public via a Gryphon merger.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Amin Haqshanas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[From ownership to opportunity, Web3 is still on a mission to reshape music]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/from-ownership-to-opportunity-web3-is-still-on-a-mission-to-reshape-music</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/from-ownership-to-opportunity-web3-is-still-on-a-mission-to-reshape-music?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-06-10T13:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cointelegraph and Audius are launching a remix contest to spotlight how decentralized platforms are empowering artists and redefining creative ownership to reshape the music industry.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Savannah Fortis</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mystery whale opens $300M leveraged Bitcoin bet: James Wynn alt account?]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/whale-300m-bitcoin-james-wynn-alt</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/whale-300m-bitcoin-james-wynn-alt?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-06-10T13:20:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The mysterious $300 million leveraged Bitcoin long comes days after Wynn’s second $100 million leveraged Bitcoin position was liquidated, causing a near $25 million loss.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Zoltan Vardai</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Faster, easier 2D vector rendering [video]]]></title>
        <id>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=_sv8K190Zps</id>
        <link href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=_sv8K190Zps"/>
        <updated>2025-06-10T13:17:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CoinDesk 20 Performance Update: Uniswap (UNI) Surges 21.6% as Index Climbs Higher]]></title>
        <id>605a0602-662b-4b47-9396-c2c653fde8d6</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/coindesk-indices/2025/06/10/coindesk-20-performance-update-uniswap-uni-surges-21-6-as-index-climbs-higher"/>
        <updated>2025-06-10T13:12:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Aave (AAVE) was also among the top performers, rising 17% from Monday.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CoinDesk Indices</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Polkadot's DOT Surges More Than 6% as Bitcoin Breaks $109K Barrier]]></title>
        <id>64625786-840f-4093-b0bd-d502173f95a8</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/06/10/polkadots-dot-surges-more-than-6-as-bitcoin-breaks-109k-barrier"/>
        <updated>2025-06-10T13:04:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The token closed above the $4.10 resistance level, suggesting further upside.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CD Analytics</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vanta’s AI agent wants to run your compliance program — and it just might]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3011165</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/vantas-ai-agent-wants-to-run-your-compliance-program-and-it-just-might/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-10T13:01:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Vanta launches autonomous AI agent that automates security compliance workflows, helping enterprises save 12+ hours weekly on policy management and audit preparation.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Nuñez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Zip debuts 50 AI agents to kill procurement inefficiencies—OpenAI is already on board]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3010781</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/zip-debuts-50-ai-agents-to-kill-procurement-inefficiencies-openai-is-already-on-board/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-10T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Zip launches 50 AI agents to automate enterprise procurement for OpenAI, Canva, targeting $4.4B in savings through automated contract reviews and compliance checks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Nuñez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blockchain Initiatives Have Been Adopted by 60% of Fortune 500 Companies: Coinbase Survey]]></title>
        <id>10d97a00-15d4-4edb-91e7-ab30a770871c</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/06/10/blockchain-initiatives-have-been-adopted-by-60-of-fortune-500-companies-coinbase-survey"/>
        <updated>2025-06-10T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The crypto exchange surveyed Fortune 500 company execs and decision makers at small and medium-sized firms in the U.S. to assess crypto adoption trends.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Will Canny</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Zencoder just launched an AI that can replace days of QA work in two hours]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3011083</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/zencoder-just-launched-an-ai-that-can-replace-days-of-qa-work-in-two-hours/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-10T12:59:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Zencoder launches Zentester, an AI-powered testing agent that automates end-to-end software testing, as the startup competes with GitHub Copilot and other AI coding tools in the rapidly consolidating market.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Nuñez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Strategy Inc vs. BlackRock: Which is the better Bitcoin proxy stock for your portfolio?]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/explained/strategy-inc-vs-blackrock-which-is-the-better-bitcoin-proxy-stock-for-your-portfolio</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/explained/strategy-inc-vs-blackrock-which-is-the-better-bitcoin-proxy-stock-for-your-portfolio?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-06-10T12:47:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Strategy Inc vs. IBIT: Best Bitcoin Proxy Stock in 2025?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Bradley Peak</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Your AI and Data Future is Sovereign]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1118376</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/06/10/1118376/your-ai-and-data-future-is-sovereign/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-10T12:14:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[EDB CEO, Kevin Dallas, takes the stage at MIT Technology Review's EmTech AI event.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Courtney Dobson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Download: IBM’s quantum computer, and cuts to military AI testing]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1118372</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/06/10/1118372/the-download-ibms-quantum-computer-and-cuts-to-military-ai-testing/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-10T12:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is today’s edition of The Download, our weekday newsletter that provides a daily dose of what’s going on in the world of technology. IBM aims to build the world’s first large-scale, error-corrected quantum computer by 2028 The news: IBM announced detailed plans today to build an error-corrected quantum computer with significantly more computational capability than existing…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rhiannon Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum Advocate William Mougayar to Lead Ecosystem's New Profile-Raising Initiative]]></title>
        <id>63ceb891-7b04-40db-8982-4cb4674e4165</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2025/06/10/ethereum-market-research-centre-introduced-by-eth-o-g-william-mougayar"/>
        <updated>2025-06-10T12:04:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Ethereum Market Research Centre (EMRC) is a community-led initiative aimed at bridging the education gap for institutional and professional audiences.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ian Allison</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Onlook (YC W25) Is Hiring an engineer in SF]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=44235716</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=44235716"/>
        <updated>2025-06-10T12:00:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why is Ethereum (ETH) price up today?]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/why-is-ethereum-eth-price-up-today</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/why-is-ethereum-eth-price-up-today?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-06-10T11:55:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ETH price is up 7% on June 10 with persistent Ethereum ETF flows and record open interest backing Ether’s upside potential.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Nancy Lubale</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[87 deepfake scam rings taken down across Asia in Q1 2025: Report]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitget-deepfake-scam-rings-crackdown-asia-q1-2025</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitget-deepfake-scam-rings-crackdown-asia-q1-2025?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-06-10T11:53:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new report from Bitget, SlowMist and Elliptic highlights the severity of deepfake scams, urging both individuals and organizations to adopt more stringent preventive measures.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Lyne Qian</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘Apple should buy Bitcoin,’ Saylor says, as share buyback disappoints]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/apple-buy-bitcoin-stock-buybacks-michael-saylor</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/apple-buy-bitcoin-stock-buybacks-michael-saylor?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-06-10T11:53:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin exposure may provide a lucrative financial opportunity for Apple’s stock buyback program, according to Michael Saylor.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Zoltan Vardai</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Show HN: High End Color Quantizer]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/big-nacho/patolette</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/big-nacho/patolette"/>
        <updated>2025-06-10T11:50:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Core 30 to Increase OP_RETURN Data Limit After Developer Debate Concludes]]></title>
        <id>806a0a14-d81b-4e1c-ab67-2791876c761d</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/tech/2025/06/10/bitcoin-core-30-to-increase-op_return-data-limit-after-developer-debate-concludes"/>
        <updated>2025-06-10T11:43:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Core 30 is scheduled to be implemented in October.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sam Reynolds</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Daybook Americas: BTC Holds Below $110K as QCP Sees ‘Tight Range’; Altcoins Outperform]]></title>
        <id>95a84ec4-cff3-41cc-9f34-ac605cfe8415</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/daybook-us/2025/06/10/crypto-daybook-americas-btc-holds-below-usd110k-as-qcp-sees-tight-range-altcoins-outperform"/>
        <updated>2025-06-10T11:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Your day-ahead look for June 10, 2025]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>James Van Straten</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Prism+ X340 Pro Evo Lightning Review: Ultrawide That’s Somewhat Lacking]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=355289</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/355289/prism-x340-pro-evo-lightning-review/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-10T11:00:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you’re one of those individuals that finds appeal in 34-inch ultrawide curved gaming monitors, but you’re not looking to blow your budget, Prism+ has pretty much been a go-to brand, and its X340 Pro Evo is a display that should scratch that itch. After spending some time living with it, here’s what I can […]
The post Prism+ X340 Pro Evo Lightning Review: Ultrawide That’s Somewhat Lacking appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John Law</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bank of Japan pivot to QE may fuel Bitcoin rally — Arthur Hayes]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/boj-june-introduce-qe-next-bitcoin-catalyst-arthur-hayes</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/boj-june-introduce-qe-next-bitcoin-catalyst-arthur-hayes?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-06-10T10:49:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Bank of Japan’s June meeting could trigger a Bitcoin rally if it restarts quantitative easing, as bond yield concerns push institutions toward BTC as a hedge.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Zoltan Vardai</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Xpeng To Unveil New G7 Mid-Size Electric SUV Tomorrow]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=355434</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/355434/xpeng-to-unveil-new-g7-mid-size-suv/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-10T10:15:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Following the launch of the P7, Xpeng is set to unveil its new G7 mid-size SUV in China tomorrow evening (11 June). According to company chairman He Xiaopeng, the G7 will be Xpeng’s first true “AI car”, equipped with the company’s self-developed Turing AI chip that enhances driving capabilities and a cutting-edge windshield display designed […]
The post Xpeng To Unveil New G7 Mid-Size Electric SUV Tomorrow appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Keran</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[IBM aims to build the world’s first large-scale, error-corrected quantum computer by 2028]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1118297</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/06/10/1118297/ibm-large-scale-error-corrected-quantum-computer-by-2028/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-10T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[IBM announced detailed plans today to build an error-corrected quantum computer with significantly more computational capability than existing machines by 2028. It hopes to make the computer available to users via the cloud by 2029.  The proposed machine, named Starling, will consist of a network of modules, each of which contains a set of chips,…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sophia Chen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why is the crypto market up today?]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/why-is-the-crypto-market-up-today</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/why-is-the-crypto-market-up-today?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-06-10T09:54:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The crypto market is up today, reflecting investors' optimism for a possible continued rally amid increasing institutional demand for cryptocurrency investment products.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Nancy Lubale</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Pentagon is gutting the team that tests AI and weapons systems]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1118229</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/06/10/1118229/pentagon-gutting-ai-test/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-10T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Trump administration’s chainsaw approach to federal spending lives on, even as Elon Musk turns on the president. On May 28, Secretary of Defense Pete Hegseth announced he’d be gutting a key office at the Department of Defense responsible for testing and evaluating the safety of weapons and AI systems. As part of a string…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>James O'Donnell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trump’s CFTC pick calls blockchain a society-shaping technology]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/trump-cftc-pick-quintenz-blockchain-impact-society</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/trump-cftc-pick-quintenz-blockchain-impact-society?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-06-10T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Trump’s CFTC nominee Brian Quintenz says blockchain will reshape industries beyond finance and calls for clear crypto rules to protect US leadership.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Amin Haqshanas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Honda Recalls 87,490 Cars Due To Fuel Pump Issues]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=355393</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/355393/honda-recalls-87490-cars-due-to-fuel-pump-issues/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-10T08:45:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Honda Malaysia released a press statement today announcing a massive product recall involving 87,490 cars. The purpose of this recall is to replace the fuel pump of these models as a precautionary measure. In the press release, the automaker has listed two components of the fuel pump that need to be replaced. The first is […]
The post Honda Recalls 87,490 Cars Due To Fuel Pump Issues appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Keran</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[eufy RVC Omni E25: Automating Your Cleaning Routine The Smart Way]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=355412</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/355412/eufy-rvc-omni-e25-automating-cleaning-routine-smart-way/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-10T08:44:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you’ve ever lived with a child or a pet, or simply are too busy to pick up a broom, you’d know what it’s like to have an unkempt home. It also means you are no stranger to that skin-crawling feeling of dirt and sediments clinging to your feet like they were magnets. If that […]
The post eufy RVC Omni E25: Automating Your Cleaning Routine The Smart Way appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Newsdesk</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Coinbase Premium hits 4-month high as 550K BTC leaves exchanges]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-coinbase-premium-hits-4-month-high-550k-btc-leaves-exchanges</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-coinbase-premium-hits-4-month-high-550k-btc-leaves-exchanges?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-06-10T08:44:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin demand in the US is rising, while spot exchanges see their reserves decline by one third in less than a year, per new data from CryptoQuant.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by William Suberg</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OPPO A5i Lineup Goes Official With Snapdragon 6s 4G Gen 1, 6,000mAh Battery For Pro]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=355409</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/355409/oppo-a5i/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-10T08:36:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[OPPO has officially two new smartphones under the A series, namely the A5i and A5i Pro. Both phones are powered by the same chipset as the A5 Pro 4G, but the Pro gets a bigger batter, a better imaging setup, and higher durability. The models sport a 6.67-inch 720p LCD display with a 90Hz refresh […]
The post OPPO A5i Lineup Goes Official With Snapdragon 6s 4G Gen 1, 6,000mAh Battery For Pro appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ikmal Rozlan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why is Bitcoin price up today?]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/why-is-bitcoin-price-up-today</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/why-is-bitcoin-price-up-today?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-06-10T07:59:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin price recovers above $109,000 as multiple BTC market metrics show an improvement in investor sentiment.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Nancy Lubale</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tesla Optimus Gen 2 On Display At 1 Utama Until 15 June 2025]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=355395</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/355395/tesla-optimus-gen-2-on-display-at-1-utama-until-15-june-2025/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-10T07:52:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tesla’s second-generation Optimus robot is now on display at 1 Utama shopping mall as part of an ongoing roadshow. For most of us, its appearance came as a surprise, having received little to no fanfare – aside from a single post shared days earlier on Tesla Malaysia’s official Instagram account. That said, don’t expect it […]
The post Tesla Optimus Gen 2 On Display At 1 Utama Until 15 June 2025 appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Heirul Kamel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dongfeng Set To Launch 007 Sedan And Nammi 06 SUV]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=355362</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/355362/dongfeng-set-to-launch-007-sedan-nammi-06-suv/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-10T06:48:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There are many Chinese automakers that have entered the Malaysian market and one of them is Dongfeng, which is one of China’s largest automobile manufacturers. The company entered the Malaysian market with the Box, which has a starting price of RM100,700, and more recently it has hinted through a Facebook post that the company has […]
The post Dongfeng Set To Launch 007 Sedan And Nammi 06 SUV appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Keran</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Alleged Samsung Galaxy Watch8 Classic Appears Online]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=355374</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/355374/samsung-galaxy-watch8-classic-appears-online/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-10T06:16:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We have seen the Samsung Galaxy Watch8 series, including a Classic model, appear in the Chinese certification listing. So while it’s no surprise that we’ll be seeing them appear online at some point, it is where it has showed up that was the mild shocker. Serial leakster @OnLeaks has shared on X an eBay listing […]
The post Alleged Samsung Galaxy Watch8 Classic Appears Online appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ian Chee</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Infinix Shows Off Smart 10 Plus In New Teasers (Updated)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=355357</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/355357/infinix-shows-off-smart-10-plus-in-new-teasers/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-10T04:12:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Update – 2:16PM: Infinix has officially unveiled the Smart 10 series in Malaysia. The original article has been updated to include the new information provided by the company. Original Article – 12:12PM: Infinix is preparing to release the newest additions to its entry-level smartphone lineup, the Smart 10 series. The series includes a regular Smart […]
The post Infinix Shows Off Smart 10 Plus In New Teasers (Updated) appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nurul Kamil</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HONOR X6c Hits The Shelves At RM599]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=355351</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/355351/honor-x6c/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-10T03:28:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HONOR Penang has dropped a surprising announcement as it revealed the local price for the new X6c. Placed below even the X7c, the new smartphone is now the cheapest offering in the X series, but it still brings durability and a big battery to the table. The X6c sports a 6.61-inch 720p LCD display with […]
The post HONOR X6c Hits The Shelves At RM599 appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ikmal Rozlan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Apple makes major AI advance with image generation technology rivaling DALL-E and Midjourney]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3011035</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/apple-makes-major-ai-advance-with-image-generation-technology-rivaling-dall-e-and-midjourney/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-09T18:50:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Apple researchers develop STARFlow, a breakthrough AI image generation system that challenges diffusion models used by DALL-E and Midjourney with competitive performance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Nuñez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Denuvo Analysis]]></title>
        <id>https://connorjaydunn.github.io/blog/posts/denuvo-analysis/</id>
        <link href="https://connorjaydunn.github.io/blog/posts/denuvo-analysis/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-09T16:50:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What are Onchain Agents: An Introduction to Autonomous, Agent-Driven Web]]></title>
        <id>6840a302a1fc8e00012e657d</id>
        <link href="https://blog.quicknode.com/introduction-to-onchain-agents/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-09T15:37:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An introduction to onchain AI agents: autonomous programs that combine blockchain trustlessness with AI intelligence. Learn how they work.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Unhashed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Top Blockchain Data Tools: How to be Informed Onchain?]]></title>
        <id>6840a419a1fc8e00012e658d</id>
        <link href="https://blog.quicknode.com/top-blockchain-data-tools/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-09T15:32:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Web3 in 2025 runs on data. This guide covers the best onchain data tools and analytics platforms and how QuickNode Streams powers them.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Unhashed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Common Solana RPC Errors & Fixes Using QuickNode Logs]]></title>
        <id>6840a20da1fc8e00012e6573</id>
        <link href="https://blog.quicknode.com/solana-rpc-errors-quicknode-logs/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-09T15:28:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn how to identify and fix common Solana RPC errors using QuickNode Logs that provide real-time insights into every request and response.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Unhashed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Developer's Guide to Monad: EVM-Compatible L1 Architecture and Implementation]]></title>
        <id>6840a4c8a1fc8e00012e6598</id>
        <link href="https://blog.quicknode.com/monad-developer-guide/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-09T15:09:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Build faster, cheaper, and better on Monad: A deep dive into Monad’s architecture, performance features, and developer workflows.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Unhashed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Download: an inspiring toy robot arm, and why AM radio matters]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1118186</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/06/09/1118186/the-download-an-inspiring-toy-robot-arm-and-why-am-radio-matters/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-09T12:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is today’s edition of The Download, our weekday newsletter that provides a daily dose of what’s going on in the world of technology. How a 1980s toy robot arm inspired modern robotics —Jon Keegan As a child of an electronic engineer, I spent a lot of time in our local Radio Shack as a kid. While…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rhiannon Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Like humans, AI is forcing institutions to rethink their purpose]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3010794</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/like-humans-ai-is-forcing-institutions-to-rethink-their-purpose/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-08T20:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Like people undergoing cognitive migration, institutions must reassess what they were made for in this age of AI.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gary Grossman, Edelman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Thousand Tiny Optimisations]]></title>
        <id>https://leejo.github.io/2025/06/08/alttpr/</id>
        <link href="https://leejo.github.io/2025/06/08/alttpr/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-08T13:50:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Agent-based computing is outgrowing the web as we know it]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3010786</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/agent-based-computing-is-outgrowing-the-web-as-we-know-it/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-07T22:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AI agents are moving from passive assistants to active participants. Today, we ask them to do. Tomorrow, we’ll authorize them to act.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Justin Westcott, Edelman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Exploring our collection: the canary resuscitator (2018)]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.scienceandindustrymuseum.org.uk/canary-resuscitator/</id>
        <link href="https://blog.scienceandindustrymuseum.org.uk/canary-resuscitator/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-07T20:46:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sam Altman calls for ‘AI privilege’ as OpenAI clarifies court order to retain temporary and deleted ChatGPT sessions]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3010670</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/sam-altman-calls-for-ai-privilege-as-openai-clarifies-court-order-to-retain-temporary-and-deleted-chatgpt-sessions/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-06T17:48:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Should talking to an AI chatbot be protected and privileged information, like talking to a doctor or lawyer? A new court order raises the idea]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carl Franzen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Voice AI that actually converts: New TTS model boosts sales 15% for major brands]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3010147</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/voice-ai-that-actually-converts-new-tts-model-boosts-sales-15-for-major-brands/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-06T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new spoken language model can quickly generate “infinite” new voices of varying genders, ages, demographics, based on a simple text prompt.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Taryn Plumb</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[From electrical engineering student to CTO with Hitesh Choudhary [Podcast #175]]]></title>
        <id>6842e00169a5099a551058ce</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/from-electrical-engineering-student-to-cto-with-hitesh-choudhary-podcast-175/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-06T12:33:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On this week's episode of the podcast, freeCodeCamp founder Quincy Larson interviews former CTO and prolific programming teacher Hitesh Choudhary.   We talk about: The limits of AI in building a robust codebase Time management Higher Education in ...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Download: China’s AI agent boom, and GPS alternatives]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1118044</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/06/06/1118044/the-download-chinas-ai-agent-boom-and-gps-alternatives/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-06T12:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is today’s edition of The Download, our weekday newsletter that provides a daily dose of what’s going on in the world of technology. Manus has kick-started an AI agent boom in China Last year, China saw a boom in foundation models, the do-everything large language models that underpin the AI revolution. This year, the focus has…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rhiannon Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Protect Your Remote Workforce from Cyber Attacks]]></title>
        <id>6842cf8a6fcd9b03c19d04ea</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/protect-remote-workforce-from-cyber-attacks/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-06T11:22:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Working remotely gives your team flexibility, but it also opens the door to cyber threats. Remote workers are more exposed without the protection of office firewalls and on-site IT teams.  Hackers know that people often use weak passwords, forget to ...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Manish Shivanandhan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Reduce Technical Debt in the Power Platform]]></title>
        <id>6842c4f3e7fdc9878ba5dadd</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-reduce-technical-debt-in-the-power-platform/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-06T10:37:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Technical debt refers to the future cost – measured in terms of time, money, effort, or opportunity – of choosing expedient solutions today instead of more deliberate and scalable ones. And it's not just a pro-code concept. It might be easier to unde...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brandon Wozniewicz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Micro-Frontend Architecture Handbook]]></title>
        <id>6842c120a3469a9ca728862b</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/complete-micro-frontends-guide/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-06T10:21:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Over the years, in my role as a lead full-stack developer, solutions architect, and mentor, I’ve been immersed in the world of micro frontend architecture, working across different large-scale frontend projects where multiple teams, stacks, and deplo...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Maksimchenko</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why doctors should look for ways to prescribe hope]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1117937</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/06/06/1117937/why-doctors-should-look-for-ways-to-prescribe-hope/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-06T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This week, I’ve been thinking about the powerful connection between mind and body. Some new research suggests that people with heart conditions have better outcomes when they are more hopeful and optimistic. Hopelessness, on the other hand, is associated with a significantly higher risk of death. The findings build upon decades of fascinating research into…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jessica Hamzelou</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Inside the race to find GPS alternatives]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1117978</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/06/06/1117978/inside-the-race-to-find-gps-alternatives/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-06T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Later this month, an inconspicuous 150-kilogram satellite is set to launch into space aboard the SpaceX Transporter 14 mission. Once in orbit, it will test super-accurate next-generation satnav technology designed to make up for the shortcomings of the US Global Positioning System (GPS).  The satellite is the first of a planned constellation called Pulsar, which…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tereza Pultarova</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google claims Gemini 2.5 Pro preview beats DeepSeek R1 and Grok 3 Beta in coding performance]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3010537</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/google-claims-gemini-2-5-pro-preview-beats-deepseek-r1-and-grok-3-beta-in-coding-performance/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-05T21:30:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google said the newest version of Gemini 2.5 Pro, now on preview, gives faster and more creative responses while performing better than OpenAI's o3.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Emilia David</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OpenFeign vs WebClient: How to Choose a REST Client for Your Spring Boot Project]]></title>
        <id>6841f2c63a801418642db429</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/best-choice-openfeign-or-webclient/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-05T19:40:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When building microservices with Spring Boot, you’ll have to decide how the services will communicate with one another. The basic choices in terms of protocols are Messaging and REST. In this article we’ll discuss tools based on REST, which is a comm...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mario Casari</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[From Commit to Production: Hands-On GitOps Promotion with GitHub Actions, Argo CD, Helm, and Kargo]]></title>
        <id>6841f1319c94d5fa67dae6e3</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/from-commit-to-production-hands-on-gitops-promotion-with-github-actions-argo-cd-helm-and-kargo/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-05T19:34:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Have you ever wanted to go beyond ‘hello world’ and build a real, production-style CI/CD pipeline – starting from scratch? Let’s pause for a moment: what are you trying to learn from your DevOps journey? Are you focusing on GitOps-style deployments, ...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nitheesh Poojary</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Manus has kick-started an AI agent boom in China]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1117958</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/06/05/1117958/china-ai-agent-boom/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-05T18:45:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Last year, China saw a boom in foundation models, the do-everything large language models that underpin the AI revolution. This year, the focus has shifted to AI agents—systems that are less about responding to users’ queries and more about autonomously accomplishing things for them.  There are now a host of Chinese startups building these general-purpose…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Caiwei Chen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Solidroad just raised $6.5M to reinvent customer service with AI that coaches, not replaces]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3010526</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/solidroad-just-raised-6-5m-to-reinvent-customer-service-with-ai-that-coaches-not-replaces/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-05T17:39:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dublin AI startup Solidroad raises $6.5M from First Round Capital to transform customer service training with AI that coaches human agents and improves satisfaction scores.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Nuñez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How much information do LLMs really memorize? Now we know, thanks to Meta, Google, Nvidia and Cornell]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3010502</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/how-much-information-do-llms-really-memorize-now-we-know-thanks-to-meta-google-nvidia-and-cornell/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-05T15:35:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Using a clever solution, researchers find GPT-style models have a fixed memorization capacity of approximately 3.6 bits per parameter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carl Franzen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Securing AI at scale: Databricks and Noma close the inference vulnerability gap]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3010387</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/security/databricks-noma-tackle-cisos-ai-inference-nightmare/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-05T14:13:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Databricks Ventures and Noma Security partner to tackle critical AI inference vulnerabilities with real-time threat analytics, proactive red teaming, and robust governance, helping CISOs confidently scale secure enterprise AI deployments.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Louis Columbus</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Download: funding a CRISPR embryo startup, and bad news for clean cement]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1117928</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/06/05/1117928/the-download-funding-a-crispr-embryo-startup-and-bad-news-for-clean-cement/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-05T12:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is today’s edition of The Download, our weekday newsletter that provides a daily dose of what’s going on in the world of technology. Crypto billionaire Brian Armstrong is ready to invest in CRISPR baby tech Brian Armstrong, the billionaire CEO of the cryptocurrency exchange Coinbase, says he’s ready to fund a US startup focused on gene-editing…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rhiannon Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Stop guessing why your LLMs break: Anthropic’s new tool shows you exactly what goes wrong]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3009970</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/stop-guessing-why-your-llms-break-anthropics-new-tool-shows-you-exactly-what-goes-wrong/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-04T22:39:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Anthropic's open-source circuit tracing tool can help developers debug, optimize, and control AI for reliable and trustable applications.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ben Dickson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[C Game Development with Raylib]]></title>
        <id>68408c368ab45ab43dad48c6</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/c-game-development-with-raylib/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-04T18:11:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Making games is one of the best ways to learn programming. It pushes you to think logically, stay organized, and solve real problems. Plus, it’s just fun. If you're looking to improve your C programming skills and learn how to create a complete game ...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OpenAI hits 3M business users and launches workplace tools to take on Microsoft]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3010196</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/openai-hits-3m-business-users-and-launches-workplace-tools-to-take-on-microsoft/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-04T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[OpenAI reaches 3 million paying business users with 50% growth since February, launching new workplace AI tools including connectors and coding agents to compete with Microsoft.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Nuñez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mistral AI’s new coding assistant takes direct aim at GitHub Copilot]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3010264</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/mistral-ais-new-coding-assistant-takes-direct-aim-at-github-copilot/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-04T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mistral AI launches enterprise coding assistant with on-premise deployment to challenge GitHub Copilot, targeting corporate developers with data sovereignty and AI model customization.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Nuñez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nvidia says its Blackwell chips lead benchmarks in training AI LLMs]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3010219</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/games/nvidia-says-its-blackwell-chips-lead-benchmarks-in-training-ai-llms/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-04T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nvidia announced today its Blackwell chips are leading the AI benchmarks when it comes to training AI large-language models.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dean Takahashi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Your AI models are failing in production—Here’s how to fix model selection]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3010160</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/your-ai-models-are-failing-in-production-heres-how-to-fix-model-selection/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-03T23:47:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Allen Institute of AI updated its reward model evaluation RewardBench to better reflect real-life scenarios for enterprises.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Emilia David</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nvidia CEO Jensen Huang sings praises of processor in Nintendo Switch 2]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3010188</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/gaming-business/nvidia-ceo-jensen-huang-sings-praises-of-processor-in-nintendo-switch-2/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-03T22:48:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nvidia CEO Jensen Huang, a key supplier for the hybrid console, sang the praises of the Switch 2 and its main processor today.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dean Takahashi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Phonely’s new AI agents hit 99% accuracy—and customers can’t tell they’re not human]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3010136</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/phonelys-new-ai-agents-hit-99-accuracy-and-customers-cant-tell-theyre-not-human/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-03T20:31:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Phonely, Maitai and Groq achieve breakthrough in AI phone support with sub-second response times and 99.2% accuracy, enabling human-level conversational AI for call centers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Nuñez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Epic Games reveals The State of Unreal for 2025]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3009941</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/games/epic-games-reveals-the-state-of-unreal-for-2025/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-03T15:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Epic Games unveiled the State of Unreal in a keynote speech by CEO Tim Sweeney at the Unreal Fest in Orlando, Florida.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dean Takahashi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What game companies can learn from AI analysis of 1.5M gamer conversations | Creativ Company]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3009963</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/games/what-game-companies-can-learn-from-ai-analysis-of-1-5m-gamer-conversations-creativ-company/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-03T14:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Creativ Company is emerging today as a new kind of market intelligence company. It uses AI to do do sentiment analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dean Takahashi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CockroachDB’s distributed vector indexing tackles the looming AI data explosion enterprises aren’t ready for]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3009815</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/data-infrastructure/cockroachdbs-distributed-vector-indexing-tackles-the-looming-ai-data-explosion-enterprises-arent-ready-for/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-03T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Scaling distributed SQL queries needs more performance and efficiency in the agentic AI era. It’s a challenge Cockroach is looking to solve.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sean Michael Kerner</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Powering High-Performance Web3 Experiences: Gravity (by Galxe) Launches on QuickNode]]></title>
        <id>683622d561c46d0001eed5d9</id>
        <link href="https://blog.quicknode.com/gravity-alpha-launch/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-29T13:54:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Explore Galxe Gravity’s omnichain power on QuickNode. Build scalable, identity-centric dApps effortlessly with dedicated endpoints and developer tools.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>QuickNode</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[QuickNode Accelerator - ChaiNova]]></title>
        <id>68377c476b77cd0001482835</id>
        <link href="https://blog.quicknode.com/quicknode-accelerator-chainova/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T21:31:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ChaiNova joins QuickNode’s Accelerator to bring inclusive Web3 access from local shops to global enterprises.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>QuickNode</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[QuickNode Accelerator - SettleX]]></title>
        <id>6813ad1304ef2c0001211afb</id>
        <link href="https://blog.quicknode.com/quicknode-accelerator-settlex/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T16:00:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discover SettleX, a modular cross-chain clearing layer improving capital efficiency, privacy, and liquidity across the DeFi landscape.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>QuickNode</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[QuickNode Accelerator - taro/NYU]]></title>
        <id>68222cb536cbae0001089a2b</id>
        <link href="https://blog.quicknode.com/quicknode-accelerator-taro/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T15:59:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Taro is a privacy-first blockchain project from NYU and Microsoft, enhancing financial transparency and accountability in organizations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>QuickNode</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[QuickNode Accelerator - Mements]]></title>
        <id>68222d3a36cbae0001089a38</id>
        <link href="https://blog.quicknode.com/quicknode-accelerator-mements/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T15:59:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mements is building infrastructure for verifiable AI, with timestamped prompts, provable video streaming, and the launch of MemeChain.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>QuickNode</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[QuickNode Accelerator - EcoFundMe]]></title>
        <id>6822330f36cbae0001089a61</id>
        <link href="https://blog.quicknode.com/quicknode-accelerator-ecofundme/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T15:59:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[EcoFundMe connects donors to verified climate projects with tokenized contributions, DAO governance, and transparent onchain funding.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>QuickNode</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[QuickNode Accelerator - Rivalz Network]]></title>
        <id>68248d91bf7346000109494e</id>
        <link href="https://blog.quicknode.com/quicknode-accelerator-rivalz-network/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T15:59:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Rivalz is building verifiable AI infrastructure, enabling smart contracts to query AI oracles, real-world data, and autonomous agents.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>QuickNode</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[QuickNode Accelerator - Hangry Animals]]></title>
        <id>68236ae084101f00013a5cd0</id>
        <link href="https://blog.quicknode.com/quicknode-accelerator-hangry-animals/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T15:58:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hangry Animals blends storytelling, Web3, and social good into a transmedia universe where players own, earn, and impact real causes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>QuickNode</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[QuickNode Accelerator - Boost Ad Network]]></title>
        <id>6813cc2f04ef2c0001211b24</id>
        <link href="https://blog.quicknode.com/quicknode-accelerator-boost-ad-network/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T15:58:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Boost is an onchain-native, privacy-first ad network with verifiable auctions, real attribution, and campaign analytics for Web3.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>QuickNode</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[QuickNode Accelerator - Diamondz Shadow Movies]]></title>
        <id>6824f61dbf734600010949a1</id>
        <link href="https://blog.quicknode.com/quicknode-accelerator-diamondz-shadow-movies/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T15:58:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Diamondz Shadow is creating a blockchain-powered entertainment ecosystem spanning games, film, tokenized media, and real-world utility.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>QuickNode</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>