<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2025-06-10T16:18:01.587Z</id>
    <title>AngJianming RSS Feed</title>
    <updated>2025-06-10T16:18:01.587Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gnome infrastructure is now sponsored by AWS]]></title>
        <id>https://foundation.gnome.org/2025/06/10/gnome-has-a-new-infrastructure-partner-welcome-aws/</id>
        <link href="https://foundation.gnome.org/2025/06/10/gnome-has-a-new-infrastructure-partner-welcome-aws/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-10T16:13:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[My personal website]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/m__mdy__m/my-personal-website-5h20</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/m__mdy__m/my-personal-website-5h20"/>
        <updated>2025-06-10T16:12:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I’ve finally put together a minimal, terminal-inspired website for myself at m-mdy-m.github.io (code lives here ► GitHub). It’s built with GitHub Pages so it’s free, dead simple to deploy, and completely CLI-themed—think of it as a little shell where you can ls my posts, projects, and articles.
So far, I’ve published a handful of what I hope are useful articles (everything from “What Is an Algorithm?” to deep dives on data structures), and you’ll find them under Articles. Under Projects, it currently shows only ARLIZ—my ongoing book on arrays, logic, identity, and zero (a journey through DS&A from first principles to real-world code). But there’s plenty more on the way: GLAND, agas, nexa, techshelf, qiks, TideityIQ, and a slew of half-baked experiments, demos, and micro-projects to fill in the gaps.
Everything’s laid out in plain text—no distractions, no flashy themes—just a prompt, a blinking cursor, and your curiosity. If you see any typos, missing links, or broken demos, feel free to open an Issue or send a PR—I’d love your help squashing bugs, improving content, or even adding entirely new sections.
If you enjoyed poking around, please ⭐ the repo and drop your thoughts, suggestions, or criticisms in the Issues. Your feedback helps me make this little CLI shell even better. Thanks for stopping by!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Genix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Quickly Create Remote MCP Servers for APIs with Zuplo]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/zuplo/quickly-create-remote-mcp-servers-for-apis-with-zuplo-18o6</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/zuplo/quickly-create-remote-mcp-servers-for-apis-with-zuplo-18o6"/>
        <updated>2025-06-10T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We're excited to introduce a powerful new feature in Zuplo's API Gateway: the MCP Server Handler that enables you to transform any API you manage through Zuplo into a remote Model Context Protocol (MCP) server with straightforward configuration, eliminating the complexity of remote MCP server setup.
You can now make your API go from zero-to-MCP in minutes! Skip straight to the documentation to learn more!
Model Context Protocol (MCP) is an open standard that enables AI tools and agents to securely connect to external data sources and services. Having an MCP server for your API is becoming essential for AI readiness as AI agents become more prevalent in business workflows, making your API discoverable and usable by intelligent systems.
While setting up local MCP servers is relatively straig…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Martyn Davies</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Convert Images to PDF in Java Using the Cloud SDK]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/shahzad_ashraf_5ea18e2b2d/how-to-convert-images-to-pdf-in-java-using-the-cloud-sdk-36e4</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/shahzad_ashraf_5ea18e2b2d/how-to-convert-images-to-pdf-in-java-using-the-cloud-sdk-36e4"/>
        <updated>2025-06-10T15:57:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Transform your image files into organized, shareable PDF documents with ease using the GroupDocs.Conversion Cloud Java SDK. With minimal coding requirements, you can programmatically convert common image formats like JPEG, PNG, BMP, and TIFF to PDF—simplifying your document processing workflows directly within Java applications.
The Cloud API is designed for both performance and user-friendliness. You have precise control over output formatting, resolution, and layout, while maintaining a lightweight and speedy integration. By utilizing this Java REST API for converting images to PDF, developers can minimize manual involvement and provide users with a consistent export experience across different platforms.
Whether you’re creating enterprise applications, cloud-based file processing system…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shahzad Ashraf</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is Tableau?]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/satya_prakash_06/what-is-tableau-332n</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/satya_prakash_06/what-is-tableau-332n"/>
        <updated>2025-06-10T15:57:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[📊 What is Tableau? A Beginner's Guide to Data Visualization


Data is everywhere. Every click, swipe, transaction, and even step we take generates data. But here’s the real challenge: how do we actually understand and use that data to make better decisions?
That’s where Tableau comes in.
Whether you're a student, a business owner, or just curious about data, this beginner’s guide will help you understand what Tableau is, how it works, who uses it, and why it's a game-changer in the world of data visualization.
At its core, Tableau is a powerful data visualization and business intelligence tool. It helps you take raw data—often messy and hard to read—and turn it into beautiful, interactive, and easy-to-understand visuals like charts, graphs, and dashboards.
Tableau helps you see and unders…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>A.Satya Prakash</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Challenge: File Download]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/travondatrack/challenge-file-download-17g9</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/travondatrack/challenge-file-download-17g9"/>
        <updated>2025-06-10T15:57:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Link: https://battle.cookiearena.org/challenges/web/file-download
You can upload and download file. Try to get the /flag.txt
Phân tích lỗ hổng
Dòng code:
<li><a href="/read?name=sad">sad</a></li>


URL này cho thấy ứng dụng đang nhận một tham số name qua query string và có thể sử dụng giá trị này để đọc một file nào đó từ server. Nếu phía backend không xử lý tốt đầu vào của người dùng, thì đây là một điểm rất dễ bị tấn công path traversal.
Thử khai thác thông qua: http://[target]/read?name=../../../../etc/passwd

==> Đã bị khai thác thành công
Thử với payload: /read?name=../../../../flag.txt

==> DONEEE!
==> FLAG: CHH{eASy_DoWN104d_F1L3_83aca8177bef161dae4bdb4b5aa9ce67}]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>tRavOndAtrACk</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction to Day 2 Serverless Operations – Part 2]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/aws-builders/introduction-to-day-2-serverless-operations-part-2-37oj</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/aws-builders/introduction-to-day-2-serverless-operations-part-2-37oj"/>
        <updated>2025-06-10T15:50:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In part 1 of this series, I introduced some of the most common Day 2 serverless operations, focusing on Function as a Service.

In this part, I will focus on serverless application integration services commonly used in event-driven architectures.

For this post, I will look into message queue services, event routing services, and workflow orchestration services for building event-driven architectures.  
Message queues enable asynchronous communication between different components in an event-driven architecture (EDA). This means that producers (systems or services generating events) can send messages to the queue and continue their operations without waiting for consumers (systems or services processing events) to respond or be available.  
Security should always be the priority, as it pro…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eyal Estrin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The writing style made it easy to connect with, and the ideas actually stick. Rare to find something this real.]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/richards_l52689/the-writing-style-made-it-easy-to-connect-with-and-the-ideas-actually-stick-rare-to-find-gng</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/richards_l52689/the-writing-style-made-it-easy-to-connect-with-and-the-ideas-actually-stick-rare-to-find-gng"/>
        <updated>2025-06-10T15:47:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Remote Work Isn't Freedom Without Structure: What TDZ PRO Knows That Most Don't
Anthony James ・ Jun 10
#remotework
        #productivity
        #entrepreneurship
        #mindset]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lauren Richards</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ArkTS programming specification(5)]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/liu_yang_fc0e605820ac220c/arkts-programming-specification5-h29</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/liu_yang_fc0e605820ac220c/arkts-programming-specification5-h29"/>
        <updated>2025-06-10T15:47:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Programming Practices



  
  
  Array Traversal




Level: Requirement
Description: For array traversal, prioritize using Array object methods such as forEach(), map(), every(), filter(), find(), findIndex(), reduce(), and some().


Negative Example:




const numbers = [1, 2, 3, 4, 5];
const increasedByOne: number[] = [];
for (let i = 0; i < numbers.length; i++) {
  increasedByOne.push(numbers[i] + 1);
}

Positive Example:




const numbers = [1, 2, 3, 4, 5];
const increasedByOne: number[] = numbers.map(num => num + 1);

Level: Requirement
Description: Avoid performing assignments in control - flow expressions used in if, while, for, or ?: statements, as this can lead to unexpected behavior and poor code readability.


Negative Example:




if (isFoo = false) {
  // ...
}

Positive Examp…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>liu yang</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[2nd Day, Introduction to SQL- 10-06-2025]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/vigneswaran_manivannan_87/2nd-day-introduction-to-sql-10-06-2025-30dj</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/vigneswaran_manivannan_87/2nd-day-introduction-to-sql-10-06-2025-30dj"/>
        <updated>2025-06-10T15:47:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[*SQL *- Structured Query Language- 
used in Data analysis.
Software development purpose
To manage and manipulate relational DBMS.
*Uses of SQL



 Querying the data. To find a specific information.
To insert, update , delete the data.
**
DDL- Data definition Language.
Used to define/ manage the tables.
The commands are,
CREATE- Create  a table
ALTER- To modify the table structure, which was created already.
DROP- To delete the complete table
RENAME- To rename the table
TRUNCATE- To delete all records except the table structure.
DML- Data manipulation language.


To manipulate the data into the table.
INSERT- Add new data in rows.
UPDATE- Modify the existing data.
3.DELETE- Remove data from the row.
DQL - Data Query Language


SELECT- To retrieve a data from the table.
( Select* from table …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Vigneswaran Manivannan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WordPress Tutorial for Beginners 2025: Complete Guide to Build a Website from Scratch]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/neonwebid/wordpress-tutorial-for-beginners-2025-complete-guide-to-build-a-website-from-scratch-5161</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/neonwebid/wordpress-tutorial-for-beginners-2025-complete-guide-to-build-a-website-from-scratch-5161"/>
        <updated>2025-06-10T15:46:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This WordPress tutorial for beginners is designed specifically for those who want to start building their own website in 2025. No coding skills required — we’ll walk through each step so you can follow along easily.
Understanding WordPress is essential before diving in. WordPress is the most popular Content Management System (CMS) in the world. It allows you to build websites, blogs, online stores, portfolios, or landing pages — all without touching code.
With WordPress, you can build and manage a professional site using a simple interface and a huge collection of themes and plugins.
Reasons to use WordPress as a beginner are stronger than ever in 2025:
Free and open-source
Huge global community and support
Thousands of themes and plugins
SEO-friendly by default
For beginners, WordPress is…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Wichaksono</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Terraforming the Voice: Deploying a Clone Application with Infrastructure as Code on AWS]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/semperfitodd/terraforming-the-voice-deploying-a-clone-application-with-infrastructure-as-code-on-aws-338</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/semperfitodd/terraforming-the-voice-deploying-a-clone-application-with-infrastructure-as-code-on-aws-338"/>
        <updated>2025-06-10T15:46:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Terraforming the Voice: Deploying a Clone Application with Infrastructure as Code on AWS
By Todd Bernson, CTO of BSC Analytics, Terraform Whisperer
There’s something beautiful about watching an entire production-grade environment spring to life from a single command — like watching a barbell float off the ground when the form is just right. This article is for those of us who believe that if your infrastructure isn’t defined in code, it’s one rogue click away from disaster.
Welcome to the story of how I built and deployed a self-hosted voice cloning application on AWS using Terraform for full-stack automation. We’re not talking about a toy project or an ML demo in a Jupyter notebook — this is a fully containerized, production-ready, auto-scaling, API-driven platform running in the cloud, d…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Todd Bernson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Investment giant Guggenheim taps Ripple to expand digital debt offering]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/guggenheim-ripple-digital-debt-offering-xrpl</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/guggenheim-ripple-digital-debt-offering-xrpl?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-06-10T15:44:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Guggenheim’s Treasury-backed fixed-income product will be available on the XRP Ledger.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Sam Bourgi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[First Impressions of Claude Code: Where Does it Fit?]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/thutch1976/first-impressions-of-claude-code-where-does-it-fit-45m9</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/thutch1976/first-impressions-of-claude-code-where-does-it-fit-45m9"/>
        <updated>2025-06-10T15:43:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction


Claude Code has been getting a lot of attention lately. I've been following its increase of the youtube mindshare, and I finally decided I needed to try it out for myself. Since I've been using Cursor so heavily, I was curious about what value Claude Code actually provided: how I would incorporate it into my workflow and if it complimented or replaced Cursor.   
The topic of combining Claude Code with Cursor has been covered in some new videos in the past week, and I watched each of these:
This Cursor Setup Changes Everything (Claude Code)
Claude Code + Cursor AI = Vibe Coding Paradise
Each video is interesting and informative in its own right. This is where I learned that Claude Code was now offered as part of their subscription plans, and is no longer limited to the metere…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Trey Hutcheson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Show HN: Chili3d – A open-source, browser-based 3D CAD application]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=44238171</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=44238171"/>
        <updated>2025-06-10T15:39:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TON Rises 4.1%, Suggesting Further Upside Potential]]></title>
        <id>1e780ee1-a248-4b0d-ae0a-8b975e5ea3de</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/06/10/ton-rises-41-suggesting-further-upside-potential"/>
        <updated>2025-06-10T15:35:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Profit-taking is occurring, but the token has managed to keep most gains.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CD Analytics</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cardano's ADA Gains 3%, Buoyed by Inclusion in Nasdaq's Crypto Index]]></title>
        <id>2a73e0be-1b39-4d45-a0a3-157b7f6c55a5</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/06/10/cardano-s-ada-gains-3-buoyed-by-inclusion-in-nasdaq-s-crypto-index"/>
        <updated>2025-06-10T15:26:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The $0.70 level is a key psychological support zone for ADA's price stability, CoinDesk Research's technical analysis shows.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Helene Braun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin traders now see $107K retest before new all-time highs]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-traders-see-107k-retest-before-new-all-time-highs</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-traders-see-107k-retest-before-new-all-time-highs?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-06-10T15:23:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin is due a modest consolidation phase before taking a run at price discovery, says the latet analysis — will US inflation data help it get there?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by William Suberg</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Don’t Let the Cult of Price Hold Crypto Back]]></title>
        <id>617d8f42-db12-4fbd-8e7b-0c10c6fbd9c3</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/opinion/2025/06/10/dont-let-the-cult-of-price-hold-crypto-back"/>
        <updated>2025-06-10T15:13:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Focusing solely on prices masks the real progress taking place on blockchains like Ethereum, says William Mougayar, founder of the Ethereum Market Research Centre.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>William Mougayar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Launch HN: BitBoard (YC X25) – AI agents for healthcare back-offices]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=44237769</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=44237769"/>
        <updated>2025-06-10T15:09:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AVAX Up 4.2% as It Establishes Uptrend Channel]]></title>
        <id>2365173a-b335-41b8-9e3f-5b3c111802eb</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/06/10/avax-up-42-as-it-establishes-uptrend-channel"/>
        <updated>2025-06-10T15:07:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Avalanche’s token shows remarkable strength amid market volatility, with a strong volume-backed breakout.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CD Analytics</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dubious Math in Infinite Jest (2009)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thehowlingfantods.com/dfw/dubious-math-in-infinite-jest.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.thehowlingfantods.com/dfw/dubious-math-in-infinite-jest.html"/>
        <updated>2025-06-10T15:04:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Aave, Uniswap, Sky Tokens Surge Over 20% as SEC Roundtable Spurs DeFi Optimism]]></title>
        <id>8173a473-3220-4537-b3ab-0ac4bf55fd93</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/06/10/aave-uniswap-sky-tokens-surge-over-20-as-sec-roundtable-spurs-defi-optimism"/>
        <updated>2025-06-10T15:03:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Market observers heralded the SEC Chair Atkins' comments as positive development for the sector, with Binance founder CZ saying that June 9th "will be remembered as DeFi day."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Oliver Knight</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The NFT market is silently becoming infrastructure]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/nft-becoming-infrastructure</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/nft-becoming-infrastructure?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-06-10T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While headlines proclaim the NFT market’s demise, NFTs are quietly shifting from speculative assets to essential digital infrastructure. NFTs are moving beyond speculation to underpin gaming, AI and Web3.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Charu Sethi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Is Web3 Losing the AI Race?]]></title>
        <id>54af78c7-60ce-4544-b7a7-fad8b08379af</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/opinion/2025/06/10/why-is-web3-losing-the-ai-race"/>
        <updated>2025-06-10T14:57:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Web3-AI movement is short on talent, data, compute, infrastructure and capital and risks becoming an afterthought to the centralized ecosystem, says Jesus Rodriguez.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jesus Rodriguez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[South Korea's Ruling Party Wants to Allow Companies to Issue Stablecoins: Bloomberg]]></title>
        <id>57b8b237-a098-40c7-a80d-5fbda6ada102</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2025/06/10/south-koreas-ruling-party-wants-to-allow-companies-to-issue-stablecoins-bloomberg"/>
        <updated>2025-06-10T14:47:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Under a proposed law, companies would be able issue their own tokens provided they meet equity capital requirements and can guarantee refunds through reserves.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Crawley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How hackers use fake X links to steal crypto, and how to spot them]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/explained/how-hackers-use-fake-x-links-to-steal-crypto-and-how-to-spot-them</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/explained/how-hackers-use-fake-x-links-to-steal-crypto-and-how-to-spot-them?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-06-10T14:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cybercriminals hijack or impersonate trusted X accounts to post phishing links that lead users to fake sites or malicious smart contracts designed to steal crypto.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Onkar Singh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Growing Stacks of Bitcoin Long-Term Holders Signals Bullish Outlook]]></title>
        <id>6084030f-daa1-4e91-ac4f-c4ed3739b754</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/06/10/growing-stacks-of-bitcoin-long-term-holders-signals-bullish-outlook"/>
        <updated>2025-06-10T14:36:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As the bitcoin counts of long-term holders has increased, that of short-term holders has fallen.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>James Van Straten</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Always On, Always Connected, Always Searching, Always Distracted]]></title>
        <id>https://leejo.github.io/2025/06/10/always_on/</id>
        <link href="https://leejo.github.io/2025/06/10/always_on/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-10T14:29:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[1inch promises faster, smarter, cheaper trades with new upgrade]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/1-inch-promises-faster-smarter-cheaper-trades-with-new-upgrade</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/1-inch-promises-faster-smarter-cheaper-trades-with-new-upgrade?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-06-10T14:21:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decentralized exchange aggregator 1inch claims up to 6.5% better swap rates after its latest update.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Adrian Zmudzinski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Here’s what happened in crypto today]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/what-happened-in-crypto-today</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/what-happened-in-crypto-today?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-06-10T14:13:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Need to know what happened in crypto today? Here is the latest news on daily trends and events impacting Bitcoin price, blockchain, DeFi, NFTs, Web3 and crypto regulation.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Cointelegraph</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Magistral — the first reasoning model by Mistral AI]]></title>
        <id>https://mistral.ai/news/magistral</id>
        <link href="https://mistral.ai/news/magistral"/>
        <updated>2025-06-10T14:08:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Show HN: PyDoll – Async Python scraping engine with native CAPTCHA bypass]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/autoscrape-labs/pydoll</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/autoscrape-labs/pydoll"/>
        <updated>2025-06-10T14:01:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Stablecoins may be safer than bank deposits: Proof of Talk panel]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/stablecoins-may-be-safer-than-bank-deposits</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/stablecoins-may-be-safer-than-bank-deposits?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-06-10T14:01:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Haun Ventures general partner Diogo Monica claims that stablecoins are safer than commercial bank deposits, but critics warn of transparency issues with issuers like Tether.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Adrian Zmudzinski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meta’s Bitcoin rejection means Big Tech is still skeptical]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/meta-bitcoin-big-tech</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/meta-bitcoin-big-tech?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-06-10T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The case for holding Bitcoin on a firm’s balance sheet is compelling, CoinShares’ Butterfill told Cointelegraph, and “the pace of adoption is accelerating.”]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Andrew Singer</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Finding Atari Games in Randomly Generated Data]]></title>
        <id>https://bbenchoff.github.io/pages/FiniteAtari.html</id>
        <link href="https://bbenchoff.github.io/pages/FiniteAtari.html"/>
        <updated>2025-06-10T13:58:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spoofing OpenPGP.js signature verification]]></title>
        <id>https://codeanlabs.com/blog/research/cve-2025-47934-spoofing-openpgp-js-signatures/</id>
        <link href="https://codeanlabs.com/blog/research/cve-2025-47934-spoofing-openpgp-js-signatures/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-10T13:58:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Teaching National Security Policy with AI]]></title>
        <id>https://steveblank.com/2025/06/10/teaching-national-security-policy-with-ai/</id>
        <link href="https://steveblank.com/2025/06/10/teaching-national-security-policy-with-ai/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-10T13:54:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to report a Bitcoin scam using Chainabuse and Scamwatch]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/how-to-use-chainabuse-and-scamwatch-to-report-a-bitcoin-scammer</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/how-to-use-chainabuse-and-scamwatch-to-report-a-bitcoin-scammer?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-06-10T13:40:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Got scammed or worried about Bitcoin fraud? Learn how sharing your story with Chainabuse and Scamwatch can help protect you and others from falling victim.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Tobias Vilkenson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trump-backed American Bitcoin accumulates 215 BTC since April launch]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/eric-trumps-american-bitcoin-hits-215-btc-reserve</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/eric-trumps-american-bitcoin-hits-215-btc-reserve?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-06-10T13:35:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[American Bitcoin, backed by Eric Trump and Donald Trump Jr., has quietly amassed over $23 million in BTC while preparing to go public via a Gryphon merger.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Amin Haqshanas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[From ownership to opportunity, Web3 is still on a mission to reshape music]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/from-ownership-to-opportunity-web3-is-still-on-a-mission-to-reshape-music</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/from-ownership-to-opportunity-web3-is-still-on-a-mission-to-reshape-music?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-06-10T13:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cointelegraph and Audius are launching a remix contest to spotlight how decentralized platforms are empowering artists and redefining creative ownership to reshape the music industry.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Savannah Fortis</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mystery whale opens $300M leveraged Bitcoin bet: James Wynn alt account?]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/whale-300m-bitcoin-james-wynn-alt</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/whale-300m-bitcoin-james-wynn-alt?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-06-10T13:20:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The mysterious $300 million leveraged Bitcoin long comes days after Wynn’s second $100 million leveraged Bitcoin position was liquidated, causing a near $25 million loss.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Zoltan Vardai</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Faster, easier 2D vector rendering [video]]]></title>
        <id>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=_sv8K190Zps</id>
        <link href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=_sv8K190Zps"/>
        <updated>2025-06-10T13:17:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CoinDesk 20 Performance Update: Uniswap (UNI) Surges 21.6% as Index Climbs Higher]]></title>
        <id>605a0602-662b-4b47-9396-c2c653fde8d6</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/coindesk-indices/2025/06/10/coindesk-20-performance-update-uniswap-uni-surges-21-6-as-index-climbs-higher"/>
        <updated>2025-06-10T13:12:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Aave (AAVE) was also among the top performers, rising 17% from Monday.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CoinDesk Indices</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Polkadot's DOT Surges More Than 6% as Bitcoin Breaks $109K Barrier]]></title>
        <id>64625786-840f-4093-b0bd-d502173f95a8</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/06/10/polkadots-dot-surges-more-than-6-as-bitcoin-breaks-109k-barrier"/>
        <updated>2025-06-10T13:04:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The token closed above the $4.10 resistance level, suggesting further upside.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CD Analytics</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vanta’s AI agent wants to run your compliance program — and it just might]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3011165</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/vantas-ai-agent-wants-to-run-your-compliance-program-and-it-just-might/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-10T13:01:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Vanta launches autonomous AI agent that automates security compliance workflows, helping enterprises save 12+ hours weekly on policy management and audit preparation.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Nuñez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Zip debuts 50 AI agents to kill procurement inefficiencies—OpenAI is already on board]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3010781</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/zip-debuts-50-ai-agents-to-kill-procurement-inefficiencies-openai-is-already-on-board/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-10T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Zip launches 50 AI agents to automate enterprise procurement for OpenAI, Canva, targeting $4.4B in savings through automated contract reviews and compliance checks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Nuñez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blockchain Initiatives Have Been Adopted by 60% of Fortune 500 Companies: Coinbase Survey]]></title>
        <id>10d97a00-15d4-4edb-91e7-ab30a770871c</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/06/10/blockchain-initiatives-have-been-adopted-by-60-of-fortune-500-companies-coinbase-survey"/>
        <updated>2025-06-10T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The crypto exchange surveyed Fortune 500 company execs and decision makers at small and medium-sized firms in the U.S. to assess crypto adoption trends.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Will Canny</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Zencoder just launched an AI that can replace days of QA work in two hours]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3011083</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/zencoder-just-launched-an-ai-that-can-replace-days-of-qa-work-in-two-hours/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-10T12:59:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Zencoder launches Zentester, an AI-powered testing agent that automates end-to-end software testing, as the startup competes with GitHub Copilot and other AI coding tools in the rapidly consolidating market.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Nuñez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The curious case of shell commands, or how "this bug is required by POSIX" (2021)]]></title>
        <id>https://notes.volution.ro/v1/2021/01/notes/502e747f/</id>
        <link href="https://notes.volution.ro/v1/2021/01/notes/502e747f/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-10T12:56:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Strategy Inc vs. BlackRock: Which is the better Bitcoin proxy stock for your portfolio?]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/explained/strategy-inc-vs-blackrock-which-is-the-better-bitcoin-proxy-stock-for-your-portfolio</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/explained/strategy-inc-vs-blackrock-which-is-the-better-bitcoin-proxy-stock-for-your-portfolio?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-06-10T12:47:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Strategy Inc vs. IBIT: Best Bitcoin Proxy Stock in 2025?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Bradley Peak</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Your AI and Data Future is Sovereign]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1118376</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/06/10/1118376/your-ai-and-data-future-is-sovereign/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-10T12:14:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[EDB CEO, Kevin Dallas, takes the stage at MIT Technology Review's EmTech AI event.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Courtney Dobson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Download: IBM’s quantum computer, and cuts to military AI testing]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1118372</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/06/10/1118372/the-download-ibms-quantum-computer-and-cuts-to-military-ai-testing/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-10T12:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is today’s edition of The Download, our weekday newsletter that provides a daily dose of what’s going on in the world of technology. IBM aims to build the world’s first large-scale, error-corrected quantum computer by 2028 The news: IBM announced detailed plans today to build an error-corrected quantum computer with significantly more computational capability than existing…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rhiannon Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum Advocate William Mougayar to Lead Ecosystem's New Profile-Raising Initiative]]></title>
        <id>63ceb891-7b04-40db-8982-4cb4674e4165</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2025/06/10/ethereum-market-research-centre-introduced-by-eth-o-g-william-mougayar"/>
        <updated>2025-06-10T12:04:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Ethereum Market Research Centre (EMRC) is a community-led initiative aimed at bridging the education gap for institutional and professional audiences.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ian Allison</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Onlook (YC W25) Is Hiring an engineer in SF]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=44235716</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=44235716"/>
        <updated>2025-06-10T12:00:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why is Ethereum (ETH) price up today?]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/why-is-ethereum-eth-price-up-today</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/why-is-ethereum-eth-price-up-today?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-06-10T11:55:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ETH price is up 7% on June 10 with persistent Ethereum ETF flows and record open interest backing Ether’s upside potential.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Nancy Lubale</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[87 deepfake scam rings taken down across Asia in Q1 2025: Report]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitget-deepfake-scam-rings-crackdown-asia-q1-2025</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitget-deepfake-scam-rings-crackdown-asia-q1-2025?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-06-10T11:53:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new report from Bitget, SlowMist and Elliptic highlights the severity of deepfake scams, urging both individuals and organizations to adopt more stringent preventive measures.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Lyne Qian</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘Apple should buy Bitcoin,’ Saylor says, as share buyback disappoints]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/apple-buy-bitcoin-stock-buybacks-michael-saylor</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/apple-buy-bitcoin-stock-buybacks-michael-saylor?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-06-10T11:53:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin exposure may provide a lucrative financial opportunity for Apple’s stock buyback program, according to Michael Saylor.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Zoltan Vardai</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Show HN: High End Color Quantizer]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/big-nacho/patolette</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/big-nacho/patolette"/>
        <updated>2025-06-10T11:50:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Core 30 to Increase OP_RETURN Data Limit After Developer Debate Concludes]]></title>
        <id>806a0a14-d81b-4e1c-ab67-2791876c761d</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/tech/2025/06/10/bitcoin-core-30-to-increase-op_return-data-limit-after-developer-debate-concludes"/>
        <updated>2025-06-10T11:43:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Core 30 is scheduled to be implemented in October.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sam Reynolds</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Daybook Americas: BTC Holds Below $110K as QCP Sees ‘Tight Range’; Altcoins Outperform]]></title>
        <id>95a84ec4-cff3-41cc-9f34-ac605cfe8415</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/daybook-us/2025/06/10/crypto-daybook-americas-btc-holds-below-usd110k-as-qcp-sees-tight-range-altcoins-outperform"/>
        <updated>2025-06-10T11:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Your day-ahead look for June 10, 2025]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>James Van Straten</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Prism+ X340 Pro Evo Lightning Review: Ultrawide That’s Somewhat Lacking]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=355289</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/355289/prism-x340-pro-evo-lightning-review/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-10T11:00:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you’re one of those individuals that finds appeal in 34-inch ultrawide curved gaming monitors, but you’re not looking to blow your budget, Prism+ has pretty much been a go-to brand, and its X340 Pro Evo is a display that should scratch that itch. After spending some time living with it, here’s what I can […]
The post Prism+ X340 Pro Evo Lightning Review: Ultrawide That’s Somewhat Lacking appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John Law</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bank of Japan pivot to QE may fuel Bitcoin rally — Arthur Hayes]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/boj-june-introduce-qe-next-bitcoin-catalyst-arthur-hayes</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/boj-june-introduce-qe-next-bitcoin-catalyst-arthur-hayes?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-06-10T10:49:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Bank of Japan’s June meeting could trigger a Bitcoin rally if it restarts quantitative easing, as bond yield concerns push institutions toward BTC as a hedge.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Zoltan Vardai</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Guggenheim Treasury Services to Issue Digital Commercial Paper on the XRP Ledger]]></title>
        <id>e4f6761c-2a46-4347-bfb7-cdea40f76d02</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/06/10/guggenheim-treasury-services-taps-zeconomy-to-issue-digital-commercial-paper-on-the-xrp-ledger"/>
        <updated>2025-06-10T10:47:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With over $280 million of volume to date, the Zeconomy-powered DCP marks the first native issuance of digital commercial paper on the XRP Ledger.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shaurya Malwa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CompactLog – Solving CT Scalability with LSM-Trees]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/Barre/compact_log</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/Barre/compact_log"/>
        <updated>2025-06-10T10:45:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Xpeng To Unveil New G7 Mid-Size Electric SUV Tomorrow]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=355434</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/355434/xpeng-to-unveil-new-g7-mid-size-suv/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-10T10:15:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Following the launch of the P7, Xpeng is set to unveil its new G7 mid-size SUV in China tomorrow evening (11 June). According to company chairman He Xiaopeng, the G7 will be Xpeng’s first true “AI car”, equipped with the company’s self-developed Turing AI chip that enhances driving capabilities and a cutting-edge windshield display designed […]
The post Xpeng To Unveil New G7 Mid-Size Electric SUV Tomorrow appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Keran</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[IBM aims to build the world’s first large-scale, error-corrected quantum computer by 2028]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1118297</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/06/10/1118297/ibm-large-scale-error-corrected-quantum-computer-by-2028/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-10T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[IBM announced detailed plans today to build an error-corrected quantum computer with significantly more computational capability than existing machines by 2028. It hopes to make the computer available to users via the cloud by 2029.  The proposed machine, named Starling, will consist of a network of modules, each of which contains a set of chips,…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sophia Chen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Next as Ether Zooms 7%, DOGE Leads Majors Gains Amid Bitcoin Euphoria]]></title>
        <id>cc900e96-a1b7-48e6-a4a8-ae61f0e4d6e4</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/06/10/what-next-as-ether-zooms-7-doge-leads-majors-gains-amid-bitcoin-euphoria"/>
        <updated>2025-06-10T09:57:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin’s climb above $109,000 set the stage for broad-based gains in altcoins, with traders eyeing key inflation data later this week.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shaurya Malwa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why is the crypto market up today?]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/why-is-the-crypto-market-up-today</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/why-is-the-crypto-market-up-today?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-06-10T09:54:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The crypto market is up today, reflecting investors' optimism for a possible continued rally amid increasing institutional demand for cryptocurrency investment products.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Nancy Lubale</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Strategy Shifts Capital Raise to Preferred Stocks as Common Share Issuance Loses Allure]]></title>
        <id>be8876e7-385e-4c6e-8577-ebc69b8e7a8c</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/06/10/strategy-shifts-capital-raise-to-preferred-stocks-as-common-share-issuance-loses-allure"/>
        <updated>2025-06-10T09:23:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sales of STRK and STRF preferred shares allow Strategy to fund bitcoin purchases without diluting common shareholders.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>James Van Straten</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Pentagon is gutting the team that tests AI and weapons systems]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1118229</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/06/10/1118229/pentagon-gutting-ai-test/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-10T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Trump administration’s chainsaw approach to federal spending lives on, even as Elon Musk turns on the president. On May 28, Secretary of Defense Pete Hegseth announced he’d be gutting a key office at the Department of Defense responsible for testing and evaluating the safety of weapons and AI systems. As part of a string…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>James O'Donnell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trump’s CFTC pick calls blockchain a society-shaping technology]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/trump-cftc-pick-quintenz-blockchain-impact-society</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/trump-cftc-pick-quintenz-blockchain-impact-society?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-06-10T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Trump’s CFTC nominee Brian Quintenz says blockchain will reshape industries beyond finance and calls for clear crypto rules to protect US leadership.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Amin Haqshanas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Denmark: Minister for Digitalization wants to phase out Microsoft]]></title>
        <id>https://nordjyske.dk/nyheder/politik/digitaliseringsminister-vil-udfase-microsoft-i-sit-eget-ministerium/5616096</id>
        <link href="https://nordjyske.dk/nyheder/politik/digitaliseringsminister-vil-udfase-microsoft-i-sit-eget-ministerium/5616096"/>
        <updated>2025-06-10T08:56:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Riot Sells $1.58M of Bitfarms Shares as Part of Investment Review]]></title>
        <id>a37db60e-6bf1-42c6-a43c-c728437a9453</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2025/06/10/riot-sells-usd1-58m-of-bitfarms-shares-as-part-of-investment-review"/>
        <updated>2025-06-10T08:55:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[U.S.-based miner retains over 14% ownership after open market sales.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>James Van Straten</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Honda Recalls 87,490 Cars Due To Fuel Pump Issues]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=355393</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/355393/honda-recalls-87490-cars-due-to-fuel-pump-issues/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-10T08:45:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Honda Malaysia released a press statement today announcing a massive product recall involving 87,490 cars. The purpose of this recall is to replace the fuel pump of these models as a precautionary measure. In the press release, the automaker has listed two components of the fuel pump that need to be replaced. The first is […]
The post Honda Recalls 87,490 Cars Due To Fuel Pump Issues appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Keran</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[eufy RVC Omni E25: Automating Your Cleaning Routine The Smart Way]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=355412</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/355412/eufy-rvc-omni-e25-automating-cleaning-routine-smart-way/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-10T08:44:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you’ve ever lived with a child or a pet, or simply are too busy to pick up a broom, you’d know what it’s like to have an unkempt home. It also means you are no stranger to that skin-crawling feeling of dirt and sediments clinging to your feet like they were magnets. If that […]
The post eufy RVC Omni E25: Automating Your Cleaning Routine The Smart Way appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Newsdesk</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Coinbase Premium hits 4-month high as 550K BTC leaves exchanges]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-coinbase-premium-hits-4-month-high-550k-btc-leaves-exchanges</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-coinbase-premium-hits-4-month-high-550k-btc-leaves-exchanges?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-06-10T08:44:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin demand in the US is rising, while spot exchanges see their reserves decline by one third in less than a year, per new data from CryptoQuant.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by William Suberg</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OPPO A5i Lineup Goes Official With Snapdragon 6s 4G Gen 1, 6,000mAh Battery For Pro]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=355409</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/355409/oppo-a5i/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-10T08:36:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[OPPO has officially two new smartphones under the A series, namely the A5i and A5i Pro. Both phones are powered by the same chipset as the A5 Pro 4G, but the Pro gets a bigger batter, a better imaging setup, and higher durability. The models sport a 6.67-inch 720p LCD display with a 90Hz refresh […]
The post OPPO A5i Lineup Goes Official With Snapdragon 6s 4G Gen 1, 6,000mAh Battery For Pro appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ikmal Rozlan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SocGen’s Crypto Arm Unveils Dollar Stablecoin on Ethereum and Solana]]></title>
        <id>ed1388cc-8bdf-4335-b190-bc3ff65d28f2</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2025/06/10/socgen-s-crypto-arm-unveils-dollar-stablecoin-on-ethereum-and-solana"/>
        <updated>2025-06-10T08:30:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SG Forge’s USD CoinVertible has Bank of New York Mellon acting as reserve custodian for the token.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ian Allison</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why is Bitcoin price up today?]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/why-is-bitcoin-price-up-today</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/why-is-bitcoin-price-up-today?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-06-10T07:59:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin price recovers above $109,000 as multiple BTC market metrics show an improvement in investor sentiment.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Nancy Lubale</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tesla Optimus Gen 2 On Display At 1 Utama Until 15 June 2025]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=355395</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/355395/tesla-optimus-gen-2-on-display-at-1-utama-until-15-june-2025/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-10T07:52:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tesla’s second-generation Optimus robot is now on display at 1 Utama shopping mall as part of an ongoing roadshow. For most of us, its appearance came as a surprise, having received little to no fanfare – aside from a single post shared days earlier on Tesla Malaysia’s official Instagram account. That said, don’t expect it […]
The post Tesla Optimus Gen 2 On Display At 1 Utama Until 15 June 2025 appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Heirul Kamel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ripple commits $5M more toward crypto research in APAC]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/ripple-commits-5-million-crypto-research-apac</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/ripple-commits-5-million-crypto-research-apac?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-06-10T07:05:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The funds are on top of the $25 million that Ripple committed last month to education nonprofit organizations in the US.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Tarang Khaitan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Société Générale launches US dollar stablecoin on Ethereum and Solana]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/societe-generale-forge-to-launch-a-usd-denominated-stablecoin</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/societe-generale-forge-to-launch-a-usd-denominated-stablecoin?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-06-10T06:55:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Société Générale’s crypto arm launches its USDCV stablecoin on Ethereum and Solana, with BNY as custodian and a global rollout aimed at trading and settlement.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Adrian Zmudzinski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dongfeng Set To Launch 007 Sedan And Nammi 06 SUV]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=355362</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/355362/dongfeng-set-to-launch-007-sedan-nammi-06-suv/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-10T06:48:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There are many Chinese automakers that have entered the Malaysian market and one of them is Dongfeng, which is one of China’s largest automobile manufacturers. The company entered the Malaysian market with the Box, which has a starting price of RM100,700, and more recently it has hinted through a Facebook post that the company has […]
The post Dongfeng Set To Launch 007 Sedan And Nammi 06 SUV appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Keran</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto social media sees rising interest in AI taking jobs: Santiment]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/crypto-social-media-sees-rising-interest-in-ai-taking-jobs-santiment</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/crypto-social-media-sees-rising-interest-in-ai-taking-jobs-santiment?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-06-10T06:24:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Other narratives of interest on social media included the accumulation of crypto by whales like millionaire crypto trader James Wynn, Solana, Loud Token and various memecoins.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Stephen Katte</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Alleged Samsung Galaxy Watch8 Classic Appears Online]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=355374</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/355374/samsung-galaxy-watch8-classic-appears-online/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-10T06:16:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We have seen the Samsung Galaxy Watch8 series, including a Classic model, appear in the Chinese certification listing. So while it’s no surprise that we’ll be seeing them appear online at some point, it is where it has showed up that was the mild shocker. Serial leakster @OnLeaks has shared on X an eBay listing […]
The post Alleged Samsung Galaxy Watch8 Classic Appears Online appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ian Chee</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[South Korea moves to legalize stablecoins with new crypto bill]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/south-korea-plan-allow-stablecoins-introduces-bill</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/south-korea-plan-allow-stablecoins-introduces-bill?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-06-10T06:16:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[South Korea’s ruling party under new president Lee Jae-myung is pushing legislation to allow local stablecoin issuance and boost crypto market growth.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Martin Young</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin lacks strong catalyst to beat its $112K ATH: Analyst]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-price-lacks-fuel-surpass-all-time-high</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-price-lacks-fuel-surpass-all-time-high?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-06-10T06:11:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitfinex analysts say that Bitcoin holders who bought in Q1 are now being tested as “the price churns sideways near ATH levels.”]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Ciaran Lyons</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Canary Capital spins up Delaware trust for staked Injective ETF]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/canary-capital-delaware-trust-staked-injective-etf</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/canary-capital-delaware-trust-staked-injective-etf?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-06-10T05:47:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fund manager Canary Capital has taken a typical first step for an ETF, creating a Delaware trust for a fund that would stake the Injective token.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Jesse Coghlan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Reinforcement Pre-Training]]></title>
        <id>https://arxiv.org/abs/2506.08007</id>
        <link href="https://arxiv.org/abs/2506.08007"/>
        <updated>2025-06-10T05:30:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto scammers plead guilty to $37M scheme targeting Americans]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/5-plead-guilty-multinational-crypto-scam-scheme</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/5-plead-guilty-multinational-crypto-scam-scheme?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-06-10T05:13:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Five members of an international crypto scam ring are accused of stealing nearly $37 million from American victims and sending the funds to Cambodia.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Brayden Lindrea</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Successful people set constraints rather than chasing goals]]></title>
        <id>https://www.joanwestenberg.com/smart-people-dont-chase-goals-they-create-limits/</id>
        <link href="https://www.joanwestenberg.com/smart-people-dont-chase-goals-they-create-limits/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-10T05:01:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon doubles down on AI with $20B Pennsylvania investment]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/amazon-invests-20b-pennsylvania-ai-data-centers</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/amazon-invests-20b-pennsylvania-ai-data-centers?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-06-10T04:47:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon made similar commitments in North Carolina, with $10 billion earmarked to expand its data center infrastructure in the US State.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Stephen Katte</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto platform Parataxis eyes public listing via SPAC merger]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/crypto-platform-parataxis-eyes-public-listing-via-spac-merger</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/crypto-platform-parataxis-eyes-public-listing-via-spac-merger?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-06-10T04:29:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New York City-based Bitcoin investment company Parataxis Holdings is exploring a public listing via merging with SilverBox Corp IV, a special purpose acquisition company.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Martin Young</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Infinix Shows Off Smart 10 Plus In New Teasers (Updated)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=355357</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/355357/infinix-shows-off-smart-10-plus-in-new-teasers/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-10T04:12:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Update – 2:16PM: Infinix has officially unveiled the Smart 10 series in Malaysia. The original article has been updated to include the new information provided by the company. Original Article – 12:12PM: Infinix is preparing to release the newest additions to its entry-level smartphone lineup, the Smart 10 series. The series includes a regular Smart […]
The post Infinix Shows Off Smart 10 Plus In New Teasers (Updated) appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nurul Kamil</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HONOR X6c Hits The Shelves At RM599]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=355351</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/355351/honor-x6c/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-10T03:28:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HONOR Penang has dropped a surprising announcement as it revealed the local price for the new X6c. Placed below even the X7c, the new smartphone is now the cheapest offering in the X series, but it still brings durability and a big battery to the table. The X6c sports a 6.61-inch 720p LCD display with […]
The post HONOR X6c Hits The Shelves At RM599 appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ikmal Rozlan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Implementing DOES> in Forth, the entire reason I started this mess]]></title>
        <id>https://boston.conman.org/2025/06/09.1</id>
        <link href="https://boston.conman.org/2025/06/09.1"/>
        <updated>2025-06-10T01:36:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Asia Morning Briefing: BTC Slips Below $110K as 'Signs of Fatigue' Emerging]]></title>
        <id>ad44cefa-8cd0-4203-95cd-ea71ac1d7ab3</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/06/09/asia-morning-briefing-btc-slips-below-110k-as-signs-of-fatigue-emerging"/>
        <updated>2025-06-10T01:32:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[PLUS: Institutional Ethereum staking might drive ETH’s next rally.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sam Reynolds</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why agents are bad pair programmers]]></title>
        <id>https://justin.searls.co/posts/why-agents-are-bad-pair-programmers/</id>
        <link href="https://justin.searls.co/posts/why-agents-are-bad-pair-programmers/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-09T23:36:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sly Stone has died]]></title>
        <id>https://abcnews.go.com/US/sly-stone-pioneering-leader-funk-band-sly-family/story?id=122666345</id>
        <link href="https://abcnews.go.com/US/sly-stone-pioneering-leader-funk-band-sly-family/story?id=122666345"/>
        <updated>2025-06-09T21:42:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Climbs Above $110K, 'At Crossroads' for Next Major Move]]></title>
        <id>9eaf7e7f-eead-4cab-bc34-5bc75be07930</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/06/09/bitcoin-climbs-above-110k-at-crossroads-for-next-major-move"/>
        <updated>2025-06-09T21:31:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One analyst characterized bitcoin's recovery from last week's decline as a "peaceful rally," with buyers stepping in to support the uptrend.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Krisztian Sandor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Aptos' APT Gains 4% on Significant Volume, Has More Potential Upside]]></title>
        <id>38602652-bd8c-4917-bb01-d1b446d2fce2</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/06/09/aptos-apt-gains-4-on-significant-volume-has-more-potential-upside"/>
        <updated>2025-06-09T21:11:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Support at $4.84 held through subsequent retests suggesting potential continuation of the uptrend.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CD Analytics</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Containerization is a Swift package for running Linux containers on macOS]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/apple/containerization</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/apple/containerization"/>
        <updated>2025-06-09T20:53:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Apple makes major AI advance with image generation technology rivaling DALL-E and Midjourney]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3011035</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/apple-makes-major-ai-advance-with-image-generation-technology-rivaling-dall-e-and-midjourney/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-09T18:50:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Apple researchers develop STARFlow, a breakthrough AI image generation system that challenges diffusion models used by DALL-E and Midjourney with competitive performance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Nuñez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trump Media and Semler Scientific Could Be Cheapest Bitcoin Treasury Companies by This Metric]]></title>
        <id>2abcb288-e047-4b22-810e-47dc6bb7c0fa</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/06/09/trump-media-and-semler-scientific-could-be-cheapest-bitcoin-treasury-companies-by-this-metric"/>
        <updated>2025-06-09T18:40:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The commonly used mNAV is an insufficient gauge for measuring relative valuations, argues NYDIG's Greg Cipolaro]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tom Carreras</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[U.S. SEC Chair Says Working on 'Innovation Exemption' for DeFi Platforms]]></title>
        <id>714b2225-a624-499b-9efc-60b43f5cf30b</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2025/06/09/u-s-sec-chair-says-working-on-innovation-exemption-for-defi-platforms"/>
        <updated>2025-06-09T18:28:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a final SEC crypto roundtable, the securities watchdog dug into decentralized finance, with Chairman Paul Atkins promising efforts to ease developers' path.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jesse Hamilton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Plasma’s XPL Token Sale Attracts $500M as Investors Chase Stablecoin Plays]]></title>
        <id>5ee0061c-eea0-4edf-846b-22d0a079cbc7</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/06/09/plasmas-xpl-token-sale-attracts-500m-as-investors-chase-stablecoin-plays"/>
        <updated>2025-06-09T18:14:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The oversubscribed raise follows stablecoin issuer Circle’s massive IPO last week, underscoring investor appetite for stablecoin-related projects.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Krisztian Sandor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Apple announces Foundation Models and Containerization frameworks, etc]]></title>
        <id>https://www.apple.com/newsroom/2025/06/apple-supercharges-its-tools-and-technologies-for-developers/</id>
        <link href="https://www.apple.com/newsroom/2025/06/apple-supercharges-its-tools-and-technologies-for-developers/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-09T17:44:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Show HN: Munal OS: a graphical experimental OS with WASM sandboxing]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/Askannz/munal-os</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/Askannz/munal-os"/>
        <updated>2025-06-09T17:34:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Denuvo Analysis]]></title>
        <id>https://connorjaydunn.github.io/blog/posts/denuvo-analysis/</id>
        <link href="https://connorjaydunn.github.io/blog/posts/denuvo-analysis/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-09T16:50:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tell HN: Help restore the tax deduction for software dev in the US (Section 174)]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=44226145</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=44226145"/>
        <updated>2025-06-09T16:28:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What are Onchain Agents: An Introduction to Autonomous, Agent-Driven Web]]></title>
        <id>6840a302a1fc8e00012e657d</id>
        <link href="https://blog.quicknode.com/introduction-to-onchain-agents/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-09T15:37:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An introduction to onchain AI agents: autonomous programs that combine blockchain trustlessness with AI intelligence. Learn how they work.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Unhashed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Top Blockchain Data Tools: How to be Informed Onchain?]]></title>
        <id>6840a419a1fc8e00012e658d</id>
        <link href="https://blog.quicknode.com/top-blockchain-data-tools/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-09T15:32:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Web3 in 2025 runs on data. This guide covers the best onchain data tools and analytics platforms and how QuickNode Streams powers them.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Unhashed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Common Solana RPC Errors & Fixes Using QuickNode Logs]]></title>
        <id>6840a20da1fc8e00012e6573</id>
        <link href="https://blog.quicknode.com/solana-rpc-errors-quicknode-logs/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-09T15:28:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn how to identify and fix common Solana RPC errors using QuickNode Logs that provide real-time insights into every request and response.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Unhashed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Developer's Guide to Monad: EVM-Compatible L1 Architecture and Implementation]]></title>
        <id>6840a4c8a1fc8e00012e6598</id>
        <link href="https://blog.quicknode.com/monad-developer-guide/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-09T15:09:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Build faster, cheaper, and better on Monad: A deep dive into Monad’s architecture, performance features, and developer workflows.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Unhashed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Download: an inspiring toy robot arm, and why AM radio matters]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1118186</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/06/09/1118186/the-download-an-inspiring-toy-robot-arm-and-why-am-radio-matters/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-09T12:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is today’s edition of The Download, our weekday newsletter that provides a daily dose of what’s going on in the world of technology. How a 1980s toy robot arm inspired modern robotics —Jon Keegan As a child of an electronic engineer, I spent a lot of time in our local Radio Shack as a kid. While…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rhiannon Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Like humans, AI is forcing institutions to rethink their purpose]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3010794</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/like-humans-ai-is-forcing-institutions-to-rethink-their-purpose/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-08T20:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Like people undergoing cognitive migration, institutions must reassess what they were made for in this age of AI.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gary Grossman, Edelman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Agent-based computing is outgrowing the web as we know it]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3010786</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/agent-based-computing-is-outgrowing-the-web-as-we-know-it/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-07T22:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AI agents are moving from passive assistants to active participants. Today, we ask them to do. Tomorrow, we’ll authorize them to act.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Justin Westcott, Edelman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Animate a mesh across a sphere's surface]]></title>
        <id>https://garden.bradwoods.io/notes/javascript/three-js/animate-a-mesh-on-a-spheres-surface</id>
        <link href="https://garden.bradwoods.io/notes/javascript/three-js/animate-a-mesh-on-a-spheres-surface"/>
        <updated>2025-06-06T21:47:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Proof' Review: Finding Truth in Numbers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.wsj.com/arts-culture/books/proof-review-finding-truth-in-numbers-b9779228</id>
        <link href="https://www.wsj.com/arts-culture/books/proof-review-finding-truth-in-numbers-b9779228"/>
        <updated>2025-06-06T21:17:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Primer on Molecular Dynamics]]></title>
        <id>https://www.owlposting.com/p/a-primer-on-molecular-dynamics</id>
        <link href="https://www.owlposting.com/p/a-primer-on-molecular-dynamics"/>
        <updated>2025-06-06T19:39:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sam Altman calls for ‘AI privilege’ as OpenAI clarifies court order to retain temporary and deleted ChatGPT sessions]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3010670</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/sam-altman-calls-for-ai-privilege-as-openai-clarifies-court-order-to-retain-temporary-and-deleted-chatgpt-sessions/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-06T17:48:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Should talking to an AI chatbot be protected and privileged information, like talking to a doctor or lawyer? A new court order raises the idea]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carl Franzen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Voice AI that actually converts: New TTS model boosts sales 15% for major brands]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3010147</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/voice-ai-that-actually-converts-new-tts-model-boosts-sales-15-for-major-brands/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-06T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new spoken language model can quickly generate “infinite” new voices of varying genders, ages, demographics, based on a simple text prompt.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Taryn Plumb</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[From electrical engineering student to CTO with Hitesh Choudhary [Podcast #175]]]></title>
        <id>6842e00169a5099a551058ce</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/from-electrical-engineering-student-to-cto-with-hitesh-choudhary-podcast-175/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-06T12:33:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On this week's episode of the podcast, freeCodeCamp founder Quincy Larson interviews former CTO and prolific programming teacher Hitesh Choudhary.   We talk about: The limits of AI in building a robust codebase Time management Higher Education in ...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Download: China’s AI agent boom, and GPS alternatives]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1118044</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/06/06/1118044/the-download-chinas-ai-agent-boom-and-gps-alternatives/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-06T12:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is today’s edition of The Download, our weekday newsletter that provides a daily dose of what’s going on in the world of technology. Manus has kick-started an AI agent boom in China Last year, China saw a boom in foundation models, the do-everything large language models that underpin the AI revolution. This year, the focus has…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rhiannon Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Protect Your Remote Workforce from Cyber Attacks]]></title>
        <id>6842cf8a6fcd9b03c19d04ea</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/protect-remote-workforce-from-cyber-attacks/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-06T11:22:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Working remotely gives your team flexibility, but it also opens the door to cyber threats. Remote workers are more exposed without the protection of office firewalls and on-site IT teams.  Hackers know that people often use weak passwords, forget to ...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Manish Shivanandhan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Reduce Technical Debt in the Power Platform]]></title>
        <id>6842c4f3e7fdc9878ba5dadd</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-reduce-technical-debt-in-the-power-platform/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-06T10:37:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Technical debt refers to the future cost – measured in terms of time, money, effort, or opportunity – of choosing expedient solutions today instead of more deliberate and scalable ones. And it's not just a pro-code concept. It might be easier to unde...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brandon Wozniewicz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Micro-Frontend Architecture Handbook]]></title>
        <id>6842c120a3469a9ca728862b</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/complete-micro-frontends-guide/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-06T10:21:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Over the years, in my role as a lead full-stack developer, solutions architect, and mentor, I’ve been immersed in the world of micro frontend architecture, working across different large-scale frontend projects where multiple teams, stacks, and deplo...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Maksimchenko</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why doctors should look for ways to prescribe hope]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1117937</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/06/06/1117937/why-doctors-should-look-for-ways-to-prescribe-hope/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-06T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This week, I’ve been thinking about the powerful connection between mind and body. Some new research suggests that people with heart conditions have better outcomes when they are more hopeful and optimistic. Hopelessness, on the other hand, is associated with a significantly higher risk of death. The findings build upon decades of fascinating research into…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jessica Hamzelou</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Inside the race to find GPS alternatives]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1117978</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/06/06/1117978/inside-the-race-to-find-gps-alternatives/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-06T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Later this month, an inconspicuous 150-kilogram satellite is set to launch into space aboard the SpaceX Transporter 14 mission. Once in orbit, it will test super-accurate next-generation satnav technology designed to make up for the shortcomings of the US Global Positioning System (GPS).  The satellite is the first of a planned constellation called Pulsar, which…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tereza Pultarova</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google claims Gemini 2.5 Pro preview beats DeepSeek R1 and Grok 3 Beta in coding performance]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3010537</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/google-claims-gemini-2-5-pro-preview-beats-deepseek-r1-and-grok-3-beta-in-coding-performance/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-05T21:30:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google said the newest version of Gemini 2.5 Pro, now on preview, gives faster and more creative responses while performing better than OpenAI's o3.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Emilia David</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OpenFeign vs WebClient: How to Choose a REST Client for Your Spring Boot Project]]></title>
        <id>6841f2c63a801418642db429</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/best-choice-openfeign-or-webclient/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-05T19:40:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When building microservices with Spring Boot, you’ll have to decide how the services will communicate with one another. The basic choices in terms of protocols are Messaging and REST. In this article we’ll discuss tools based on REST, which is a comm...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mario Casari</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[From Commit to Production: Hands-On GitOps Promotion with GitHub Actions, Argo CD, Helm, and Kargo]]></title>
        <id>6841f1319c94d5fa67dae6e3</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/from-commit-to-production-hands-on-gitops-promotion-with-github-actions-argo-cd-helm-and-kargo/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-05T19:34:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Have you ever wanted to go beyond ‘hello world’ and build a real, production-style CI/CD pipeline – starting from scratch? Let’s pause for a moment: what are you trying to learn from your DevOps journey? Are you focusing on GitOps-style deployments, ...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nitheesh Poojary</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Manus has kick-started an AI agent boom in China]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1117958</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/06/05/1117958/china-ai-agent-boom/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-05T18:45:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Last year, China saw a boom in foundation models, the do-everything large language models that underpin the AI revolution. This year, the focus has shifted to AI agents—systems that are less about responding to users’ queries and more about autonomously accomplishing things for them.  There are now a host of Chinese startups building these general-purpose…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Caiwei Chen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Solidroad just raised $6.5M to reinvent customer service with AI that coaches, not replaces]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3010526</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/solidroad-just-raised-6-5m-to-reinvent-customer-service-with-ai-that-coaches-not-replaces/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-05T17:39:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dublin AI startup Solidroad raises $6.5M from First Round Capital to transform customer service training with AI that coaches human agents and improves satisfaction scores.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Nuñez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How much information do LLMs really memorize? Now we know, thanks to Meta, Google, Nvidia and Cornell]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3010502</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/how-much-information-do-llms-really-memorize-now-we-know-thanks-to-meta-google-nvidia-and-cornell/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-05T15:35:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Using a clever solution, researchers find GPT-style models have a fixed memorization capacity of approximately 3.6 bits per parameter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carl Franzen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Securing AI at scale: Databricks and Noma close the inference vulnerability gap]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3010387</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/security/databricks-noma-tackle-cisos-ai-inference-nightmare/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-05T14:13:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Databricks Ventures and Noma Security partner to tackle critical AI inference vulnerabilities with real-time threat analytics, proactive red teaming, and robust governance, helping CISOs confidently scale secure enterprise AI deployments.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Louis Columbus</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Download: funding a CRISPR embryo startup, and bad news for clean cement]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1117928</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/06/05/1117928/the-download-funding-a-crispr-embryo-startup-and-bad-news-for-clean-cement/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-05T12:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is today’s edition of The Download, our weekday newsletter that provides a daily dose of what’s going on in the world of technology. Crypto billionaire Brian Armstrong is ready to invest in CRISPR baby tech Brian Armstrong, the billionaire CEO of the cryptocurrency exchange Coinbase, says he’s ready to fund a US startup focused on gene-editing…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rhiannon Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Stop guessing why your LLMs break: Anthropic’s new tool shows you exactly what goes wrong]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3009970</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/stop-guessing-why-your-llms-break-anthropics-new-tool-shows-you-exactly-what-goes-wrong/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-04T22:39:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Anthropic's open-source circuit tracing tool can help developers debug, optimize, and control AI for reliable and trustable applications.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ben Dickson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[C Game Development with Raylib]]></title>
        <id>68408c368ab45ab43dad48c6</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/c-game-development-with-raylib/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-04T18:11:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Making games is one of the best ways to learn programming. It pushes you to think logically, stay organized, and solve real problems. Plus, it’s just fun. If you're looking to improve your C programming skills and learn how to create a complete game ...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OpenAI hits 3M business users and launches workplace tools to take on Microsoft]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3010196</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/openai-hits-3m-business-users-and-launches-workplace-tools-to-take-on-microsoft/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-04T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[OpenAI reaches 3 million paying business users with 50% growth since February, launching new workplace AI tools including connectors and coding agents to compete with Microsoft.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Nuñez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mistral AI’s new coding assistant takes direct aim at GitHub Copilot]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3010264</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/mistral-ais-new-coding-assistant-takes-direct-aim-at-github-copilot/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-04T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mistral AI launches enterprise coding assistant with on-premise deployment to challenge GitHub Copilot, targeting corporate developers with data sovereignty and AI model customization.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Nuñez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nvidia says its Blackwell chips lead benchmarks in training AI LLMs]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3010219</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/games/nvidia-says-its-blackwell-chips-lead-benchmarks-in-training-ai-llms/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-04T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nvidia announced today its Blackwell chips are leading the AI benchmarks when it comes to training AI large-language models.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dean Takahashi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Go is a good fit for agents]]></title>
        <id>https://docs.hatchet.run/blog/go-agents</id>
        <link href="https://docs.hatchet.run/blog/go-agents"/>
        <updated>2025-06-04T12:14:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn Godot – Course for Beginners in Spanish]]></title>
        <id>68402e7af9ce257b34574bed</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-godot-course-for-beginners-in-spanish/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-04T11:31:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Godot is an open-source, lightweight, and powerful game engine. This course will teach you how to use it to bring your game ideas to life. We just published a course on the freeCodeCamp.org Spanish YouTube channel that will guide you step by step thr...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Estefania Cassingena Navone</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[General Chemistry College Course]]></title>
        <id>683f922e111e5ab9c8a4e188</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/general-chemistry-college-course/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-04T00:24:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learning general chemistry is one of the most important steps you can take if you're planning to study science in any serious way. Chemistry is foundational. It connects to biology, physics, environmental science, engineering, medicine, and so much m...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Your AI models are failing in production—Here’s how to fix model selection]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3010160</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/your-ai-models-are-failing-in-production-heres-how-to-fix-model-selection/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-03T23:47:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Allen Institute of AI updated its reward model evaluation RewardBench to better reflect real-life scenarios for enterprises.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Emilia David</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nvidia CEO Jensen Huang sings praises of processor in Nintendo Switch 2]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3010188</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/gaming-business/nvidia-ceo-jensen-huang-sings-praises-of-processor-in-nintendo-switch-2/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-03T22:48:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nvidia CEO Jensen Huang, a key supplier for the hybrid console, sang the praises of the Switch 2 and its main processor today.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dean Takahashi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Phonely’s new AI agents hit 99% accuracy—and customers can’t tell they’re not human]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3010136</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/phonelys-new-ai-agents-hit-99-accuracy-and-customers-cant-tell-theyre-not-human/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-03T20:31:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Phonely, Maitai and Groq achieve breakthrough in AI phone support with sub-second response times and 99.2% accuracy, enabling human-level conversational AI for call centers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Nuñez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Epic Games reveals The State of Unreal for 2025]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3009941</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/games/epic-games-reveals-the-state-of-unreal-for-2025/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-03T15:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Epic Games unveiled the State of Unreal in a keynote speech by CEO Tim Sweeney at the Unreal Fest in Orlando, Florida.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dean Takahashi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What game companies can learn from AI analysis of 1.5M gamer conversations | Creativ Company]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3009963</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/games/what-game-companies-can-learn-from-ai-analysis-of-1-5m-gamer-conversations-creativ-company/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-03T14:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Creativ Company is emerging today as a new kind of market intelligence company. It uses AI to do do sentiment analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dean Takahashi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Open Source LLM Agent Handbook: How to Automate Complex Tasks with LangGraph and CrewAI]]></title>
        <id>683f04aedfb685791a4e8dd2</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/the-open-source-llm-agent-handbook/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-03T14:20:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ever feel like your AI tools are a bit...well, passive? Like they just sit there, waiting for your next command? Imagine if they could take initiative, break down big problems, and even work together to get things done. That's exactly what LLM agents...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Balajee Asish Brahmandam</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CockroachDB’s distributed vector indexing tackles the looming AI data explosion enterprises aren’t ready for]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3009815</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/data-infrastructure/cockroachdbs-distributed-vector-indexing-tackles-the-looming-ai-data-explosion-enterprises-arent-ready-for/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-03T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Scaling distributed SQL queries needs more performance and efficiency in the agentic AI era. It’s a challenge Cockroach is looking to solve.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sean Michael Kerner</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Inside Intuit’s GenOS update: Why prompt optimization and intelligent data cognition are critical to enterprise agentic AI success]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3009858</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/inside-intuits-genos-update-why-prompt-optimization-and-intelligent-data-cognition-are-critical-to-enterprise-agentic-ai-success/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-03T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Intuit is using advanced genetic algorithms to help with prompt optimizations that could have significant impact for users.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sean Michael Kerner</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Car and chipmakers form group to develop open in-car connectivity]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3009910</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/games/car-and-chipmakers-form-group-to-develop-open-in-car-connectivity/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-03T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Automotive car makers, suppliers, semiconductor manufacturers and ecosystem partners announced the formation of the OpenGMSL Association.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dean Takahashi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Enterprise alert: PostgreSQL just became the database you can’t ignore for AI applications]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3009895</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/data-infrastructure/enterprise-alert-postgresql-just-became-the-database-you-cant-ignore-for-ai-applications/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-03T03:16:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Analysts provide insight on what the latest acquisition of a PostgreSQL database vendor means for enterprise data and AI.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sean Michael Kerner</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How S&P is using deep web scraping, ensemble learning and Snowflake architecture to collect 5X more data on SMEs]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3009651</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/data-infrastructure/how-sp-is-using-deep-web-scraping-ensemble-learning-and-snowflake-architecture-to-collect-5x-more-data-on-smes/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-02T21:45:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Previously, S&P only had data on about 2 million SMEs, but its AI-powered RiskGauge platform expanded that to 10 million.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Taryn Plumb</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google quietly launches AI Edge Gallery, letting Android phones run AI without the cloud]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3009810</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/google-quietly-launches-ai-edge-gallery-letting-android-phones-run-ai-without-the-cloud/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-02T20:46:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google quietly launched AI Edge Gallery, an experimental Android app that runs AI models offline without internet, bringing Hugging Face models directly to smartphones with enhanced privacy.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Nuñez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OpenAI’s Sora is now available for FREE to all users through Microsoft Bing Video Creator on mobile]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3009808</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/openais-sora-is-now-available-for-free-to-all-users-through-microsoft-bing-video-creator-on-mobile/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-02T19:01:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[OpenAI‘s Sora was one of the most hyped releases of the AI era, launching in December 2024, nearly 10 months after it was first previewed to awe-struck reactions due to its — at the time, at least — unprecedented level of realism, camera dynamism, and prompt adherence and 60-second long generation clips. However, much of […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carl Franzen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Powering High-Performance Web3 Experiences: Gravity (by Galxe) Launches on QuickNode]]></title>
        <id>683622d561c46d0001eed5d9</id>
        <link href="https://blog.quicknode.com/gravity-alpha-launch/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-29T13:54:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Explore Galxe Gravity’s omnichain power on QuickNode. Build scalable, identity-centric dApps effortlessly with dedicated endpoints and developer tools.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>QuickNode</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[QuickNode Accelerator - ChaiNova]]></title>
        <id>68377c476b77cd0001482835</id>
        <link href="https://blog.quicknode.com/quicknode-accelerator-chainova/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T21:31:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ChaiNova joins QuickNode’s Accelerator to bring inclusive Web3 access from local shops to global enterprises.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>QuickNode</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[QuickNode Accelerator - SettleX]]></title>
        <id>6813ad1304ef2c0001211afb</id>
        <link href="https://blog.quicknode.com/quicknode-accelerator-settlex/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T16:00:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discover SettleX, a modular cross-chain clearing layer improving capital efficiency, privacy, and liquidity across the DeFi landscape.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>QuickNode</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[QuickNode Accelerator - taro/NYU]]></title>
        <id>68222cb536cbae0001089a2b</id>
        <link href="https://blog.quicknode.com/quicknode-accelerator-taro/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T15:59:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Taro is a privacy-first blockchain project from NYU and Microsoft, enhancing financial transparency and accountability in organizations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>QuickNode</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[QuickNode Accelerator - Mements]]></title>
        <id>68222d3a36cbae0001089a38</id>
        <link href="https://blog.quicknode.com/quicknode-accelerator-mements/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T15:59:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mements is building infrastructure for verifiable AI, with timestamped prompts, provable video streaming, and the launch of MemeChain.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>QuickNode</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[QuickNode Accelerator - EcoFundMe]]></title>
        <id>6822330f36cbae0001089a61</id>
        <link href="https://blog.quicknode.com/quicknode-accelerator-ecofundme/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T15:59:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[EcoFundMe connects donors to verified climate projects with tokenized contributions, DAO governance, and transparent onchain funding.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>QuickNode</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[QuickNode Accelerator - Rivalz Network]]></title>
        <id>68248d91bf7346000109494e</id>
        <link href="https://blog.quicknode.com/quicknode-accelerator-rivalz-network/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T15:59:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Rivalz is building verifiable AI infrastructure, enabling smart contracts to query AI oracles, real-world data, and autonomous agents.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>QuickNode</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[QuickNode Accelerator - Hangry Animals]]></title>
        <id>68236ae084101f00013a5cd0</id>
        <link href="https://blog.quicknode.com/quicknode-accelerator-hangry-animals/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T15:58:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hangry Animals blends storytelling, Web3, and social good into a transmedia universe where players own, earn, and impact real causes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>QuickNode</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[QuickNode Accelerator - Boost Ad Network]]></title>
        <id>6813cc2f04ef2c0001211b24</id>
        <link href="https://blog.quicknode.com/quicknode-accelerator-boost-ad-network/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T15:58:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Boost is an onchain-native, privacy-first ad network with verifiable auctions, real attribution, and campaign analytics for Web3.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>QuickNode</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[QuickNode Accelerator - Diamondz Shadow Movies]]></title>
        <id>6824f61dbf734600010949a1</id>
        <link href="https://blog.quicknode.com/quicknode-accelerator-diamondz-shadow-movies/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T15:58:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Diamondz Shadow is creating a blockchain-powered entertainment ecosystem spanning games, film, tokenized media, and real-world utility.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>QuickNode</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[QuickNode Accelerator - Badchain]]></title>
        <id>6825fdc9bf734600010949cf</id>
        <link href="https://blog.quicknode.com/quicknode-accelerator-badchain/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T15:57:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Badchain is Solana’s culture layer, where behavior drives rewards through meme quests, raffles, and community-led incentives.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>QuickNode</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>