<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2025-05-24T13:05:10.829Z</id>
    <title>AngJianming RSS Feed</title>
    <updated>2025-05-24T13:05:10.829Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase in S&amp;P 500: More crypto firms to come?]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/coinbase-sp500-more-crypto-firms-to-come</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/coinbase-sp500-more-crypto-firms-to-come?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-24T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This past week, Coinbase joined the S&P 500, one of the world’s most elite stock indexes — a triumph for the crypto firm, which spent much of the 2020s battling US government agencies like the SEC and Commodity Futures Trading Commission for its survival. 
But this attainment is not about one company alone. 
“This is more than an achievement for Coinbase; it’s a landmark for the broader crypto and blockchain industry,” said Meryem Habibi, chief revenue officer of Bitpace. Coinbase joining the S&P 500 doesn’t just boost the owner of the largest US cryptocurrency exchange. “It cements the legitimacy of an entire asset class,” she told Cointelegraph. 
Jason Kennard, head of business development at ARK Invest Europe, told Cointelegraph that for the first time, a crypto-native firm had met the …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Andrew Singer</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[And my 270 days of coding journey began...]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/chakshuisadev/and-my-270-days-of-coding-journey-began-1fkj</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/chakshuisadev/and-my-270-days-of-coding-journey-began-1fkj"/>
        <updated>2025-05-24T12:50:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The journey of a thousand miles start from a single step. - LAO TZU
WHAT I DID TODAY
Decided to commit to a 270-Day journey to become a better coder and try to be in the top 1%.I started my journey before by learning c#, python and unity engine. But now i ain't shooting arrows in the empty sky. I've got to get myself a strategy, a roadmap.
Let's go - 269 Days more to go!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ChakshuMalik</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How I Built and Compared a Custom CNN vs MobileNetV2 for Boat Image Classification]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/ezinne_anne/how-i-built-and-compared-a-custom-cnn-vs-mobilenetv2-for-boat-image-classification-4gj4</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/ezinne_anne/how-i-built-and-compared-a-custom-cnn-vs-mobilenetv2-for-boat-image-classification-4gj4"/>
        <updated>2025-05-24T12:41:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello everyone! How are you all doing?
Today, I want to share a mini story about my experience completing a deep learning assignment—part of my DeepTechReady Week 2 Challenge, where I built and compared two models: a Custom CNN and a MobileNetV2 for multiclass boat image classification.
Let’s dive in! 
First things first—yes, I’m learning machine learning!
In February 2025, I joined a data science and machine learning training program called DeepTechReady, organized by Data Science Nigeria and 3MTT NITDA. Classes kicked off in March with foundational topics, and by April, we were neck-deep in specialization. I chose the Data Science/Machine Learning track.

During Week 2 of the Deep Learning module, we were given this assignment:
Objective:
Challenge accepted. 
I used Google Colab for this…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ezinne Anne😎👩🏿‍💻</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Listen up vibe coders, and basement wizards, this is for all of you.]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/generalist1/listen-up-vibe-coders-and-basement-wizards-this-is-for-all-of-you-6jn</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/generalist1/listen-up-vibe-coders-and-basement-wizards-this-is-for-all-of-you-6jn"/>
        <updated>2025-05-24T12:40:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Stop Freaking Out—Your Career Isn’t Dead, You’re Just Avoiding the Hard Stuff
Salar Khan ・ May 24
#llm
        #programming
        #beginners
        #mentorship]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Salar Khan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Postmarks - emailable, searchable link bookmarking]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/leesus/postmarks-emailable-searchable-link-bookmarking-365o</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/leesus/postmarks-emailable-searchable-link-bookmarking-365o"/>
        <updated>2025-05-24T12:35:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is a submission for the Postmark Challenge: Inbox Innovators.
Postmarks (naming things eh...) is a personal link bookmarking service.
Users interact with the service via email, obviously, and can email a link to be bookmarked, email to list their links, and email a query to search for links via content. Each user get's their own database, courtesy of Cloudflare Durable Objects.
It's barebones, but it was a fun little project.
Screenshots are below - it's email, so not much to demo. I've redacted the inbound email address to protect my Postmark free account email limit, but if the judges reach out I'll share the email address to interact with the app.
Email a link:

Link added reply:

Search for a link:

Search result reply:

https://github.com/leesus/postmarks
The app makes use of Postmarks Inbound and Transactional streams, to interact with a Cloudflare Worker, backed by Vectorize and Durable Objects. The smarts are provided by Workers AI, via the Vercel AI SDK.
A full step-by-step tutorial is available on the GitHub repo.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lee Ellam</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[how to create github profile page]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/saqibtanveer-dev/how-to-create-github-profile-page-5b3h</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/saqibtanveer-dev/how-to-create-github-profile-page-5b3h"/>
        <updated>2025-05-24T12:33:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A post by Saqib Tanveer]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Saqib Tanveer</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Xiaomi Joins the Custom SoC Race]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/bhuvaneshm_dev/xiaomi-joins-the-custom-soc-race-321a</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/bhuvaneshm_dev/xiaomi-joins-the-custom-soc-race-321a"/>
        <updated>2025-05-24T12:28:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Xiaomi has officially entered the custom SoC arena, joining tech giants like Samsung (Exynos), Google (Tensor), and Huawei (Kirin). Their in-house chipset aims to reduce dependency on third-party vendors like Qualcomm while delivering tighter integration with MIUI or HyperOS. This move allows Xiaomi to optimize AI, camera processing, and energy efficiency natively. By developing its own silicon, Xiaomi gains complete hardware-software control across its devices. Like Google’s Tensor designed for Pixel, Xiaomi’s chip will fuel smarter experiences. The shift marks a significant step toward a fully owned and unified tech platform. It’s more than performance—it's ecosystem empowerment.
Xiaomi has unveiled a fully autonomous smart factory capable of round-the-clock operation without human worke…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>BHUVANESH M</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Here’s what happened in crypto today]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/what-happened-in-crypto-today</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/what-happened-in-crypto-today?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-24T12:24:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today in crypto, a judge has vacated key fraud and manipulation convictions against Mango Markets exploiter Avraham Eisenberg, US-based spot Bitcoin ETFs posted a significant amount of inflows this week, and US lawmakers have urged the Justice Department to investigate President Donald Trump's crypto dinner. 
Judge overturns fraud convictions in Mango Markets exploit case
A US federal judge has vacated key fraud and manipulation convictions against Avraham Eisenberg, the trader at the center of the case involving a $110 million exploit of the decentralized exchange Mango Markets.
On Friday, US District Judge Arun Subramanian ruled that the evidence presented at trial failed to support the jury’s conclusion that Eisenberg made materially false representations to Mango Markets.
The decision …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Cointelegraph</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Unlocking Potential: 6 Compelling Reasons to Outsource Software Development to Peru in 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/jetthoughts/unlocking-potential-6-compelling-reasons-to-outsource-software-development-to-peru-in-2024-23c3</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/jetthoughts/unlocking-potential-6-compelling-reasons-to-outsource-software-development-to-peru-in-2024-23c3"/>
        <updated>2025-05-24T12:24:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The software development outsourcing landscape is evolving, and Peru is emerging as a prime destination for companies looking to enhance their tech capabilities. With a burgeoning IT sector and a wealth of skilled developers, Peru offers numerous advantages for businesses considering outsourcing in 2024.
  Peru's IT market is projected to grow significantly, reaching $7.02 billion by 2026.
  The country boasts a large pool of over 38,000 skilled software developers.
  Competitive salary rates make Peru an attractive option for outsourcing.
  Cultural similarities and time zone compatibility enhance collaboration.
  Government initiatives are improving the technical infrastructure.
  Despite some challenges, the benefits of outsourcing to Peru are substantial.
Peru's capital, Lima, is at th…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>JetThoughts Dev</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Are Dating Apps Just Digital Honeytraps?]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/nightmare-lynx/are-dating-apps-just-digital-honeytraps-a4f</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/nightmare-lynx/are-dating-apps-just-digital-honeytraps-a4f"/>
        <updated>2025-05-24T12:24:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the era of digital romance, dating apps have become a popular way for people to connect, find love, and build relationships. However, beneath the surface of swipes and matches lies a complex landscape of data mining, privacy concerns, and potential risks. Let's explore the dual nature of dating apps, examining whether they foster real love or serve as digital honeytraps for data mining and blackmail.
Dating apps have revolutionized the way people meet and interact, offering convenience, accessibility, and a vast pool of potential partners. Platforms like Tinder, Bumble, Hinge, and OkCupid have gained immense popularity, with millions of users worldwide seeking love, companionship, and meaningful connections.
Dating apps promise to simplify the process of finding love, using algorithms a…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Your's Nightmare</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Deploying a Multi-Tier Web App on AWS: A Journey Through Challenges and Costly Lesson]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/tharun_reddy_a193bc1b993b/deploying-a-multi-tier-web-app-on-aws-a-journey-through-challenges-and-costly-lesson-4m44</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/tharun_reddy_a193bc1b993b/deploying-a-multi-tier-web-app-on-aws-a-journey-through-challenges-and-costly-lesson-4m44"/>
        <updated>2025-05-24T12:22:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As part of my journey to master cloud computing and DevOps, I recently completed an intermediate-level project: deploying a multi-tier web application on AWS. The goal was to build a secure, scalable architecture with a web server in a public subnet and a database server in a private subnet, using AWS services like EC2, VPC, and security groups. While the project was a success, it came with significant hurdles—both technical and financial. In this blog post, I’ll walk you through the project’s objectives, the numerous issues I faced, how I resolved them, and a costly lesson about AWS resource cleanup that left me with a $27 bill.
The project had clear goals to test my AWS and Linux skills:
Launch EC2 Instances: Set up one web server and one database server using Amazon EC2.
Configure Nginx…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tharun Reddy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why I Chose Biotechnology and Why I’m Learning Bioinformatics with R]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/ouzhan_f4b5b9b556f406f82/why-i-chose-biotechnology-and-why-im-learning-bioinformatics-with-r-1am0</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/ouzhan_f4b5b9b556f406f82/why-i-chose-biotechnology-and-why-im-learning-bioinformatics-with-r-1am0"/>
        <updated>2025-05-24T12:21:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi! I'm Oğuzhan, a 3rd-year biotechnology student based in Turkey. I've always been fascinated by how the brain works, how genes influence our behavior, and how we can use data and artificial intelligence to understand—and maybe even enhance—human cognition.
Recently, I started learning bioinformatics, especially using R and Galaxy to analyze gene expression and biological datasets. It’s a challenging but exciting journey. I plan to learn Biopython next, but for now, I’m focusing on building a solid foundation in R.
In this blog, I’ll share:
What I learn in bioinformatics and biotechnology
Tutorials and beginner-friendly projects in R
Reflections from my classes and personal studies
Ideas about neuroscience, AI, and the future of biotech
If you're a student, a beginner in bioinformatics, or just curious about where biology meets technology, I’d love to connect.
Have you also started learning bioinformatics? What helped you the most? I'd love to hear your experience in the comments!
Let’s learn and grow together 🚀

Stay tuned for my first technical post: A beginner’s guide to gene expression analysis in R.
— Oğuzhan]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Oğuzhan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hyperliquid trader James Wynn goes ‘all-in’ on $1.25B Bitcoin Long]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/james-wynn-bitcoin-leverage-position-hyperliquid</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/james-wynn-bitcoin-leverage-position-hyperliquid?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-24T12:18:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Well-known Hyperliquid trader James Wynn has increased his 40x leverage long Bitcoin bet to $1.25 billion after closing his $PEPE position for a $25.2 million profit.
On May 24, Lookonchain reported that Wynn entered an 11,588 BTC position with an average entry price of $108,243 and a liquidation level of $105,180.
The move came hours after Wynn exited his Ether (ETH) and Sui (SUI) longs at a $5.3 million loss. At the time, he used the proceedings to double down on Bitcoin (BTC), increasing his position to 11,070 BTC.
Wynn began his Bitcoin long position with $830 million on May 21, trimming $400 million in profits the same day. By May 22, he ramped the position back up to $1.1 billion, holding high leverage as BTC crossed $110,000 and gained $39 million on paper. He later sold 540 BTC for…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Amin Haqshanas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Your Deleted Data Can Come Back to Haunt You!]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/nightmare-lynx/your-deleted-data-can-come-back-to-haunt-you-4hj4</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/nightmare-lynx/your-deleted-data-can-come-back-to-haunt-you-4hj4"/>
        <updated>2025-05-24T12:17:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the digital age, the question of whether a file can be truly deleted is more relevant than ever. With the evolution of storage technologies, particularly the shift from traditional hard disk drives (HDDs) to solid-state drives (SSDs), the methods and effectiveness of file deletion have changed significantly. Let's explore the intricacies of file deletion, the differences between SSD forensics and old-school disk wiping, and debunk some common myths.
When you delete a file from your computer, it's not immediately erased from the storage device. Instead, the operating system removes the file's entry from the file system, marking the space it occupied as available for new data. This means that the file's data remains on the storage device until it is overwritten by new files.
In traditiona…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Your's Nightmare</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How We Fixed Our Shipping Integration Chaos with Ditto: A Fulfillment Use Case in E-Commerce]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/manav_lahariya_ac292b787a/how-we-fixed-our-shipping-integration-chaos-with-ditto-a-fulfillment-use-case-in-e-commerce-370n</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/manav_lahariya_ac292b787a/how-we-fixed-our-shipping-integration-chaos-with-ditto-a-fulfillment-use-case-in-e-commerce-370n"/>
        <updated>2025-05-24T12:13:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How We Fixed Our Shipping Integration Chaos with Ditto: A Fulfillment Use Case in E-Commerce


The modern e-commerce supply chain moves fast—but integrating with third-party shipping services doesn’t. We learned this the hard way, juggling broken APIs, unreliable sandbox environments, and zero visibility into request/response flows.
📦 The Problem: Shipping APIs Were Slowing Us Down


We’re an e-commerce platform managing thousands of orders per day. Shipping is critical to our customer experience. But integrating with new carriers or updating old integrations was painful:
No reliable sandboxes: Most shipping providers had inconsistent or outdated test environments.
Delayed feedback: Every change needed a full deploy, then a real API hit, and then debugging based on logs.
Hard to test edge cases: Simulating scenarios like "address not found", "label unavailable", or "customs hold" was impossible.
Cross-team bottlenecks: Backend, QA, and devOps were constantly waiting on each other just to test a single flow.
Every integration took weeks longer than it should have, with late nights spent tailing logs and replaying requests.
🚀 Enter Ditto: Mock APIs That Work Like the Real Thing


We deployed Ditto internally as a drop-in mock server platform. Think of it like Postman—but private, flexible, and built for teams.
1. Created realistic mocks for all shipping APIs
2. Collaborative interface
3. Integrated with CI/CD
4. Zero downtime testing
🏭 Use Case: Fulfillment → Shipping in E-Commerce


Here’s a specific example:
Scenario:
Pain Point:
With Ditto:
💰 ROI: Faster Delivery Times, Happier Devs, and Lower Costs


After adopting Ditto, our team saw immediate benefits:

We estimate that Ditto saved over 200 hours of dev time in the first quarter alone. More importantly, it helped us ship (pun intended) with confidence.
APIs should never be a bottleneck. With Ditto, they’re not.
Want to see Ditto in action? Check it out here or spin up your own mock environment in minutes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Manav Lahariya</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hong Kong's Famous Bamboo Scaffolding Hangs on (For Now)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nytimes.com/2025/05/24/world/asia/hongkong-bamboo-scaffolding.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.nytimes.com/2025/05/24/world/asia/hongkong-bamboo-scaffolding.html"/>
        <updated>2025-05-24T12:08:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Show HN: Lnk – Git-native dotfiles manager]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/yarlson/lnk</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/yarlson/lnk"/>
        <updated>2025-05-24T11:41:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tariffs in American History]]></title>
        <id>https://imprimis.hillsdale.edu/tariffs-in-american-history/</id>
        <link href="https://imprimis.hillsdale.edu/tariffs-in-american-history/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-24T11:02:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trump’s use of presidential seal at memecoin event raises legal questions]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/trump-presidential-seal-memecoin-dinner-legal-review</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/trump-presidential-seal-memecoin-dinner-legal-review?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-24T09:48:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[President Donald Trump is facing scrutiny after speaking at a private event for top investors in his $TRUMP memecoin while standing behind a lectern emblazoned with the official presidential seal — a move that may violate federal law.
The event took place Thursday at Trump National Golf Club in Virginia, where Trump addressed 220 investors in his cryptocurrency project.
According to US law, the presidential seal cannot be used in any manner that could imply government approval or sponsorship. Violators can face fines or up to six months in prison.
Trump, who arrived at the club aboard a military helicopter, praised attendees and took aim at the Biden administration’s crypto stance.
When asked about potential conflicts of interest, White House Press Secretary Karoline Leavitt said the presi…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Amin Haqshanas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin treasury companies will hold &#039;way more&#039; than Bitcoiners expect: Exec]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-treasury-companies-significant-holdings-forecast-btc-jesse-myers</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-treasury-companies-significant-holdings-forecast-btc-jesse-myers?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-24T07:26:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Moon Inc. head of Bitcoin strategy Jesse Myers says that Bitcoin holders are underestimating the significant amount of Bitcoin that corporations will accumulate by 2045.
“Bitcoin Treasury Companies will hold 50% of all BTC, way more than most Bitcoiners are prepared for,” Jesse Myers said in a May 23 X thread.
Strategy will own $70T of Bitcoin by 2025, says Myers
Myers further forecasted that Michael Saylor’s Strategy will own $70 trillion worth of Bitcoin (BTC) by 2045, “making it by far the most valuable company in the history of the world.” At the time of publication, Strategy holds 576,320 Bitcoin, worth approximately $62.24 billion, according to Saylor Tracker.
Source: Jesse Myers
Myers said, “To set the stage, there is $1,000T of asset value in the world.” He added that Bitcoin repre…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Ciaran Lyons</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Polygon Co-Founder Mihailo Bjelic Exits Layer 2]]></title>
        <id>10ee5024-52f1-4600-9048-8a723ececfc3</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/24/polygon-co-founder-mihailo-bjelic-exits-layer-2"/>
        <updated>2025-05-24T07:07:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Polygon, initially known as Matic, was founded by Jaynti Kanani, Sandeep Nailwal, Mihailo Bjelic, and Anurag Arjun.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Parikshit Mishra</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Bulls Lose $500M as Bitcoin Hovers Around $108K After Trump’s Tariff Threats]]></title>
        <id>b0cfcdd6-9c72-4378-a4f3-dfa28b0ce5ff</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/24/crypto-bulls-lose-500m-as-bitcoin-hovers-around-108k-after-trumps-tariff-threats"/>
        <updated>2025-05-24T07:03:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[U.S. President Donald Trump threatened a 50% tariff on all European Union imports and a 25% levy on imported Apple iPhones late Friday, sending markets tumbling.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shaurya Malwa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Judge overturns fraud convictions in Mango Markets exploit case]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/judge-overturns-avraham-eisenberg-fraud-convictions-mango-markets</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/judge-overturns-avraham-eisenberg-fraud-convictions-mango-markets?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-24T07:00:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A US federal judge has vacated key fraud and manipulation convictions against Avraham Eisenberg, the trader at the center of the case involving a $110 million exploit of the decentralized exchange Mango Markets.
On Friday, US District Judge Arun Subramanian ruled that the evidence presented at trial failed to support the jury’s conclusion that Eisenberg made materially false representations to Mango Markets.
The decision vacates Eisenberg’s convictions for commodities fraud and market manipulation and acquits him of a third charge, significantly weakening the government’s case.
Eisenberg, a self-proclaimed “applied game theorist,” was convicted in 2024 for artificially inflating the price of Mango’s MNGO token by over 1,300% in a matter of minutes and using the resulting gains as collatera…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Amin Haqshanas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dogecoin, Cardano’s ADA, XRP Fall 7% in Weekend Bloodbath]]></title>
        <id>40f3971e-209f-4a2e-840e-fa7bd2219f1d</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/24/dogecoin-cardanos-ada-xrp-fall-7-in-weekend-bloodbath"/>
        <updated>2025-05-24T06:48:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Market capitalization slumped 5% as traders took profits on the week-long rally ahead of the weekend.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shaurya Malwa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin ETFs post $2.75B in weekly inflows as price sits above $108K]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-etfs-weekly-inflows-significant-price-sits-108k</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-etfs-weekly-inflows-significant-price-sits-108k?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-24T05:21:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[US-based spot Bitcoin exchange-traded-funds (ETFs) have recorded a total of $2.75 billion in inflows this week amid Bitcoin surpassing its January all-time high of $109,000.
The $2.75 billion in inflows is approximately 4.5 times larger than the previous week’s $608 million, according to Farside data.
BlackRock Bitcoin ETF continues inflow streak
On May 23, the final day of the trading week, spot Bitcoin (BTC) ETFs recorded $211.7 million in inflows. However, BlackRock’s IBIT was the only fund to post gains in the trading day, adding $430.8 million and extending its inflow streak to eight consecutive days. 
Grayscale’s GBTC led outflows with $89.2 million, followed by ARK 21Shares’ ARKB with $73.9 million.
Just two days before, on May 21, the Bitcoin ETFs saw $607.1 million in inflows, the…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Ciaran Lyons</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Make a Living as a Writer]]></title>
        <id>https://thewalrus.ca/how-to-make-a-living-as-a-writer/</id>
        <link href="https://thewalrus.ca/how-to-make-a-living-as-a-writer/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-24T04:36:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Algebraic Effects?]]></title>
        <id>https://antelang.org/blog/why_effects/</id>
        <link href="https://antelang.org/blog/why_effects/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-24T03:00:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Polygon co-founder steps down, will be &#039;cheering from the sidelines&#039;]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/polygon-cofounder-mihailo-bjelic-steps-down-operations</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/polygon-cofounder-mihailo-bjelic-steps-down-operations?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-24T02:01:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mihailo Bjelic, co-founder of Ethereum layer-2 scaling solution Polygon, has stepped down from his role at Polygon but suggests he will stay active in the crypto industry in some capacity.
His resignation drew reactions across Polygon and the wider crypto community, with several seeing it as a loss for Polygon, which has been tied to several major developments in recent months.
Bjelic winds down ‘day-to-day involvement’
“After much thought and reflection, I’ve decided to step down from the board of the Polygon Foundation and wind down my day-to-day involvement with Polygon Labs,” Bjelic said in a May 23 X post.
“I’ll always be cheering from the sidelines and supporting however and whenever I can,” Bjelic added.
“As projects evolve and mature, it is natural for visions to evolve, and someti…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Ciaran Lyons</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Stuff I Learned at Carta]]></title>
        <id>https://lethain.com/stuff-learned-at-carta/</id>
        <link href="https://lethain.com/stuff-learned-at-carta/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-24T01:24:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Show HN: HNRelevant – Add a "related" section to Hacker News]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/imdj/HNRelevant</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/imdj/HNRelevant"/>
        <updated>2025-05-24T01:07:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Modification of acetaminophen to reduce liver toxicity and enhance drug efficacy]]></title>
        <id>https://www.societyforscience.org/regeneron-sts/2025-student-finalists/chloe-lee/</id>
        <link href="https://www.societyforscience.org/regeneron-sts/2025-student-finalists/chloe-lee/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-24T00:29:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Will Bitcoin bulls secure $110K before BTC’s $13.8B options expiry?]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-bulls-must-secure-110k-before-13-8b-btc-options-expiry</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-bulls-must-secure-110k-before-13-8b-btc-options-expiry?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-24T00:22:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Key takeaways:

Bitcoin bulls aim to push BTC above $110,000 by May 30 to capitalize on $4.8 billion in call options.

Spot BTC ETF inflows and weak put positioning give bulls a strong edge in the monthly expiry.

Bitcoin (BTC) is approaching its largest monthly options expiry of 2025, with total exposure reaching $13.8 billion. This event gives bulls a chance to secure Bitcoin’s price above $110,000, as bears were caught off guard by a 25% rally over the past 30 days.
May 30 Bitcoin options open interest, USD. Source: Laevitas.ch
The open interest in Bitcoin put (sell) options stands at $6.5 billion, but 95% of these positions are set below $109,000. Therefore, if Bitcoin’s price holds near current levels, less than $350 million worth of put options will remain relevant at expiry.
Convers…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Marcel Pechman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Root for your friends]]></title>
        <id>https://josephthacker.com/personal/2025/05/13/root-for-your-friends.html</id>
        <link href="https://josephthacker.com/personal/2025/05/13/root-for-your-friends.html"/>
        <updated>2025-05-23T23:28:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Solana &#039;will make everyone an investor&#039; — Solana nCMO]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/solana-will-make-everyone-an-investor-or-a-dreamer-over-time-solana-exec</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/solana-will-make-everyone-an-investor-or-a-dreamer-over-time-solana-exec?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-23T23:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The current structure of capital markets is failing to serve a broad base of investors, according to Akshay BD, non-chief marketing officer at the Solana Foundation. During a panel at the Accelerate 2025 conference, Akshay argued that blockchain technology could help address these shortcomings, claiming that Solana could “make everyone an investor or a dreamer over time.”
Akshay noted growing uncertainty among investors, citing concerns from investment managers who report heightened anxiety among clients. “You have low bond yields, you have asset price bubbles, and people don't really know how the traditional asset allocation model works anymore,” he said. The 60-40 portfolio hasn’t delivered consistent returns in a long time.”
He attributed some of this tension to a widening gap between i…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Christopher Tepedino</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Onchain privacy is a necessity in the age of AI — Shielded CEO]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/onchain-privacy-necessity-age-ai-shielded-ceo</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/onchain-privacy-necessity-age-ai-shielded-ceo?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-23T22:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Blockchain privacy tools such as zero-knowledge (ZK) proofs will become increasingly necessary to protect online user data in the age of artificial intelligence, according to Eran Barak, CEO of Shielded Technologies, the developer behind the Midnight privacy chain.
In an interview with Cointelegraph at Consensus 2025, Barak said corporate service providers and centralized servers are expected to become honeypots for AI-assisted hackers and malicious actors looking to steal valuable data, including private keys, financial metadata, medical records, and government documents.
Hackers targeting centralized entities have a "massive" return on investment (ROI) and are incentivized to hack centralized targets that contain millions of valuable records, the CEO told Cointelegraph. Barak added that …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Vince Quill</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Semler Scientific boosts BTC holdings with $50M purchase]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/semler-scientific-buys-50m-worth-bitcoin</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/semler-scientific-buys-50m-worth-bitcoin?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-23T22:19:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Semler Scientific, a medical device company, purchased of $50 million worth of Bitcoin between May 13 and May 22, bringing the market value of the company’s Bitcoin (BTC) holdings to $474.4 million, keeping it within the top 13 of BTC Treasury companies.
According to a May 23 disclosure, Semler bought a total of 455 BTC for an average purchase price of $109,801. To buy the Bitcoin, Semler Scientific used proceeds from an at-the-market stock offering program. So far, the company has sold roughly 3 million shares of common stock for net proceeds of $115 million.
Semler Scientific’s shares have fallen 1.36% on the same day as the disclosure, though the decrease in its share price is largely in line with the Nasdaq’s performance. That index, which follows top tech stocks, is down 1% on the day.
Semler Scientific share price. Source: Google Finance
In its Q1 2025 earnings report released on May 13, the company revealed a 44% drop in revenue year-over-year. Despite the claimed success of its Bitcoin treasury plan, Semler Scientific’s shares have dropped 18% in 2025, according to Google Finance.
Bitcoin treasury companies, or companies that traditionally sell equity or issue debt to buy BTC, had been drawing the interest of investors looking for exposure to Bitcoin price fluctuations.
Michael Saylor's Strategy debuted its BTC reserve in August 2020, when it started purchasing Bitcoin. Bitcoin is up 181.6% year to date, while Semler Scientific shares rose 53% since announcing the BTC approach in May 2024. 
Magazine: ZK-proofs are bringing smart contracts to Bitcoin — BitcoinOS and Starknet]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Christopher Tepedino</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OpenAI updates Operator to o3, making its $200 monthly ChatGPT Pro subscription more enticing]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008828</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/openai-updates-operator-to-o3-making-its-200-monthly-chatgpt-subscription-more-enticing/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-23T21:51:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Operator remains a research preview and is accessible only to ChatGPT Pro users. The Responses API version will continue to use GPT-4o.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carl Franzen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Texas governor signals support for Bitcoin reserve bill]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/texas-governor-bitcoin-reserve-law</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/texas-governor-bitcoin-reserve-law?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-23T21:24:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Texas Governor Greg Abbott has signaled support for a bill recently passed by the state House of Representatives that would establish a strategic cryptocurrency reserve.
In a May 22 X post, Abbott posted a Techstory article about Texas state lawmakers’ efforts to create a Bitcoin (BTC) reserve. The story pointed out that the decision for the passage of SB 21, the bill in question, now rests on Abbott’s shoulders, roughly three months after it was introduced. 
Since taking office, Abbott referred to himself as a “crypto law proposal supporter” in 2021 and suggested that he would support policies to establish Texas as a “crypto capital” in 2024. Texas was one of a handful of state-level governments that proposed setting up a strategic crypto reserve after the 2024 federal elections.   

Rela…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Turner Wright</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The battle to AI-enable the web: NLweb and what enterprises need to know]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008795</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/the-battle-to-ai-enable-the-web-nlweb-and-what-enterprises-need-to-know/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-23T21:05:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft's NLWeb protocol transforms websites into AI-powered apps with conversational interfaces.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sean Michael Kerner</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The world of Japan's PC-98 computer]]></title>
        <id>https://strangecomforts.com/the-strange-world-of-japans-pc-98-computer/</id>
        <link href="https://strangecomforts.com/the-strange-world-of-japans-pc-98-computer/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-23T20:51:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Show HN: I built a more productive way to manage AI chats]]></title>
        <id>https://contextch.at/</id>
        <link href="https://contextch.at/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-23T20:46:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The 3 biggest bombshells from this week’s AI extravaganza]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008808</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/the-3-biggest-bombshells-from-this-weeks-ai-extravaganza/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-23T20:29:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Enterprises looking to build with AI should find plenty to look forward to with the announcements from Microsoft, Google & Anthropic this week.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nick Mokey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[UndoDB – The interactive time travel debugger for Linux C/C++ for debugging]]></title>
        <id>https://undo.io/</id>
        <link href="https://undo.io/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-23T20:22:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Formal Proof of Complexity Bounds on Diophantine Equations]]></title>
        <id>https://arxiv.org/abs/2505.16963</id>
        <link href="https://arxiv.org/abs/2505.16963"/>
        <updated>2025-05-23T20:09:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Biz: From shorting the Venezuelan Bolivar to shorting the US dollar]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/crypto-biz-from-shorting-venezuelan-bolivar-shorting-us-dollar</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/crypto-biz-from-shorting-venezuelan-bolivar-shorting-us-dollar?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-23T20:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When Venezuela was experiencing hyperinflation, Ledn co-founder Mauricio di Bartolomeo hedged against the collapsing local currency by shorting it in favor of the more stable US dollar. Today, he’s using a similar strategy — this time borrowing against his Bitcoin (BTC) to hedge against the crumbling US dollar.
Di Bartolomeo connected with me during Canada Crypto Week in Toronto, where he talked about the advantages of Bitcoin-backed loans and the rapid growth of collateralized BTC lending. In our interview, he made a compelling case for continuing to stack sats, even as Bitcoin’s price keeps rising.
This week’s Crypto Biz dives into our conversation with the Ledn co-founder and covers the latest business news from the blockchain world.
A lesson from hyperinflation
Before Bitcoin, di Barto…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Sam Bourgi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[US House members call for investigation into Trump&#039;s memecoin dinner]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/house-investigation-donald-trump-memecoin-dinner</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/house-investigation-donald-trump-memecoin-dinner?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-23T19:57:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Members of the US House of Representatives called for the Justice Department to investigate Donald Trump’s May 22 dinner for his top memecoin investors, citing concerns about “foreign influence over US policy decisions” and “potential corruption and emoluments clause violations.”
In a May 22 letter to the Justice Department, 35 House members asked the public integrity section acting chief, Edward Sullivan, to launch an inquiry over the memecoin dinner to determine whether it violated the federal bribery statute or the foreign emoluments clause of the US Constitution. 
Under the emoluments clause, a US president is barred from accepting any gift from a foreign state without the approval of Congress. Bloomberg reported that a majority of the attendees at the memecoin dinner were likely forei…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Turner Wright</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Show HN: Genetic Boids Web Simulation]]></title>
        <id>https://attentionmech.github.io/genetic-boids/</id>
        <link href="https://attentionmech.github.io/genetic-boids/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-23T19:40:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin price ‘breather’ expected as short-term traders realize $11.6B in profit]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-price-breather-starts-as-short-term-traders-take-profit</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-price-breather-starts-as-short-term-traders-take-profit?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-23T19:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Key takeaways:

Short-term Bitcoin holders realized $11.6 billion in profit over the past 30 days, suggesting a potential pause or local top in the market.

Technical indicators show cooling momentum as retail investor sentiment falls to a 90-day low and liquidity data points to price volatility.

Bitcoin (BTC) price recently hit a new all-time high of $111,800, but the bullish momentum may slow down as onchain data from Glassnode reveals significant profit-taking by short-term holders (STHs), potentially signaling a market "breather."
Glassnode analysis shows that STHs, often considered traders rather than long-term investors, have realized a staggering $11.6 billion in profits over the last 30 days. This follows a sharp rebound in Bitcoin’s price, pushing past the STH cost-basis of $93,0…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Biraajmaan Tamuly</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Show HN: DoubleMemory – more efficient local-first read-it-later app]]></title>
        <id>https://doublememory.com/</id>
        <link href="https://doublememory.com/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-23T18:55:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Price predictions 5/23: BTC, ETH, XRP, BNB, SOL, DOGE, ADA, SUI, HYPE, LINK]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/analise-de-precos-em-23-05-btc-eth-xrp-bnb-sol-doge-ada-sui-hype-link</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/analise-de-precos-em-23-05-btc-eth-xrp-bnb-sol-doge-ada-sui-hype-link?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-23T18:07:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Key points:

Bitcoin slipped below $109,588, but technical charts suggest traders are buying each dip.

Excessive leverage in Bitcoin futures increases the risk of a quick correction.

Select altcoins have turned down from their respective overhead resistance levels, signaling that the bears remain sellers on rallies.

Sellers have pulled Bitcoin (BTC) back below the breakout level of $109,588, but lower levels are likely to attract buyers. Investor interest remains strong, with the US spot Bitcoin exchange-traded funds witnessing inflows of $934 million on May 22 and $608 million on May 21, according to SoSoValue data.
Glassnode noted that the all-time high above $109,588 led to a total profit-taking volume of roughly $1 billion, far more muted than the $2 billion when the price rose abov…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Rakesh Upadhyay</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto, NFTs are a lifeboat in the sinking fiat system: Finance Redefined]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/crypto-nfts-lifeboat-sinking-fiat-system-finance-redefined</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/crypto-nfts-lifeboat-sinking-fiat-system-finance-redefined?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-23T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Risk appetite across traditional and cryptocurrency markets saw a sharp rise this week, helping United States cryptocurrency funds recover the capital lost to the correction of February and March, amassing over $7.5 billion worth of weekly inflows.
Bitcoin (BTC) surpassed its old all-time high on May 21, two days after President Donald Trump confirmed ongoing ceasefire negotiations between Russia and Ukraine in a May 19 X post.
Meanwhile, popular analyst and Global Macro Investor CEO Raoul Pal warned of more fiat currency debasement, urging investors to gain more exposure to cryptocurrencies and non-fungible tokens (NFTs), as these assets “will never be this cheap again.”
Exponential currency debasement: “You don’t own enough crypto, NFTs”
Cryptocurrencies and NFTs can help investors prote…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Zoltan Vardai</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘In ‘93, it became clear to me AI should be decentralized’ — Ben Goertzel]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/ben-goertzel-ai-decentralization-interview</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/ben-goertzel-ai-decentralization-interview?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-23T17:58:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s been 30 years since computer scientist Ben Goertzel wrote his first line of AI code, already convinced that artificial intelligence should be decentralized. Today, as the world approaches the dawn of Artificial General Intelligence (AGI), who leads this breakthrough could have profound consequences for the future of humanity.
Speaking with Cointelegraph at the Consensus conference in Toronto, Canada, Goertzel said, “We’re likely to be able to launch AGI that can think and generalize beyond its training and programming within the next one to three years.”
His project, SingularityNET, is a decentralized ecosystem building a global marketplace for AI services. Along the way, it has secured partnerships with Mind Network and Filecoin Foundation, invested $53 million in a modular supercomp…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Sam Bourgi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Positional preferences, order effects, prompt sensitivity undermine AI judgments]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cip.org/blog/llm-judges-are-unreliable</id>
        <link href="https://www.cip.org/blog/llm-judges-are-unreliable"/>
        <updated>2025-05-23T17:20:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Strategy Slumps 6%, Leading Crypto Names Lower as Bitcoin Treasury Strategies Are Questioned]]></title>
        <id>bb31eaf5-b257-4ca6-9286-4b88bfd2bc92</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/23/strategy-slumps-6-leading-crypto-names-lower-as-bitcoin-treasury-strategies-are-questioned"/>
        <updated>2025-05-23T17:16:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin slumped just modestly from record high levels on Friday, but the carnage in related stocks was far worse.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tom Carreras</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin’s bull market will ‘redefine’ BTC’s role in modern portfolios — Fidelity research]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-bull-market-redefines-btc-s-role-in-modern-portfolios-fidelity</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-bull-market-redefines-btc-s-role-in-modern-portfolios-fidelity?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-23T17:08:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Key takeaways:

Bitcoin’s performance in the current bull market and a new cohort of buyers reflect a maturing market and widening adoption.

A 50% rise in hashrate and a 63% jump in Realized Cap highlight investors’ confidence in Bitcoin.

A recent report from Fidelity Digital Assets explored how the current Bitcoin market cycle reflects a shift toward a maturing market where the rate of adoption deepens and expands.
At block height 892,500—marking 25% progress into the current halving epoch—Bitcoin traded between $82,500 and $85,000, representing a 31% increase from its value on April 19, 2024, when the fourth halving reduced block rewards to 3.125 BTC.
Bitcoin: halving cycles compared. Source: Fidelity Digital Assets
Fidelity’s senior research analyst Daniel Gray emphasized Bitcoin’s ne…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Biraajmaan Tamuly</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to live on $432 a month in America]]></title>
        <id>https://shagbark.substack.com/p/how-to-live-on-432-a-month-in-america</id>
        <link href="https://shagbark.substack.com/p/how-to-live-on-432-a-month-in-america"/>
        <updated>2025-05-23T16:40:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Beyond Semantics: Unreasonable Effectiveness of Reasonless Intermediate Tokens]]></title>
        <id>https://arxiv.org/abs/2505.13775</id>
        <link href="https://arxiv.org/abs/2505.13775"/>
        <updated>2025-05-23T16:13:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Find Your People]]></title>
        <id>https://foundersatwork.posthaven.com/find-your-people</id>
        <link href="https://foundersatwork.posthaven.com/find-your-people"/>
        <updated>2025-05-23T16:02:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Alchemy acquires no-code NFT launchpad HeyMint for undisclosed amount]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/alchemy-acquires-heymint-nft-launchpad</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/alchemy-acquires-heymint-nft-launchpad?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-23T15:52:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Web3 developer platform Alchemy has acquired HeyMint, a California-based non-fungible token (NFT) launchpad, in a move designed to enhance the company’s smart wallet infrastructure. 
The undisclosed funding deal will see HeyMint’s infrastructure embedded within Alchemy as it seeks to simplify user onboarding for Web3 applications, the company disclosed on May 23. HeyMint’s co-founder and chief technology officer, Flor Ronsmans De Vry, joins Alchemy as part of the deal. 
While not a household name in crypto, HeyMint attracted more than 1 million users over its first two years of operations. It was the launchpad behind $38 million in NFT sales and supported the Web3 efforts of major brands, including The Sandbox, Universal Music Group and Ubisoft. 
In 2023, HeyMint facilitated NFT sales for …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Sam Bourgi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The metre originated in the French Revolution]]></title>
        <id>https://www.abc.net.au/news/science/2025-05-20/metre-treaty-anniversary-metric-system-measurement-metrology/105302024</id>
        <link href="https://www.abc.net.au/news/science/2025-05-20/metre-treaty-anniversary-metric-system-measurement-metrology/105302024"/>
        <updated>2025-05-23T15:43:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin price drops 4% as Trump EU tariff talk liquidates over $300M]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-price-drops-4-trump-eu-tariff-talk-liquidates-over-300m</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-price-drops-4-trump-eu-tariff-talk-liquidates-over-300m?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-23T15:29:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Key points:

Bitcoin joins risk assets in a knee-jerk reaction to the latest instalment of the US trade war, this time focused on the EU.

BTC price action dives up to 4% before recovering with $110,000 now a resistance level.

Traders demand that price holds higher levels going forward to protect bullish momentum.

Bitcoin (BTC) saw flash volatility into the May 23 Wall Street open as news headlines liquidated longs.
BTC/USD 1-hour chart. Source: Cointelegraph/TradingView
Bitcoin trips as Trump says EU talks “going nowhere”
Data from Cointelegraph Markets Pro and TradingView showed BTC/USD hitting lows of $107,367 on Bitstamp before rebounding.
This marked daily losses of up to 4% as markets reacted to comments from US President Donald Trump over tariffs on the European Union.
“Our discus…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by William Suberg</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Postgres IDE in VS Code]]></title>
        <id>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/blog/adforpostgresql/announcing-a-new-ide-for-postgresql-in-vs-code-from-microsoft/4414648</id>
        <link href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/blog/adforpostgresql/announcing-a-new-ide-for-postgresql-in-vs-code-from-microsoft/4414648"/>
        <updated>2025-05-23T15:12:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build a Testing Framework for E-Commerce Checkout and Payments]]></title>
        <id>68308f32f4205e3b843cfb37</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-build-a-testing-framework-for-e-commerce-checkout-and-payments/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-23T15:07:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When I first started working on E-commerce applications, I assumed testing checkout flows and payments would be straightforward. My expectation was simple: users select items, provide an address, pay, and receive confirmation. But I quickly learned t...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Venkata Sai Sandeep</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Architecture of Mathematics – And How Developers Can Use it in Code]]></title>
        <id>68308ee8ccde6bc325c82393</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/the-architecture-of-mathematics-and-how-developers-can-use-it-in-code/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-23T15:06:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA["To understand is to perceive patterns." - Isaiah Berlin Math is not just numbers. It is the science of finding complex patterns that shape our world. This means that to truly understand it, we need to see beyond numbers, formulas, and theorems and ...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tiago Capelo Monteiro</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spoiler alert: The future of Web3 is not blockchain]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/future-of-web3-is-not-blockchain</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/future-of-web3-is-not-blockchain?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-23T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Opinion by: Grigore Roșu, founder and chief executive officer of Pi Squared
For some, the audacity of questioning the primacy of blockchain in Web3 is borderline heretical. The idea that decentralization and progress could exist without blockchains seems absurd to those who built careers around Bitcoin, Ethereum, and their descendants. Given blockchain's well-documented scaling limits, however, there is an argument to be made that Web3 doesn't actually need blockchains to thrive. Instead, it requires payment systems and verifiable settlement systems that are super fast. Blockchains are just one way to achieve that, not the only way.
While blockchain solved the double-spending problem, it introduced its own architectural burden: the rigid fixation on total ordering, dictating that every tra…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Grigore Roșu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Who attended Trump’s controversial memecoin dinner?]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/who-attended-trumps-controversial-memecoin-dinner</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/who-attended-trumps-controversial-memecoin-dinner?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-23T14:52:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The top 220 holders of US President Donald Trump’s memecoin met yesterday at the president’s golf course in Virginia for an exclusive dinner and purported meet-and-greet.
Attendees spent a grand total of $148 million for an “ultra-exclusive VIP reception with the president,” which crypto industry advocates and critics alike saw as a potential opportunity to discuss crypto policy with the president. 
The crowd contained a number of foreign crypto executives and influencers who otherwise would not have access to the US president, raising questions around corruption and foreign influence. 
Concerns were further augmented when White House Press Secretary Karoline Leavitt declined to release a list of attendees, stating that the event was a private affair outside of Trump’s presidential duties.…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Aaron Wood</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum price chart targets $4K as transaction fees hit 3-month high]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/ethereum-price-chart-targets-4k-transaction-fees-hit-3-month-highs</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/ethereum-price-chart-targets-4k-transaction-fees-hit-3-month-highs?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-23T14:49:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Key takeaways:

Ethereum is forming a bull flag on the daily chart, with a potential breakout to $4,000.

If Ethereum’s network activity and total value locked continue to grow, ETH price may see further gains.

Ether’s price printed a “bull flag” on the daily chart, a technical chart formation associated with strong upward momentum. Could a strengthening technical setup and increasing transaction fees signal the continuation of ETH’s rally toward $4,000?
Ethereum transaction fees rising is bullish
Marketwide recovery, fueled by Bitcoin’s rise to new all-time highs and improving macroeconomic conditions, saw Ether’s (ETH) price rise by nearly 56% to an eight-week high of $2,734 on May 23, from a low of $1,750 on May 6. 
This strength in price is reflected in onchain activity, with Ethereum…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Nancy Lubale</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[US DOJ seizes $24M in crypto from accused Qakbot malware developer]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/us-seizes-24m-crypto-qakbot-developer</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/us-seizes-24m-crypto-qakbot-developer?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-23T14:29:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The US Department of Justice (DOJ) has filed a civil forfeiture complaint to seize more than $24 million in cryptocurrency from Rustam Rafailevich Gallyamov, a Russian national accused of developing the Qakbot malware.
According to a May 22 announcement, the DOJ unsealed charges against the 48-year-old Moscovite with a federal indictment. Gallyamov is allegedly the malware developer behind the Qakbot botnet. 
“Today’s announcement of the Justice Department’s latest actions to counter the Qakbot malware scheme sends a clear message to the cybercrime community,” said Matthew Galeotti, head of the DOJ’s criminal division.
Screenshot of the indictment. Source: US Department of Justice
Galeotti highlighted that the DOJ is “determined to hold cybercriminals accountable.” He added that the depart…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Adrian Zmudzinski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Caesar's Last Breath]]></title>
        <id>https://charliesabino.com/caesars-last-breath/</id>
        <link href="https://charliesabino.com/caesars-last-breath/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-23T14:22:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Bead Too Far: Rethinking Global Connections Before Columbus]]></title>
        <id>https://peterfrankopan.substack.com/p/a-bead-too-far-rethinking-global</id>
        <link href="https://peterfrankopan.substack.com/p/a-bead-too-far-rethinking-global"/>
        <updated>2025-05-23T14:22:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is DNS hijacking? How it took down Curve Finance’s website]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/explained/what-is-dns-hijacking-how-it-took-down-curve-finances-website</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/explained/what-is-dns-hijacking-how-it-took-down-curve-finances-website?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-23T14:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Understanding the Curve Finance DNS hijacking            
            
                
On May 12, 2025, at 20:55 UTC, hackers hijacked the “.fi” domain name system (DNS) of Curve Finance after managing to access the registrar. They began sending its users to a malicious website, attempting to drain their wallets. This was the second attack on Curve Finance’s infrastructure in a week.
Users were directed to a website that was a non-functional decoy, designed only to trick users into providing wallet signatures. The hack hadn’t breached the protocol’s smart contracts and was limited to the DNS layer.
The DNS is a critical component of the internet that functions like a phonebook. It allows you to use simple, memorable domain names (such as facebook.com) instead of complex numerical IP addre…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Dilip Kumar Patairya</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Market Sees $300M Liquidations as Trump Tariff Threats Flush Late Bulls]]></title>
        <id>b8f8ab22-fcaf-4344-ab7c-d856c3e58532</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/23/crypto-market-sees-usd300m-liquidations-as-trump-tariff-threats-flush-late-bulls"/>
        <updated>2025-05-23T13:53:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The leverage flush happened as crypto prices quickly dropped on renewed trade war fears, with BTC slipping 3% from near record highs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Krisztian Sandor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Twice lucky? Cetus’ recovery plan on Sui mirrors a Solana blueprint]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/cetus-hack-sui-successful-solana</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/cetus-hack-sui-successful-solana?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-23T13:52:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The bounty offer to recover stolen funds from Sui-based decentralized exchange (DEX) Cetus closely resembles a successful strategy used by a Solana project three years ago.
It turns out that Cetus shares the same development team as Crema Finance, a Solana-based DeFi project that suffered a $9-million hack in 2022 but recovered most of the funds by negotiating with its hacker. Now, Cetus is relying on the same strategy.
Cetus is asking the hacker to return all but $6 million, or 2,324 Ether (ETH), of the stolen funds in exchange for a promise not to pursue legal action. The protocol lost $223 million to an exploit on May 22.
The size of the bounty has sparked backlash from users, with many calling for a formal compensation plan instead. Several community members argue that even if funds ar…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Yohan Yun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Feature Fridays: dTelecom]]></title>
        <id>682f3eb8646f7c0001399182</id>
        <link href="https://blog.quicknode.com/feature-fridays-dtelecom/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-23T13:37:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[dTelecom is reshaping digital communication with decentralized, AI-powered infrastructure for Web3 developers and businesses.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>QuickNode</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Washington moves on crypto: Stablecoin and blockchain bills signal regulatory momentum]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/washington-moves-on-crypto-stablecoin-and-blockchain-bills-signal-regulatory-momentum</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/washington-moves-on-crypto-stablecoin-and-blockchain-bills-signal-regulatory-momentum?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-23T13:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this week’s episode of Byte-Sized Insight, on Decentralize with Cointelegraph, we break down a pivotal moment for US crypto legislation. 
In a 66–32 procedural vote on May 19, the US Senate advanced the GENIUS Act, a landmark bill aimed at establishing a comprehensive regulatory framework for stablecoins. Meanwhile, across the Capitol, Representative Tom Emmer reintroduced the Blockchain Regulatory Certainty Act, backed by bipartisan support.

Breaking down GENIUS
The GENIUS Act — short for “Guiding and Establishing National Innovation for U.S. Stablecoins Act” — seeks to answer foundational questions around stablecoin issuance and oversight.
“It defines this idea of a payment stablecoin,” explained Rashan Colbert, director of US policy at the Crypto Council for Innovation, in this week…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Savannah Fortis</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use React 19 in Power Apps PCF Components]]></title>
        <id>6830767c62d9a28c0de11007</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-react-19-in-pcf-components/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-23T13:22:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Power Apps Component Framework – PCF for short – lets you create complex custom components using traditional web development tools like HTML, CSS, and JavaScript. When creating a new PCF project, you can choose from two types of controls: standar...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brandon Wozniewicz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CoinDesk 20 Performance Update: Index Declines 3.2% as All Assets Trade Lower]]></title>
        <id>ee46e543-c59c-4ad8-ba6c-93619e202250</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/coindesk-indices/2025/05/23/coindesk-20-performance-update-index-declines-3-2-as-all-assets-trade-lower"/>
        <updated>2025-05-23T13:13:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sui (SUI) Dropped 6.8% and NEAR Protocol (NEAR) fell  5.8%, leading the index lower from Thursday.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CoinDesk Indices</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Can ChatGPT-powered AI agents really trade crypto for you?]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/can-chatgpt-powered-ai-agents-really-trade-crypto-for-you</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/can-chatgpt-powered-ai-agents-really-trade-crypto-for-you?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-23T13:13:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Key takeaways

ChatGPT-powered AI agents automate trading tasks using natural language prompts and API integrations, improving speed and consistency.

Successes occur when ChatGPT is used as a support tool, not a fully autonomous trading system.

Failures happen when traders over-rely on ChatGPT without real-time data, proper risk management or manual oversight.

Regulatory focus on AI in trading is increasing, with new frameworks emerging to ensure transparency, accountability and compliance.

What if a crypto trader didn’t need to constantly check charts, worry about emotions, or stay up all night watching for sudden price swings? What if those tasks could be handled by an intelligent agent that understands instructions in plain English — and reacts within milliseconds? That’s where Chat…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Callum Reid</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Semler Scientific Bolsters Bitcoin Holdings with $50M Acquisition]]></title>
        <id>d746f167-b10a-4d8e-bf78-26d09f63294c</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/23/semler-scientific-bolsters-bitcoin-holdings-with-usd50m-acquisition"/>
        <updated>2025-05-23T13:04:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The company acquired 455 bitcoin in its third-largest announced purchase.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>James Van Straten</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why enterprise RAG systems fail: Google study introduces ‘sufficient context’ solution]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008684</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/why-enterprise-rag-systems-fail-google-study-introduces-sufficient-context-solution/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-23T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google's "sufficient context" helps refine RAG systems, reduce LLM hallucinations, and boost AI reliability for business applications.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ben Dickson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Lender Ledn Goes Full Bitcoin Maxi as It Seeks to Reduce Client Asset Risk]]></title>
        <id>523aaf44-b3a2-49dc-874e-8bf44fd3ccc7</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2025/05/23/crypto-lender-ledn-goes-full-bitcoin-maxi-as-it-seeks-to-reduce-client-asset-risk"/>
        <updated>2025-05-23T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ledn said the shift is part of its broader strategy to simplify its product and sharpen its focus around bitcoin.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Crawley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Good Vibes Shattered as Trump Revives Trade War, Sending Bitcoin Tumbling Below $109K]]></title>
        <id>e6b9f8b7-005e-460f-87a2-463276d1c040</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/23/good-vibes-shattered-as-trump-revives-trade-war-bitcoin-tumbles-below-usd109k"/>
        <updated>2025-05-23T12:14:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The president Friday morning threatened an imminent 50% tariff on all EU imports as well as a 25% levy on imported Apple iPhones.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephen Alpher</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Download: meet Cathy Tie, and Anthropic’s new AI models]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1117399</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/05/23/1117399/the-download-meet-cathy-tie-and-anthropics-new-ai-models/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-23T12:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is today’s edition of The Download, our weekday newsletter that provides a daily dose of what’s going on in the world of technology. Meet Cathy Tie, Bride of “China’s Frankenstein” Since the Chinese biophysicist He Jiankui was released from prison in 2022, he has sought to make a scientific comeback and to repair his reputation after…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rhiannon Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Daybook Americas: Bitcoin Market Cap Tops $2.2T as Derivatives, Sentiment Signal More Upside]]></title>
        <id>153c2526-d517-492e-9439-65525a732529</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/daybook-us/2025/05/23/crypto-daybook-americas-bitcoin-market-cap-tops-usd2-2t-as-derivatives-sentiment-signal-more-upside"/>
        <updated>2025-05-23T11:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Your day-ahead look for May 23, 2025]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>James Van Straten</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why I no longer have an old-school cert on my HTTPS site]]></title>
        <id>https://rachelbythebay.com/w/2025/05/22/ssl/</id>
        <link href="https://rachelbythebay.com/w/2025/05/22/ssl/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-23T10:56:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Writing A Job Runner (In Elixir) (Again) (10 years later)]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/notactuallytreyanastasio/genstage_tutorial_2025/blob/main/README.md</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/notactuallytreyanastasio/genstage_tutorial_2025/blob/main/README.md"/>
        <updated>2025-05-23T10:41:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Laid off but not afraid with X-senior Microsoft Dev MacKevin Fey [Podcast #173]]]></title>
        <id>68304756ecdb03ab557f3974</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/laid-off-but-not-afraid-with-x-senior-microsoft-dev-mackevin-fey-podcast-173/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-23T10:00:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On this week's episode of the podcast, freeCodeCamp founder Quincy Larson interviews MacKevin Fey. He just got laid off last week from his senior engineering role at Microsoft. We talk about: How Mack's approaching the job search after being laid of...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CFTC’s Plans for Crypto Perpetual Trading Puts Focus on Hyperliquid’s HYPE]]></title>
        <id>780dccef-8a69-4d87-91ae-6203e5ab8d74</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/23/cftcs-plans-for-crypto-perpetual-trading-puts-focus-on-hyperliquids-hype"/>
        <updated>2025-05-23T09:24:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HYPE is up 15% in the past 24 hours, outperforming majors, as developers said they submitted comments to the derivatives agency on using DeFi principles to create better products.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shaurya Malwa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The FDA plans to limit access to covid vaccines. Here’s why that’s not all bad.]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1117329</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/05/23/1117329/fda-limit-access-covid-vaccines/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-23T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This week, two new leaders at the US Food and Drug Administration announced plans to limit access to covid vaccines, arguing that there is not much evidence to support the value of annual shots in healthy people. New vaccines will be made available only to the people who are most vulnerable—namely, those over 65 and…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jessica Hamzelou</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meet Cathy Tie, Bride of “China’s Frankenstein”]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1117373</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/05/23/1117373/cathy-tie-he-jiankui-china-crispr-x-twitter-feed/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-23T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Since the Chinese biophysicist He Jiankui was released from prison in 2022, he has sought to make a scientific comeback and to repair his reputation after a three-year incarceration for illegally creating the world’s first gene-edited children.  While he has bounced between cities, jobs, and meetings with investors, one area of visible success on his…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Caiwei Chen, Antonio Regalado</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Major U.S. Banks Mull Jointly Launching Stablecoin: WSJ]]></title>
        <id>4c76c31a-f15f-4bf8-af51-2a9c7f7f18bd</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2025/05/23/major-us-banks-mull-jointly-launching-stablecoin-wsj"/>
        <updated>2025-05-23T08:48:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Such a stablecoin, potentially open to other banks, aims to improve transaction speeds and efficiency while fending off competition from crypto firms.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Francisco Rodrigues</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Enters Strongest Accumulation Phase Since January as BTC Price Passes $110K]]></title>
        <id>29205afd-ca8c-4683-93b4-3286329cb66c</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/23/bitcoin-enters-strongest-accumulation-phase-since-january-as-btc-price-passes-110k"/>
        <updated>2025-05-23T07:46:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Glassnode data shows all wallet cohorts are now accumulating, with options markets pricing in potential upside beyond $200K in June.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>James Van Straten</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Justin Sun Defends TRUMP After Presidential Dinner, Says 'Memecoins Have Merit']]></title>
        <id>bc2347ce-4dd2-42f3-afbd-6c99d9881bc9</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/23/justin-sun-defends-trump-after-presidential-dinner-says-memecoins-have-merit"/>
        <updated>2025-05-23T05:45:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tron's Sun sees the President fueling a new American crypto boom.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sam Reynolds</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[XRP Could Rocket to $8 as Focus Shifts to Crypto Majors After Bitcoin's Record Run: Traders]]></title>
        <id>63916677-2e5f-47e3-9059-f526edc85b38</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/23/xrp-could-rocket-to-8-as-focus-shifts-to-crypto-majors-after-bitcoins-record-run-traders"/>
        <updated>2025-05-23T05:33:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Traders are rotating into major altcoins like XRP and Solana’s SOL as bitcoin consolidates near its record highs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shaurya Malwa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[After GPT-4o backlash, researchers benchmark models on moral endorsement—find sycophancy persists across the board]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008691</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/after-gpt-4o-backlash-researchers-benchmark-models-on-moral-endorsement-find-sycophancy-persists-across-the-board/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-22T23:46:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new benchmark can test how much LLMs become sycophants, and found that GPT-4o was the most sycophantic of the models tested.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Emilia David</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Memecoin Moo Deng, MEW Surges After Robinhood Listing]]></title>
        <id>045b859b-4a96-468a-930e-c896c2a17b78</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/22/memecoin-moo-deng-mew-surges-after-robinhood-listing"/>
        <updated>2025-05-22T21:27:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Both tokens jumped on the news, adding to their already large gains this month.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Helene Braun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn Vue.js in This Beginner's Course]]></title>
        <id>682f84537a13a40bfa336307</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-vuejs-in-this-beginners-course/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-22T20:08:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you’ve been meaning to add Vue.js to your front-end toolbelt, today’s your day. We just published a full, 6-hour Vue 3 course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel. Instructor Bhrugen Patel walks you through everything you need to build modern, ...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BlockTrust IRA Brings Quant Trading Tools to Crypto Retirement Accounts]]></title>
        <id>a5315ae8-f5e0-44d7-a384-5068f2df64aa</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/22/blocktrust-ira-brings-quant-trading-tools-to-crypto-retirement-accounts"/>
        <updated>2025-05-22T19:16:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By leveraging trading signals from Animus Technologies, BlockTrust IRA promises to beat benchmark BTC and ETH positions.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tom Carreras</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Anthropic faces backlash to Claude 4 Opus behavior that contacts authorities, press if it thinks you’re doing something ‘egregiously immoral’]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008672</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/anthropic-faces-backlash-to-claude-4-opus-behavior-that-contacts-authorities-press-if-it-thinks-youre-doing-something-immoral/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-22T19:12:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bowman later edited his tweet and the following one in a thread to read as follows, but it still didn't convince the naysayers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carl Franzen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Major Wake-Up Call': How $400M Coinbase Breach Exposes Crypto's Dark Side]]></title>
        <id>6ba27993-c6da-4035-876c-4ecc7282f4c4</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2025/05/22/major-wake-up-call-how-usd400m-coinbase-breach-exposes-crypto-s-dark-side"/>
        <updated>2025-05-22T18:21:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase said 69,461 customers were initially impacted by the breach, but fears remain over the threat of real-world robberies.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Oliver Knight</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Centrifuge Expands Tokenized RWAs to Solana, Starting With $400M Treasury Fund]]></title>
        <id>b7b95f56-2902-4daa-a192-c48b5b4a2397</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/22/centrifuge-expands-tokenized-rwas-to-solana-starting-with-400m-treasury-fund"/>
        <updated>2025-05-22T18:18:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Solana is gaining momentum in the fast-growing tokenized real-world asset space as traditional finance and DeFi gets increasingly intertwined.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Krisztian Sandor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Democrats Threaten Lawsuits, Join Protests Ahead of Trump Memecoin Dinner]]></title>
        <id>f7b1009d-92f3-48ba-bdf1-a1ec95b8d506</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2025/05/22/democrats-threaten-lawsuits-join-protests-ahead-of-trump-memecoin-dinner"/>
        <updated>2025-05-22T18:06:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Democratic lawmakers went through a flurry of actions to highlight concerns that Donald Trump's memecoin dinner is "corrupt."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jesse Hamilton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Anthropic’s new hybrid AI model can work on tasks autonomously for hours at a time]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1117338</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/05/22/1117338/anthropics-new-hybrid-ai-model-can-work-on-tasks-autonomously-for-hours-at-a-time/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-22T16:51:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Anthropic has announced two new AI models that it claims represent a major step toward making AI agents truly useful. AI agents trained on Claude Opus 4, the company’s most powerful model to date, raise the bar for what such systems are capable of by tackling difficult tasks over extended periods of time and responding…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rhiannon Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Anthropic overtakes OpenAI: Claude Opus 4 codes seven hours nonstop, sets record SWE-Bench score and reshapes enterprise AI]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008575</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/anthropic-claude-opus-4-can-code-for-7-hours-straight-and-its-about-to-change-how-we-work-with-ai/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-22T16:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Anthropic's Claude Opus 4 outperforms OpenAI's GPT-4.1 with unprecedented seven-hour autonomous coding sessions and record-breaking 72.5% SWE-bench score, transforming AI from quick-response tool to day-long collaborator.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Nuñez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Major TradFi Institutions to Pursue Tokenization Efforts on Solana]]></title>
        <id>1e9f7d9e-f627-457a-8dda-a93e35c00f69</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2025/05/22/major-tradfi-institutions-to-pursue-tokenization-efforts-on-solana"/>
        <updated>2025-05-22T16:12:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tokenization is one of the principal use cases of blockchain technology attracting the attention and investment of the TradFi world]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Crawley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Justin Sun-Linked Wallet Leading Access to Trump Dinner Tagged as Belonging to HTX]]></title>
        <id>bca545d8-d0c9-4cfa-a211-44f6c0f97575</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2025/05/22/justin-sun-linked-wallet-leading-access-to-trump-dinner-tagged-as-belonging-to-htx"/>
        <updated>2025-05-22T16:05:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sun, a Chinese-born crypto billionaire, is also involved with the Trump-linked ecosystem through a $75 million investment in World Liberty Financial.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Francisco Rodrigues</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Deploy Your FastAPI + PostgreSQL App on Render: A Beginner's Guide]]></title>
        <id>682f4900bcc94cb9bccbf905</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/deploy-fastapi-postgresql-app-on-render/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-22T15:55:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This guide is a comprehensive roadmap for deploying a FastAPI backend connected to a PostgreSQL database using Render, a cloud platform that supports hosting Python web apps and managed PostgreSQL databases.   You can find the complete source code he...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Preston Osoro</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kraken to List Tokenized Version of Nvidia, Apple, Tesla Shares]]></title>
        <id>3b9fba56-daf9-4556-b83f-f6eaa28ad999</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/22/kraken-to-list-tokenized-version-of-nvidia-apple-tesla-shares"/>
        <updated>2025-05-22T15:55:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The tokens will be deployed on Solana and backed by real securities held by Kraken’s partner, Backed Finance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Helene Braun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[First U.S. XRP Futures ETF Begins Trading on Nasdaq]]></title>
        <id>0a64f011-e949-485d-b984-18f3a3d2971d</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/22/first-u-s-xrp-futures-etf-begins-trading-on-nasdaq"/>
        <updated>2025-05-22T15:53:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The fund will invest at least 80% of its assets in XRP futures contracts and shares of other XRP-linked exchange-traded products.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Helene Braun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[An Animated Introduction to Elixir]]></title>
        <id>682f44e3dcb21c615cf1a12d</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/an-animated-introduction-to-elixir/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-22T15:38:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Elixir is a dynamic, functional programming language designed for building scalable and maintainable applications. It leverages the battle-tested Erlang VM, known for running low-latency, distributed, and fault-tolerant systems. Elixir is based on an...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mark Mahoney</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Time Magazine appears to accidentally publish embargoed story confirming new Anthropic model]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008649</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/time-magazine-appears-to-accidentally-publish-embargoed-story-confirming-anthropic-claude-4-opus/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-22T15:26:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Someone also appears to have published a full scrape of the Time article online on the news aggregator app Newsbreak.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carl Franzen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto for Advisors: When Crypto Meets Netflix]]></title>
        <id>7f516d56-430a-487d-90aa-11357443c3c4</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/coindesk-indices/2025/05/21/crypto-for-advisors-when-crypto-meets-netflix"/>
        <updated>2025-05-22T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How Black Mirror’s on-chain experiment is paving the way for the future of entertainment monetization.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shivani Phull</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Enchant launches zero-equity accelerator for gaming and AI startups]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008571</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/games/enchant-launches-zero-equity-accelerator-for-gaming-and-ai-startups/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-22T12:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Enchant is launching a new zero-equity accelerator for gaming and AI startups, with applications now open for its three-month program.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dean Takahashi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Download: the desert data center boom, and how to measure Earth’s elevations]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1117300</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/05/22/1117300/the-download-the-desert-data-center-boom-and-how-to-measure-earths-elevations/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-22T12:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is today’s edition of The Download, our weekday newsletter that provides a daily dose of what’s going on in the world of technology. The data center boom in the desert In the high desert east of Reno, Nevada, construction crews are flattening the golden foothills of the Virginia Range, laying the foundations of a data center…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rhiannon Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Three takeaways about AI’s energy use and climate impacts]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1117277</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/05/22/1117277/ai-energy-three-takeaways/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-22T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This week, we published Power Hungry, a package all about AI and energy. At the center of this package is the most comprehensive look yet at AI’s growing power demand, if I do say so myself.  This data-heavy story is the result of over six months of reporting by me and my colleague James O’Donnell…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Casey Crownhart</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A new atomic clock in space could help us measure elevations on Earth]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1117294</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/05/22/1117294/a-new-atomic-clock-in-space-could-help-us-measure-elevations-on-earth/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-22T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In 2003, engineers from Germany and Switzerland began building a bridge across the Rhine River simultaneously from both sides. Months into construction, they found that the two sides did not meet. The German side hovered 54 centimeters above the Swiss side. The misalignment occurred because the German engineers had measured elevation with a historic level…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sophia Chen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[At Google I/O, Sergey Brin makes surprise appearance — and declares Google will build the first AGI]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008490</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/at-google-i-o-sergey-brin-makes-surprise-appearance-and-declares-google-will-build-the-first-agi/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-21T22:20:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google co-founder Sergey Brin makes surprise appearance at Google I/O, declaring "Gemini will be the very first AGI," revealing philosophical tensions with DeepMind CEO Hassabis who urges scientific caution in the high-stakes AI race.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Nuñez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Master Database Management Systems]]></title>
        <id>682e3c04117e792e5f46edc3</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/master-database-management-systems/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-21T20:48:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Understanding how to manage data effectively is a critical skill for anyone pursuing a career in tech. And we just published a course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will teach you all about Database Management Systems (DBMS). This in-de...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Show HN: High-resolution surface analysis with Lidar data]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/r-follador/delta-relief</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/r-follador/delta-relief"/>
        <updated>2025-05-21T20:40:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Roundtables: A New Look at AI’s Energy Use]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1117287</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/05/21/1117287/roundtables-a-new-look-at-ais-energy-use-2/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-21T19:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Recorded on May 21, 2025 Big Tech’s appetite for energy is growing rapidly as adoption of AI accelerates. But just how much energy does even a single AI query use? And what does it mean for the climate? Hear from MIT Technology Review editor in chief Mat Honan, senior climate reporter Casey Crownhart, and AI reporter James…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>MIT Technology Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Refactor Complex Codebases – A Practical Guide for Devs]]></title>
        <id>682df5a0f2057ab279952dbe</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-refactor-complex-codebases/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-21T15:47:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Developers often see refactoring as a secondary concern that they can delay indefinitely because it doesn’t immediately contribute to revenue or feature development. And managers frequently view refactoring as "not a business need" until it boils ove...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ankur Tyagi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Vibe Coding Won't Destroy Software Engineering]]></title>
        <id>682df55da72360814bcae9ef</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/why-vibe-coding-wont-destroy-software-engineering/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-21T15:46:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AI is disrupting all industries at a pace not seen at any time in history. Technologies and industries that were once dominated by one or two companies or were very much “human-focused” are coming under threat. Google is losing ground to AI search, t...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ben</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OpenAI updates its new Responses API rapidly with MCP support, GPT-4o native image gen, and more enterprise features]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008465</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/programming-development/openai-updates-its-new-responses-api-rapidly-with-mcp-support-gpt-4o-native-image-gen-and-more-enterprise-features/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-21T15:30:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Support for remote Model Context Protocol servers, integration of image generation and Code Interpreter tools, and upgrades to file search...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carl Franzen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mistral AI launches Devstral, powerful new open source SWE agent model that runs on laptops]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008458</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/mistral-ai-launches-devstral-powerful-new-open-source-swe-agent-model-that-runs-on-laptops/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-21T14:57:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Beyond performance and portability, its Apache 2.0 license offers a compelling proposition for commercial applications.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carl Franzen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Download: Google’s AI mission, and America’s reliance on natural gas]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1117249</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/05/21/1117249/the-download-googles-ai-mission-and-americas-reliance-on-natural-gas/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-21T12:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is today’s edition of The Download, our weekday newsletter that provides a daily dose of what’s going on in the world of technology. By putting AI into everything, Google wants to make it invisible If you want to know where AI is headed, this year’s Google I/O has you covered. The company’s annual showcase of next-gen…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rhiannon Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[By putting AI into everything, Google wants to make it invisible]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1117251</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/05/21/1117251/by-putting-ai-into-everything-google-wants-to-make-it-invisible/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-21T11:49:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you want to know where AI is headed, this year’s Google I/O has you covered. The company’s annual showcase of next-gen products, which kicked off yesterday, has all of the pomp and pizzazz, the sizzle reels and celebrity walk-ons, that you’d expect from a multimillion-dollar marketing event. But it also shows us just how…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Will Douglas Heaven</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Jupiter was formerly twice its current size, had a much stronger magnetic field]]></title>
        <id>https://phys.org/news/2025-05-jupiter-current-size-stronger-magnetic.html</id>
        <link href="https://phys.org/news/2025-05-jupiter-current-size-stronger-magnetic.html"/>
        <updated>2025-05-21T09:26:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mermaid: Generation of diagrams like flowcharts or sequence diagrams from text]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/mermaid-js/mermaid</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/mermaid-js/mermaid"/>
        <updated>2025-05-21T09:06:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AMD unveils new Threadripper CPUs and Radeon GPUs for gamers at Computex 2025]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008206</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/games/amd-unveils-new-threadripper-cpus-and-radeon-gpus-for-gamers-at-computex-2025/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-21T03:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AMD held a Computex press event to introduce its Radeon RX 9060 XT graphics cards and Threadripper CPUs for next-gen gaming and workstations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dean Takahashi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google finally launches NotebookLM mobile app at I/O: hands-on, first impressions]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008400</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/google-finally-launches-notebooklm-mobile-app-at-i-o-hands-on-first-impressions/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T19:29:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As NotebookLM matures, its emerging business-tier capabilities suggest growing alignment with the productivity and compliance...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carl Franzen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Alone and Adrift in the Pacific]]></title>
        <id>https://www.theatlantic.com/magazine/archive/2025/06/commercial-fisherman-shipwreck/682580/</id>
        <link href="https://www.theatlantic.com/magazine/archive/2025/06/commercial-fisherman-shipwreck/682580/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T19:15:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google just leapfrogged every competitor with mind-blowing AI that can think deeper, shop smarter, and create videos with dialogue]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008346</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/google-just-leapfrogged-every-competitor-with-mind-blowing-ai-that-can-think-deeper-shop-smarter-and-create-videos-with-dialogue/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T17:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google unveiled major AI advancements at I/O 2025, including Gemini 2.5 with Deep Think, AI Mode in Search, Veo 3 for video with audio, and a $249 Ultra plan aimed at power users and enterprises.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Nuñez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google’s Jules aims to out-code Codex in battle for the AI developer stack]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008361</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/googles-jules-aims-to-out-code-codex-in-battle-for-the-ai-developer-stack/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T17:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google released Jules, its coding agent, into beta as autonomous coding agents are quickly gaining market share.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Emilia David</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Inside Google’s AI leap: Gemini 2.5 thinks deeper, speaks smarter and codes faster]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008366</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/inside-google-ai-leap-gemini-2-5-thinks-deeper-speaks-smarter-codes-faster/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T17:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google is moving closer to its goal of autonomous agentic AI with a series of enhancements to Gemini 2.5 Pro and Flash.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Taryn Plumb</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blazing-fast Solana data via gRPC: access the freshest Solana data from Shredstream leaders]]></title>
        <id>68273f14bf73460001094b35</id>
        <link href="https://blog.quicknode.com/yellowstone-grpc/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T15:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Access the fastest Solana data with the Yellowstone Geyser gRPC self-serve add-on or with the premium hybrid dedicated gRPC node.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>QuickNode</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Autopsy of an LHC Beam Dump]]></title>
        <id>https://home.cern/news/news/accelerators/autopsy-lhc-beam-dump</id>
        <link href="https://home.cern/news/news/accelerators/autopsy-lhc-beam-dump"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T15:37:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft just launched an AI that discovered a new chemical in 200 hours instead of years]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008310</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/microsoft-just-launched-an-ai-that-discovered-a-new-chemical-in-200-hours-instead-of-years/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T18:34:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft launches Discovery platform that uses agentic AI to compress years of scientific research into days, transforming R&D across pharmaceuticals, materials science, and semiconductor industries.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Nuñez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Is your AI app pissing off users or going off-script? Raindrop emerges with AI-native observability platform to monitor performance]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008299</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/is-your-ai-app-pissing-off-users-or-going-off-script-raindrop-emerges-with-ai-native-observability-platform-to-monitor-performance/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T18:09:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With its rebrand and product expansion, Raindrop is betting that the next generation of software observability will be AI-first by design.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carl Franzen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft just taught its AI agents to talk to each other—and it could transform how we work]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008254</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/microsoft-just-taught-its-ai-agents-to-talk-to-each-other-and-it-could-transform-how-we-work/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T16:01:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft unveils multi-agent systems, WhatsApp integration, and Python-powered analytics for Copilot Studio at Build 2025, transforming how enterprises build and deploy AI solutions.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Nuñez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Microsoft Fabric has already been adopted by 70% of the Fortune 500 — and what’s next]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3007980</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/70-of-the-fortune-500-already-use-microsoft-fabric-and-its-now-getting-even-more-features-including-cosmosdb-support/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft integrates CosmosDB into Fabric, open sources DiskANN vector search, and unifies its data platforms to eliminate integration complexity that has slowed enterprise AI adoption.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sean Michael Kerner</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub Copilot evolves into autonomous agent with asynchronous code testing]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008231</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/github-copilot-evolves-into-autonomous-agent-with-asynchronous-code-testing/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub adds agentic capabilities to its Copilot coding assistant, competing with other more asynchronous coding platforms.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Emilia David</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft announces over 50 AI tools to build the ‘agentic web’ at Build 2025]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008229</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/microsoft-announces-over-50-ai-tools-to-build-the-agentic-web-at-build-2025/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T15:59:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft reveals its ambitious AI agent strategy, showcasing how multi-agent systems with persistent memory will transform enterprise workflows and accelerate development timelines.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Nuñez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Reddit, Webflow, and Superhuman are already customers—now GrowthX has $12M to grow]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008276</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/reddit-webflow-and-superhuman-are-already-customers-now-growthx-has-12m-to-grow/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[GrowthX secures $12M in funding for its "service-as-software" platform that combines AI with human expertise to boost content marketing results by up to 300%.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Nuñez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Quantum Machines launches Qualibrate open source framework to speed quantum computer calibration]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008032</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/games/quantum-machines-launches-qualibrate-open-source-framework-to-speed-quantum-computer-calibration/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Quantum Machines, a provider of advanced hybrid quantum-classical control solutions, announced today the release of Qualibrate.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dean Takahashi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Samsung boosts OLED TV gaming with Nvidia G-Sync compatibility]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008019</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/games/samsung-boosts-oled-tv-gaming-with-nvidia-g-sync-compatibility/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Samsung said its 2025 OLED TV lineup will feature Nvidia G-Sync compatibility, delivering smooth gameplay, low latency, and more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dean Takahashi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Salesforce just unveiled AI ‘digital teammates’ in Slack — and they’re coming for Microsoft Copilot]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008273</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/salesforce-just-unveiled-ai-digital-teammates-in-slack-and-theyre-coming-for-microsoft-copilot/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Salesforce launches Agentforce in Slack, transforming workplace productivity with specialized AI agents that operate as digital teammates, replacing one-size-fits-all AI assistants with purpose-built solutions.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Nuñez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Foxconn builds AI factory in partnership with Taiwan and Nvidia]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008261</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/games/foxconn-builds-ai-factory-in-partnership-with-taiwan-and-nvidia/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T07:14:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nvidia and Foxconn announced they are working with the Taiwan government to build an AI factory supercomputer.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dean Takahashi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is Sui: A Comprehensive Guide to Web3 Scalability]]></title>
        <id>6823533984101f00013a5ca4</id>
        <link href="https://blog.quicknode.com/what-is-sui-a-comprehensive-guide-to-web3-scalability/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-15T23:34:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Explore how Sui Network achieves 300,000 TPS through parallel processing, and its applications in gaming, DeFi, and supply chain management.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>QuickNode</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AI Meets Blockchain: Transforming Technology for the Next Era]]></title>
        <id>682354c584101f00013a5cb9</id>
        <link href="https://blog.quicknode.com/ai-and-blockchain-transforming-technology-together/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-15T23:34:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discover how AI and blockchain integration enhances security, efficiency, and innovation in healthcare, supply chains, and financial services.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>QuickNode</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Adventure Layer: AI Native Onchain Games, Unleashed]]></title>
        <id>6824c55abf73460001094973</id>
        <link href="https://blog.quicknode.com/adventure-layer-launches-on-quicknode-raas/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-15T12:04:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Adventure Layer launches layer-2 chain leveraging QuickNode's Rollup-as-a-Service (RaaS) product.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>QuickNode</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[QuickLee V2: An Improved Transparent Look into RPC Provider Latency]]></title>
        <id>680fc8e1f8ae810001969b47</id>
        <link href="https://blog.quicknode.com/quicklee-v2/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-14T13:57:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[View public and real-time dashboards to better understand latency and speed when evaluating RPC providers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>QuickNode</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>