<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2025-05-28T15:44:52.775Z</id>
    <title>AngJianming RSS Feed</title>
    <updated>2025-05-28T15:44:52.775Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Don't Talk to Strangers (Unless You're Serious About Growth)]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/tlorent/dont-talk-to-strangers-unless-youre-serious-about-growth-4acf</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/tlorent/dont-talk-to-strangers-unless-youre-serious-about-growth-4acf"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T15:35:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We all know the rule: "Don’t talk to strangers."
But here’s the twist: Some of the bravest career decisions I’ve seen recently started with breaking that rule.
Over the past few weeks, developers from all kinds of backgrounds booked free 1-on-1 growth calls with me, a total stranger. No job offer. No catch. Just 30 minutes to reflect on where they are and where they want to go.
And you know what? That first step, scheduling the call and showing up, was the real moment of growth.
Not the frameworks.
Just choosing courage over comfort.
Many developers feel stuck, overwhelmed, or unsure of their next move. They think they need more skills, more courses, or more "readiness."
But often, what they actually need is…

💬 a conversation
a listener
a bit of clarity from someone outside their own head
Growth doesn't have to be loud. Sometimes, it starts quietly: with a message, a call, a stranger who’s been there before.
Yes. If that stranger is someone who’s walked the path and wants to help, do it.
Take the call. Ask the question. Start the conversation that scares you a little.
It might be the bravest, smartest move you make all year.
Want to talk to a stranger? You know where to find me!
https://calendly.com/tim-lorent/free-30-minute-growth-call-for-developers]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tim Lorent</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Understanding JavaScript Built-in Functions and Events day-2]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/elayaraj31/understanding-javascript-built-in-functions-and-events-2k2d</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/elayaraj31/understanding-javascript-built-in-functions-and-events-2k2d"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T15:30:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[🌟 What Are Built-in Functions in JavaScript?
Built-in functions are predefined functions provided by the JavaScript language itself. You don’t have to write these from scratch — they’re available right out of the box.
✨ Common Built-in Functions
Here are some you’ll use all the time:
✅ alert()
alert("Hello, world!");

✅ prompt()
let name = prompt("What’s your name?");

✅ parseInt() and parseFloat()
let num = parseInt("42");
let price = parseFloat("99.99");


✅ isNaN()
isNaN("hello"); // true
isNaN(123);     // false


✅ Math functions
Math.round(4.7);    // 5

✅ Date object functions
let now = new Date();

These are just a few — JavaScript offers many built-in functions, which help reduce the amount of code you need to write.
🖱️ What Are Events in JavaScript?
An event is something that h…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Elayaraj C</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Empowering Contact Center Agents with Amazon Q Business]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/aws-builders/empowering-contact-center-agents-with-amazon-q-business-117g</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/aws-builders/empowering-contact-center-agents-with-amazon-q-business-117g"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T15:30:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In today's customer service environment, call center agents face significant operational challenges. They navigate multiple information systems while striving to efficiently support customers across diverse products and services. This complexity directly impacts critical performance metrics including average handle time, first-call resolution rates, and customer satisfaction scores.
Meeting these performance benchmarks requires agents to quickly access accurate information while maintaining natural conversation flow - a difficult balance when knowledge is scattered across various platforms. 
In this article, we'll explore how Amazon Q Business transforms these operational challenges into opportunities for enhanced call center performance. We'll examine how this solution empowers agents to …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Vini Ganancio</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lists in Python]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/datatoinfinity/lists-in-python-493g</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/datatoinfinity/lists-in-python-493g"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T15:29:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A list is data structure in python that is mutable, or changeable, ordered sequence of element.
Now break it down this definition. Let's start with why list is a data structure.
Data Structure: A data structure is a way to store, organize, and manage data so it can be used efficiently.
When we say list is data structure its means:
A list is one of the built-in tools Python provides to hold a collection of items in an ordered and changeable way.
Now understand what it means mutable and changeable.
 


Output:
[4, 2, 3]


Lets take an example of ordered sequence
A list being ordered means the position of each item is fixed, and you can rely on it to stay that way—unless you change it.
Position means index of an item like 
cherry->index 0
tomato->index 1
brinjal->index 2]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>datatoinfinity</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[From e-mail to e-ink: an inbox-powered feed for TRMNL]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/schrockwell/from-e-mail-to-e-ink-an-inbox-powered-feed-for-trmnl-2p60</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/schrockwell/from-e-mail-to-e-ink-an-inbox-powered-feed-for-trmnl-2p60"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T15:28:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is a submission for the Postmark Challenge: Inbox Innovators.
Since 2014, Postmark has been my email backend of choice for business, client, and personal web apps.
When I joined the TRMNL team last year, it was no surprise to find Postmark in their Rails app, too. They had even developed an analytics dashboard for the TRMNL itself for users to track their e-mail health.

That works great for monitoring outbound email, but this week's challenge is all about inbound messages. So I decided to build a new fun plugin that works in the other direction.
PSTMRK is an e-ink dashboard for TRMNL that transforms a Postmark inbound email address into a personal microblog for display around the home or workplace.

Simply send a message to the inbound address and the display automatically updates. T…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rockwell Schrock</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build a Low-Cost Smart Fence: DIY Guide for Homeowners and Developers]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/karen_londres/how-to-build-a-low-cost-smart-fence-diy-guide-for-homeowners-and-developers-466e</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/karen_londres/how-to-build-a-low-cost-smart-fence-diy-guide-for-homeowners-and-developers-466e"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T15:28:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Smart home security is no longer a luxury—it’s becoming a necessity. As homeowners look for innovative ways to safeguard their property without breaking the bank, the concept of a low-cost smart fence has gained momentum.
Whether you're a tech-savvy DIYer, run a fence company, or are a blogger writing about smart home trends, this guide will show you how to design and implement an affordable smart fencing solution. We'll also look at practical code snippets to help you build and test components for your system.
With increasing concerns over home safety and rising demand for digital convenience, smart fences offer a powerful solution. They can:
Detect unauthorized entry
Notify you instantly via mobile
Allow remote access or lockdown
Integrate with smart lights, locks, and cameras
The good n…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Karen Londres</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[I Was So Angry, I Built My Own]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/sebs/i-was-so-angry-i-built-my-own-4mj1</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/sebs/i-was-so-angry-i-built-my-own-4mj1"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T15:24:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Frustration often breeds innovation. After years of wrestling with project management tools that never quite fit my needs, I reached my breaking point. The tools were either too complex, too rigid, or missing critical features that my teams needed. So I did what any frustrated developer would do – I built my own.
Most project management tools force you into their proprietary editors with fancy formatting options that ultimately create more problems than they solve. All I wanted was to edit markdown files – simple, portable, version-control friendly text that everyone already understands. Why should documenting a story be more complicated than writing code?

My solution: a project management system where everything is markdown at its core. Stories, documentation, comments – all just markdow…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sebastian Schürmann</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lift and Slide Doors — Innovative Solutions for Comfort and Security]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/anna2606/lift-and-slide-doors-innovative-solutions-for-comfort-and-security-4a57</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/anna2606/lift-and-slide-doors-innovative-solutions-for-comfort-and-security-4a57"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T15:24:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In modern construction and interior design, special attention is given to combining functionality with aesthetics. One of the best solutions that meets these requirements is lift and slide doors. These innovative doors are rapidly gaining popularity thanks to their ease of use, stylish appearance, and high energy efficiency.
Unlike traditional sliding doors, lift and slide doors offer improved sealing and durability. The lifting mechanism allows the door panel to slightly raise when opening, enabling smooth and silent gliding along the track. When closed, the door lowers and fits tightly against the seals, providing reliable protection against drafts, moisture, and noise. This significantly enhances thermal insulation and helps reduce heating and cooling costs.
Large glass panels used in lift and slide doors maximize natural light penetration into the room and create the effect of a seamless transition between interior and exterior spaces. Such doors are especially relevant for homes with views of a garden, terrace, or pool — they visually expand the living area and give the room a modern and elegant look.
From a design perspective, lift and slide doors are highly versatile. They come in various materials — aluminum, wood, and combinations — allowing you to choose the optimal option to match any building style. Additionally, there are different finishing and color options that will harmoniously fit your interior or exterior.
Security is another advantage of these doors. Modern models are equipped with multi-point locking systems, making unauthorized access difficult. This makes lift and slide doors an excellent choice for those who value comfort and home protection.
If you are planning a renovation or construction and want to invest in a durable, convenient, and stylish solution, we recommend considering lift and slide doors. They will not only improve the functionality of your home but also significantly increase its market value.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Anna</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[XAI to pay Telegram $300M to integrate Grok into the chat app]]></title>
        <id>https://techcrunch.com/2025/05/28/xai-to-invest-300m-in-telegram-integrate-grok-into-app/</id>
        <link href="https://techcrunch.com/2025/05/28/xai-to-invest-300m-in-telegram-integrate-grok-into-app/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T15:12:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The mysterious Gobi wall uncovered]]></title>
        <id>https://phys.org/news/2025-05-secrets-mysterious-gobi-wall-uncovered.html</id>
        <link href="https://phys.org/news/2025-05-secrets-mysterious-gobi-wall-uncovered.html"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T15:07:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin sags below $108K as rate-cut bets evaporate before Fed minutes]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-sags-below-108k-rate-cut-bets-evaporate-before-fed-minutes</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-sags-below-108k-rate-cut-bets-evaporate-before-fed-minutes?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T15:05:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Key points:

Markets increasingly see fewer Fed rate cuts this year, with the first only coming in September.

Despite potential labor market weakness to come, crypto and risk assets lack an overall bullish catalyst, analysis says.

BTC/USD continues to drop toward new multiday lows.

Bitcoin (BTC) sold off at the May 28 Wall Street open as markets continued to price out US interest rate cuts.
BTC/USD 1-hour chart. Source: Cointelegraph/TradingView
BTC price retreats with Fed rate cut bets
Data from Cointelegraph Markets Pro and TradingView showed BTC/USD dipping below $108,000 to challenge multiday lows.
Ahead of the minutes of the Federal Reserve’s May meeting, the mood among risk assets was cautious.
CME Group’s FedWatch Tool showed decreasing odds of a rate cut — a key tailwind for cry…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by William Suberg</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A crash course in Next.js middleware]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/logrocket/a-crash-course-in-nextjs-middleware-3b7h</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/logrocket/a-crash-course-in-nextjs-middleware-3b7h"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Written by Temitope Oyedele✏️
Next.js middleware lets you run code before a request finishes and update the response. Alongside Edge Functions, it's a powerful tool that enables developers to achieve enhanced functionality and performance. Middleware was introduced in Next.js v12 and has been improved in consecutive versions. Starting with Next.js v13, middleware can be used to respond directly to requests without going through the route handler. 
This can improve performance and security. Middleware can also be used to work with Vercel Edge Functions. Edge Functions allow you to run code at the network's edge. So, in this post, we’ll learn how middleware works with Edge Functions and why it’s important to know. Now, let’s get started!
Middleware in Next.js is a piece of code that allows y…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Megan Lee</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rumi raises $4.7M to change passive media into interactive AI experiences]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3009144</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/games/rumi-raises-4-7m-to-change-passive-media-into-interactive-ai-experiences/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Rumi, an AI media company, has raised $4.7 million in a pre-seed funding round to transform passive media with rewards.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dean Takahashi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Polygon, GSR Release Katana Network Tackle DeFi Fragmentation]]></title>
        <id>3a4ed530-44f4-47df-991a-24a9890b4236</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/tech/2025/05/28/polygon-gsr-release-katana-network-tackle-defi-fragmentation"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Katana aims to improve blockchain liquidity — including lending, trading, and yield bearing strategies — by integrating with popular apps like Sushi and Morpho.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Margaux Nijkerk</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Jersey's Bergen County to Tokenize $240B in Real Estate Deeds on Avalanche Network]]></title>
        <id>e1a17b36-5139-48d5-bb9d-5c34b6ded820</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2025/05/28/new-jerseys-bergen-county-to-tokenize-240b-in-real-estate-deeds-on-avalanche-network"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The wealthy New York City suburb will migrate 370,000 property deeds — representing about $240 billion worth of real estate — onto an immutable, searchable blockchain ledger.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Krisztian Sandor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Polygon-backed, high-yield blockchain launches for institutional adoption]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/katana-defi-chain-launches-private-mainnet-for-higher-yields</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/katana-defi-chain-launches-private-mainnet-for-higher-yields?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Katana Foundation, a nonprofit focused on decentralized finance (DeFi) development, is launching its private mainnet, aiming to unlock greater crypto asset productivity via deeper liquidity and higher yields for users.
The Katana Foundation launched a DeFi-optimized, private blockchain, Katana, on May 28, incubated by GSR Markets and Polygon Labs, with the public mainnet launch set for June.
The new blockchain will enable users to earn higher yields and explore DeFi in a “unique, optimized yield environment” that unlocks latent value through an ecosystem that makes every digital asset “work harder,” according to an announcement shared with Cointelegraph.
“DeFi users deserve ecosystems that prioritize sustainable liquidity and consistent ‘real’ yields,” wrote Marc Boiron, the CEO of Pol…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Zoltan Vardai</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin’s physical infrastructure is the industry’s most overlooked asset]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-physical-infrastructure</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-physical-infrastructure?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Opinion by: Scott Buchanan, chief operating officer of Bitcoin Depot
A new proposal to install Bitcoin ATMs in federal buildings highlights an important question: Can crypto truly go mainstream without a stronger physical presence? For years, the industry has focused on software and decentralization, but its reluctance to invest in real-world infrastructure is starting to show. Without physical access points, crypto risks becoming an exclusive, insiders-only system, rather than the open alternative it sets out to be.
Everyone loves to talk about decentralization. There’s a good reason behind this. It defines the movement, shapes the technology, and supports the vision of a better financial system. While the industry focuses on code and algorithms, it lacks something basic. A decentralized …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Scott Buchanan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Stop Struggling with Forms in React - 4 Smart Ways to Handle Them]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/werliton/stop-struggling-with-forms-in-react-4-smart-ways-to-handle-them-1hbp</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/werliton/stop-struggling-with-forms-in-react-4-smart-ways-to-handle-them-1hbp"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T14:58:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Forms are an essential part of any web application. In React, there are several ways to manage forms, from manual control to powerful libraries. In this article, we’ll explore four popular methods to handle forms in React, with practical examples for each.
React uses "controlled" inputs, where the input value is stored in the state.
import React, { useState } from 'react';

function BasicForm() {
  const [form, setForm] = useState({ name: '', email: '' });

  function handleChange(e) {
    setForm({ ...form, [e.target.name]: e.target.value });
  }

  function handleSubmit(e) {
    e.preventDefault();
    console.log(form);
  }

  return (
    <form onSubmit={handleSubmit}>
      <input placeholder="TCHACA" name="name" value={form.name} onChange={handleChange}  />
      <input placeholder="…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Werliton Silva</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Grafana Agent Installation and Configuration]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/thdevops/grafana-agent-installation-and-configuration-49m4</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/thdevops/grafana-agent-installation-and-configuration-49m4"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T14:55:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Grafana Agent Installation and Configuration Documentation



  
  
  Introduction to Grafana Agent


Grafana Agent is a single, lightweight binary that consolidates multiple observability tools into one solution. It replaces the need to run separately:
Prometheus for metrics collection
Promtail for log collection
Node Exporter for system metrics
cAdvisor for container metrics
Other exporters from the Prometheus ecosystem
Single binary: Reduces operational complexity
Smaller footprint: Lower resource usage compared to multiple agents
Native Remote Write: Direct integration with Prometheus, Mimir, Cortex
Unified configuration: Single YAML for all functionalities
Flexibility: Enable/disable components as needed
┌─────────────────────────────────────────────────────────────┐
│                …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Thiago da Silva</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[🌍 Building a Digital Health Platform for Africa — Looking for a Volunteer Developer (Remote, Part-time)]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/elox/building-a-digital-health-platform-for-africa-looking-for-a-volunteer-developer-remote-1cmo</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/elox/building-a-digital-health-platform-for-africa-looking-for-a-volunteer-developer-remote-1cmo"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T14:55:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi Dev Community! 👋
My name is El Bachir (Elox), and I’m based in Senegal. I’m currently leading Santel Healthcare, an early-stage project aiming to transform healthcare access across Africa through digital innovation, community-led savings, and systemic reform.
We believe that tech can be a bridge — not just a tool — in addressing deep-rooted challenges in health systems. Santel is designed to be more than an app: it’s a movement combining technology, policy advocacy, and inclusive models of care.
🚀 What we’re building:
A first digital prototype (web/mobile) that helps:
We’re currently a small team:
⸻

👩‍💻 Who we’re looking for:
A volunteer developer (frontend or fullstack) who:
💡 We’re also open to evolving the role into a long-term collaboration — potentially even a cofounder position — if there’s shared vision and alignment.
⸻

🧭 Why this matters:
In many African countries, people are one illness away from financial catastrophe. Health access is unequal, data is fragmented, and community potential is underused. We believe we can build something simple but powerful to help shift that — together.
⸻

📩 Interested?
Feel free to comment below, message me directly, or email me at sene.95@hotmail.fr
Cheers from Senegal 🇸🇳
— El Bachir]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>El Bachir Sene</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Show HN: Wetlands – a lightweight Python library for managing Conda environments]]></title>
        <id>https://arthursw.github.io/wetlands/0.2.0/</id>
        <link href="https://arthursw.github.io/wetlands/0.2.0/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T14:54:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[EToro Adds DOGE, XRP, SHIB and 9 Others in U.S. Crypto Push After Nasdaq Debut]]></title>
        <id>b6160f92-051a-4b5a-bd20-dcd6d904bbe8</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/28/etoro-adds-doge-xrp-shib-and-9-others-in-u-s-crypto-push-after-nasdaq-debut"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T14:46:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The trading platform now offers 15 tokens in the U.S., expanding access as it settles into life as a public company.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Helene Braun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mullvad Leta]]></title>
        <id>https://leta.mullvad.net/</id>
        <link href="https://leta.mullvad.net/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T14:38:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DeFi Platform Cork Protocol Suffers $12M Smart Contract Exploit]]></title>
        <id>d158ccea-6e73-496f-bea2-3242887ce8a9</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2025/05/28/a16z-backed-cork-protocol-suffers-usd12m-smart-contract-exploit"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T14:25:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cork Protocol has paused all markets as a precaution.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Oliver Knight</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Show HN: Loodio 2 – A Simple Rechargable Bathroom Privacy Device]]></title>
        <id>https://loodio.com/</id>
        <link href="https://loodio.com/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T14:19:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elderly crypto investors are getting scammed: Teach them these key safety tips]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/explained/elderly-crypto-investors-are-getting-scammed-teach-them-these-key-safety-tips</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/explained/elderly-crypto-investors-are-getting-scammed-teach-them-these-key-safety-tips?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T14:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Why are seniors being targeted in crypto scams?            
            
                
Scammers prey on seniors because they view them as financially secure, trusting and less familiar with rapidly evolving technology.
Let’s understand why seniors are key targets.

Perception of wealth: Many older adults have retirement savings or pensions, making them lucrative targets.
Lower tech fluency: Navigating crypto wallets, private keys and blockchain concepts can be intimidating, something scammers exploit.
Embarrassment prevents reporting: Victims often feel ashamed, making them less likely to report the crime.
Crypto is irreversible: Once funds are sent via Bitcoin or another cryptocurrency, there’s no reversing the transaction. That’s a dream scenario for scammers.

According to the Federa…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by SK Arora</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The AI Hype Index: College students are hooked on ChatGPT]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1117468</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/05/28/1117468/ai-hype-index-college-students-chatgpt-meta-apple-anthropic-grok/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T14:13:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Separating AI reality from hyped-up fiction isn’t always easy. That’s why we’ve created the AI Hype Index—a simple, at-a-glance summary of everything you need to know about the state of the industry. Large language models confidently present their responses as accurate and reliable, even when they’re neither of those things. That’s why we’ve recently seen…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Editors</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Comprehensive Analysis of De-Anonymization Attacks Against the Privacy Coin XMR]]></title>
        <id>https://monero.forex/is-monero-totally-private-a-comprehensive-analysis-of-de-anonymization-attacks-against-the-privacy-coin/</id>
        <link href="https://monero.forex/is-monero-totally-private-a-comprehensive-analysis-of-de-anonymization-attacks-against-the-privacy-coin/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T14:11:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Toncoin: Telegram's Native Cryptocurrency Soars as Ex-Visa Exec Joins TON Foundation]]></title>
        <id>53e74a74-f088-4f76-ad78-f441d4f5635c</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/28/toncoin-telegram-s-native-cryptocurrency-soars-as-ex-visa-exec-joins-ton-foundation"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T14:08:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Toncoin rallies after former Visa executive joins TON Foundation, triggering a surge in volume and renewed market optimism.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>AI Boost</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to mine Bitcoin at home in 2025]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/how-to-mine-bitcoin-at-home</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/how-to-mine-bitcoin-at-home?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Key takeaways
Lottery mining is cheap and fun, but don’t count on hitting a block.
Solo ASIC mining gives you complete control, but it’s a long-odds game.
Pool mining is the most practical way to earn steady payouts at home.
Cloud mining saves you the hassle but usually isn’t worth the cost.

Bitcoin is rapidly gaining legitimacy, and you couldn’t be blamed for wanting to peek behind the curtain to see how it’s made.
Throughout 2024 and into 2025, you've seen a whirlwind of institutional investment from companies like Strategy, which continues to aggressively accumulate Bitcoin (BTC), and Metaplanet, Japan’s listed company that recently adopted BTC as a treasury reserve asset. 
Moreover, on the regulatory front, the return of a US President Donald Trump administration signals a friendlier …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Bradley Peak</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Here’s what happened in crypto today]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/what-happened-in-crypto-today</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/what-happened-in-crypto-today?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T13:48:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today in crypto, GameStop confirmed it has made its first Bitcoin investment, US Representative Bryan Steil told Cointelegraph he wants lawmakers to stop adding non-relevant clauses into crypto bills, and Trump Media confirmed a capital raise to buy Bitcoin after initially denying reports it was planning to do so.
GameStop officially confirms first Bitcoin purchase of 4,710 BTC
GameStop, the US video game and consumer electronics retailer, has confirmed its first Bitcoin investment, acquiring 4,710 Bitcoin, according to a statement posted May 28 on the company’s X account.
The company did not specify how much it paid for the Bitcoin (BTC) or when the purchases were made in the announcement, while its Form 8-K filing with the US Securities and Exchange Commission also offers little detail. …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Cointelegraph</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Blowtorch Theory: A New Model for Structure Formation in the Universe]]></title>
        <id>https://theeggandtherock.com/p/the-blowtorch-theory-a-new-model</id>
        <link href="https://theeggandtherock.com/p/the-blowtorch-theory-a-new-model"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T13:43:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin price will reach $130K or even $1.5M, top bulls say]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-price-top-bulls</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-price-top-bulls?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T13:37:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Top Bitcoin (BTC) bulls in 2025 have updated their price forecasts, and they range from a relatively cautious $130,000 to seven-figure moonshots.
Familiar doubters like gold bug Peter Schiff and economist Nouriel Roubini continue to predict a catastrophic ending for the world’s largest cryptocurrency. Meanwhile, Bitcoin spent the year with record-breaking rallies behind renewed institutional uptake.
It set a new all-time high of $111,970 on May 22 and has been trading near that level since, teasing investors with the possibility of a new ceiling.
Here are some of the boldest Bitcoin price predictions from the first half of 2025 (so far).
Bitcoin has stormed back since dropping to 2025 lows of $76,300 in April. Source: CoinGecko
1. Adam Back says Bitcoin tops $1 million if US jumps in
Block…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Yohan Yun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Conduit Raises $36M to Expand Stablecoin-Based Cross-Border Payments Beyond SWIFT]]></title>
        <id>c82bc401-178f-42cb-8efa-b4b29b9b83b3</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2025/05/28/conduit-raises-36m-to-expand-stablecoin-based-cross-border-payments-beyond-swift"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T13:36:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Stablecoins are one of the fastest-growing sectors in crypto and an increasingly popular tool for global payments, attracting interest from venture capital investments.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Krisztian Sandor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[UK FCA requests public comments on stablecoin, crypto custody regulation]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/uk-s-fca-requests-commentary-on-stablecoin-regulation-and-crypto-custody</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/uk-s-fca-requests-commentary-on-stablecoin-regulation-and-crypto-custody?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T13:33:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The United Kingdom’s Financial Conduct Authority (FCA) has requested public feedback on proposed regulations for stablecoins and cryptocurrency custody.
In a May 28 request for comment, the United Kingdom’s financial regulator announced that its regulatory proposals are “the latest milestone on the road to crypto regulation.” The draft rules are based on prior roundtables and industry feedback. David Geale, executive director of payments and digital finance at the FCA, said the agency aims to support innovation while ensuring market trust:
“At the FCA, we have long supported innovation that benefits consumers and markets. At present, crypto is largely unregulated in the UK. We want to strike a balance in support of a sector that enables innovation and is underpinned by market integrity and…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Adrian Zmudzinski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Texas' annual reading test adjusted difficulty yearly, masking improvement]]></title>
        <id>https://theconversation.com/texas-annual-reading-test-adjusted-its-difficulty-every-year-masking-whether-students-are-improving-244159</id>
        <link href="https://theconversation.com/texas-annual-reading-test-adjusted-its-difficulty-every-year-masking-whether-students-are-improving-244159"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T13:31:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NFT monthly sales break 2025 downward trend in May: CryptoSlam]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/nft-sales-rebound-may-2025-cryptoslam</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/nft-sales-rebound-may-2025-cryptoslam?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T13:19:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Non-fungible tokens (NFTs) caught an uptick in sales in May after months of consistent decline throughout 2025. 
Data from CryptoSlam shows that May’s NFT sales climbed to $430 million, up from $373 million in April, a 15% increase. It marks the first monthly sales increase this year, suggesting renewed interest in digital collectibles. 
This follows a five-month decline in sales since volume peaked at over $900 million in December 2024. May also had the highest number of transactions in 2025, reaching 5.5 million, according to CryptoSlam. 
The sales uptick may be attributed to the divergence between unique NFT buyers and NFT sellers. NFT buyers continued to increase in May, while sellers declined. 
Chart compiled by Cointelegraph to demonstrate CryptoSlam data on NFT monthly sales. Source…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Ezra Reguerra</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SHIB Stalls Below Key Resistance as Whale Activity Collapses 83%.]]></title>
        <id>53409a4a-9eae-47bd-b3f9-9b4c4000af8f</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/28/shib-stalls-below-key-resistance-as-whale-activity-collapses-83"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T13:15:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Large SHIB holders pull back sharply as liquidity shrinks, but analysts say ecosystem growth and long-term token burn plans may offer upside potential.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>AI Boost</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CoinDesk 20 Performance Update: Solana (SOL) Drops 2.1% as Index Trades Lower]]></title>
        <id>5725961a-91d0-4227-ac64-63c0ff3a3495</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/coindesk-indices/2025/05/28/coindesk-20-performance-update-solana-sol-drops-2-1-as-index-trades-lower"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T13:13:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Aave (AAVE) was also among the underperformers, declining 1.8% from Tuesday.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CoinDesk Indices</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Privacy Crypto Dero Targeted With New Self-Spreading Malware]]></title>
        <id>c8b32253-0aed-4b00-a421-0e351e30ec6e</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/tech/2025/05/28/privacy-crypto-dero-targeted-with-new-self-spreading-malware"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T13:11:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The malware spread like a worm and spawned malicious containers after infecting fresh devices.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shaurya Malwa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SUI price chart hints at 2x rally amid Nasdaq ETF filing]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/sui-price-chart-hints-2x-rally-nasdaq-etf-filing</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/sui-price-chart-hints-2x-rally-nasdaq-etf-filing?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T13:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sui (SUI) is making a strong technical case for a 100% price rally in the coming weeks, helped further by a slew of optimistic updates, such as the recent Nasdaq ETF filing with the US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC).
Gooner EMA support raises 40% SUI bounce potential 
As of May 28, SUI has reclaimed the “Gooner EMA” as support on the weekly chart.
SUI/USDT weekly price chart. Source: NebraskanGooner/TradingView
Gooner EMA is a technical indicator created by trader NebraskanGooner that uses the 11- and 22-period exponential moving averages (EMA). When the price crosses above the EMA range, it often leads to further gains. 
When the price closes below the EMA range, it tends to follow deeper losses. 
SUI lost this support, roughly between $3.34 and $3.59, last week after a $200 mil…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Yashu Gola</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Who Cares Era]]></title>
        <id>https://dansinker.com/posts/2025-05-23-who-cares/</id>
        <link href="https://dansinker.com/posts/2025-05-23-who-cares/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T13:07:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elon Musk’s xAI inks $300M deal with Telegram for Grok integration]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/elon-musk-xai-300-million-telegram-deal-grok-integration</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/elon-musk-xai-300-million-telegram-deal-grok-integration?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T13:06:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Elon Musk’s artificial intelligence company xAI has partnered with Telegram to integrate its AI chatbot Grok across the messaging platform, according to Telegram CEO Pavel Durov.
Telegram and xAI have agreed to a one-year partnership to distribute Grok to a billion Telegram users and integrate it into its apps, Durov announced on X on May 28.
As part of the agreement, Telegram will receive $300 million in cash and equity from Musk’s AI company, in addition to 50% of revenue from xAI subscriptions sold via Telegram, the CEO noted.
“This summer, Telegram users will gain access to the best AI technology on the market,” Durov said in a post on his Telegram channel.
Grok integration begins with Telegram
According to a promo video accompanying Durov’s announcement, the partnership is expected to…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Helen Partz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Australian Regulator Sues Ex-Director of Crypto Exchange ACX for Mishandling Funds]]></title>
        <id>1c7d6940-2d30-4406-aace-e7f28bc47693</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2025/05/28/australian-regulator-sues-ex-director-of-crypto-exchange-acx-for-mishandling-funds"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T13:00:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Investigations have been ongoing since ACX Exchange collapsed in 2019.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Camomile Shumba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Akool Live Camera can translate video calls in real time, swap faces, and get live virtual avatars to mimic human movements]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008843</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/games/akool-live-camera-can-translate-video-calls-in-real-time-swap-faces-and-get-virtual-avatars-to-mimic-human-movements/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Akool Live Camera uses AI to capture human movement and mimic that movement with a generated virtual avatar in real time.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dean Takahashi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Former Chainlink, Two Sigma execs build ‘Moirai’ to uncover crypto gems]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/former-chainlink-two-sigma-execs-moirai-uncover-crypto-gems</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/former-chainlink-two-sigma-execs-moirai-uncover-crypto-gems?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Metalayer Ventures, a crypto-focused venture capital firm led by former executives from Chainlink and Two Sigma, has launched a $25 million fund to invest in early-stage blockchain projects with a focus on stablecoins, tokenization and cryptocurrency infrastructure. 
Metalayer’s fund has already backed seven companies, the company disclosed to Cointelegraph on May 28. These include AnchorZero, a platform helping crypto founders use Roth IRAs for tax advantages, and Spark Capital, a new venture focused on stablecoin infrastructure.
Other portfolio companies include Ethena, ClearToken, Crossover Markets, Station70 and Theo — an onchain trading infrastructure project that recently raised $20 million from 17 different VC firms.
The company plans to eventually back up to 30 companies with early…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Sam Bourgi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Show HN: Voiden – a free, offline, Git-native API Client]]></title>
        <id>https://voiden.md/</id>
        <link href="https://voiden.md/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T12:48:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Telegram Signs $300M Deal With Elon Musk's xAI to Integrate Grok Into Its Messaging App, TON up 16%]]></title>
        <id>bb67b222-2a8d-4beb-ad54-115b5de06914</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2025/05/28/telegram-signs-usd300m-deal-to-integrate-grok-ai-into-app-ton-token-up-16"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T12:32:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Telegram will also receive 50% of revenue from xAI subscriptions sold via the app.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Oliver Knight</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Download: the story of OpenAI, and making magnesium]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1117492</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/05/28/1117492/the-download-the-story-of-openai-and-making-magnesium/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T12:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is today’s edition of The Download, our weekday newsletter that provides a daily dose of what’s going on in the world of technology. OpenAI: The power and the pride OpenAI’s release of ChatGPT 3.5 set in motion an AI arms race that has changed the world. How that turns out for humanity is something we are…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rhiannon Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Telegram to Raise $1.5B Through Bond Sale Backed by BlackRock and Citadel: WSJ]]></title>
        <id>69d6fcd6-1ed7-4524-9802-92366c43e96a</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/28/telegram-to-raise-15b-through-bond-sale-backed-by-blackrock-and-citadel-wsj"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T12:00:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The funds will be used to repurchase debt and are convertible into equity if Telegram goes public.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Francisco Rodrigues</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[XRP price set for 48% jump as spot ETF reality draws closer]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/xrp-price-48-jump-spot-etf-reality-draws-closer</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/xrp-price-48-jump-spot-etf-reality-draws-closer?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T11:50:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Key takeaways:

XRP’s falling wedge pattern signals a bullish reversal; 48% price surge potential.

SEC’s review of WisdomTree’s XRP ETF may spark investor interest as approval odds jump to 84% on Polymarket. 

XRP price is forming a falling wedge pattern on the daily chart, a technical chart formation associated with strong bullish momentum following an upward breakout. Could this technical setup, coupled with the SEC’s review of a spot XRP ETF application by WisdomTree, signal the start of a rally to $3.40 and higher?
XRP falling wedge pattern targets $3.40
From a technical perspective, XRP (XRP) price could gain significant momentum if it breaks out of this falling wedge pattern.
In technical analysis, a falling wedge is a bullish reversal chart pattern that comprises two converging tre…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Nancy Lubale</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ether Favored Over Bitcoin by Big Money, Here Are 3 Clues That Point to ETH Bias in Crypto Market]]></title>
        <id>79f6034e-b020-4ec2-8fc8-96dcc4e17b41</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/28/ether-favored-over-bitcoin-by-big-money-here-are-3-clues-that-point-to-eth-bias-in-crypto-market"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T11:47:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Key indicators suggests traders are becoming more bullish on ether relative to bitcoin.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Omkar Godbole</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TnG Introduces Limited Edition NFC Card With LED Light]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=354227</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/354227/tng-introduces-limited-edition-nfc-card-with-led-light/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T11:36:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Touch ‘n Go (TnG) has introduced a new limited edition NFC card which is much different than its usual offerings. Apart from featuring a unique graphic, this version is the first to include a built-in light-up function. Befitting its “You light up my life” theme, this limited edition release features an LED-equipped lightbulb which activates […]
The post TnG Introduces Limited Edition NFC Card With LED Light appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Heirul Kamel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GameStop officially confirms first Bitcoin purchase of 4,710 BTC]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/gamestop-buys-bitcoin-4710-btc</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/gamestop-buys-bitcoin-4710-btc?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T11:27:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[GameStop, the US video game and consumer electronics retailer, has confirmed its first Bitcoin investment, acquiring 4,710 Bitcoin, according to a statement posted May 28 on the company’s X account.
The company did not specify how much it paid for the Bitcoin (BTC) or when the purchases were made in the announcement, while its Form 8-K filing with the US Securities and Exchange Commission also offers little detail. The amount purchased was worth around $513 million at the time of writing.
The announced acquisition is GameStop's first publicly acknowledged Bitcoin purchase since the company disclosed plans to move into Bitcoin investment in March.
At the time, GameStop said it would fund the Bitcoin purchase through debt financing and launched a $1.3 billion convertible notes offering.
Sour…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Helen Partz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GameStop Purchases Over $500M Worth of Bitcoin]]></title>
        <id>54ccdbd6-adac-4863-adab-241fb08dbf67</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2025/05/28/gamestop-purchases-over-usd500m-worth-of-bitcoin"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T11:25:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[GameStop announced the purchase on X on Wednesday but did not offer further details about when the BTC were acquired or the price paid.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Crawley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Daybook Americas: Bitcoin Dominance Tops 64% While Options Indicate Bullish Tilt]]></title>
        <id>e4441cf1-cf04-44b4-9d90-b65964f01777</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/daybook-us/2025/05/28/crypto-daybook-americas-bitcoin-dominance-tops-64-while-options-indicate-bullish-tilt"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T11:15:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Your day-ahead look for May 28, 2025]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>James Van Straten</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mazda 6e BEV Set To Launch In Indonesia Following Thailand Debut]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=354212</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/354212/mazda-6e-bev-set-to-launch-in-indonesia-following-thailand-debut/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T10:58:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mazda 6e (also known as EZ-6 in China) will be launching in the Indonesian market soon after it was confirmed for the Thailand market. This information was confirmed by PT Eurokars Motor Indonesia Chief Operating Officer Ricky Thio. He also added that the pure electric variant of the 6e will be the model that will […]
The post Mazda 6e BEV Set To Launch In Indonesia Following Thailand Debut appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Keran</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hollyland Launches Lark A1 And Lark Max 2 Microphones]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=354193</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/354193/hollyland-launches-lark-a1-and-lark-max-2-microphones/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T10:53:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hollyland has announced two new wireless microphones, the Lark A1 and the Lark Max 2. To start off, the Lark A1 is designed with vloggers, streamers, and other content creators in mind. The mics can deliver 24-bit high-fidelity audio quality and have a sound pressure level of 120dB. They also come with three levels of noise […]
The post Hollyland Launches Lark A1 And Lark Max 2 Microphones appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nurul Kamil</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TON Foundation hires former Visa executive to lead payments strategy]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/ton-foundation-hires-visa-executive-nikola-plecas</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/ton-foundation-hires-visa-executive-nikola-plecas?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T10:52:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Open Network Foundation (TON Foundation) appointed former Visa executive Nikola Plecas as its new vice president of payments.
Plecas will be responsible for shaping and executing TON’s payment infrastructure strategy, the company said in a May 28 blog post.
He is tasked with expanding the network’s capabilities, managing financial partnerships and ensuring compliance across jurisdictions as the foundation scales services for over 1 billion Telegram users.
“Joining TON Foundation represents an incredible opportunity to shape the future of payments on a truly global scale,” Plecas said.
Related: How to use tsUSDe on TON for yield-generating dollar savings
Plecas to lead TON’s new payment strategy
Plecas will lead the push to build a payments architecture that is both globally interoperab…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Amin Haqshanas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AI: Accelerated Incompetence]]></title>
        <id>https://www.slater.dev/accelerated-incompetence/</id>
        <link href="https://www.slater.dev/accelerated-incompetence/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T10:50:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Synology Introduces New BeeStation Plus NAS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=354195</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/354195/synology-introduces-new-beestation-plus-nas/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T10:49:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Synology has introduced its latest consumer Network-Attached Storage (NAS) product, the BeeStation Plus. A tier above its existing BeeStation model, which offered up to 4TB of storage, the Plus brings to the table a higher capacity support of up to 8TB. Design-wise, the BeeStation Plus’ overall look and connectivity layout resembles that of its sibling. […]
The post Synology Introduces New BeeStation Plus NAS appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Heirul Kamel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft is starting to open Windows Update up to any third-party app]]></title>
        <id>https://www.theverge.com/news/675446/microsoft-windows-update-all-apps-orchestration-platform</id>
        <link href="https://www.theverge.com/news/675446/microsoft-windows-update-all-apps-orchestration-platform"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T10:48:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why is Bitcoin price stuck?]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/why-is-bitcoin-price-stuck</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/why-is-bitcoin-price-stuck?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T10:46:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Key points:

Bitcoin price is stuck in a range, with overhead resistance at $110,000 continuing to obstruct a rally to new all-time highs.

Traders are in a wait-and-see mood due to uncertainty surrounding macroeconomic events.

Bitcoin’s (BTC) bull run has stalled, with the price consolidating within a roughly $3,500 range since May 23. The $110,000 level proves to be a stubborn barrier.
BTC/USD four-hour chart. Cointelegraph/TradingView
Let’s look at some of the reasons why Bitcoin price remains stuck.
Bitcoin runs into resistance at $110,000
Data from Cointelegraph Markets Pro and Bitstamp shows that BTC price oscillates within a tight range between $106,600 and $110,700, with no clear directional bias.
BTC price has “broken out of the triangle pattern and is moving upward,” but a key r…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Nancy Lubale</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amina Bank hits $40M revenue in 2024 as crypto AUM doubles]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/amina-bank-2024-crypto-revenue-aum-growth</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/amina-bank-2024-crypto-revenue-aum-growth?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T10:32:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Swiss crypto bank Amina Bank, formerly Seba Bank, reported record financial results for 2024, with revenue climbing 69% year-over-year to $40.4 million.
The bank also saw its assets under management (AUM) rise by 136% to $4.2 billion, driven by institutional demand and strategic expansion, according to a May 28 news release.
The Zurich-based bank credited the growth to its multi-jurisdictional footprint, 24/7 trading capabilities and a lending book that has maintained zero defaults over five years.
“I’m incredibly proud of our team’s tenacity and focus, which led to quarterly profitability in Q4 2024, a pivotal milestone that confirms the value of our approach,” CEO Franz Bergmueller said.
Related: Bitcoin Suisse eyes UAE expansion with regulatory nod in Abu Dhabi
Amina adds $801 million i…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Amin Haqshanas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Razer Iskur V2 X Lightning Review: Comfortable And Well-Rounded For Its Price]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=350725</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/350725/razer-iskur-v2-x-lightning-review-comfortable-and-well-rounded-for-its-price/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T10:20:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Back during CES 2025 earlier this year, I had the chance to literally have a brief seat on Razer’s Iskur V2 X gaming chair. It felt comfortable at the time but as it is with demo booths, I couldn’t draw any conclusive points until I had a right and proper sit-down with it. Fast forward […]
The post Razer Iskur V2 X Lightning Review: Comfortable And Well-Rounded For Its Price appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John Law</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BlackRock to join Telegram’s $1.5B bond sale: WSJ]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/blackrock-telegram-bond-sale-1-5b-ipo-discount</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/blackrock-telegram-bond-sale-1-5b-ipo-discount?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T10:10:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BlackRock, one of the world’s largest Bitcoin holders, is reportedly participating in a bond raise by crypto-friendly messenger Telegram.
Telegram is expected to raise at least $1.5 billion in a bond issue on May 28, with support from existing backers like BlackRock and Abu Dhabi’s investment firm Mubadala, The Wall Street Journal reported.
As part of the sale, Telegram is offering investors five-year bonds at a 9% yield, the report said, citing sources familiar with the matter.
Telegram plans to use the proceeds to buy back remaining debt from bonds issued in 2021, which are due to mature in March 2026.
Discounts for potential Telegram IPO
Apart from existing Telegram bondholders like BlackRock and Mubadala, the sale is also expected to bring new investors, including the US hedge fund fir…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Helen Partz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OpenAI: The power and the pride]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1117486</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/05/28/1117486/openai-the-power-and-the-pride/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T10:07:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In April, Paul Graham, the founder of the tech startup accelerator Y Combinator, sent a tweet in response to former YC president and current OpenAI CEO Sam Altman. Altman had just bid a public goodbye to GPT-4 on X, and Graham had a follow-up question.  “If you had [GPT-4’s model weights] etched on a piece…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mat Honan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This startup wants to make more climate-friendly metal in the US]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1117481</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/05/28/1117481/metal-magrathea/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A California-based company called Magrathea just turned on a new electrolyzer that can make magnesium metal from seawater. The technology has the potential to produce the material, which is used in vehicles and defense applications, with net-zero greenhouse-gas emissions. Magnesium is an incredibly light metal, and it’s used for parts in cars and planes, as…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Casey Crownhart</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fungible cryptos in secondary sales are not securities, Ripple tells SEC]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/ripple-sec-letter-crypto-not-securities</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/ripple-sec-letter-crypto-not-securities?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T09:59:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ripple, the blockchain company behind XRP, argued that fungible cryptocurrencies are not securities when transferred in secondary transactions in a recent letter sent to the US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC).
In its May 27 letter, Ripple cited US attorney and crypto law thought leader Lewis Cohen to support its claim. In his widely cited 2022 paper, “The Ineluctable Modality of Securities Law: Why Fungible Crypto Assets Are Not Securities,” he wrote:
“[T]here is no current basis in the law relating to ‘investment contracts’ to classify most fungible crypto assets as ‘securities’ when transferred in secondary transactions.”
In his paper, Cohen explained that in secondary transactions, an investment contract transaction is generally not present. He further claimed that fungible cry…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Adrian Zmudzinski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Ordinals Can Now Be Bridged to Cardano Through BitVMX]]></title>
        <id>b447c47b-7de1-4781-be62-2c7d9b55fb08</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/tech/2025/05/23/bitcoin-ordinals-can-now-be-bridged-to-cardano-through-bitvmx"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T09:48:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The on-chain transaction between Bitcoin and Cardano was facilitated by BitVMX, an interoperability protocol built using the BitVM programming language]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Crawley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Apple May Launch A Gaming App To Replace Game Center]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=354187</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/354187/apple-gaming-app-to-replace-game-center/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T09:38:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Apple will reportedly launch a dedicated gaming app to replace its current Game Center, as per Bloomberg via Android Authority. The purported app may come pre-installed on iPhones, iPads, Macs, and Apple TVs sometime later this year, corresponding with the expected launch of iOS 19. The report states that the new gaming app will launch […]
The post Apple May Launch A Gaming App To Replace Game Center appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Newsdesk</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin whales keep buying as BTC price dip targets include $94K]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-whales-keep-buying-btc-price-dip-targets-include-94k</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-whales-keep-buying-btc-price-dip-targets-include-94k?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T09:32:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Key points:

Bitcoin whales are adding to their BTC positions while price ranges below all-time highs.

If a new market correction comes, one potential bounce level lies in the mid-$90,000 zone.

Hyperliquid trader James Wynn hints at large-volume traders shaping low-timeframe price performance.

Bitcoin (BTC) may see support only at $94,000 if a fresh BTC price correction ensues, new analysis says.
In its latest X commentary, Keith Alan, co-founder of trading resource Material Indicators, pointed to a Bitcoin bounce zone at the 21-week moving average.
Bitcoin whales jump in amid “consolidating” price
Bitcoin continues to track sideways within a $5,000 range after hitting all-time highs of $112,000, data from Cointelegraph Markets Pro and TradingView shows.
For Alan, the market is giving o…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by William Suberg</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ether Likely Building Energy To Smash Through $3K]]></title>
        <id>ad059040-85de-42af-aaee-8c8fbd3fb602</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/28/ether-likely-building-energy-to-smash-through-usd3k"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T09:01:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ether is forming an ascending triangle pattern, suggesting a potential rise above $3,000.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Omkar Godbole</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Surges Ahead as Strategy Lags]]></title>
        <id>6435de2c-c974-4be6-b38d-d84fe54d2733</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/28/bitcoin-surges-ahead-as-strategy-stock-lags"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T08:48:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Divergence grows amid mNAV compression and a shift in Strategy's funding approach for bitcoin accumulation]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>James Van Straten</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Toyota And Lexus To Streamline Its Line-Ups With Unified Vehicle Architecture]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=354177</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/354177/toyota-lexus-to-streamline-with-unified-vehicle-architecture/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T08:33:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Toyota and Lexus have been developing standalone EVs and ICE vehicles on separate platforms since the introduction of its first electrified models. However, both the companies, have announced plans to streamline their electric vehicle (EV) and internal combustion engine (ICE) lineups. Instead of producing separate models for each powertrain type, the automakers will offer multiple […]
The post Toyota And Lexus To Streamline Its Line-Ups With Unified Vehicle Architecture appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Keran</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sui validators vote on $162M Cetus recovery plan to restore user funds]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/cetus-protocol-vote-recover-frozen-funds</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/cetus-protocol-vote-recover-frozen-funds?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T08:30:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sui-based decentralized exchange Cetus may be one step closer to recovering funds lost in a recent exploit, pending the outcome of a community governance vote scheduled to end June 3.
Cetus was exploited for over $220 million worth of digital assets on May 22. Shortly after the incident, Cetus managed to freeze $162 million of the funds.
In a May 27 post on X, Sui said Cetus had requested a community vote to approve the recovery of the frozen funds. 
“If the community vote is approved, the funds will be recovered from the attacker and held in a multisig trust account until they can be returned to accounts that had positions in Cetus,” the post said.
The vote is part of a broader recovery plan that includes using Cetus’s treasury and securing an emergency loan from the Sui Foundation.  
Sou…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Zoltan Vardai</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[XRP Spot ETF in the U.S. Moves Closer to Reality]]></title>
        <id>80550bef-bd55-4271-8043-f119034bf2fb</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/28/xrp-spot-etf-in-the-us-moves-closer-to-reality"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T08:06:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The SEC is evaluating whether a proposed XRP ETF by WisdomTree offers enough investor protection and safeguards against manipulation.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shaurya Malwa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OnePlus 13s To Fully Embrace AI; Will Feature New Plus Key]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=354150</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/354150/oneplus-13s-to-fully-embrace-ai-will-feature-new-plus-key/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T08:02:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[OnePlus recently announced that it will be going all-in on AI, with the launch of the OnePlus 13s. As part of the embrace, one major change to the phone will be the introduction of the Plus Key, which also serves as the replacement for the long-used Alert Slider.  In essence, the Plus Key is a […]
The post OnePlus 13s To Fully Embrace AI; Will Feature New Plus Key appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Newsdesk</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Metaplanet issues $50M in new debt to buy more Bitcoin]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/metaplanet-raises-50m-zero-interest-bonds-bitcoin-purchase</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/metaplanet-raises-50m-zero-interest-bonds-bitcoin-purchase?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T07:55:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Japanese investment company Metaplanet is raising $50 million through a private placement of zero-interest bonds as part of its strategy to increase its Bitcoin exposure. 
In a May 28 announcement, the company said it was raising $50 million through bonds. The bonds are issued in $1.25 million denominations and carry no interest. Investors will not receive regular payments, with any potential profit expected to come from the bonds’ redemption value.
Evo Fund, a Cayman Islands-based investment firm, will be the sole bondholder. The investment company has been Metaplanet’s primary backer for its Bitcoin acquisition strategy, subscribing to multiple rounds of Metaplanet’s zero-interest bonds, providing capital for its Bitcoin (BTC) buys.
The bonds are unsecured and not guaranteed, with neithe…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Ezra Reguerra</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Spot ETFs Pull in $5.77B in May, Their Best Performance Since November]]></title>
        <id>06b5d5e2-ab27-4183-bea5-80fdadb01349</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/28/bitcoin-spot-etfs-pull-in-usd5-77b-in-may-their-best-performance-since-november"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T07:45:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin's spot price recently reached record highs above $110,000.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Omkar Godbole</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sony WF-C710N Lightning Review: Bass For Your Buck]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=353657</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/353657/sony-wf-c710n-lightning-review-bass-for-your-buck/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T07:42:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Sony WF-C710N TWS earbuds launched a few months ago and are the successor to the WF-C700N. Designed as a budget-friendly option, the WF-C710N features a few upgrades from its older counterpart, namely improved ANC and longer battery life. Given that these aren’t Sony’s top-of-the-line offering, one should not expect them to be particularly mindblowing. […]
The post Sony WF-C710N Lightning Review: Bass For Your Buck appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nurul Kamil</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[vivo X Fold5 Gets Certified By SIRIM On Its Way To Launch]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=354162</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/354162/vivo-x-fold5-sirim/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T07:28:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[vivo is said to introduce its next flagship foldable, the X Fold5, some time in the next few months, with a tentative launch window in July. While the company has not announced anything concrete yet, the upcoming foldable has made an appearance on the SIRIM database, indicating that it will be coming here soon after […]
The post vivo X Fold5 Gets Certified By SIRIM On Its Way To Launch appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ikmal Rozlan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Are Monero Traders Buying The Dip? XMR Futures Open Interest Surges as Price Falls By Nearly $100 in 3 Days]]></title>
        <id>b9147f16-dc3e-4f8f-9a10-a1b19b807b2b</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/28/are-xmr-traders-buying-the-dip-monero-futures-open-interest-surges-as-price-falls-by-nearly-usd100-in-3-days"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T07:12:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The price drop follows a meteoric rally from $165 to $420.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Omkar Godbole</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[As a developer, my most important tools are a pen and a notebook]]></title>
        <id>https://hamatti.org/posts/as-a-developer-my-most-important-tools-are-a-pen-and-a-notebook/</id>
        <link href="https://hamatti.org/posts/as-a-developer-my-most-important-tools-are-a-pen-and-a-notebook/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T06:27:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto czar Sacks says US could possibly ‘acquire more Bitcoin’]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/david-sacks-us-potentially-acquire-more-bitcoin</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/david-sacks-us-potentially-acquire-more-bitcoin?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T06:21:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[White House AI and crypto czar David Sacks says the US could buy more Bitcoin if the government can fund the purchase in a “budget-neutral” way without a tax or adding to the growing national debt.
Sacks told Gemini co-founders Cameron and Tyler Winklevoss during a May 27 fireside chat at the Bitcoin 2025 conference that while he “can’t promise anything,” a pathway does exist for the government to buy more Bitcoin (BTC).
However, it would require convincing Commerce Secretary Howard Lutnick or Treasury Secretary Scott Besson to OK the buy and fund it “without a new tax or adding to the debt,” Sacks said, adding that “maybe by finding the money from some other program that’s not using it — then we could potentially acquire more Bitcoin.”
David Sacks said the US could buy more Bitcoin, but h…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Stephen Katte</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Australian regulator takes former Blockchain Global director to court]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/australian-regulator-legal-action-former-blockchain-global-director</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/australian-regulator-legal-action-former-blockchain-global-director?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T06:16:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Australia’s markets regulator has filed civil proceedings against Liang “Allan” Guo, the former director of Blockchain Global. 
Guo will face the court on “allegations relating to multiple breaches of his directors’ duties,” the Australian Securities and Investments Commission said in a May 28 press release.
ASIC alleged Guo made multiple breaches of directors’ duties relating to his dealings with ACX Exchange customer funds, and claimed he made false and misleading statements about those dealings and failed to maintain proper books and records. 
The now-liquidated Blockchain Global operated the ACX Exchange from mid-2016 until December 2019, when it collapsed as customers could no longer withdraw their assets. 
During liquidator’s examinations in 2022, the courts were told that ACX exchan…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Martin Young</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Altcoin ‘wildfire’ inbound as trader shuts down bear market fears]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/trader-rejects-altcoin-bear-market-fears-literally-at-the-bottom</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/trader-rejects-altcoin-bear-market-fears-literally-at-the-bottom?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T06:08:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A crypto trader has pushed back against claims that altcoin season is already over, arguing that it hasn’t even started yet, as many tokens are still near their local price bottoms.
“I don’t understand why people start claiming that a bear market is around the corner,” MN Trading Capital founder Michaël van de Poppe said in a May 28 X post.
Calls for altcoin season mount
“They are literally on the bottom,” van de Poppe added before stating that the “final easy 12-24 months are coming.” While many altcoins have posted gains over the past 30 days, they remain below their levels from the market uptrend until US President Donald Trump’s inauguration in January.
Solana (SOL) posted 17.84% gains over the past 30 days, trading at $175.17, but is still down 32% since Jan. 19, according to CoinMark…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Ciaran Lyons</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sui Network Steps in to Compensate Cetus Losses in Full After $223M Exploit]]></title>
        <id>30ac7fbc-8a4a-491e-b202-fa2fbcd85c68</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/28/sui-network-steps-in-to-compensate-cetus-losses-in-full-after-223m-exploit"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T06:04:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Sui Foundation has extended a loan to Cetus to fully reimburse affected users, with repayment contingent on an upcoming on-chain community vote.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shaurya Malwa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[IMF says El Salvador to make ‘efforts’ to stop Bitcoin buys with $120M payments deal]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/imf-el-salvador-efforts-stop-bitcoin-buys-120m-payments-deal</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/imf-el-salvador-efforts-stop-bitcoin-buys-120m-payments-deal?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T06:01:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The International Monetary Fund said it has reached an agreement with El Salvador to pay the country $120 million following an initial review of its $1.4 billion loan agreement struck last year.
The IMF said on May 27 that as part of the deal, El Salvador will need to fulfill its prior obligations around limiting further government involvement in Bitcoin (BTC), and it will have to cease its involvement in the Chivo wallet by the end of July.
“On Bitcoin, efforts will continue to ensure that the total amount of Bitcoin held across all government-owned wallets remains unchanged,” the global lender said.
The planned payout, subject to IMF executive board approval, is part of a larger $1.4 billion, 40-month loan deal struck in December, which saw El Salvador agree to confine its Bitcoin ambiti…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Tarang Khaitan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Traders Eye New Highs by End of Summer; Ether Rises 3% on Treasury Optimism]]></title>
        <id>6e04b4fe-7b4e-4dfa-adcc-e2cd2140bafd</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/28/bitcoin-traders-eye-new-highs-by-end-of-summer-ether-rises-3-on-treasury-optimism"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T05:58:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With volatility elevated ahead of an upcoming Bitcoin conference, investors eye a summer breakout as ETH rises and BTC consolidates near $110,000.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shaurya Malwa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Uptrend at Risk of Breakdown Ahead of Nvidia Earnings, Fed Minutes]]></title>
        <id>46d2bfbb-d26c-403c-a39d-e0b23568e2da</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/28/bitcoin-uptrend-at-risk-ahead-of-nvda-earnings-fed-minutes-xrp-holds-key-support-amid-xrpfi-narrative"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T05:35:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Federal Reserve's minutes and Nvidia's earnings are key events that could influence market movements.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Omkar Godbole</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DWARF as a Shared Reverse Engineering Format]]></title>
        <id>https://lief.re/blog/2025-05-27-dwarf-editor/</id>
        <link href="https://lief.re/blog/2025-05-27-dwarf-editor/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T05:34:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CFTC’s Goldsmith Romero says commissioner exodus ‘not a great situation’]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/goldsmith-romero-cf-exodus-not-a-great-situation</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/goldsmith-romero-cf-exodus-not-a-great-situation?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T05:10:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Outgoing US Commodity Futures Trading Commission commissioner Christy Goldsmith Romero says the exodus of the agency’s top brass is “not a great situation” for crypto regulations.
The CFTC could be headed by just one commissioner once the other four depart later this year, which Goldsmith Romero said in a May 27 interview at the Brookings Institution will make creating regulations harder because it leaves a less diverse pool of opinions. 
“I think it’s not a great situation if you have one person who’s determining what the rules should be; you lose the benefit of this back-and-forth, this push-and-pull as to what’s the right thing to do,” she said.
“I’ve always wanted to hear from my fellow commissioners about what makes sense to them, and there are many things that they’ve convinced me of…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Stephen Katte</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trump’s CFTC pick Quintenz discloses crypto links, $3.4M assets]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/trump-cftc-pick-quintenz-discloses-crypto-links-assets</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/trump-cftc-pick-quintenz-discloses-crypto-links-assets?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T05:01:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[US President Donald Trump’s pick to chair the Commodity Futures Trading Commission has disclosed millions of dollars worth of assets, along with his various ties to crypto-related organizations.
In paperwork released by the US Office of Government Ethics on May 25, Brian Quintenz disclosed his key positions in crypto and market firms that would directly relate to the CFTC’s regulatory priorities and disclosed assets worth at least $3.4 million, according to a May 27 Bloomberg report. 
Quintenz was a CFTC commissioner from 2017 to 2021 and is currently the global head of crypto policy at Andreessen Horowitz, a position he said he will step down from if the Senate confirms him as CFTC chair. 
He holds an interest in three AH Capital Management investment funds, CNK Fund III, CNK Seed 1 Fund,…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Martin Young</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rep. Steil urges restraint on adding ‘non-germane items’ to crypto bills]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/steil-wants-lawmakers-restrain-adding-non-relevant-items-crypto-bills</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/steil-wants-lawmakers-restrain-adding-non-relevant-items-crypto-bills?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T04:46:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[US Representative Bryan Steil wants lawmakers to stop adding “non-germane items” into two key crypto bills, claiming that doing so is slowing the implementation of a regulatory framework for the industry.
“Individuals, when they see legislation that’s going to move forward, want to attach non-germane items to any bill that’s going to move through and be signed into law,” Steil, a Republican from Wisconsin who chairs the House Financial Services Subcommittee on crypto, told Cointelegraph at the Bitcoin 2025 conference in Las Vegas on May 27.
“We have to restrain ourselves from that instinct and attempt by our colleagues — both sides of the aisle,” he added.
Congress’s biggest crypto backers hope to pass the stablecoin-regulating Guiding and Establishing National Innovation for US Stablecoin…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Brayden Lindrea</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Jack Dorsey’s Block to bring Bitcoin payments to Square by 2026]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/block-inc-bitcoin-payments-square-2026</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/block-inc-bitcoin-payments-square-2026?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T03:21:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jack Dorsey’s financial services firm Block, Inc. will launch Bitcoin payments on Square, its payments processing arm, with a rollout to begin later this year before a full launch in 2026.
The company announced the plan at the Bitcoin 2025 conference in Las Vegas on May 27, where Block demonstrated the feature at the BTC Inc. merchandise store.
Merchants will be able to accept Bitcoin (BTC) payments through existing Square hardware using the Lightning Network, Bitcoin’s faster, lower-cost layer-2 scaling network. 
“Merchants can choose to hold the Bitcoin, or auto-convert it to fiat in real-time,” Dorsey said on X. 
The company said it expects to start rolling out in the second half of 2025, reaching all eligible Square sellers by 2026, subject to regulatory approvals. 
The move builds on …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Martin Young</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Show HN: AutoThink – Boosts local LLM performance with adaptive reasoning]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=44112326</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=44112326"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T02:39:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Asia Morning Briefing: Bitcoin Becomes ‘Generational Asset’ as Speculators Ditch Rolexes]]></title>
        <id>3bdfdfa2-66d8-46b4-b7c7-362d6d9a1206</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/27/asia-morning-briefing-bitcoin-becomes-generational-asset-as-speculators-ditch-rolexes"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T01:33:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[PLUS: ETH's rally might be in its early stages, but there are a few headwinds holding it back]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>AI Boost</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Everyone’s looking to get in on vibe coding — and Google is no different with Stitch, its follow-up to Jules]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3009114</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/everyones-looking-to-get-in-on-vibe-coding-and-google-is-no-different-with-stitch-its-follow-up-to-jules/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T00:49:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google is looking to compete in vibe coding with Stitch, which designs user interfaces (UIs) with one prompt.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Taryn Plumb</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spott’s AI-native recruiting platform scores $3.2M to end hiring software chaos]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3009108</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/spotts-ai-native-recruiting-platform-scores-3-2m-to-end-hiring-software-chaos/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T00:07:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Spott secures $3.2 million in funding to build an all-in-one AI-native recruitment platform that automates workflows and eliminates tech fragmentation for recruitment agencies seeking to focus on high-value activities.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Nuñez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Look Ma, No Bubbles: Designing a Low-Latency Megakernel for Llama-1B]]></title>
        <id>https://hazyresearch.stanford.edu/blog/2025-05-27-no-bubbles</id>
        <link href="https://hazyresearch.stanford.edu/blog/2025-05-27-no-bubbles"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T00:01:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Negotiating PoE+ Power in the Pre‑Boot Environment]]></title>
        <id>https://roderickkhan.com/posts/2025-05-16-poe-uefi-solution</id>
        <link href="https://roderickkhan.com/posts/2025-05-16-poe-uefi-solution"/>
        <updated>2025-05-27T23:45:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Anthropic debuts Claude conversational voice mode on mobile that searches your Google Docs, Drive, Calendar]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3009105</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/anthropic-debuts-conversational-voice-mode-for-claude-mobile-apps/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-27T23:23:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With the rollout of voice mode, Anthropic continues to broaden Claude's functionality and accessibility to all users.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carl Franzen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OpenTPU: Open-Source Reimplementation of Google Tensor Processing Unit (TPU)]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/UCSBarchlab/OpenTPU</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/UCSBarchlab/OpenTPU"/>
        <updated>2025-05-27T23:10:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Best AWS Services to Deploy Front-End Applications in 2025]]></title>
        <id>68363d68d27e47d637cc580b</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/best-aws-services-for-frontend-deployment/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-27T22:32:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As front-end development evolves, finding the right deployment service is more important than ever. Amazon Web Services (AWS), a cloud-based service, offers a number of helpful tools and platforms for hosting modern front-end applications. Although i...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ijeoma Igboagu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security leaders lose visibility as consultants deploy shadow AI copilots to stay employed]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008925</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/security/shadow-ai-is-consultings-survival-strategy-in-the-genai-era/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-27T22:15:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fearing sweeping layoffs driven by AI and automation, elite consultants and high performers are turning to shadow AI for a competitive edge.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Louis Columbus</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Show HN: My LLM CLI tool can run tools now, from Python code or plugins]]></title>
        <id>https://simonwillison.net/2025/May/27/llm-tools/</id>
        <link href="https://simonwillison.net/2025/May/27/llm-tools/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-27T20:53:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mistral launches API for building AI agents that run Python, generate images, perform RAG and more]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3009083</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/mistral-launches-api-for-building-ai-agents-that-run-python-generate-images-perform-rag-and-more/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-27T18:52:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For professionals like the Lead AI Engineer or Senior AI Engineer, the Mistral Agents API represents a powerful addition to their AI toolkit.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carl Franzen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Build a Rocket Boy drops trailer detailing MindsEye’s blend of Grand Theft Auto and AI robot combat]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3009068</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/games/build-a-rocket-boy-drops-trailer-detailing-mindseyes-blend-of-grand-theft-auto-and-ai-robot-combat/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-27T18:21:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[IOI Partners and Build a Rocket Boy dropped a new trailer on MindsEye, a new title coming on June 10 from the co-creator of Grand Theft Auto V.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dean Takahashi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Salesforce’s $8B acquisition of Informatica means for enterprise data and AI]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3009056</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/data-infrastructure/what-salesforces-8b-acquisition-of-informatica-means-for-enterprise-data-and-ai/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-27T17:20:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Industry analysts explain how Salesforce's $8 billion Informatica acquisition will transform enterprise data management and accelerate agentic AI adoption .]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sean Michael Kerner</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Square Theory]]></title>
        <id>https://aaronson.org/blog/square-theory</id>
        <link href="https://aaronson.org/blog/square-theory"/>
        <updated>2025-05-27T15:33:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A new sodium metal fuel cell could help clean up transportation]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1117456</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/05/27/1117456/sodium-fuel-cell/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-27T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new type of fuel cell that runs on sodium metal could one day help clean up sectors where it’s difficult to replace fossil fuels, like rail, regional aviation, and short-distance shipping. The device represents a departure from technologies like lithium-based batteries and is more similar conceptually to hydrogen fuel cell systems.  The sodium-air fuel…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Casey Crownhart</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use Your Raspberry Pi Headlessly with VS Code and SSH (No Monitor Needed)]]></title>
        <id>6835cf3101fd0876c3c66de0</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-your-raspberry-pi-headlessly-with-vs-code-and-ssh/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-27T14:41:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Raspberry Pi is a portable computer with an onboard processor that fits comfortably in the palm of your hand. Compared with general purpose computers, it’s an affordable option developed by the Raspberry Pi Foundation. The Raspberry Pi Model B wa...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Josiah Adesola</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Building customer-centric convenience]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1116819</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/05/27/1116819/building-customer-centric-convenience/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-27T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the U.S., two-thirds of the country’s 150,000 convenience stores are run by independent operators. Mom-and-pop shops, powered by personal relationships and local knowledge, are the backbone of the convenience sector. These neighborhood operators have long lacked the resources needed to compete with larger chains when it comes to technology, operations, and customer loyalty programs. …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>MIT Technology Review Insights</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Download: nuclear-powered AI, and a short history of creativity]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1117453</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/05/27/1117453/the-download-nuclear-powered-ai-and-a-short-history-of-creativity/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-27T12:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is today’s edition of The Download, our weekday newsletter that provides a daily dose of what’s going on in the world of technology. Can nuclear power really fuel the rise of AI? In the AI arms race, all the major players say they want to go nuclear. Over the past year, the likes of Meta, Amazon,…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rhiannon Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How a hawk learned to use traffic signals to hunt more successfully]]></title>
        <id>https://www.frontiersin.org/news/2025/05/23/street-smarts-hawk-use-traffic-signals-hunting</id>
        <link href="https://www.frontiersin.org/news/2025/05/23/street-smarts-hawk-use-traffic-signals-hunting"/>
        <updated>2025-05-27T11:46:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[From disruption to reinvention: How knowledge workers can thrive after AI]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008969</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/from-disruption-to-reinvention-how-knowledge-workers-can-thrive-after-ai/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-26T19:05:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We are beginning a cognitive migration: Away from what AI now does well, and toward a redefinition of what humans are now made for.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gary Grossman, Edelman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A thought on JavaScript "proof of work" anti-scraper systems]]></title>
        <id>https://utcc.utoronto.ca/~cks/space/blog/web/JavaScriptScraperObstacles</id>
        <link href="https://utcc.utoronto.ca/~cks/space/blog/web/JavaScriptScraperObstacles"/>
        <updated>2025-05-26T05:01:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Homo erectus from the seabed, new archaeological discoveries in Indonesia]]></title>
        <id>https://www.universiteitleiden.nl/en/news/2025/05/homo-erectus-from-the-seabed-new-archaeological-discoveries-in-indonesia</id>
        <link href="https://www.universiteitleiden.nl/en/news/2025/05/homo-erectus-from-the-seabed-new-archaeological-discoveries-in-indonesia"/>
        <updated>2025-05-26T03:56:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Windows Registry Adventure #7: Attack surface analysis]]></title>
        <id>https://googleprojectzero.blogspot.com/2025/05/the-windows-registry-adventure-7-attack-surface.html</id>
        <link href="https://googleprojectzero.blogspot.com/2025/05/the-windows-registry-adventure-7-attack-surface.html"/>
        <updated>2025-05-25T20:24:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google’s ‘world-model’ bet: building the AI operating layer before Microsoft captures the UI]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008900</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/googles-world-model-bet-building-the-ai-operating-layer-before-microsoft-captures-the-ui/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-25T17:42:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google doubles down on its ‘world-model’ vision, racing to build an AI operating layer to drive a universal personal assistant with Gemini. Even as Microsoft moves to capture the enterprise UI. Here's what's at stake.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matt Marshall</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Designing Tools for Scientific Thought]]></title>
        <id>https://www.forester-notes.org/tfmt-0001/index.xml</id>
        <link href="https://www.forester-notes.org/tfmt-0001/index.xml"/>
        <updated>2025-05-25T14:51:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Programming Basics with Tiki]]></title>
        <id>https://tiki.li/</id>
        <link href="https://tiki.li/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-25T13:08:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chairs, Chairs, Chairs]]></title>
        <id>https://www.parliament.uk/about/living-heritage/building/cultural-collections/historic-furniture/the-collection/chairs-chairs-chairs/</id>
        <link href="https://www.parliament.uk/about/living-heritage/building/cultural-collections/historic-furniture/the-collection/chairs-chairs-chairs/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-25T11:14:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Level Design Book]]></title>
        <id>https://book.leveldesignbook.com/</id>
        <link href="https://book.leveldesignbook.com/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-25T11:03:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Ingredients of a Productive Monorepo]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.swgillespie.me/posts/monorepo-ingredients/</id>
        <link href="https://blog.swgillespie.me/posts/monorepo-ingredients/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-25T10:49:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The length of file names in early Unix]]></title>
        <id>https://utcc.utoronto.ca/~cks/space/blog/unix/UnixEarlyFilenameLenghts</id>
        <link href="https://utcc.utoronto.ca/~cks/space/blog/unix/UnixEarlyFilenameLenghts"/>
        <updated>2025-05-25T07:37:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Beyond single-model AI: How architectural design drives reliable multi-agent orchestration]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008888</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/beyond-single-model-ai-how-architectural-design-drives-reliable-multi-agent-orchestration/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-24T22:35:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Successful AI agents require enterprises to orchestrate interactions, manage shared knowledge and plan for failure.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nikhil Gupta, Atlassian</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OpenAI updates Operator to o3, making its $200 monthly ChatGPT Pro subscription more enticing]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008828</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/openai-updates-operator-to-o3-making-its-200-monthly-chatgpt-subscription-more-enticing/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-23T21:51:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Operator remains a research preview and is accessible only to ChatGPT Pro users. The Responses API version will continue to use GPT-4o.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carl Franzen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The battle to AI-enable the web: NLweb and what enterprises need to know]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008795</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/the-battle-to-ai-enable-the-web-nlweb-and-what-enterprises-need-to-know/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-23T21:05:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft's NLWeb protocol transforms websites into AI-powered apps with conversational interfaces.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sean Michael Kerner</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The 3 biggest bombshells from this week’s AI extravaganza]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008808</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/the-3-biggest-bombshells-from-this-weeks-ai-extravaganza/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-23T20:29:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Enterprises looking to build with AI should find plenty to look forward to with the announcements from Microsoft, Google & Anthropic this week.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nick Mokey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build a Testing Framework for E-Commerce Checkout and Payments]]></title>
        <id>68308f32f4205e3b843cfb37</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-build-a-testing-framework-for-e-commerce-checkout-and-payments/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-23T15:07:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When I first started working on E-commerce applications, I assumed testing checkout flows and payments would be straightforward. My expectation was simple: users select items, provide an address, pay, and receive confirmation. But I quickly learned t...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Venkata Sai Sandeep</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Architecture of Mathematics – And How Developers Can Use it in Code]]></title>
        <id>68308ee8ccde6bc325c82393</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/the-architecture-of-mathematics-and-how-developers-can-use-it-in-code/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-23T15:06:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA["To understand is to perceive patterns." - Isaiah Berlin Math is not just numbers. It is the science of finding complex patterns that shape our world. This means that to truly understand it, we need to see beyond numbers, formulas, and theorems and ...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tiago Capelo Monteiro</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Feature Fridays: dTelecom]]></title>
        <id>682f3eb8646f7c0001399182</id>
        <link href="https://blog.quicknode.com/feature-fridays-dtelecom/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-23T13:37:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[dTelecom is reshaping digital communication with decentralized, AI-powered infrastructure for Web3 developers and businesses.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>QuickNode</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use React 19 in Power Apps PCF Components]]></title>
        <id>6830767c62d9a28c0de11007</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-react-19-in-pcf-components/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-23T13:22:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Power Apps Component Framework – PCF for short – lets you create complex custom components using traditional web development tools like HTML, CSS, and JavaScript. When creating a new PCF project, you can choose from two types of controls: standar...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brandon Wozniewicz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why enterprise RAG systems fail: Google study introduces ‘sufficient context’ solution]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008684</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/why-enterprise-rag-systems-fail-google-study-introduces-sufficient-context-solution/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-23T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google's "sufficient context" helps refine RAG systems, reduce LLM hallucinations, and boost AI reliability for business applications.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ben Dickson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Download: meet Cathy Tie, and Anthropic’s new AI models]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1117399</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/05/23/1117399/the-download-meet-cathy-tie-and-anthropics-new-ai-models/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-23T12:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is today’s edition of The Download, our weekday newsletter that provides a daily dose of what’s going on in the world of technology. Meet Cathy Tie, Bride of “China’s Frankenstein” Since the Chinese biophysicist He Jiankui was released from prison in 2022, he has sought to make a scientific comeback and to repair his reputation after…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rhiannon Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Laid off but not afraid with X-senior Microsoft Dev MacKevin Fey [Podcast #173]]]></title>
        <id>68304756ecdb03ab557f3974</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/laid-off-but-not-afraid-with-x-senior-microsoft-dev-mackevin-fey-podcast-173/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-23T10:00:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On this week's episode of the podcast, freeCodeCamp founder Quincy Larson interviews MacKevin Fey. He just got laid off last week from his senior engineering role at Microsoft. We talk about: How Mack's approaching the job search after being laid of...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The FDA plans to limit access to covid vaccines. Here’s why that’s not all bad.]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1117329</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/05/23/1117329/fda-limit-access-covid-vaccines/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-23T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This week, two new leaders at the US Food and Drug Administration announced plans to limit access to covid vaccines, arguing that there is not much evidence to support the value of annual shots in healthy people. New vaccines will be made available only to the people who are most vulnerable—namely, those over 65 and…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jessica Hamzelou</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meet Cathy Tie, Bride of “China’s Frankenstein”]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1117373</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/05/23/1117373/cathy-tie-he-jiankui-china-crispr-x-twitter-feed/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-23T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Since the Chinese biophysicist He Jiankui was released from prison in 2022, he has sought to make a scientific comeback and to repair his reputation after a three-year incarceration for illegally creating the world’s first gene-edited children.  While he has bounced between cities, jobs, and meetings with investors, one area of visible success on his…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Caiwei Chen, Antonio Regalado</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[After GPT-4o backlash, researchers benchmark models on moral endorsement—find sycophancy persists across the board]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008691</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/after-gpt-4o-backlash-researchers-benchmark-models-on-moral-endorsement-find-sycophancy-persists-across-the-board/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-22T23:46:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new benchmark can test how much LLMs become sycophants, and found that GPT-4o was the most sycophantic of the models tested.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Emilia David</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn Vue.js in This Beginner's Course]]></title>
        <id>682f84537a13a40bfa336307</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-vuejs-in-this-beginners-course/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-22T20:08:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you’ve been meaning to add Vue.js to your front-end toolbelt, today’s your day. We just published a full, 6-hour Vue 3 course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel. Instructor Bhrugen Patel walks you through everything you need to build modern, ...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Anthropic faces backlash to Claude 4 Opus behavior that contacts authorities, press if it thinks you’re doing something ‘egregiously immoral’]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008672</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/anthropic-faces-backlash-to-claude-4-opus-behavior-that-contacts-authorities-press-if-it-thinks-youre-doing-something-immoral/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-22T19:12:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bowman later edited his tweet and the following one in a thread to read as follows, but it still didn't convince the naysayers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carl Franzen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Anthropic overtakes OpenAI: Claude Opus 4 codes seven hours nonstop, sets record SWE-Bench score and reshapes enterprise AI]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008575</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/anthropic-claude-opus-4-can-code-for-7-hours-straight-and-its-about-to-change-how-we-work-with-ai/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-22T16:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Anthropic's Claude Opus 4 outperforms OpenAI's GPT-4.1 with unprecedented seven-hour autonomous coding sessions and record-breaking 72.5% SWE-bench score, transforming AI from quick-response tool to day-long collaborator.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Nuñez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Deploy Your FastAPI + PostgreSQL App on Render: A Beginner's Guide]]></title>
        <id>682f4900bcc94cb9bccbf905</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/deploy-fastapi-postgresql-app-on-render/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-22T15:55:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This guide is a comprehensive roadmap for deploying a FastAPI backend connected to a PostgreSQL database using Render, a cloud platform that supports hosting Python web apps and managed PostgreSQL databases.   You can find the complete source code he...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Preston Osoro</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[An Animated Introduction to Elixir]]></title>
        <id>682f44e3dcb21c615cf1a12d</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/an-animated-introduction-to-elixir/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-22T15:38:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Elixir is a dynamic, functional programming language designed for building scalable and maintainable applications. It leverages the battle-tested Erlang VM, known for running low-latency, distributed, and fault-tolerant systems. Elixir is based on an...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mark Mahoney</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Time Magazine appears to accidentally publish embargoed story confirming new Anthropic model]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008649</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/time-magazine-appears-to-accidentally-publish-embargoed-story-confirming-anthropic-claude-4-opus/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-22T15:26:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Someone also appears to have published a full scrape of the Time article online on the news aggregator app Newsbreak.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carl Franzen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Enchant launches zero-equity accelerator for gaming and AI startups]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008571</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/games/enchant-launches-zero-equity-accelerator-for-gaming-and-ai-startups/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-22T12:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Enchant is launching a new zero-equity accelerator for gaming and AI startups, with applications now open for its three-month program.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dean Takahashi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[At Google I/O, Sergey Brin makes surprise appearance — and declares Google will build the first AGI]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008490</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/at-google-i-o-sergey-brin-makes-surprise-appearance-and-declares-google-will-build-the-first-agi/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-21T22:20:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google co-founder Sergey Brin makes surprise appearance at Google I/O, declaring "Gemini will be the very first AGI," revealing philosophical tensions with DeepMind CEO Hassabis who urges scientific caution in the high-stakes AI race.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Nuñez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Master Database Management Systems]]></title>
        <id>682e3c04117e792e5f46edc3</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/master-database-management-systems/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-21T20:48:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Understanding how to manage data effectively is a critical skill for anyone pursuing a career in tech. And we just published a course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will teach you all about Database Management Systems (DBMS). This in-de...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OpenAI updates its new Responses API rapidly with MCP support, GPT-4o native image gen, and more enterprise features]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008465</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/programming-development/openai-updates-its-new-responses-api-rapidly-with-mcp-support-gpt-4o-native-image-gen-and-more-enterprise-features/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-21T15:30:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Support for remote Model Context Protocol servers, integration of image generation and Code Interpreter tools, and upgrades to file search...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carl Franzen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mistral AI launches Devstral, powerful new open source SWE agent model that runs on laptops]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008458</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/mistral-ai-launches-devstral-powerful-new-open-source-swe-agent-model-that-runs-on-laptops/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-21T14:57:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Beyond performance and portability, its Apache 2.0 license offers a compelling proposition for commercial applications.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carl Franzen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AMD unveils new Threadripper CPUs and Radeon GPUs for gamers at Computex 2025]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008206</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/games/amd-unveils-new-threadripper-cpus-and-radeon-gpus-for-gamers-at-computex-2025/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-21T03:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AMD held a Computex press event to introduce its Radeon RX 9060 XT graphics cards and Threadripper CPUs for next-gen gaming and workstations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dean Takahashi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google finally launches NotebookLM mobile app at I/O: hands-on, first impressions]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008400</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/google-finally-launches-notebooklm-mobile-app-at-i-o-hands-on-first-impressions/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T19:29:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As NotebookLM matures, its emerging business-tier capabilities suggest growing alignment with the productivity and compliance...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carl Franzen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google just leapfrogged every competitor with mind-blowing AI that can think deeper, shop smarter, and create videos with dialogue]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008346</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/google-just-leapfrogged-every-competitor-with-mind-blowing-ai-that-can-think-deeper-shop-smarter-and-create-videos-with-dialogue/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T17:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google unveiled major AI advancements at I/O 2025, including Gemini 2.5 with Deep Think, AI Mode in Search, Veo 3 for video with audio, and a $249 Ultra plan aimed at power users and enterprises.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Nuñez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google’s Jules aims to out-code Codex in battle for the AI developer stack]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008361</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/googles-jules-aims-to-out-code-codex-in-battle-for-the-ai-developer-stack/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T17:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google released Jules, its coding agent, into beta as autonomous coding agents are quickly gaining market share.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Emilia David</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Inside Google’s AI leap: Gemini 2.5 thinks deeper, speaks smarter and codes faster]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008366</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/inside-google-ai-leap-gemini-2-5-thinks-deeper-speaks-smarter-codes-faster/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T17:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google is moving closer to its goal of autonomous agentic AI with a series of enhancements to Gemini 2.5 Pro and Flash.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Taryn Plumb</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blazing-fast Solana data via gRPC: access the freshest Solana data from Shredstream leaders]]></title>
        <id>68273f14bf73460001094b35</id>
        <link href="https://blog.quicknode.com/yellowstone-grpc/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T15:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Access the fastest Solana data with the Yellowstone Geyser gRPC self-serve add-on or with the premium hybrid dedicated gRPC node.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>QuickNode</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is Sui: A Comprehensive Guide to Web3 Scalability]]></title>
        <id>6823533984101f00013a5ca4</id>
        <link href="https://blog.quicknode.com/what-is-sui-a-comprehensive-guide-to-web3-scalability/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-15T23:34:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Explore how Sui Network achieves 300,000 TPS through parallel processing, and its applications in gaming, DeFi, and supply chain management.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>QuickNode</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AI Meets Blockchain: Transforming Technology for the Next Era]]></title>
        <id>682354c584101f00013a5cb9</id>
        <link href="https://blog.quicknode.com/ai-and-blockchain-transforming-technology-together/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-15T23:34:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discover how AI and blockchain integration enhances security, efficiency, and innovation in healthcare, supply chains, and financial services.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>QuickNode</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Adventure Layer: AI Native Onchain Games, Unleashed]]></title>
        <id>6824c55abf73460001094973</id>
        <link href="https://blog.quicknode.com/adventure-layer-launches-on-quicknode-raas/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-15T12:04:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Adventure Layer launches layer-2 chain leveraging QuickNode's Rollup-as-a-Service (RaaS) product.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>QuickNode</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[QuickLee V2: An Improved Transparent Look into RPC Provider Latency]]></title>
        <id>680fc8e1f8ae810001969b47</id>
        <link href="https://blog.quicknode.com/quicklee-v2/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-14T13:57:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[View public and real-time dashboards to better understand latency and speed when evaluating RPC providers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>QuickNode</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>