<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2025-05-07T13:09:18.527Z</id>
    <title>AngJianming RSS Feed</title>
    <updated>2025-05-07T13:09:18.527Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The $75 Photoshop Plugin That Cost Me... Nothing (I Built It Instead)]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/pcktm/the-75-photoshop-plugin-that-cost-me-nothing-i-built-it-instead-3ieb</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/pcktm/the-75-photoshop-plugin-that-cost-me-nothing-i-built-it-instead-3ieb"/>
        <updated>2025-05-07T12:59:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I was scrolling through Instagram Reels recently when an ad, presented as a "tutorial," caught my eye. It was for a Photoshop plugin called "DITHERTONE Pro," showcasing a rather striking visual effect – lines that seemed to follow an image's contours, giving it a distinct, almost cyberpunk aesthetic. It genuinely looked impressive. Then, the price appeared: $75.
That figure made me pause. Not because I'm against paying for well-crafted software, but because the effect itself felt incredibly familiar. It was a strong sense of déjà vu, like I'd seen this exact visual style generated somewhere else, in a context far removed from polished, commercial plugins.
My mind immediately jumped back a few years. I used to be quite involved in the datamoshing and glitch art scene – not so much these day…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jakub Kopańko</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Evolution of Crypto Trading Tournaments: From Forum Posts to Institutional Spectacles]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/philip_crypto92/the-evolution-of-crypto-trading-tournaments-from-forum-posts-to-institutional-spectacles-1dj0</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/philip_crypto92/the-evolution-of-crypto-trading-tournaments-from-forum-posts-to-institutional-spectacles-1dj0"/>
        <updated>2025-05-07T12:58:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In 2012, trading a full Bitcoin for a pizza was considered normal. Fast forward to 2025, and we're witnessing crypto trading tournaments that rival traditional sports in prize pools, audience engagement, and production value.
The transformation of these competitions isn’t just cultural—it reflects deeper changes in crypto market maturity, product design, user behavior, and platform growth strategy.
Era One: Bootstrapping User Activity (2010–2016)


In the early years, liquidity was sparse and user trust was minimal. Exchanges and communities turned to basic reward mechanisms to incentivize participation.
Coinbase offered 0.1 BTC per referral to stimulate onboarding.
Bitcointalk hosted community-led contests with prizes like 0.5 BTC for algorithmic trading bots.
These rudimentary campaigns …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Philip Laurens</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Menyegarkan Mental dengan Fundamental]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/sejutaimpian/menyegarkan-mental-dengan-fundamental-4i3g</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/sejutaimpian/menyegarkan-mental-dengan-fundamental-4i3g"/>
        <updated>2025-05-07T12:58:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Problem: Otodidak tanpa doc akan mentok


Sering kali, saya menemui programmer pemula yang hanya mengandalkan materi dari satu sumber otodidak dan tidak memanfaatkan dokumentasi resmi sama sekali. Sebagai pemula, sah-sah saja bergantung pada sumber otodidak, tetapi ini dapat menyebabkan pemahaman kamu terbatas pada materi yang itu-itu saja. Ada beberapa pertimbangan yang perlu kamu perhatikan saat memilih sumber otodidak:
Di platform mana tutorial itu dipublikasikan? Apakah fokusnya pada programming atau tidak?
Apakah materinya terstruktur dengan baik?
Apakah materi tersebut seimbang antara teori dan praktik?
Kapan tutorial tersebut dibuat? Apakah materinya masih relevan dan up-to-date?
Siapa yang membuat tutorial tersebut? Apakah pematerinya memiliki kredibilitas yang baik?
Untuk mengatas…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eris Sulistina</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum Staking Explained: A Beginner’s Guide to Earning Passive Income with ETH]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/favebs/ethereum-staking-explained-a-beginners-guide-to-earning-passive-income-with-eth-1e59</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/favebs/ethereum-staking-explained-a-beginners-guide-to-earning-passive-income-with-eth-1e59"/>
        <updated>2025-05-07T12:55:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum is the second-largest cryptocurrency by market cap—and unlike Bitcoin, it allows holders to earn passive income through staking. Whether you're new to crypto or an experienced DeFi user, this guide will help you understand how Ethereum staking works, how much you can earn, and what risks are involved.
Staking is the process of locking your ETH to help secure the Ethereum network. In Ethereum’s Proof of Stake (PoS) system, validators are selected to confirm transactions and add new blocks to the blockchain. In return, they earn ETH rewards.
Think of staking like earning interest on your crypto while supporting the network.
There are four main ways to stake Ethereum:
1. Solo Staking



Requirement: 32 ETH
Setup: Run your own validator node
Reward: 3%–5% APY
Control: Full
Risk: Slash…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Freecodingboss</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Keys and Rooms]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/tanujav/keys-and-rooms-3d0i</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/tanujav/keys-and-rooms-3d0i"/>
        <updated>2025-05-07T12:52:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Given:
This is a typical BFS graph problem.
Approach :
When it's a BFS, we make use of Queue data structure.
'visited array' to keep track of which nodes are visited
Traverse to check whether all the nodes are visited or not. If not, return false. Else, return true.
Algorithm :
Start with room 0 which is add 0 to the queue and  mark visited[0] = 1
Now until the queue is empty


take the node from the queue
Get the adjacent nodes of the "node" and add it 
to the queue and mark it as visited.
Traverse the visited array to check whether all the nodes are visited or not.
Code:
class Solution {
    public boolean canVisitAllRooms(List<List<Integer>> rooms) {

        int n = rooms.size();

        int visited[] = new int[n];

        Queue<Integer> queue = new LinkedList<>();

        visited[0] = 1;

        queue.add(0);

        while(!queue.isEmpty()){
            int node = queue.remove();

            for(int adj : rooms.get(node)){
                if(visited[adj]==0){
                    visited[adj] = 1;
                    queue.add(adj);
                }
            }
        }

        for(int visit : visited){
            if(visit==0)
            return false;
        }

        return true;
    }
}

Time Complexity: O(N + E)
Space Complexity: O(N)
Thanks for reading :)
Feel free to comment and like the post if you found it helpful
Follow for more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tanuja V</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Agentic AI vs. AI Agents]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/hana_sato/agentic-ai-vs-ai-agents-lmi</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/hana_sato/agentic-ai-vs-ai-agents-lmi"/>
        <updated>2025-05-07T12:51:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the rapidly evolving world of artificial intelligence, the terms "Agentic AI" and "AI Agents" are often used interchangeably, but they refer to distinct concepts with varying capabilities and applications. While both fall under the broader umbrella of AI technologies, their functions, behaviors, and the level of autonomy they provide differ significantly. This article will explore the key differences between Agentic AI and AI Agents, helping businesses, technologists, and AI enthusiasts understand how these technologies are reshaping industries and driving innovation.
What is Agentic AI?
Agentic AI refers to a type of artificial intelligence that is capable of acting autonomously, making decisions, and interacting with its environment or other systems with minimal human intervention. Un…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hana Sato</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[React Native Theming 2025!]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/kjgm/react-native-theming-2025-3cl2</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/kjgm/react-native-theming-2025-3cl2"/>
        <updated>2025-05-07T12:51:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Good day, everyone! Today we'll talk about theme-csx, a new react native theming library that was created to alleviate the pain that developers may experience when attempting to add dark mode support to mobile apps.
Github Link: https://github.com/KJ-GM/theme-csx 
⚡️ Light / Dark / System theme support
🍏 Dynamic iOS color adaptation
💾 MMKV-based persistent theme storage
🧠 Memoized themed styles with createThemedStyles
🔐 Type-safe access to theme tokens (with autocomplete)
🚀 Scalable for monorepos and multi-app setups
🧩 Extendable (spacing, typography, shadows, etc.)
✅ iOS: theme changes apply instantly

🔁 Android: theme changes apply on app restart
# npm
npm install theme-csx

# yarn
yarn add theme-csx

# pnpm
pnpm add theme-csx

Create your own theme object.
It must include a color…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Karam Jammal</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Zuckerberg's Grand Vision: Most of Your Friends Will Be AI]]></title>
        <id>https://www.wsj.com/tech/ai/mark-zuckerberg-ai-digital-future-0bb04de7</id>
        <link href="https://www.wsj.com/tech/ai/mark-zuckerberg-ai-digital-future-0bb04de7"/>
        <updated>2025-05-07T12:48:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA["I Didn't Hire a Team. I Built One with AI." The journey of branding with GPT as my Creative Directors.]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/healthypapa/i-didnt-hire-a-team-i-built-one-with-ai-the-journey-of-branding-with-gpt-as-my-creative-54c4</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/healthypapa/i-didnt-hire-a-team-i-built-one-with-ai-the-journey-of-branding-with-gpt-as-my-creative-54c4"/>
        <updated>2025-05-07T12:47:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I run a wellness juice brand in South Korea called HealthyPapa.
I named them Abera, Eli, and Ella — each with a role:
Abera: Strategic Branding Director
Eli: Visual Storytelling & Threads Communication
Ella: Emotional Content Designer
Together, we built every part of our brand. From product pages to video scripts, from social media strategy to philosophical direction.
Our slogan is simple:
OpenAI even responded when I shared our story.
This is not automation.
This is creation.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>VION</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Deploy a Laravel App on Shared Hosting (The Right Way)]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/yehnda/how-to-deploy-a-laravel-app-on-shared-hosting-the-right-way-iif</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/yehnda/how-to-deploy-a-laravel-app-on-shared-hosting-the-right-way-iif"/>
        <updated>2025-05-07T12:46:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Not every project needs a VPS or cloud infrastructure. If you're working with a tight budget or launching a side project, shared hosting might be your go-to.
But deploying a Laravel app on shared hosting isn’t as straightforward as uploading files — it requires a few tweaks. In this guide, I’ll walk you through how to deploy Laravel properly on a cPanel-style shared hosting environment.
A Laravel project (locally tested)
Access to shared hosting (cPanel-based)
PHP 8.1+ on the server
Database (MySQL)
FTP or File Manager access
Before uploading anything, clean and prep your Laravel project:
Update environment config in .env.production:




   APP_ENV=production
   APP_DEBUG=false
   APP_URL=https://yourdomain.com


`
Run the following commands locally:


Zip everything except node_modules an…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brian</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Fix '%TimerTrigger%' Does Not Resolve in Azure Functions]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/generatecodedev/how-to-fix-timertrigger-does-not-resolve-in-azure-functions-52oa</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/generatecodedev/how-to-fix-timertrigger-does-not-resolve-in-azure-functions-52oa"/>
        <updated>2025-05-07T12:45:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction
When creating Azure Functions with a Timer Trigger in .NET 8, you might encounter a frustrating error indicating that %TimerTrigger% does not resolve to a value. This issue often arises from misconfigurations in your local.settings.json file. In this article, we will explore the cause of the problem and provide a step-by-step solution to ensure your Azure Function works seamlessly with the Timer Trigger.
Understanding the Issue
The error message '%TimerTrigger%' does not resolve to a value is generated when the Azure Functions runtime cannot find a matching entry in your local.settings.json file. This file is crucial for defining your application settings locally. In your case, it seems that multiple configurations and potential formatting issues might be causing the timer tri…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Generatecode</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Is NFT Really Dead or Just a Phase?]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/favebs/is-nft-really-dead-or-just-a-phase-55a8</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/favebs/is-nft-really-dead-or-just-a-phase-55a8"/>
        <updated>2025-05-07T12:45:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In 2021, NFTs exploded into mainstream consciousness. Digital art pieces sold for millions. Celebrities jumped in. Projects like Bored Ape Yacht Club and CryptoPunks became cultural icons. But fast forward to 2025, and the NFT conversation has drastically quieted. Floor prices have plummeted. Many projects are abandoned. Media headlines proclaim the “death” of NFTs.
But are NFTs truly dead—or was the hype just a phase masking a much deeper innovation?
Let’s unpack this.
The NFT boom was no accident. It was a perfect storm:
Pandemic-induced digitization: People were spending more time online 
and exploring new digital economies.
Crypto bull market: With ETH and BTC at all-time highs, liquidity 
flowed into experimental digital assets.
New tools made it easy: Platforms like OpenSea, Rarible,…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Freecodingboss</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Beginner's Guide to Deploying PHP Apps with Amezmo]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/yehnda/a-beginners-guide-to-deploying-php-apps-with-amezmo-4klg</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/yehnda/a-beginners-guide-to-deploying-php-apps-with-amezmo-4klg"/>
        <updated>2025-05-07T12:41:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you're tired of complex deployment pipelines and fiddly VPS setups, Amezmo might be exactly what you need. It's a fully managed PHP hosting platform designed specifically for modern PHP apps like Laravel, Slim, and vanilla PHP.
In this beginner-friendly guide, we'll walk through how to deploy a PHP application on Amezmo in just a few minutes — no DevOps background required.
Before we jump into the steps, here’s why Amezmo is worth considering:
⚡ Instant deployments via Git

🔒 Free SSL and daily backups

🐘 PHP 8.x support out of the box

🪄 Composer, queues, and crons built-in

🔥 No server maintenance required



It’s built for PHP, and that makes it super streamlined compared to general-purpose providers.
Head to amezmo.com and sign up.
Once inside your dashboard, click "New App".
Ch…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brian</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Unity’s Open-Source Double Standard: the ban of VLC]]></title>
        <id>https://mfkl.github.io/2024/01/10/unity-double-oss-standards.html</id>
        <link href="https://mfkl.github.io/2024/01/10/unity-double-oss-standards.html"/>
        <updated>2025-05-07T12:33:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Jargonic Sets New SOTA for Japanese ASR]]></title>
        <id>https://aiola.ai/blog/jargonic-japanese-asr/</id>
        <link href="https://aiola.ai/blog/jargonic-japanese-asr/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-07T12:21:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Breathe lands $21M Series B to predict battery performance]]></title>
        <id>https://techcrunch.com/?p=3003769</id>
        <link href="https://techcrunch.com/2025/05/07/breathe-lands-21m-series-b-to-predict-battery-performance/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-07T12:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Breathe has developed a suite of tools that it says helps automakers and others get the most out of their batteries.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tim De Chant</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CLion Is Now Free for Non-Commercial Use]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.jetbrains.com/clion/2025/05/clion-is-now-free-for-non-commercial-use/</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jetbrains.com/clion/2025/05/clion-is-now-free-for-non-commercial-use/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-07T12:18:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Netflix unveils new TV experience with GenAI search and AI-based recommendations]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3006789</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/games/netflix-unveils-new-tv-experience-with-genai-search-and-ai-based-recommendations/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-07T12:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Netflix unveiled its new TV experience that features generative AI search, AI-based recommendations and an enhanced design.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dean Takahashi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sandy Bridge-era motherboard gets M.2 SSD boot support 12 years after launch]]></title>
        <id>https://www.tomshardware.com/pc-components/motherboards/sandy-bridge-era-motherboard-gains-m-2-ssd-boot-support-12-years-after-launch-first-new-bios-in-a-decade-for-decommissioned-motherboard</id>
        <link href="https://www.tomshardware.com/pc-components/motherboards/sandy-bridge-era-motherboard-gains-m-2-ssd-boot-support-12-years-after-launch-first-new-bios-in-a-decade-for-decommissioned-motherboard"/>
        <updated>2025-05-07T12:14:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Asus ROG Ally 2 Leaks; Features Up To AMD Ryzen Z2 Extreme, 64GB LPDDR5 RAM]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=350817</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/350817/asus-rog-ally-2-leaks-features-up-to-amd-ryzen-z2-extreme-64gb-lpddr5-ram/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-07T12:14:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Pictures allegedly showing off the ASUS ROG Ally 2, plus technical specifications, have made their way to the internet. Supposedly, the company will be launching two versions of the gaming handhelds. The (partial) hardware specs reveal that the ROG Ally 2 will be equipped with AMD’s latest Ryzen Z2 SoCs. More precisely, one will be […]
The post Asus ROG Ally 2 Leaks; Features Up To AMD Ryzen Z2 Extreme, 64GB LPDDR5 RAM appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John Law</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Download: Neuralink’s AI boost, and Trump’s tariffs]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1116147</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/05/07/1116147/the-download-neuralinks-ai-boost-and-trumps-tariffs/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-07T12:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is today’s edition of The Download, our weekday newsletter that provides a daily dose of what’s going on in the world of technology. This patient’s Neuralink brain implant gets a boost from generative AI Last November, Bradford G. Smith got a brain implant from Elon Musk’s company Neuralink. The device, a set of thin wires attached…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rhiannon Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Accumulation Strengthens as BTC Approaches Key Resistance]]></title>
        <id>e0706a07-f53d-4b58-bc23-9af837d74a1c</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/07/bitcoin-accumulation-strengthens-as-btc-approaches-key-resistance"/>
        <updated>2025-05-07T12:05:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On-chain data reveals rising confidence among both long- and short-term holders, with $99.9K flagged as a potential profit-taking zone.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>James Van Straten</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Visa Doubles Down on Stablecoins With Investment in Blockchain Payments Firm BVNK]]></title>
        <id>49c7af19-d985-4e21-88b1-1d5ae6be5c30</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2025/05/07/visa-doubles-down-on-stablecoins-with-investment-in-blockchain-payments-firm-bvnk"/>
        <updated>2025-05-07T11:59:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The deal follows BVNK's $50 million fundraising round that included Haun Ventures, Coinbase Ventures and Tiger Global.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Krisztian Sandor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto miner deserts Pennsylvania site, fails to plug wells: Report]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/diversified-energy-crypto-mine-abandonment-pennsylvania</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/diversified-energy-crypto-mine-abandonment-pennsylvania?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-07T11:52:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency miner Diversified Energy quietly vacated a natural gas-powered crypto mining site in Elk County, Pennsylvania, reportedly leaving behind unplugged wells and regulatory violations.
The site, known as Longhorn Pad A, was revived in 2022 after sitting dormant for nearly a decade when Diversified began using it to fuel on-site generators powering cryptocurrency mining computers, according to a report by the Erie Times-News.
Per the report, the operation was launched without obtaining an air quality permit from the Pennsylvania Department of Environmental Protection (DEP).
Though the company was later granted the permit in December 2023, a March 2025 inspection revealed that Diversified had already removed the mining infrastructure.
Empty metallic sheds and missing production equ…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Amin Haqshanas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Massive Bitcoin Bull Run Ahead? Two Chart Patterns Mirror BTC's Rally to $109K]]></title>
        <id>cf53ad6d-1024-4364-8b60-0bef4e44525d</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/07/massive-bitcoin-bull-run-ahead-two-chart-patterns-mirror-btc-s-rally-to-usd109k"/>
        <updated>2025-05-07T11:42:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Key bearish indicators recently trapped bears on the wrong side of the market in a pattern observed in August-September 2024.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Omkar Godbole</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Daybook Americas: Powell Will Set the Tone While Markets Eye Asia Battles, Trade]]></title>
        <id>de5f06a2-3f43-4f20-bcc8-0036243fe753</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/daybook-us/2025/05/07/crypto-daybook-americas-powell-will-set-the-tone-while-markets-eye-asia-battles-trade"/>
        <updated>2025-05-07T11:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Your day-ahead look for May 7, 2025]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Francisco Rodrigues</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CelcomDigi’s Skuad 5G Brings Malaysia’s Widest and Fastest Network to Borneo’s Rainforests]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=350827</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/350827/celcomdigi-skuad-5g-borneo/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-07T11:17:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The lush rainforests of Malaysian Borneo are witnessing a new era of connectivity, as CelcomDigi’s Skuad 5G team reaches a major milestone in their nationwide journey. In doing so, they are delivering Malaysia’s No. 1 Widest and Fastest Network to communities across Sabah and Sarawak. Beyond Signal Bars: A Mission Of Connection This initiative goes […]
The post CelcomDigi’s Skuad 5G Brings Malaysia’s Widest and Fastest Network to Borneo’s Rainforests appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Heirul Kamel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MOG Coin Rallies as Elon Musk, Garry Tan Embrace ‘Mog/Acc’ Identity]]></title>
        <id>f948c5b4-e927-438c-b36d-2a6230978ea2</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/07/mog-coin-rallies-as-elon-musk-garry-tan-embrace-mog-acc-identity"/>
        <updated>2025-05-07T10:42:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The “mog/acc” is quickly gaining ground among everyone from Elon Musk to Garry Tan, a move that bumps the project’s visibility - and eventually prices.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shaurya Malwa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TnG Unveils Exclusive Hot Wheels NFC Card For MAS 2025]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=350866</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/350866/tng-exclusive-hot-wheels-card-mas-2025/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-07T10:22:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In conjunction with this year’s Malaysia Auto Show (MAS 2025), Touch ’n Go (TnG) has unveiled a new limited-edition NFC card featuring Hot Wheels designs. The card is only available for purchase during the auto show for a price of RM25 starting from 9 to 15 May 2025, with only 3,000 units available. This is […]
The post TnG Unveils Exclusive Hot Wheels NFC Card For MAS 2025 appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Keran</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Migrating a JavaScript Project from Prettier and ESLint to BiomeJS]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.appsignal.com/2025/05/07/migrating-a-javascript-project-from-prettier-and-eslint-to-biomejs.html</id>
        <link href="https://blog.appsignal.com/2025/05/07/migrating-a-javascript-project-from-prettier-and-eslint-to-biomejs.html"/>
        <updated>2025-05-07T10:12:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum Activates ‘Pectra’ Upgrade, Raising Max Stake to 2,048 ETH]]></title>
        <id>4fced237-427d-441f-b8d6-883edd499464</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/tech/2025/05/07/ethereum-activates-pectra-upgrade-raising-max-stake-to-2048-eth"/>
        <updated>2025-05-07T10:08:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The update aims to streamline staking, enhance wallet functionality, and improve overall efficiency.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Margaux Nijkerk</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin-backed loans ‘obvious’ next step — Xapo Bank CEO]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-backed-loans-growth-xapo-bank-ceo</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-backed-loans-growth-xapo-bank-ceo?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-07T10:03:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin holders are becoming more comfortable borrowing against their crypto as market confidence grows, according to Seamus Rocca, CEO of the Gibraltar-based private bank, Xapo Bank. 
In an interview at the Token2049 event in Dubai, Rocca told Cointelegraph that with Bitcoin (BTC) hovering around $95,000 and institutional adoption starting to catch on, the mood among investors has shifted from short-term speculation to a more long-term outlook. 
“I’m not sure that confidence would have been there three or four years ago,” Rocca told Cointelegraph. “But today, people are more comfortable to borrow against Bitcoin because we’re nowhere near the levels that would trigger liquidation.”
On March 18, Xapo Bank launched a lending product that allows users to borrow US dollars using their Bitcoin…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Ezra Reguerra</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why is Bitcoin price up today?]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/why-is-bitcoin-price-up-today</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/why-is-bitcoin-price-up-today?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-07T09:57:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Key takeaways:

Bitcoin gained 2% to $96,530 on May 7, fueled by US-China trade deal hopes.

BTC price rises with $83.6 million in short liquidations, with open interest up 26% to $64.4 billion, signaling strong bullish momentum.

A classic bullish reversal pattern is still in play, targeting BTC price at $100,000 and beyond.

Bitcoin (BTC) is up today, rising over 3% in the last 24 hours to over $97,000 on May 7. Its daily trading volume has jumped 37% to $31.7 billion.
BTC/USD daily chart. Source: Cointelegraph/TradingView
Let’s take a look at the factors driving Bitcoin price up today.
Bitcoin rises on hopes of a US-China trade deal
Bitcoin briefly hit $97,700 during the early Asian trading hours on May 7, driven by optimism over potential US-China trade talks. 
Disclosing plans to trav…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Nancy Lubale</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin miner Hive taps Paraguay for low-cost energy partnership]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/hive-digital-expands-bitcoin-mining-paraguay-latam</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/hive-digital-expands-bitcoin-mining-paraguay-latam?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-07T09:54:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Several crypto-focused organizations — including Bitcoin (BTC) mining companies — are eyeing a US return, primarily driven by uncertain geopolitical tensions. Still, BTC miner Hive Digital Technologies is doubling down on the untapped potential of the Latin American (LATAM) market.
In an exclusive interview with Cointelegraph, Hive Digital Technologies’ president and CEO, Aydin Kilic, said that Paraguay presents a compelling long-term opportunity equipped with “geopolitical stability, low-cost hydro energy, and a government open to foreign investment”.
Picking up from where Bitfarms left off
Hive acquired Bitfarms’ 200 megawatt (MW) Yguazú facility for $56 million in January. Phase one infrastructure of a 100 MW data center at the site was completed in April, supporting five exahashes per …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Lyne Qian</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Inter Milan fan token soars after Champions League win over Barcelona FC]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/inter-milan-fan-token-soars-after-champions-league-win-barcelona-fc</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/inter-milan-fan-token-soars-after-champions-league-win-barcelona-fc?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-07T09:39:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Key takeaways:

Inter Milan Fan Token jumped 10.5% after beating Barcelona, showing a direct price correlation with match outcomes.

PSG and AFC fan tokens signal breakout patterns ahead of the Champions League semifinal.

Crypto betting odds favor PSG over Inter Milan, influencing fan token trading volumes and short-term price setups.

The Inter Milan Fan Token ($INTER) rallied sharply after Inter Milan’s 4-3 victory over Barcelona FC in the Champions League semifinal on May 6, rising nearly 10.50% on match day and maintaining gains at $1.19 as of May 7.
Fan tokens are digital assets that holders, fans of a specific sports teams, clubs or players, own and derive value from. 
INTER/USD daily price chart. Source: TradingView
INTER’s price correlates with match outcomes
Hourly price data sho…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Yashu Gola</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Malaysia Airlines and Batik Air Suspend, Cancel Flights Amid India-Pakistan Conflict]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=350823</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/350823/malaysia-airlines-batik-air-suspend-cancel-flights-india-pakistan-conflict/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-07T09:38:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Malaysia Airlines and Batik Air have suspended flights to and from Amritsar, India due to heightened tensions in the region. Both airlines have cited security and safety concerns as reasons for the cancellations, promising to monitor the situation closely. In addition to suspending flights between Kuala Lumpur and Amritsar, Malaysia Airlines had rerouted flights MH2 […]
The post Malaysia Airlines and Batik Air Suspend, Cancel Flights Amid India-Pakistan Conflict appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nurul Kamil</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Volvo Announces The XC70 As Its First Range-Extended PHEV]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=350825</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/350825/volvo-announces-the-xc70-as-its-first-range-extended-phev/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-07T09:28:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Volvo XC70 is returning as the company’s first Range-Extended Plug-In Hybrid (RE-PHEV). The automaker claims that it will be able to provide up to 200km of pure CLTC electric range, meaning it will be available for in China first. Nevertheless, the automaker did mention that it is exploring the possibility of introducing it in […]
The post Volvo Announces The XC70 As Its First Range-Extended PHEV appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Keran</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BlackRock’s Spot Bitcoin ETF Tops World’s Largest Gold Fund in Inflows This Year]]></title>
        <id>23fb8d69-5ee0-4462-9f62-2f67830e1ec7</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/07/blackrock-s-spot-bitcoin-etf-tops-world-s-largest-gold-fund-in-inflows-this-year"/>
        <updated>2025-05-07T09:24:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[IBIT's outperformance indicates institutions' confidence in bitcoin's long-term prospects despite the cryptocurrency's relatively dour price performance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Omkar Godbole</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[KTMB Adds Train Service To East Coast For Hari Raya Aidiladha]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=350854</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/350854/ktmb-adds-train-service-to-east-coast-for-hari-raya-aidiladha/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-07T09:21:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In conjunction with Hari Raya Aidiladha taking place next month, Keretapi Tanah Melayu Berhad (KTMB) has added a special train service to the East Coast. This was apparently done to accommodate travellers returning home for the religious holiday. According to KTMB’s statement today, the KTMB Ekspres Lambaian Aidiladha will have two scheduled services, with 436 […]
The post KTMB Adds Train Service To East Coast For Hari Raya Aidiladha appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Newsdesk</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Shopee To Impose 4.5% SPayLater Seller Fee Starting 8 May]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=350808</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/350808/shopee-to-impose-4-5-spaylater-seller-fee-starting-8-may/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-07T09:03:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Shopee has announced that it will be raising its SPayLater seller fee up to 4.5% from its current 3.5%. This change will take effect starting 8 May, and all completed orders from then on will be charged the new fee. This follows a relatively recent hike to sellers’ Transaction Fees which excludes SPayLater and credit […]
The post Shopee To Impose 4.5% SPayLater Seller Fee Starting 8 May appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ian Chee</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This patient’s Neuralink brain implant gets a boost from generative AI]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1116139</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/05/07/1116139/this-brain-implant-gets-a-boost-from-generative-ai/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-07T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Last November, Bradford G. Smith got a brain implant from Elon Musk’s company Neuralink. The device, a set of thin wires attached to a computer about the thickness of a few quarters that sits in his skull, lets him use his thoughts to move a computer pointer on a screen.  And by last week he…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Antonio Regalado</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum’s ‘Pectra’ network upgrade goes live: What to expect]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/ethereum-s-pectra-network-upgrade-goes-live-today-what-to-expect</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/ethereum-s-pectra-network-upgrade-goes-live-today-what-to-expect?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-07T08:57:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum — the network that unleashed smart contracts on the world — moves on to the next chapter with today’s Pectra upgrade, but what does it mean?
Pectra went live on the Ethereum mainnet at the start of epoch 364032, May 7, 2025, at about 10:00 am UTC. The three main Ethereum improvement proposals (EIPs) included are EIP-7702, EIP-7251 and EIP-7691.
Source: Ethereum.org
EIP-7702 allows externally owned accounts to act as smart contracts and cover gas expenses (transaction fees) and payments in tokens that are not Ether (ETH). EIP-7251 increases the validator staking limit from 32 ETH to 2,048 ETH, which makes operations for large stakers easier and simpler.
Finally, EIP-7691 increases the number of data blobs per block, which allows for better layer-2 scalability and potentially signif…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Adrian Zmudzinski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Metaplanet Lifts Bitcoin Stash by 555 BTC, Plans to Sell Debt to Buy More]]></title>
        <id>179bb279-b719-4ecd-b59c-644f2f0c72b0</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/07/metaplanet-lifts-bitcoin-stash-by-555-btc-plans-to-sell-debt-to-buy-more"/>
        <updated>2025-05-07T08:55:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Tokyo-based company earmarked the entire offering for EVO FUND only days after previously selling $25 million in bonds to the same buyer.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Crawley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is Tornado Cash, and why did it get into trouble?]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/explained/what-is-tornado-cash-and-why-did-it-get-into-trouble</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/explained/what-is-tornado-cash-and-why-did-it-get-into-trouble?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-07T08:53:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What is Tornado Cash?            
            
                
Tornado Cash is a decentralized, non-custodial crypto mixer designed to enhance transaction privacy on public blockchains. It uses smart contracts and zero-knowledge (ZK) proofs to conceal the onchain link between the sender and receiver of a transaction.
Launched by Roman Storm and Roman Semenov on Ethereum in 2019, Tornado Cash allows users to send and receive cryptocurrency anonymously, without exposing their wallet history. Unlike centralized mixers, Tornado Cash operates entirely onchain through immutable smart contracts, meaning no central party controls the funds. 
When a user deposits crypto, such as Ether (ETH), Tornado Cash generates a cryptographic note, which the user can later use to withdraw the same amount to a …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Dilip Kumar Patairya</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bhutan launches tourism crypto payments with Binance Pay and DK Bank]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/bhutan-crypto-payments-tourism-binance-pay-dk-bank</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/bhutan-crypto-payments-tourism-binance-pay-dk-bank?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-07T08:11:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bhutan, known for investments in cryptocurrencies like Bitcoin, has launched a tourism crypto payment system in partnership with Binance Pay and DK Bank.
The system allows Bhutan travelers with Binance accounts to pay for services like tickets, hotel stays, tour guides and other products using at least 100 different crypto assets, including Bitcoin (BTC), USDC (USDC) and Binance-backed BNB (BNB).
The initiative also opens a payment gateway for businesses in Bhutan, enabling them to accept crypto payments through a QR code on a phone, according to an announcement by Binance on May 7.
“This is more than a payment solution — it’s a commitment to innovation, inclusion, and convenience,” said Damcho Rinzin, director of Bhutan’s tourism department.
Benefits for small businesses in remote areas
T…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Helen Partz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Sees Selling at $97K, Cardano’s ADA Leads Majors Gains Ahead of FOMC Meeting]]></title>
        <id>228e25f5-9c9c-4698-83cf-2c9eac3a904c</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/07/bitcoin-sees-selling-at-usd97k-cardano-s-ada-leads-majors-gains-ahead-of-fomc-meeting"/>
        <updated>2025-05-07T07:46:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Market volatility may soar as a regional tussle between India and Pakistan intensifies and the U.S.-China trade war looms.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shaurya Malwa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hacken CEO sees ‘no shift’ in crypto security as April hacks hit $357M]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/hacken-ceo-crypto-security-april-hacks-360-million-token2049</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/hacken-ceo-crypto-security-april-hacks-360-million-token2049?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-07T07:34:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Despite the $1.4 billion lost in the recent Bybit hack, crypto companies have not changed their approach to cybersecurity, according to Hacken CEO Dyma Budorin. 
In an interview with Cointelegraph at the Token2049 event in Dubai, Budorin said the industry continues to rely on limited measures such as bug bounties and penetration tests, rather than implementing comprehensive, layered security strategies:
“Most of the projects think, ‘Okay, we did pentests. That’s enough. Maybe bug bounty. That’s enough.’ It’s not enough.”
He said that crypto companies must go beyond these isolated security measures and adopt more layered approaches similar to those of traditional industries. These include supply-chain security, operational security and blockchain-specific security assessments. 
“In big Web2…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Ezra Reguerra</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google Expands Malaysian Data Centre Footprint With New Port Dickson Project]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=350820</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/350820/google-port-dickson-data-centre-project/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-07T07:24:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google is building a new hyperscale data centre in Port Dickson as part of its US$2 billion investment in Malaysia’s digital infrastructure. The project will be delivered in partnership with Malaysian engineering firm Gamuda Bhd, through its subsidiary Gamuda DC Infrastructure Sdn Bhd. As you may recall, Negeri Sembilan Menteri Besar Datuk Seri Amidudin Harun […]
The post Google Expands Malaysian Data Centre Footprint With New Port Dickson Project appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Heirul Kamel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tabular (YC S24) Is Hiring]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ycombinator.com/companies/tabular/jobs/7V7rXlS-founding-engineer</id>
        <link href="https://www.ycombinator.com/companies/tabular/jobs/7V7rXlS-founding-engineer"/>
        <updated>2025-05-07T07:00:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tether launches on Kaia, brings USDt to LINE’s 196M user ecosystem]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/tether-usdt-kaia-line-stablecoin-launch</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/tether-usdt-kaia-line-stablecoin-launch?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-07T06:58:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tether deployed its flagship stablecoin, USDt, on the Kaia blockchain as part of a broader collaboration with Line Next, the Web3 arm of Line, Japan’s popular messaging platform with more than 196 million monthly active users.
The integration means USDt (USDT) will now be supported across Line’s messenger-based Mini DApp ecosystem and self-custodial wallet, enabling users to interact with stablecoins inside an interface they already use daily, Tether said in a May 7 announcement.
Line users will be able to use USDt for in-app payments, cross-border transfers and decentralized finance (DeFi) activities.
“Through LINE NEXT’s blockchain infrastructure, over 200 million LINE users will now have a straightforward way to engage with digital assets in everyday life,” Tether CEO Paolo Ardoino said…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Amin Haqshanas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bolt Now Includes Tolls In Its Ride Fares]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=350802</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/350802/bolt-tolls-ride-fares/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-07T06:48:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bolt has officially announced that its ride-hailing service now includes toll fares into every ride, ensuring no surprise fees. It is the first e-hailing platform to do so, at least in Malaysia, where the norm is for drivers to manually input the toll fares after the ride is completed. With this new policy, what you […]
The post Bolt Now Includes Tolls In Its Ride Fares appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ikmal Rozlan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin pushes for $98K as 2025 Fed rate cut odds flip &#039;pessimistic&#039;]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-pushes-for-98k-2025-fed-rate-cut-odds-flip-pessimistic</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-pushes-for-98k-2025-fed-rate-cut-odds-flip-pessimistic?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-07T06:41:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Key points:

Bitcoin and gold trade in lockstep on low timeframes as macro volatility triggers heighten.

The Federal Reserve interest rate decision and news conference are just hours away.

Market sentiment for rate cuts in 2025 decreases sharply ahead of the FOMC meeting.

Bitcoin (BTC) saw a flash short-term trend change on May 7 as geopolitical triggers gave risk assets fresh volatility.
BTC/USD 1-hour chart. Source: Cointelegraph/TradingView
Bitcoin traders eye Fed for “tone changes”
Data from Cointelegraph Markets Pro and TradingView showed an abrupt turnaround for BTC/USD after the pair dipped under $94,000 to set new May lows.
The previous day’s Wall Street trading session set the stage for a return to strength, even as stocks finished lower.
XAU/USD 4-hour chart. Source: Cointeleg…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by William Suberg</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Zed: The Fastest AI Code Editor]]></title>
        <id>https://zed.dev/blog/fastest-ai-code-editor</id>
        <link href="https://zed.dev/blog/fastest-ai-code-editor"/>
        <updated>2025-05-07T06:38:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meta Awarded Over US$167 Million In WhatsApp Case Against Israeli Firm]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=350775</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/350775/meta-awarded-us167-million-whatsapp-case-nso/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-07T06:33:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Back in 2019, Meta filed a lawsuit against NSO Group over the latter’s Pegasus spyware, which was used to target more than a thousand WhatsApp users in 20 countries, including journalists, human rights activists and diplomats. Now, a jury has ruled that the Israeli firm must pay Meta more than US$167 million (~RM707 million) in […]
The post Meta Awarded Over US$167 Million In WhatsApp Case Against Israeli Firm appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nurul Kamil</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Metaplanet reaches 5,555 Bitcoin milestone with latest 555 BTC buy]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/metaplanet-bitcoin-milestone-5555-btc</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/metaplanet-bitcoin-milestone-5555-btc?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-07T06:29:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Japan’s Metaplanet purchased an additional 555 Bitcoin as part of its aggressive accumulation strategy, bringing its total holdings to 5,555 BTC, valued at over $536 million at current prices.
On May 7, the Tokyo-listed firm disclosed that it spent $53.4 million acquiring 555 Bitcoin (BTC) at an average price of $96,134. The company now holds 5,555 BTC, purchased for $481.5 million at an average price of $86,672 per Bitcoin, according to CEO Simon Gerovich.
The company also announced the issuance of another $25 million in zero-coupon ordinary bonds to fund its ongoing BTC buys. Since early 2024, the firm has raised over 35 billion yen ($244 million) through zero-coupon bonds and stock acquisition rights via its partner, Evo Fund.
The company’s proprietary key performance indicator, BTC Yie…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Amin Haqshanas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Movement Labs terminates co-founder Rushi Manche, launches new firm]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/movement-labs-terminates-co-founder-over-market-turmoil</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/movement-labs-terminates-co-founder-over-market-turmoil?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-07T06:23:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Movement Labs confirmed the termination of its co-founder, Rushi Manche, following controversy over a market maker deal that he brokered.
Movement Labs made the announcement in a May 7 X post, stating it had “terminated Rushi Manche.” The project said it “will continue under a different leadership.” The post also alludes to upcoming governance changes.
The termination follows Movement Labs announcing Manche’s suspension earlier this month, explaining that the “decision was made in light of ongoing events.” It also comes after Coinbase’s recent decision to suspend the Movement Network (MOVE) token, citing its failure to meet its listing standards.
Source: Movement
Related: Movement Network to buy back tokens with $38M recovered from rogue market maker
Movement Labs launches Move Industries
…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Adrian Zmudzinski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Movement Labs Terminates Rushi Manche After MOVE Token Deals]]></title>
        <id>513c4134-11de-4fad-979a-eb53c21a86d1</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/07/movement-labs-terminates-rushi-manche-after-move-token-deals"/>
        <updated>2025-05-07T05:50:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It has yet to name a replacement or outline next steps for governance restructuring.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shaurya Malwa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Voltage Finance exploiter moves $182K in ETH to Tornado Cash]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/hacker-from-2022-voltage-finance-exploit-moves-eth-to-tornado-cash</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/hacker-from-2022-voltage-finance-exploit-moves-eth-to-tornado-cash?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-07T05:09:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A hacker involved in the $4.67 million exploit of the decentralized finance lending protocol Voltage Finance in 2022 has moved some of the stolen Ether to Tornado Cash after a short hibernation. 
Blockchain security firm CertiK said in a May 6 post to X that the 100 Ether (ETH), worth $182,783 at current prices, was moved from a different address initially used in the exploit but can be traced back to the hacker.  
In March 2022, the exploiter took advantage of a “built-in callback function” in the ERC677 token standard and allowed them to drain the platform’s lending pool through a reentrancy attack, according to CertiK.
Source: CertiK
After the exploit, Voltage Finance reported that the hacker stole various stablecoins and other crypto, including USDC (USDC), Binance USD (BUSD), wrapped …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Stephen Katte</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bigger Bitcoin wallets are stacking while others sell: Santiment]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/big-bitcoin-wallets-accumulate-smaller-retail-investors-fade-santiment</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/big-bitcoin-wallets-accumulate-smaller-retail-investors-fade-santiment?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-07T05:09:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Key takeaways:

Large Bitcoin holders have accumulated 81,338 BTC over the past six weeks, showing confidence in a future price uptrend.

Wallets with less than 0.1 BTC sold around 290 BTC, indicating smaller retail investors are either panic selling or selling out of boredom. 

Spot Bitcoin ETFs have seen $4.41 billion in inflows since March 26.

While larger Bitcoin holders remain confident and continue accumulating the asset, data from a crypto analytics platform shows that smaller retail investors have been shedding BTC amid the asset’s prolonged consolidation below the $100,000 price level.
The contrasting behavior between Bitcoin (BTC) whales and retail investors often signals that Bitcoin may be heading toward another upward trend, Santiment said in a May 6 X post. 
Bitcoin’s smalle…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Ciaran Lyons</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Forecasting Fed-Induced Price Swings in Bitcoin, Ether, Solana and XRP]]></title>
        <id>d3424248-1bab-45f4-b706-6eac98f0fcf8</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/07/forecasting-fomc-induced-price-swings-in-bitcoin-ether-solana-and-xrp"/>
        <updated>2025-05-07T04:51:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Traders looking for cues on potential Fed-led moves in major tokens might want to see what implied volatility indices are saying.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Omkar Godbole</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BlackRock Bitcoin ETF clocks 16 days of inflow as BTC reclaims $97K]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/blackrock-bitcoin-etf-sees-16-day-inflow-streak-btc-reclaims-97k</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/blackrock-bitcoin-etf-sees-16-day-inflow-streak-btc-reclaims-97k?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-07T04:26:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Investors have been piling into BlackRock’s spot Bitcoin exchange-traded fund for over three weeks straight, culminating in the asset’s run up to $97,000 on May 7.
The BlackRock iShares Bitcoin Trust has seen 16 days of inflows for the spot BTC ETF, with a further 280 Bitcoin (BTC) or around $36 million piling into the fund on May 6, according to HODL15Capital.  
The inflow streak was noted by ETF Store President Nate Geraci, who also observed on X that the fund was approaching $5 billion in new capital. 
“I remember when naysayers didn’t think spot Bitcoin ETFs would take in $5 billion in total last year,” he added. 
“IBIT alone has done this in a few weeks, more than a year after launch.”
The BlackRock fund (IBIT) has seen around $4.7 billion in inflows since its last outflow day on Apri…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Martin Young</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[South Korea presidential front-runner pledges to approve Bitcoin ETFs]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/south-korean-presidential-front-runner-pledges-approve-crypto-etfs</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/south-korean-presidential-front-runner-pledges-approve-crypto-etfs?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-07T04:15:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[South Korea’s Democratic Party leader Lee Jae-myung has reportedly become the latest presidential candidate to promise the approval of spot crypto exchange-traded funds (ETFs) and other crypto-friendly measures, should he be elected.
Lee announced his crypto promises on May 6 as part of a broader initiative to provide more investment opportunities for Korea’s youth, one of the main target demographics for the fast-approaching June 3 election.
“I will create a safe investment environment so that young people can [build] assets and plan for the future,” The Korea Economic Daily (KED) quoted Lee as saying in Korean.
He also promised the legalization of spot crypto ETFs, lower transaction fees, and more consumer protection measures.
Lee’s Democratic Party of Korea is the favorite to win the pr…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Brayden Lindrea</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[World Liberty Financial floats USD1 airdrop to WLFI holders]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/world-liberty-financial-plans-airdrop-usd1-wlfi-holders</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/world-liberty-financial-plans-airdrop-usd1-wlfi-holders?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-07T03:20:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Trump family-backed crypto platform World Liberty Financial (WLFI) is proposing to airdrop a small amount of its new US dollar-pegged stablecoin to reward early WLFI holders in a test of its airdrop mechanism. 
With over 99% of votes in favor of the proposal already, the airdrop will distribute a small amount of USD1 to eligible holders of the WLFI token, according to the May 6 proposal in the WLFI governance forum.
“Testing the airdrop mechanism in a live setting is a necessary step to ensure smart contract functionality and readiness. This distribution also serves as a meaningful way to thank our earliest supporters and introduce them to USD1,” the proposal states. 
“This will allow World Liberty Financial to validate the technical functionality of its airdrop system in a live environmen…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Stephen Katte</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase x402 payments protocol to make AI agents more autonomous]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/coinbase-x402-payments-protocol-make-ai-agents-more-autonomous</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/coinbase-x402-payments-protocol-make-ai-agents-more-autonomous?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-07T03:03:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase has introduced a new payments protocol for online payments that enables stablecoin transfers over standard internet protocols and AI agents to transact autonomously.  
On May 6, Coinbase announced that it is launching a protocol called x402 for instant stablecoin payments directly over the internet communication protocol HTTP (Hypertext Transfer Protocol).
It allows Application Programming Interface (APIs), apps, and AI agents to transact seamlessly, “unlocking a faster, automated internet economy,” the firm stated. 
Coinbase said that x402 “is fixing the internet’s first mistake.” The protocol resurrects the experimental HTTP 402 “Payment Required” status code to create a seamless payment system native to the internet.
The firm noted that traditional payment rails, such as credit…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Martin Young</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin must hold above $95K or face short-term rejection: Bitfinex]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-price-95k-hold-short-term-rejection-bitfinex-crypto-analysts</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-price-95k-hold-short-term-rejection-bitfinex-crypto-analysts?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-07T02:45:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Key takeaways:

Bitcoin must maintain above $95,000 to have a chance at retesting its $109,000 all-time high; failure to hold could lead to a deeper correction, crypto analysts warn.

Several crypto analysts told Cointelegraph in March that Bitcoin may have a chance of reaching new all-time highs in June.

The upcoming Federal Reserve decision on May 7 could influence Bitcoin’s price movement over the coming days.

Bitcoin needs to continue to hold above the $95,000 level for a chance to climb back and retest its all-time high, or face an even deeper correction, crypto analysts say.
It comes after several analysts told Cointelegraph earlier this year that June could be the month Bitcoin (BTC) reaches new all-time highs.
“The $95,000 level — currently under consolidation — is a critical piv…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Ciaran Lyons</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Zerebro dev’s death in question as ‘proof’ surfaces on X]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/zerebro-devs-death-speculated-fake-as-proof-surfaces-x</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/zerebro-devs-death-speculated-fake-as-proof-surfaces-x?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-07T02:24:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Members of the crypto community are circulating apparent “proof” that Zerebro developer Jeffy Yu faked his suicide as he promoted his new memecoin during a Pump.fun livestream on May 4.
The belief appears to come from an unverified private letter supposedly sent by Yu to a Zerebro investor, trading activity linked to crypto wallets owned by Yu, and the removal of his obituary from Legacy.com.
Others speculate that Yu used a tool to pass off a pre-edited video as if it were filmed in real-time during the Pump.fun live stream.
The unverified letter from Yu to an early investor states that he deliberately created a livestream pretending to shoot himself as it was the only “viable exit” from persistent harassment, blackmail, threats and hate crimes.
“Being fully doxxed has placed me under cons…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Brayden Lindrea</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Democrats aim at Trump’s crypto profits with a 3-prong pincer move]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/us-senator-proposes-bill-would-prevent-trump-from-profiting-from-memecoins</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/us-senator-proposes-bill-would-prevent-trump-from-profiting-from-memecoins?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-07T02:24:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[US Democrat lawmakers have launched a multi-angle attack on President Donald Trump’s crypto ventures with two bills and a subcommittee inquiry aimed at cutting his ability to profit from the initiatives.   
The Modern Emoluments and Malfeasance Enforcement Act, or the MEME Act, aims to prevent federal officials from using their position to profit from memecoins, Democrat Senator Chris Murphy said in a May 6 statement. 
If passed, the MEME Act prohibits the president, vice president, members of Congress, senior executive branch officials, their spouses and children from issuing, sponsoring, or promoting a security, future, commodity, or digital asset, according to the bill’s description. 

Today I’m introducing a bill - the MEME Act - to ban a President or Member of Congress from issuing a …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Stephen Katte</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Races Above $97K on U.S.-China Trade Deal Progress]]></title>
        <id>b79cca00-5ab4-4bce-8e18-7f7b07263ab5</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/06/bitcoin-races-above-97k-on-uschina-trade-deal-progress"/>
        <updated>2025-05-07T00:57:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Treasury Secretary Scott Bessent is headed to Switzerland for talks with Chinese representatives.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephen Alpher</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bloat is still software's biggest vulnerability (2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://spectrum.ieee.org/lean-software-development</id>
        <link href="https://spectrum.ieee.org/lean-software-development"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T23:33:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Alignment is not free: How model upgrades can silence your confidence signals]]></title>
        <id>https://www.variance.co/post/alignment-is-not-free-how-a-model-silenced-our-confidence-signals</id>
        <link href="https://www.variance.co/post/alignment-is-not-free-how-a-model-silenced-our-confidence-signals"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T23:22:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[VVVVVV Source Code]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/TerryCavanagh/VVVVVV</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/TerryCavanagh/VVVVVV"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T23:22:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Show HN: Whippy Term - GUI terminal for embedded development (Linux and Windows)]]></title>
        <id>https://whippyterm.com/</id>
        <link href="https://whippyterm.com/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T23:02:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Senate Democrat Says He's Looking Into Trump's Crypto Businesses]]></title>
        <id>bc00aadf-da85-4d94-a4e7-f04b0fa248e2</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2025/05/06/senate-democrat-says-hes-looking-into-trumps-crypto-businesses"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T22:30:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sen. Richard Blumenthal wrote letters to Trump-affiliated business executives, asking about their ownership and investment structure.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nikhilesh De</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitwise throws spot NEAR ETF in race for SEC approval]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitwise-files-s-1-near-etf-sec-approval-s1-filing</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitwise-files-s-1-near-etf-sec-approval-s1-filing?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T22:23:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Digital asset manager Bitwise has filed to list a spot Near exchange-traded fund with the US Securities and Exchange Commission, adding to a growing list of altcoins currently vying to win regulatory approval.
The Bitwise Near (NEAR) ETF will track the price movements of the NEAR token, minus expenses, through a traditional brokerage, Bitwise’s May 6 registration statement shows.
Bitwise named Coinbase Custody as the proposed custodian of the Bitwise NEAR ETF. The management fee, ticker and stock exchange it seeks to list on weren’t named yet. 
Source: Cointelegraph
Bitwise must also file a 19b-4 filing with the SEC to kickstart the regulator's approval process for the fund. The crypto native asset manager indicated it would make such a filing when it registered a trust linked to the NEAR …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Brayden Lindrea</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS report: Generative AI overtakes security in global tech budgets for 2025]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3006670</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/aws-report-generative-ai-overtakes-security-in-global-tech-budgets-for-2025/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T21:33:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New AWS report reveals 45% of global IT leaders now prioritize generative AI over cybersecurity in 2025 tech budgets as companies race to hire AI talent and implement AI strategies despite persistent skills shortages.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Nuñez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Dominance Soars Ahead of FOMC as Volatility Burst Looms, Says Analyst]]></title>
        <id>16a745db-3737-443d-b1b5-6860e516673b</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/06/bitcoin-dominance-soars-ahead-of-fomc-as-volatility-burst-looms-says-analyst"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T21:04:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto markets are in a holding pattern as capital rotation from altcoins pushed bitcoin's market share to fresh 4-year high.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Krisztian Sandor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[US regulator moves to drop appeal against Kalshi]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/cftc-dismiss-appeal-kalshi</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/cftc-dismiss-appeal-kalshi?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T20:55:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The US Commodity Futures Trading Commission (CFTC) is seeking permission from the court to drop an appeal against prediction market Kalshi. The move could allow the platform to offer political event contracts to users without contest.
In a May 5 filing in the US Court of Appeals for the District of Columbia Circuit, lawyers for the CFTC filed an unopposed motion for voluntary dismissal, suggesting an agreement with Kalshi. 
The motion, subject to approval by the court, could end the CFTC’s appeal against a federal court ruling that the financial regulator could not bar Kalshi from listing political event contracts, i.e., bets on elections.
Motion to dismiss appeal filed by the CFTC on May 5. Source: Courtlistener
Kalshi stipulated in a joint filing that the company would “bear its own cost…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Turner Wright</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Here’s what happened in crypto today]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/what-happened-in-crypto-today</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/what-happened-in-crypto-today?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T20:48:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today in Crypto, US Democrats have launched a new assault targeting President Donald Trump’s involvement in various memecoin and crypto ventures, New Hampshire has greenlit state crypto investments and Binance founder Changpeng “CZ” Zhao forecasts Bitcoin could surge to $500,000–$1 million this cycle.
Democrats aim at Trump’s crypto profits with a 3-prong pincer move
US Democrat lawmakers have launched a multi-angle attack on President Donald Trump’s crypto ventures with two bills and a subcommittee inquiry aimed at cutting his ability to profit from the initiatives.   
The Modern Emoluments and Malfeasance Enforcement Act, or the MEME Act, aims to prevent federal officials from using their position to profit from memecoins, Democrat Senator Chris Murphy said in a May 6 statement. 

With h…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Cointelegraph</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[India launches attack on 9 sites in Pakistan and Pakistani Jammu and Kashmir]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reuters.com/world/india/india-launches-attack-9-sites-pakistan-pakistan-occupied-jammu-kashmir-2025-05-06/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reuters.com/world/india/india-launches-attack-9-sites-pakistan-pakistan-occupied-jammu-kashmir-2025-05-06/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T20:41:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Claude's system prompt is over 24k tokens with tools]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/asgeirtj/system_prompts_leaks/blob/main/claude.txt</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/asgeirtj/system_prompts_leaks/blob/main/claude.txt"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T20:39:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ACE-Step: A step towards music generation foundation model]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/ace-step/ACE-Step</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/ace-step/ACE-Step"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T20:38:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Secure Mobile APIs in Flutter]]></title>
        <id>681a707658599a397b11b418</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-secure-mobile-apis-in-flutter/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T20:26:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As mobile applications continue to evolve in functionality and scope, securing the APIs that power these apps has become more critical than ever. In the context of Flutter, a framework that enables cross-platform development, understanding how to sec...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Atuoha Anthony</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tether adds Chainalysis tokenization platform for compliance, monitoring]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/tether-adds-chainalysis-tokenization-platform-compliance-monitoring</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/tether-adds-chainalysis-tokenization-platform-compliance-monitoring?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T20:24:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tether, the issuer of the world’s largest stablecoin by market cap USDt (USDT), has announced a partnership with Chainalysis that will integrate the company’s compliance and monitoring tools onto Tether’s tokenization platform. The move comes amid expanding oversight across the crypto industry.
Launched in November 2024, the Hadron by Tether platform is designed for institutions, corporations and governments, entities that may be interested in tokenizing real-world assets ranging from financial instruments and real estate to debt and commodities.

The months following the launch have seen increased adoption of real-world asset (RWA) tokenization. According to RWA.xyz, the total RWA market amounts to $22.1 billion, up 10.5% in the past 30 days. There are a total of 100,115 holders of RWA to…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Christopher Tepedino</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FT report suggests advance knowledge of Melania Trump memecoin launch]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/report-advance-knowledge-melania-trump-memecoin</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/report-advance-knowledge-melania-trump-memecoin?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T19:53:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A group of crypto traders reportedly purchased millions of dollars worth of Melania Trump’s memecoins minutes before she announced the launch on social media.
According to a May 6 Financial Times report, the crypto traders earned roughly $100 million from buying $2.6 million worth of MELANIA tokens before the public launch on Jan. 19. Shortly after Trump announced the memecoin launch on social media, the price surged from roughly $2.00 to $12.95 — a 550% increase. The traders reportedly sold their holdings within 12 hours.
“In total, the 24 accounts bought up 16.7mn of the 200mn total $MELANIA tokens scheduled for sale during the launch period,” the Financial Times reported. “[...] the run of sales that started pre-launch continued. About $900,000 worth of tokens [were] bought by an additi…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Turner Wright</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin could rally regardless of what the Federal Reserve FOMC decides this week: Here’s why]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-could-rally-regardless-of-what-the-federal-reserve-fomc-decides-this-week-here-s-why</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-could-rally-regardless-of-what-the-federal-reserve-fomc-decides-this-week-here-s-why?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T19:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Key Takeaways:

The Fed may pause rates but inject liquidity. Crypto could rally as a recession hedge.

The weak US dollar and gold rally signal a shift to scarce assets.

The US Federal Reserve Open Market Committee (FOMC) interest rate decision on May 7 will be a defining moment for risk-on assets, including cryptocurrencies. While the consensus points to no change in interest rates, Bitcoin (BTC) and altcoins could see gains if the US Treasury is compelled to inject liquidity to stave off an economic recession.
A more accommodative monetary policy could stimulate activity, but the Federal Reserve (Fed) is also contending with a weakening US dollar. Some analysts argue that a US interest rate cut may fail to stimulate growth as recession risks persist, potentially creating an ideal envir…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Marcel Pechman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[21Shares launches ETP for Crypto.com&#039;s Cronos token]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/21-shares-launches-cronos-etp</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/21-shares-launches-cronos-etp?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T19:24:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[21Shares has launched an exchange traded product (ETP) in Europe, providing investors with exposure to Crypto.com’s Cronos token, the asset manager said. 
The ETP is listed on Euronext’s Paris and Amsterdam exchanges, 21Shares said in a May 6 announcement. 
Cronos (CRO) is a layer-1 blockchain network affiliated with Crypto.com, a centralized exchange. 
The chain is designed to integrate with the Ethereum and Cosmos ecosystems and support “decentralised finance (DeFi), NFTs, and Web3 applications,” 21Shares said. 
The ETP aims to provide investors with a “straightforward way to integrate CRO into their portfolios through traditional banks and brokers, eliminating the need to directly handle digital wallets or exchanges,” 21Shares said. 
The CRO token’s historical performance. Source: CoinM…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Alex O’Donnell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brush (Bo(u)rn(e) RUsty SHell) a POSIX and Bash-Compatible Shell in Rust]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/reubeno/brush</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/reubeno/brush"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T18:47:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin bulls rush into long positions ahead of May 7 Fed FOMC interest rate decision]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-bulls-rush-into-long-positions-ahead-of-may-7-fed-fomc-interest-rate-decision</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-bulls-rush-into-long-positions-ahead-of-may-7-fed-fomc-interest-rate-decision?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T18:44:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Key Takeaways:

Data shows Bitcoin bulls opening margin long positions from $94,400.

A $189 million increase in Bitcoin futures open interest and a 15% increase in trading volume show sustained buying interest.

BTC momentum tends to slow before FOMC meetings and then turns volatile afterward. The same could happen following this week’s Federal Reserve statements.

Bitcoin (BTC) bulls are holding strong around the $94,500 level as the market awaits the Federal Open Market Committee (FOMC) meeting on May 7. Bitcoin analyst Axel Adler Jr. noted BTC’s price strength and pointed out a bullish cluster of long positions forming around $94,400 in the futures market. A similar cluster was observed at the end of April, which pushed BTC prices to $97,500.
Bitcoin futures position dominance data. So…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Biraajmaan Tamuly</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meet the new king of AI coding: Google’s Gemini 2.5 Pro I/O Edition dethrones Claude 3.7 Sonnet]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3006623</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/meet-the-new-king-of-ai-coding-googles-gemini-2-5-pro-i-o-edition-dethrones-claude-3-7-sonnet/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T18:39:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One of the standout features of the update is its ability to build full, interactive web apps or simulations from a single prompt.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carl Franzen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Create Documentation with docs.page – A Beginner's Tutorial]]></title>
        <id>681a558b9791d0e469b84519</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-create-documentation-with-docspage/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T18:31:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One of the most tedious tasks for every startup, company, and open-source project is often building and managing documentation – especially for medium to large-scale documentation websites. docs.page is an open-source documentation tool that helps yo...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rajdeep Singh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CFTC Drops Appeal in Kalshi Election Betting Case]]></title>
        <id>85951e45-a13e-4284-bbf8-b177d7c6170e</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2025/05/06/cftc-drops-appeal-in-kalshi-election-betting-case"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T18:14:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The CFTC appealed a federal judge’s ruling last year clearing Kalshi’s listing of a political prediction market, arguing that it presented a “profound” harm to the public.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cheyenne Ligon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lightricks just made AI video generation 30x faster — and you won’t need a $10,000 GPU]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3006613</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/lightricks-just-made-ai-video-generation-30x-faster-and-you-wont-need-a-10000-gpu/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T17:56:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Lightricks unveils groundbreaking LTXV-13B AI video model that runs 30X faster than competitors on consumer hardware through innovative "multiscale rendering" technology.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Nuñez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Matt Godbolt sold me on Rust by showing me C++]]></title>
        <id>https://www.collabora.com/news-and-blog/blog/2025/05/06/matt-godbolt-sold-me-on-rust-by-showing-me-c-plus-plus/</id>
        <link href="https://www.collabora.com/news-and-blog/blog/2025/05/06/matt-godbolt-sold-me-on-rust-by-showing-me-c-plus-plus/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T17:51:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Hampshire Becomes First State to Approve Crypto Reserve Law]]></title>
        <id>859dba7b-b33d-4dab-8b80-15d692542d64</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2025/05/06/new-hampshire-becomes-first-state-to-approve-crypto-reserve-law"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T17:25:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Governor Kelly Ayotte signed a bill into law that allows the investment of a portion of the state's public funds in precious metals and crypto assets.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jesse Hamilton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ServiceNow lets users see more of their AI]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3006589</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/servicenow-lets-users-see-more-of-their-ai/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ServiceNow also announced a way for agents to communicate with others along with its new observability platform.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Emilia David</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Stabledollars: The Third Act of Dollar Reinvention]]></title>
        <id>48fcb34c-2602-47d8-80b2-989a6941b07a</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/opinion/2025/05/06/stabledollars-the-third-act-of-dollar-reinvention"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T16:39:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Blockchain-based dollar infrastructure holds enormous opportunities for the U.S. But only if it treats the technology wisely, says John deVadoss.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John deVadoss</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Planned Crypto Hearing in U.S. House Derailed by Democrat Revolt]]></title>
        <id>57b4aa63-7cac-486b-b717-dd966a2ca409</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2025/05/06/planned-crypto-hearing-in-u-s-house-derailed-by-democrat-revolt"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T16:26:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Democrats abandoned a joint hearing of two committees on crypto policy, inviting people to instead attend their own discussion of Trump's "crypto corruption."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jesse Hamilton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MARA Holdings Cut to Sell at Compass Point Ahead of Earnings, Citing Cash Burn]]></title>
        <id>ed7e6fd2-d48d-411a-8148-b9c68e8cee49</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/06/marathon-digital-downgraded-to-sell-at-compass-point-citing-unsustainable-cash-burn"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T16:20:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Compass Point slashed Marathon’s price target to $9.50, warning of dilution and premium bitcoin exposure.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Helene Braun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Launch HN: Exa (YC S21) – The web as a database]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=43906841</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=43906841"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T16:18:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build Your Own Local AI: Create Free RAG and AI Agents with Qwen 3 and Ollama]]></title>
        <id>681a35d4d5da806f5e9467b1</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-a-local-ai/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T16:16:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The landscape of Artificial Intelligence is rapidly evolving, and one of the most exciting trends is the ability to run powerful Large Language Models (LLMs) directly on your local machine. This shift away from reliance on cloud-based APIs offers sig...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chaitanya Rahalkar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Create Serverless AI Agents with Langbase Docs MCP Server in Minutes]]></title>
        <id>681a2ce0aebfc718f4e6da03</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-create-serverless-ai-agents-with-langbase-docs-mcp-server-in-minutes/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T15:38:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Building serverless AI agents has recently become a lot simpler. With the Langbase Docs MCP server, you can instantly connect AI models to Langbase documentation – making it easy to build composable, agentic AI systems with memory without complex inf...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maham Codes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gemini 2.5 Pro Preview]]></title>
        <id>https://developers.googleblog.com/en/gemini-2-5-pro-io-improved-coding-performance/</id>
        <link href="https://developers.googleblog.com/en/gemini-2-5-pro-io-improved-coding-performance/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T15:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Show HN: Clippy – 90s UI for local LLMs]]></title>
        <id>https://felixrieseberg.github.io/clippy/</id>
        <link href="https://felixrieseberg.github.io/clippy/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T15:02:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ECB Establishes Innovation Hub to Test Digital Euro as Preparation Phase Nears End]]></title>
        <id>932c193f-a0e2-4908-9e44-fef4f3800a40</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2025/05/06/ecb-establishes-innovation-hub-to-test-digital-euro-as-preparation-phase-nears-end"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T14:51:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The hub has 70 participants including Accenture, KPMG and CaixaBank.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Camomile Shumba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DeFi Development Adds $11.2M in SOL, Bringing Holdings to More Than 400K Tokens]]></title>
        <id>d4cf9af1-e8ad-4a42-abfd-57df47608336</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/06/defi-development-adds-usd11-2m-in-sol-bringing-holdings-to-more-than-400k-tokens"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T14:47:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Formerly known as Janover, the company's SOL holdings are worth more than $57 million at current prices.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Francisco Rodrigues</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Report: OpenAI is buying AI-powered developer platform Windsurf — what happens to its support for rival LLMs?]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3006587</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/report-openai-is-buying-ai-powered-developer-platform-windsurf-what-happens-to-its-support-for-rival-llms/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T14:37:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[OpenAI could see which types of developers use rival models such as the Meta Llama variants and Anthropic's Claude, and for what purposes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carl Franzen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Will Crypto Values Survive the Regulatory Wave?]]></title>
        <id>74e3106c-868a-4cdc-9407-092818a1a538</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/opinion/2025/05/06/will-crypto-values-survive-the-regulatory-wave"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T14:32:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ahead of the People’s Regulatory Roundtable at Consensus 2025, six leading crypto lawyers discuss whether core crypto principles, like decentralization and privacy, will be included in upcoming legislation and regulation.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ivo Entchev</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trump's Crypto Play Fuels Senators' Backlash and Bill to Ban President Memecoins]]></title>
        <id>b95b85bc-3f1c-4cbf-abca-23b1e9859ea5</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2025/05/06/trump-s-crypto-play-fuels-senators-backlash-and-bill-to-ban-president-memecoins"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T14:30:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Democratic Senator Chris Murphy pushed a bill to block presidential coins while Elizabeth Warren described how to get Dems to move forward on stablecoins.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jesse Hamilton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SOL Strategies Buys $18M of Solana Tokens With First Tranche of $500M Note Deal]]></title>
        <id>8522ebda-a761-4edd-aea5-0d8800e95e62</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/06/sol-strategies-buys-18m-of-solana-tokens-with-first-tranche-of-500m-note-deal"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T14:25:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Canadian firm is betting on Solana by using debt financing to scale its validator footprint and crypto holdings.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Krisztian Sandor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[VanEck Submits Proposal to Launch First BNB ETF in the U.S.]]></title>
        <id>96cfffe4-6b3a-45f5-8f4e-733208bd4e43</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2025/05/06/vaneck-submits-proposal-to-launch-first-bnb-etf-in-the-u-s"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T14:15:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If approved, the fund would be the first exchange-traded fund tied to BNB in the U.S.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Helene Braun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Accents in latent spaces: How AI hears accent strength in English]]></title>
        <id>https://accent-strength.boldvoice.com/</id>
        <link href="https://accent-strength.boldvoice.com/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T14:07:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Startup Korl unveils multimodal, multi-agent tool for custom communication across disparate systems]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3006451</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/how-openai-gemini-and-anthropic-help-korl-prepare-customer-materials-in-minutes/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Korl's platform works across multiple systems, using multi-agent and multimodal AI to create highly-customized customer messaging.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Taryn Plumb</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nnd – a TUI debugger alternative to GDB, LLDB]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/al13n321/nnd</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/al13n321/nnd"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T13:58:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ōura adds AI-driven meal and glucose tracking features with Stelo by Dexcom]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3006449</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/games/oura-adds-ai-driven-meal-and-glucose-tracking-features-with-stelo-by-dexcom/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ōura, maker of a health-monitoring smart ring, announced that it will use AI to track and analyze two new metabolic health features: meals and glucose.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dean Takahashi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cuttlefish 'talk' with their arms, study reveals]]></title>
        <id>https://scienceblog.com/wildscience/2025/05/06/cuttlefish-talk-with-their-arms-study-reveals/</id>
        <link href="https://scienceblog.com/wildscience/2025/05/06/cuttlefish-talk-with-their-arms-study-reveals/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T12:46:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Download: a longevity influencer’s new religion, and humanoid robots’ shortcomings]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1116114</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/05/06/1116114/the-download-a-longevity-influencers-new-religion-and-humanoid-robots-shortcomings/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T12:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is today’s edition of The Download, our weekday newsletter that provides a daily dose of what’s going on in the world of technology. Bryan Johnson wants to start a new religion in which “the body is God” Bryan Johnson is on a mission to not die. The 47-year-old multimillionaire has already applied his slogan “Don’t Die”…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rhiannon Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why the humanoid workforce is running late]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1116108</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/05/06/1116108/why-the-humanoid-workforce-is-running-late/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On Thursday I watched Daniela Rus, one of the world’s top experts on AI-powered robots, address a packed room at a Boston robotics expo. Rus spent a portion of her talk busting the notion that giant fleets of humanoids are already making themselves useful in manufacturing and warehouses around the world.  That might come as…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>James O'Donnell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Join the 2025 Web3j Mentorships: Build the Future of Ethereum on the JVM]]></title>
        <id>6819c8dc41eeeb000183d37b</id>
        <link href="https://blog.web3labs.com/join-the-2025-web3j-mentorships-build-the-future-of-ethereum-on-the-jvm/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T08:32:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Linux Foundation’s Decentralized Trust (LFDT) mentorship program is back in 2025 with two exciting opportunities for developers passionate about Ethereum, Android, and the Java Virtual Machine (JVM). Whether you’re a seasoned blockchain developer or an Android enthusiast eager to dive into Web3, these mentorships offer]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>George Tebrean</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DoorDash to acquire Deliveroo]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cnbc.com/2025/05/06/doordash-to-buy-uk-food-delivery-firm-deliveroo-in-3point9-billion-deal.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.cnbc.com/2025/05/06/doordash-to-buy-uk-food-delivery-firm-deliveroo-in-3point9-billion-deal.html"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T06:27:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[IBM thinks that over a billion new applications will be built with gen AI : Here’s how they’re going to help that happen with agentic AI]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3006455</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/agents-are-key-to-enterprise-ai-success-heres-ibms-plan-on-how-to-make-it-happen/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T04:01:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[IBM details its plans to help enterprises to actually do more with AI, with an expanded set of agentic AI capabilities.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sean Michael Kerner</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OpenAI reaches agreement to buy Windsurf for $3B]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2025-05-06/openai-reaches-agreement-to-buy-startup-windsurf-for-3-billion</id>
        <link href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2025-05-06/openai-reaches-agreement-to-buy-startup-windsurf-for-3-billion"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T00:57:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meta, Cisco put open-source LLMs at the core of next-gen SOC workflows]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3006384</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/rsac-2025-cisco-and-meta-put-open-source-ai-at-the-heart-of-enterprise-threat-defense/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T00:08:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cisco’s Foundation-sec-8B LLM & Meta’s AI Defenders redefine cybersecurity with open-source AI for scalable SOCs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Louis Columbus</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[docker2exe: Convert a Docker image to an executable]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/rzane/docker2exe</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/rzane/docker2exe"/>
        <updated>2025-05-05T20:47:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nvidia launches fully open source transcription AI model Parakeet-TDT-0.6B-V2 on Hugging Face]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3006438</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/nvidia-launches-fully-open-source-transcription-ai-model-parakeet-tdt-0-6b-v2-on-hugging-face/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-05T19:17:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An attractive proposition for commercial enterprises and indie developers looking to build speech recognition and transcription services...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carl Franzen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Improve Your C++ Skills by Coding an Audio Plugin]]></title>
        <id>68190b8f1abafc5ea9d7efbf</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/improve-you-c-skills-by-coding-an-audio-plugin/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-05T19:03:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Do you want to build a practical project to help improve your C++ skills? Have you ever wanted to create your own unique audio effects? Then diving into C++ audio plugin development with the JUCE framework might be your next great step We just publis...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Visa launches ‘Intelligent Commerce’ platform, letting AI agents swipe your card—safely, it says]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3006416</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/visa-launches-intelligent-commerce-platform-letting-ai-agents-swipe-your-card-safely-it-says/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-05T18:01:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Visa launches Intelligent Commerce platform enabling AI assistants to make secure purchases with your credit card, transforming online shopping with personalized automation and consumer-controlled spending limits.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Nuñez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build a Dynamic Wardrobe App with React Drag and Drop]]></title>
        <id>6818d1793c6be4514080aea9</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-build-a-dynamic-wardrobe-app-with-react-drag-and-drop/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-05T14:55:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Have you ever found yourself stuck deciding what color outfit to wear? Maybe you’re mixing and matching different tops and bottoms, unsure if the colors go together. It’s a common dilemma – so common that many of us turn to friends or family for a se...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Timothy Olanrewaju</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Simulating, Detecting and Responding to S3 Ransomware Attacks]]></title>
        <id>https://raphabot.com/articles/simulating-detecting-and-responding-s3-ransomware/</id>
        <link href="https://raphabot.com/articles/simulating-detecting-and-responding-s3-ransomware/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-05T14:46:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bryan Johnson wants to start a new religion in which “the body is God”]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1116090</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/05/05/1116090/bryan-johnson-new-religion-body-is-god/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-05T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bryan Johnson is on a mission to not die. The 47-year-old multimillionaire has already applied his slogan “Don’t Die” to events, merchandise, and a Netflix documentary. Now he’s founding a Don’t Die religion. Johnson, who famously spends millions of dollars on scans, tests, supplements, and a lifestyle routine designed to slow or reverse the aging…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jessica Hamzelou</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The World Of dBASE (1984) [video]]]></title>
        <id>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=bYU3CQomE5M</id>
        <link href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=bYU3CQomE5M"/>
        <updated>2025-05-04T17:56:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WebMonkeys: parallel GPU programming in JavaScript]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/VictorTaelin/WebMonkeys</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/VictorTaelin/WebMonkeys"/>
        <updated>2025-05-04T17:00:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The great cognitive migration: How AI is reshaping human purpose, work and meaning]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3006326</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/the-great-cognitive-migration-ai-will-win-at-intelligence-but-only-we-can-make-it-matter/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-04T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Humans need to embrace domains where AI still falters, and where human creativity, ethics and emotion emain indispensable.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gary Grossman, Edelman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Old Timey Code and Old Timey Mono Fonts]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/dse/old-timey-mono-font</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/dse/old-timey-mono-font"/>
        <updated>2025-05-04T04:10:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Not everything needs an LLM: A framework for evaluating when AI makes sense]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3006312</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/not-everything-needs-an-llm-a-framework-for-evaluating-when-ai-makes-sense/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-03T19:35:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The answer to 'What customer needs requires an AI solution?' isn’t always 'Yes.' LLMs are still expensive and not always accurate.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sharanya Rao</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[RSAC 2025: Why the AI agent era means more demand for CISOs]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3006066</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/security/rsac-2025-why-the-ai-agent-era-means-more-demand-for-cisos/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-02T23:02:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[RSAC 2025 made one thing clear: AI agents are entering security workflows, but boards want proof they work.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Louis Columbus</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Write Good API Documentation]]></title>
        <id>68151f0be5850fcb8543375a</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-write-good-api-docs/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-02T19:37:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Imagine purchasing a standing fan straight out of the box, all parts dismantled, and you have no manual or guide to put them together. Did you imagine that just now? Cool. Here is another scenario: imagine purchasing an LG product, such as a smart TV...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Okoro Emmanuel Nzube</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OpenAI overrode concerns of expert testers to release sycophantic GPT-4o]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3006276</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/openai-overrode-concerns-of-expert-testers-to-release-sycophantic-gpt-4o/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-02T17:57:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Once again, it shows the importance of incorporating more domains beyond the traditional math and computer science into AI development.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carl Franzen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use SonarQube to Improve Your Code Quality]]></title>
        <id>6815023dec2e34790eeb71a8</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-improve-your-code-quality-with-sonarqube/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-02T17:34:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SonarQube is a powerful open-source tool that helps you maintain code quality and security by analyzing your codebase for bugs and vulnerabilities. And it can play a major role when integrated into your CI/CD pipeline. In this tutorial, we will cover...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Divya Valsala Saratchandran</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn Kubernetes – Full Handbook for Developers, Startups, and Businesses]]></title>
        <id>68150214fd424d0874293171</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-kubernetes-handbook-devs-startups-businesses/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-02T17:34:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You’ve probably heard the word Kubernetes floating around, or it’s cooler nickname k8s (pronounced “kates“). Maybe in a job post, a tech podcast, or from that one DevOps friend who always brings it up like it’s the secret sauce to everything 😅. It s...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Prince Onukwili</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Roblox breaks ground on data center in Brazil for early 2026]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3006251</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/games/roblox-breaks-ground-on-data-center-in-brazil-for-early-2026/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-02T16:55:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At Gamescom Latam, Roblox announced it has broken ground on a new data center in Brazil -- slated to go live in early 2026.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dean Takahashi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[From Art School Drop-out to Microsoft Engineer with Shashi Lo [Podcast #170]]]></title>
        <id>6814f2ab33857abe499038b0</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/from-art-school-drop-out-to-microsoft-engineer-with-shashi-lo-podcast-170/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-02T16:28:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On this week's episode of the podcast, I interview Shashi Lo. He's a software engineer at Microsoft. He grew up the child of refugees. He wanted to start earning money and build his family so he abandoned his art school degree and taught himself how ...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Quincy Larson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Download: foreign disinformation intel, and gene-edited pork]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1116079</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/05/02/1116079/the-download-foreign-disinformation-intel-and-gene-edited-pork/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-02T12:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is today’s edition of The Download, our weekday newsletter that provides a daily dose of what’s going on in the world of technology. A senior State Department official demanded records of communications with journalists, European officials, and Trump critics A previously unreported document distributed by senior US State Department official Darren Beattie reveals a sweeping effort…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rhiannon Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The US has approved CRISPR pigs for food]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1116059</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/05/02/1116059/the-us-approves-crispr-pigs-for-food/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-02T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Most pigs in the US are confined to factory farms where they can be afflicted by a nasty respiratory virus that kills piglets. The illness is called porcine reproductive and respiratory syndrome, or PRRS. A few years ago, a British company called Genus set out to design pigs immune to this germ using CRISPR gene…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Antonio Regalado</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hidden costs in AI deployment: Why Claude models may be 20-30% more expensive than GPT in enterprise settings]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3006096</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/hidden-costs-in-ai-deployment-why-claude-models-may-be-20-30-more-expensive-than-gpt-in-enterprise-settings/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-01T20:14:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It is a well-known fact that different model families can use different tokenizers. However, there has been limited analysis on how the process of “tokenization” itself varies across these tokenizers. Do all tokenizers result in the same number of tokens for a given input text? If not, how different are the generated tokens? How significant […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lavanya Gupta</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Senior State Department official sought internal communications with journalists, European officials, and Trump critics]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1115988</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/05/01/1115988/senior-state-department-official-sought-internal-communications-with-journalists-european-officials-and-trump-critics/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-01T17:41:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A previously unreported document distributed by senior US State Department official Darren Beattie reveals a sweeping effort to uncover all communications between the staff of a small government office focused on online disinformation and a lengthy list of public and private figures—many of whom are longtime targets of the political right.  The document, originally shared…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eileen Guo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Astronomer’s $93M raise underscores a new reality: Orchestration is king in AI infrastructure]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3006195</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/astronomer-93m-raise-underscores-a-new-reality-orchestration-is-king-in-ai-infrastructure/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-01T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Astronomer secures $93 million in Series D funding to solve the AI implementation gap through data orchestration, helping enterprises streamline complex workflows and operationalize AI initiatives at scale.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Nuñez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft launches Phi-4-Reasoning-Plus, a small, powerful, open weights reasoning model!]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3006213</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/microsoft-launches-phi-4-reasoning-plus-a-small-powerful-open-weights-reasoning-model/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-01T12:41:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The release demonstrates that with carefully curated data and training techniques, small models can deliver strong reasoning performance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carl Franzen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Download: China’s energy throwback, and choosing between love and immortality]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1115999</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/05/01/1115999/the-download-chinas-energy-throwback-and-choosing-between-love-and-immortality/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-01T12:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is today’s edition of The Download, our weekday newsletter that provides a daily dose of what’s going on in the world of technology. A long-abandoned US nuclear technology is making a comeback in China China has once again beat everyone else to a clean energy milestone—its new nuclear reactor is reportedly one of the first to…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rhiannon Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Salesforce takes aim at ‘jagged intelligence’ in push for more reliable AI]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3006124</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/salesforce-tackles-jagged-intelligence-problem-with-new-ai-benchmarks-and-models/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-01T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Salesforce unveils groundbreaking AI research tackling "jagged intelligence," introducing new benchmarks, models, and guardrails to make enterprise AI agents more intelligent, trusted, and consistently reliable for business use.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Nuñez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A long-abandoned US nuclear technology is making a comeback in China]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1115957</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/05/01/1115957/old-new-nuclear-technology/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-01T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[China has once again beat everyone else to a clean energy milestone—its new nuclear reactor is reportedly one of the first to use thorium instead of uranium as a fuel and the first of its kind that can be refueled while it’s running. It’s an interesting (if decidedly experimental) development out of a country that’s…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Casey Crownhart</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[UiPath’s new orchestrator guides AI agents to follow your enterprise’s rules]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3006059</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/uipaths-new-orchestrator-guides-ai-agents-to-follow-your-enterprises-rules/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T21:20:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[UiPath's agent orchestration layer Maestro moves prompts through three layers: the agent, a human and the robotic process automation system.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Emilia David</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The ‘era of experience’ will unleash self-learning AI agents across the web—here’s how to prepare]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3005579</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/the-era-of-experience-will-unleash-self-learning-ai-agents-across-the-web-heres-how-to-prepare/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T20:38:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AI visionaries predict an 'Era of Experience' where AI learns autonomously, and it will have important implications for application design.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ben Dickson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Qwen swings for a double with 2.5-Omni-3B model that runs on consumer PCs, laptops]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3006114</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/qwen-swings-for-a-double-with-2-5-omni-3b-model-that-runs-on-consumer-pcs-laptops/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T20:31:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Qwen2.5-Omni-3B model is licensed for non-commercial use only under Alibaba Cloud’s Qwen Research License Agreement.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carl Franzen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Breaking the ‘intellectual bottleneck’: How AI is computing the previously uncomputable in healthcare]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3005667</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/breaking-the-intellectual-bottleneck-how-ai-is-computing-the-previously-uncomputible-in-healthcare/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T19:03:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How University of Texas Medical Branch is using AI to identify patients at high cardiovascular risk, flag for stroke and catch 'basic stuff.']]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Taryn Plumb</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OpenAI rolls back ChatGPT’s sycophancy and explains what went wrong]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3006053</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/openai-rolls-back-chatgpts-sycophancy-and-explains-what-went-wrong/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T15:14:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Many organizations may also begin shifting toward open-source alternatives that they can host and tune themselves.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carl Franzen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Structify raises $4.1M seed to turn unstructured web data into enterprise-ready datasets]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3006010</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/structify-raises-4-1m-seed-to-turn-unstructured-web-data-into-enterprise-ready-datasets/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Brooklyn-based Structify emerges from stealth with $4.1 million in seed funding to transform how businesses prepare data for AI, promising to save data scientists from the task that consumes 80% of their time.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Nuñez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Web3j Six Month Project Update]]></title>
        <id>68109495670a1300013504c2</id>
        <link href="https://blog.web3labs.com/web3j-six-month-project-update/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T09:10:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[November 2024 - April 2025
This report summarizes the activities and accomplishments of Web3j, an LF Decentralized Trust project, from November 2024 to April 2025. During this period, the project made significant strides in improving the framework’s functionality, enhancing user engagement, and bolstering overall community interaction. 
Key]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>George Tebrean</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[QuickNode: Building the Infrastructure for the Next Generation of Blockchain]]></title>
        <id>6807d5787fb8500001c39b99</id>
        <link href="https://blog.quicknode.com/quicknode-building-the-infrastructure-for-the-next-generation-of-blockchain/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-28T16:02:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Join QuickNode co-founder Dmitry Shklovsky as he discusses blockchain infrastructure, building decentralized applications, and the future of Web3 development on TheCube's Crypto Trailblazer Series.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>QuickNode</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>