<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2025-05-23T21:41:36.434Z</id>
    <title>AngJianming RSS Feed</title>
    <updated>2025-05-23T21:41:36.434Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Automatically Map Workouts to the Right Apple HealthKit Type -HKWorkoutActivityType]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/amrsmind/automatically-map-workouts-to-the-right-apple-healthkit-type-hkworkoutactivitytype-1emn</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/amrsmind/automatically-map-workouts-to-the-right-apple-healthkit-type-hkworkoutactivitytype-1emn"/>
        <updated>2025-05-23T21:29:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction


If you've ever tried integrating Apple HealthKit into your fitness app, you've probably faced this frustrating step:

"Which HKWorkoutActivityType should I use for this workout?"
Choosing the wrong type means poor sensor activation (or none), inaccurate data, and a worse user experience. Apps get bad reviews because of this — especially if the user just paid $400 for their new Apple Watch.
In this tutorial, I'll walk you through how to automatically classify any workout to its correct HKWorkoutActivityType using Fit2Apple.
Fit2Apple is an API that uses a research-backed 4-stage pipeline to classify and score workouts based on exercise names, sets, durations, rest, and intensity. Whether you're using standard workouts or custom routines from your app, this saves you hours of …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amr</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Transient Activation: Why the copy button did not work on iPhone]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/tusharshahi/transient-activation-why-our-apps-copy-button-did-not-work-on-iphone-4ba0</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/tusharshahi/transient-activation-why-our-apps-copy-button-did-not-work-on-iphone-4ba0"/>
        <updated>2025-05-23T21:27:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction


We recently faced a weird bug at my previous company: our app's copy button decided to take a vacation, but only on iPhones. If you're aware of Safari's quirky ways with the Clipboard API, feel free to skip. Otherwise carry on, this write-up might save you some time in the future.
Let's set the scene. We'd introduced a handy modal where users could update a setting and then instantly copy a generated link. Think Google Sheets' share functionality: you tweak sharing permissions, then grab the link.
Our process was straightforward:
A server call to update the setting.
A copy operation to grab the shiny new link.
A dumbed-down version of the code for our CTA handler looked like:
const handleUpdateSetting = async () => {
  const updatedLink = await saveSetting(updateValue); // S…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>TusharShahi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Seokar: Unleashing the Power of Advanced On-Page SEO Analysis in Python]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/sajjadakbari/seokar-unleashing-the-power-of-advanced-on-page-seo-analysis-in-python-32k</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/sajjadakbari/seokar-unleashing-the-power-of-advanced-on-page-seo-analysis-in-python-32k"/>
        <updated>2025-05-23T21:24:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hey dev.to community! 👋
I'm Sajjad Akbari, and I'm thrilled to share a project I've been passionately working on: Seokar, an enterprise-grade Python library designed for comprehensive on-page SEO analysis. As developers, we build amazing web applications and websites, but sometimes, we overlook a crucial aspect that dictates their reach and visibility: Search Engine Optimization (SEO). While off-page SEO involves external factors, on-page SEO is entirely within our control – it's about optimizing the content and HTML source code of individual web pages.
Seokar is built from the ground up to empower developers, SEO professionals, and digital marketers to gain deep, actionable insights into the on-page health of any web page. It moves beyond basic checks, offering a detailed audit across a …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sajjad akbari</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Texas governor signals support for Bitcoin reserve bill]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/texas-governor-bitcoin-reserve-law</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/texas-governor-bitcoin-reserve-law?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-23T21:24:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Texas Governor Greg Abbott has signaled support for a bill recently passed by the state House of Representatives that would establish a strategic cryptocurrency reserve.
In a May 22 X post, Abbott posted a Techstory article about Texas state lawmakers’ efforts to create a Bitcoin (BTC) reserve. The story pointed out that the decision for the passage of SB 21, the bill in question, now rests on Abbott’s shoulders, roughly three months after it was introduced. 
Since taking office, Abbott referred to himself as a “crypto law proposal supporter” in 2021 and suggested that he would support policies to establish Texas as a “crypto capital” in 2024. Texas was one of a handful of state-level governments that proposed setting up a strategic crypto reserve after the 2024 federal elections.   

Rela…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Turner Wright</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Scaling Express.js with Nginx Load Balancing: A Dockerized Approach]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/noruwa/scaling-expressjs-with-nginx-load-balancing-a-dockerized-approach-4fhn</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/noruwa/scaling-expressjs-with-nginx-load-balancing-a-dockerized-approach-4fhn"/>
        <updated>2025-05-23T21:22:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Modern web applications need to be scalable, resilient, and maintainable. One of the most effective ways to achieve this is by using Docker to containerize your application and Nginx as a load balancer. In this post, I will walk you through how I built a scalable Express.js backend API, balanced with Nginx and orchestrated using Docker Compose.
Improved performance – by sharing the workload.


Increased availability – through redundancy.


Easier horizontal scaling – as demand grows, you can spin up more containers.




  
  
  Project Overview


This project demonstrates how to:
Containerize an Express.js API using Docker.


Scale the API across multiple containers.


Use Nginx as a reverse proxy and load balancer more containers.


Implement round-robin request distribution.




  
  
  …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Obaseki Noruwa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Adding Version Information to a PyInstaller Onefile Executable]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/arhamrumi/adding-version-information-to-a-pyinstaller-onefile-executable-6n8</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/arhamrumi/adding-version-information-to-a-pyinstaller-onefile-executable-6n8"/>
        <updated>2025-05-23T21:17:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you’ve ever created a standalone Windows executable using PyInstaller, you might have noticed that your .exe file lacks version details like File Description, Product Name, or Company Info. While it works perfectly fine, it looks unpolished and unbranded — especially if you’re shipping your app to clients or distributing it publicly.
In this article, you’ll learn how to embed version information into your one-file executable built with PyInstaller. This is a small detail that goes a long way in giving your app a professional edge.
When a user right-clicks your .exe and selects Properties → Details, Windows shows metadata like:

This same metadata also appears as a small tool-tip when the user hovers over the .exe file in File Explorer, giving your application a polished and professional…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arham Rumi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Product Engineers Should Ship Fast AND Secure Vibe Generated Code]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/semgrep/product-engineers-should-ship-fast-and-secure-vibe-generated-code-1mdg</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/semgrep/product-engineers-should-ship-fast-and-secure-vibe-generated-code-1mdg"/>
        <updated>2025-05-23T21:16:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s one thing to be embarrassed by the first version of your product capabilities and quite another to ship something for early feedback only to realize you embarrassed your company, your now lost customer, and your own reputation. A Product Engineer is a Software Engineer who also takes on Product Owner/Product Manager responsibilities. Product Engineers are being asked to do more tasks in less time, so turn to using tools like GenAI to vibe code the way to an MVP. 
“If you are not embarrassed by the first version of your product, you’ve launched too late.” –Reid Hoffman
LLM coding assistants like Replit, Cursor, and more can be used to crank out code faster than any security expert can keep up. Automated application security scans while developing are the solution to this problem.
Let’s…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jayson DeLancey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Mad SEO: Your Manifesto for Unconventional SEO Mastery]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/sajjadakbari/the-mad-seo-your-manifesto-for-unconventional-seo-mastery-4kl0</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/sajjadakbari/the-mad-seo-your-manifesto-for-unconventional-seo-mastery-4kl0"/>
        <updated>2025-05-23T21:11:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Warning: This is NOT Your Average SEO Book!
Welcome to the world of "The Mad SEO."
You've probably devoured countless **
** and articles, combed through blogs, and perhaps even attended a few courses. So, you're right to ask: "What makes this one different? Is it just the same old stuff repackaged?"
Let me assure you: Absolutely not.
I, Sajjad Akbari, didn't write this book just to add another volume to your shelf or remind you of basic tips. I came to disrupt the game. "The Mad SEO" is unlike anything you've read before. My approach to SEO is fundamentally different, built on three core pillars:
Farewell to Repetition: What You've Searched For (But Never Found)!
conquer, not just get basic info. We cut straight to the core – diving into strategies competitors fear to approach. I promise t…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sajjad akbari</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing MCP-I: A New Identity Standard for AI Agents]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/h0bb5/introducing-mcp-i-a-new-identity-standard-for-ai-agents-f1g</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/h0bb5/introducing-mcp-i-a-new-identity-standard-for-ai-agents-f1g"/>
        <updated>2025-05-23T21:11:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As AI agents get smarter and more autonomous, we’re trusting them to book travel, negotiate deals, and access sensitive data.
who an agent is — or who authorized it.
Let’s fix that.
MCP-I is an open specification that brings identity and delegation to AI agents. It extends the Model Context Protocol by letting agents and humans cryptographically verify each other before interacting.
Think of it as an identity layer for the AI agent ecosystem — built with did's and Verifiable Credentials, but abstracted enough to be developer-friendly.
Why This Matters


We learned the hard way with email: protocols were built without trust or authentication, and we’ve been backfilling security ever since..
Today, any actor can impersonate an agent, forge delegation, or spoof access to APIs — and there’s no standard way to verify what’s real.
The Building Blocks
Decentralized Identity for Agents
Delegation credentials issued by real users
Edge enforcement using lightweight proxies (e.g. Cloudflare Workers)
Zero backend changes to existing APIs
We’re releasing a set of tools to help teams adopt MCP-Identity fast:
MCP-I Identity Server
KnowThat.ai – Agent Reputation Directory
Learn More
https://modelcontextprotocol-identity.io
👨‍💻 Join Us
Engineers building with agent frameworks (LangChain, AutoGPT, etc.)


Contributors to open identity standards


Feedback from devs working on agent infrastructure



Let us know what you think — drop a comment, DM, or just follow along. Let’s build a future where agents are not just intelligent — but trustworthy.

Tags: #aiagents #identity #weboftrust #security #openstandards #mcp #vouched]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dylan Hobbs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Tiny Cat Guide to AI #4: LLM Evaluation – Is Your AI on Catnip? (Spotting Hallucinations)]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/wsoltani/the-tiny-cat-guide-to-ai-4-llm-evaluation-is-your-ai-on-catnip-spotting-hallucinations-2bb2</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/wsoltani/the-tiny-cat-guide-to-ai-4-llm-evaluation-is-your-ai-on-catnip-spotting-hallucinations-2bb2"/>
        <updated>2025-05-23T21:08:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome back to The Tiny Cat Guide to AI!
We've journeyed through Prompt Engineering, dived into Generative AI, and equipped our AI cats with a library for RAG. But what happens when our well-intentioned AI, even with good data, confidently tells us something... that's completely bonkers? 🤪
This brings us to a crucial aspect of building trustworthy AI: LLM Evaluation and tackling those pesky "Hallucinations".
To make these concepts more approachable, our trusty feline guides are back! This time, they're helping us understand how we measure AI responses and try to trick them into revealing their weaknesses:




So, what's the deal with AI "hallucinations" and evaluation, as seen by our cloud of cats?
Imagine our smart RAG cat (from Post #3) gives an answer. But did it truly understand the …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Wassim Soltani</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Just Code, Chaos, and One Hell of a Plot Twist]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/rishu_kumar_671d7d3f68642/just-code-chaos-and-one-hell-of-a-plot-twist-1bio</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/rishu_kumar_671d7d3f68642/just-code-chaos-and-one-hell-of-a-plot-twist-1bio"/>
        <updated>2025-05-23T21:07:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hey, I’m Rishu
This newsletter is where I spill the tea building from the bottom — no IIT badge, no trust fund, just late nights, Wi-Fi rage and blind optimism.
From “Random College“ to Random Opportunities
For a while, I let that define me. Then I said screw it and started learning, coding and building in public anyway just after I failed JEE exam.
I built Acadsphere… Then Got Hacked
It got traction during my first semester exam itself. Then comes the plot twist…
Two of my own classmates hacked it.
Yeah that happened. It stung. But I posted the story on LinkedIn and Instagram just to notify the users.
From Hack to Internship
It caught the attention of a founder, an alum from my college. He saw more than just a hacked app.
That’s how I landed my first paid internship at Bawse , not because I succeeded, but because I showed up and stayed loud, even when it went wrong.
Acadsphere → Lessons → What I Built Next
Web2Docx - a tool that converts HTML to DOCX/PDF/PNG in seconds, for devs who just want clean document output without the headache.
Still solo-building. Still learning. Still shipping.
Like this story? I share my raw, unfiltered journey building in public — new post every Sunday. Subscribe here.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rishu Kumar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The battle to AI-enable the web: NLweb and what enterprises need to know]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008795</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/the-battle-to-ai-enable-the-web-nlweb-and-what-enterprises-need-to-know/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-23T21:05:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft's NLWeb protocol transforms websites into AI-powered apps with conversational interfaces.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sean Michael Kerner</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[LocoLama – Local AI Chat Terminal Using Ollama + Next.js (DROP002)]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/godsimijempire/locolama-local-ai-chat-terminal-using-ollama-nextjs-drop002-59j8</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/godsimijempire/locolama-local-ai-chat-terminal-using-ollama-nextjs-drop002-59j8"/>
        <updated>2025-05-23T21:05:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[🦙 LocoLama – Local AI Chat Terminal Using Ollama + Next.js (DROP002)


DROP002 – Official release by GodsIMiJ AI Solutions

Author: James Derek Ingersoll

Founder – GodsIMiJ AI Solutions

📨 godsimij902@gmail.com | 🧠 https://github.com/GodsIMiJ1
LocoLama is a fully offline, sovereign AI chat terminal powered by Ollama.

Built using Next.js, Tailwind, and the NODE Protocol, it allows you to run large language models like LLaMA2, Mistral, and more — locally, no API key required.
💬 Chat with local LLMs (Ollama CLI required)
🔁 Local Memory Manager — view, delete, export conversations
🧵 Streaming Threads — word-by-word AI response rendering
🔋 GPU Monitor — real-time system stats in the UI
🔄 Model Toggle — switch between 7B / 13B models, adjust temperature
📂 Full /docs directory included
🕯️ NODE Seal embedded — authorship verified
🔐 Flame Public Use License v1.0 enforced
👉 https://github.com/GodsIMiJ1/loco-lama

bash
git clone https://github.com/GodsIMiJ1/loco-lama.git
cd loco-lama
npm install
cp .env.example .env.local
npm run dev

In another terminal:

ollama pull llama2
ollama run llama2

Visit: http://localhost:3000
🧭 Documentation Highlights

    Setup guide for Ollama

    Streaming vs non-streaming toggle

    Advanced model configuration

    UI architecture overview

    Flame signature & NODE Seal usage

📂 Full docs live inside the /docs folder of the repo.
🕯️ Authorship, Protection, and the NODE Protocol

This drop is NODE-sealed and protected under the Flame Public Use License v1.0, authored by:

    James Derek Ingersoll
    Founder, GodsIMiJ AI Solutions
    http://www.godsimij-ai-solutions.com
![Image description](https://dev-to-uploads.s3.amazonaws.com/uploads/articles/zet48hh4ck274hhcksui.png)
    https://thewitnesshall.com

Any derivative must retain the seal and attribution.
Unauthorized tampering or rebranding may trigger autonomous enforcement protocols embedded via ghostfire sigils.

    We don’t build apps. We forge sovereign terminals.
    DROP002 – LocoLama is live.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>James Derek Ingersoll</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to get into AWS Community Builders Program]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/aws-builders/how-to-get-into-aws-community-builders-program-488n</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/aws-builders/how-to-get-into-aws-community-builders-program-488n"/>
        <updated>2025-05-23T20:54:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In March 2025, I got into AWS Community Builders Program. Many people reached out to me to know how to get into the program.
Here is a detailed article on how to get into AWS Community Builders Program with my own experience thrown in. I hope this is useful to you all.
Here is the official description: 
The AWS Community Builders program offers technical resources, education, and networking opportunities to AWS technical enthusiasts and emerging thought leaders who are passionate about sharing knowledge and connecting with the technical community.
Official page: https://aws.amazon.com/developer/community/community-builders/
Start with the FAQs on the official page. Those have the latest rules and conditions. Read them. Re-read them again. It is important to understand each and everyone of …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Vijay Kumar Kodam</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Show HN: I built a more productive way to manage AI chats]]></title>
        <id>https://contextch.at/</id>
        <link href="https://contextch.at/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-23T20:46:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The 3 biggest bombshells from this week’s AI extravaganza]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008808</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/the-3-biggest-bombshells-from-this-weeks-ai-extravaganza/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-23T20:29:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Enterprises looking to build with AI should find plenty to look forward to with the announcements from Microsoft, Google & Anthropic this week.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nick Mokey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Formal Proof of Complexity Bounds on Diophantine Equations]]></title>
        <id>https://arxiv.org/abs/2505.16963</id>
        <link href="https://arxiv.org/abs/2505.16963"/>
        <updated>2025-05-23T20:09:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Biz: From shorting the Venezuelan Bolivar to shorting the US dollar]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/crypto-biz-from-shorting-venezuelan-bolivar-shorting-us-dollar</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/crypto-biz-from-shorting-venezuelan-bolivar-shorting-us-dollar?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-23T20:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When Venezuela was experiencing hyperinflation, Ledn co-founder Mauricio di Bartolomeo hedged against the collapsing local currency by shorting it in favor of the more stable US dollar. Today, he’s using a similar strategy — this time borrowing against his Bitcoin (BTC) to hedge against the crumbling US dollar.
Di Bartolomeo connected with me during Canada Crypto Week in Toronto, where he talked about the advantages of Bitcoin-backed loans and the rapid growth of collateralized BTC lending. In our interview, he made a compelling case for continuing to stack sats, even as Bitcoin’s price keeps rising.
This week’s Crypto Biz dives into our conversation with the Ledn co-founder and covers the latest business news from the blockchain world.
A lesson from hyperinflation
Before Bitcoin, di Barto…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Sam Bourgi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[US House members call for investigation into Trump&#039;s memecoin dinner]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/house-investigation-donald-trump-memecoin-dinner</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/house-investigation-donald-trump-memecoin-dinner?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-23T19:57:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Members of the US House of Representatives called for the Justice Department to investigate Donald Trump’s May 22 dinner for his top memecoin investors, citing concerns about “foreign influence over US policy decisions” and “potential corruption and emoluments clause violations.”
In a May 22 letter to the Justice Department, 35 House members asked the public integrity section acting chief, Edward Sullivan, to launch an inquiry over the memecoin dinner to determine whether it violated the federal bribery statute or the foreign emoluments clause of the US Constitution. 
Under the emoluments clause, a US president is barred from accepting any gift from a foreign state without the approval of Congress. Bloomberg reported that a majority of the attendees at the memecoin dinner were likely forei…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Turner Wright</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Transwedge Product]]></title>
        <id>https://terathon.com/blog/transwedge-product.html</id>
        <link href="https://terathon.com/blog/transwedge-product.html"/>
        <updated>2025-05-23T19:56:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Genetic Boids Web Simulation]]></title>
        <id>https://attentionmech.github.io/genetic-boids/</id>
        <link href="https://attentionmech.github.io/genetic-boids/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-23T19:40:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin price ‘breather’ expected as short-term traders realize $11.6B in profit]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-price-breather-starts-as-short-term-traders-take-profit</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-price-breather-starts-as-short-term-traders-take-profit?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-23T19:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Key takeaways:

Short-term Bitcoin holders realized $11.6 billion in profit over the past 30 days, suggesting a potential pause or local top in the market.

Technical indicators show cooling momentum as retail investor sentiment falls to a 90-day low and liquidity data points to price volatility.

Bitcoin (BTC) price recently hit a new all-time high of $111,800, but the bullish momentum may slow down as onchain data from Glassnode reveals significant profit-taking by short-term holders (STHs), potentially signaling a market "breather."
Glassnode analysis shows that STHs, often considered traders rather than long-term investors, have realized a staggering $11.6 billion in profits over the last 30 days. This follows a sharp rebound in Bitcoin’s price, pushing past the STH cost-basis of $93,0…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Biraajmaan Tamuly</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Show HN: DoubleMemory – more efficient local-first read-it-later app]]></title>
        <id>https://doublememory.com/</id>
        <link href="https://doublememory.com/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-23T18:55:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Emacs dired-mode as a file manager]]></title>
        <id>https://lynn.sh/guix-emacs-file-manager.html</id>
        <link href="https://lynn.sh/guix-emacs-file-manager.html"/>
        <updated>2025-05-23T18:46:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Show HN: hcker.news – an ergonomic, timeline-based Hacker News front page]]></title>
        <id>https://hcker.news/</id>
        <link href="https://hcker.news/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-23T18:44:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Types of optical systems in a lens designer's toolbox (2020)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.pencilofrays.com/lens-design-forms/</id>
        <link href="https://www.pencilofrays.com/lens-design-forms/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-23T18:33:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Japan and the Birth of Modern Shipbuilding]]></title>
        <id>https://www.construction-physics.com/p/how-japan-invented-modern-shipbuilding</id>
        <link href="https://www.construction-physics.com/p/how-japan-invented-modern-shipbuilding"/>
        <updated>2025-05-23T18:30:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Attention Wasn't All We Needed]]></title>
        <id>https://www.stephendiehl.com/posts/post_transformers/</id>
        <link href="https://www.stephendiehl.com/posts/post_transformers/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-23T18:14:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Price predictions 5/23: BTC, ETH, XRP, BNB, SOL, DOGE, ADA, SUI, HYPE, LINK]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/analise-de-precos-em-23-05-btc-eth-xrp-bnb-sol-doge-ada-sui-hype-link</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/analise-de-precos-em-23-05-btc-eth-xrp-bnb-sol-doge-ada-sui-hype-link?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-23T18:07:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Key points:

Bitcoin slipped below $109,588, but technical charts suggest traders are buying each dip.

Excessive leverage in Bitcoin futures increases the risk of a quick correction.

Select altcoins have turned down from their respective overhead resistance levels, signaling that the bears remain sellers on rallies.

Sellers have pulled Bitcoin (BTC) back below the breakout level of $109,588, but lower levels are likely to attract buyers. Investor interest remains strong, with the US spot Bitcoin exchange-traded funds witnessing inflows of $934 million on May 22 and $608 million on May 21, according to SoSoValue data.
Glassnode noted that the all-time high above $109,588 led to a total profit-taking volume of roughly $1 billion, far more muted than the $2 billion when the price rose abov…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Rakesh Upadhyay</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto, NFTs are a lifeboat in the sinking fiat system: Finance Redefined]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/crypto-nfts-lifeboat-sinking-fiat-system-finance-redefined</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/crypto-nfts-lifeboat-sinking-fiat-system-finance-redefined?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-23T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Risk appetite across traditional and cryptocurrency markets saw a sharp rise this week, helping United States cryptocurrency funds recover the capital lost to the correction of February and March, amassing over $7.5 billion worth of weekly inflows.
Bitcoin (BTC) surpassed its old all-time high on May 21, two days after President Donald Trump confirmed ongoing ceasefire negotiations between Russia and Ukraine in a May 19 X post.
Meanwhile, popular analyst and Global Macro Investor CEO Raoul Pal warned of more fiat currency debasement, urging investors to gain more exposure to cryptocurrencies and non-fungible tokens (NFTs), as these assets “will never be this cheap again.”
Exponential currency debasement: “You don’t own enough crypto, NFTs”
Cryptocurrencies and NFTs can help investors prote…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Zoltan Vardai</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘In ‘93, it became clear to me AI should be decentralized’ — Ben Goertzel]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/ben-goertzel-ai-decentralization-interview</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/ben-goertzel-ai-decentralization-interview?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-23T17:58:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s been 30 years since computer scientist Ben Goertzel wrote his first line of AI code, already convinced that artificial intelligence should be decentralized. Today, as the world approaches the dawn of Artificial General Intelligence (AGI), who leads this breakthrough could have profound consequences for the future of humanity.
Speaking with Cointelegraph at the Consensus conference in Toronto, Canada, Goertzel said, “We’re likely to be able to launch AGI that can think and generalize beyond its training and programming within the next one to three years.”
His project, SingularityNET, is a decentralized ecosystem building a global marketplace for AI services. Along the way, it has secured partnerships with Mind Network and Filecoin Foundation, invested $53 million in a modular supercomp…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Sam Bourgi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Alberta separatism push roils Canada]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nytimes.com/2025/05/22/world/canada/alberta-separatism-referendum.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.nytimes.com/2025/05/22/world/canada/alberta-separatism-referendum.html"/>
        <updated>2025-05-23T17:22:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Positional preferences, order effects, prompt sensitivity undermine AI judgments]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cip.org/blog/llm-judges-are-unreliable</id>
        <link href="https://www.cip.org/blog/llm-judges-are-unreliable"/>
        <updated>2025-05-23T17:20:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Into The Tunnel: The secret life of wind tunnels]]></title>
        <id>https://jordanwtaylor2.substack.com/p/into-the-tunnel</id>
        <link href="https://jordanwtaylor2.substack.com/p/into-the-tunnel"/>
        <updated>2025-05-23T17:17:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Strategy Slumps 6%, Leading Crypto Names Lower as Bitcoin Treasury Strategies Are Questioned]]></title>
        <id>bb31eaf5-b257-4ca6-9286-4b88bfd2bc92</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/23/strategy-slumps-6-leading-crypto-names-lower-as-bitcoin-treasury-strategies-are-questioned"/>
        <updated>2025-05-23T17:16:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin slumped just modestly from record high levels on Friday, but the carnage in related stocks was far worse.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tom Carreras</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin’s bull market will ‘redefine’ BTC’s role in modern portfolios — Fidelity research]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-bull-market-redefines-btc-s-role-in-modern-portfolios-fidelity</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-bull-market-redefines-btc-s-role-in-modern-portfolios-fidelity?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-23T17:08:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Key takeaways:

Bitcoin’s performance in the current bull market and a new cohort of buyers reflect a maturing market and widening adoption.

A 50% rise in hashrate and a 63% jump in Realized Cap highlight investors’ confidence in Bitcoin.

A recent report from Fidelity Digital Assets explored how the current Bitcoin market cycle reflects a shift toward a maturing market where the rate of adoption deepens and expands.
At block height 892,500—marking 25% progress into the current halving epoch—Bitcoin traded between $82,500 and $85,000, representing a 31% increase from its value on April 19, 2024, when the fourth halving reduced block rewards to 3.125 BTC.
Bitcoin: halving cycles compared. Source: Fidelity Digital Assets
Fidelity’s senior research analyst Daniel Gray emphasized Bitcoin’s ne…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Biraajmaan Tamuly</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Innodisk Shows Off 128GB On A Single DDR5 RAM Module]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=353694</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/353694/innodisk-shows-off-128gb-on-a-single-ddr5-ram-module/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-23T17:01:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Back at Computex 2025, we visited the Innodisk booth and was introduced to several AI-based professional solutions. The brand isn’t your typical or average consumer name; it’s more of an industrial-based company, with a focus on enterprise and aerospace industries. That said, Innodisk did have something interesting on its floor, and that was the single […]
The post Innodisk Shows Off 128GB On A Single DDR5 RAM Module appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John Law</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sesame Scheme: Unintended Consequences of Allergen Food Labeling]]></title>
        <id>https://www.choicesmagazine.org/choices-magazine/submitted-articles/unintended-consequences-of-allergen-food-labeling</id>
        <link href="https://www.choicesmagazine.org/choices-magazine/submitted-articles/unintended-consequences-of-allergen-food-labeling"/>
        <updated>2025-05-23T16:58:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to live on $432 a month in America]]></title>
        <id>https://shagbark.substack.com/p/how-to-live-on-432-a-month-in-america</id>
        <link href="https://shagbark.substack.com/p/how-to-live-on-432-a-month-in-america"/>
        <updated>2025-05-23T16:40:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Beyond Semantics: Unreasonable Effectiveness of Reasonless Intermediate Tokens]]></title>
        <id>https://arxiv.org/abs/2505.13775</id>
        <link href="https://arxiv.org/abs/2505.13775"/>
        <updated>2025-05-23T16:13:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Find Your People]]></title>
        <id>https://foundersatwork.posthaven.com/find-your-people</id>
        <link href="https://foundersatwork.posthaven.com/find-your-people"/>
        <updated>2025-05-23T16:02:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Alchemy acquires no-code NFT launchpad HeyMint for undisclosed amount]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/alchemy-acquires-heymint-nft-launchpad</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/alchemy-acquires-heymint-nft-launchpad?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-23T15:52:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Web3 developer platform Alchemy has acquired HeyMint, a California-based non-fungible token (NFT) launchpad, in a move designed to enhance the company’s smart wallet infrastructure. 
The undisclosed funding deal will see HeyMint’s infrastructure embedded within Alchemy as it seeks to simplify user onboarding for Web3 applications, the company disclosed on May 23. HeyMint’s co-founder and chief technology officer, Flor Ronsmans De Vry, joins Alchemy as part of the deal. 
While not a household name in crypto, HeyMint attracted more than 1 million users over its first two years of operations. It was the launchpad behind $38 million in NFT sales and supported the Web3 efforts of major brands, including The Sandbox, Universal Music Group and Ubisoft. 
In 2023, HeyMint facilitated NFT sales for …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Sam Bourgi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The metre originated in the French Revolution]]></title>
        <id>https://www.abc.net.au/news/science/2025-05-20/metre-treaty-anniversary-metric-system-measurement-metrology/105302024</id>
        <link href="https://www.abc.net.au/news/science/2025-05-20/metre-treaty-anniversary-metric-system-measurement-metrology/105302024"/>
        <updated>2025-05-23T15:43:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MCP is the coming of Web 2.0 2.0]]></title>
        <id>https://www.anildash.com//2025/05/20/mcp-web20-20/</id>
        <link href="https://www.anildash.com//2025/05/20/mcp-web20-20/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-23T15:33:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin price drops 4% as Trump EU tariff talk liquidates over $300M]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-price-drops-4-trump-eu-tariff-talk-liquidates-over-300m</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-price-drops-4-trump-eu-tariff-talk-liquidates-over-300m?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-23T15:29:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Key points:

Bitcoin joins risk assets in a knee-jerk reaction to the latest instalment of the US trade war, this time focused on the EU.

BTC price action dives up to 4% before recovering with $110,000 now a resistance level.

Traders demand that price holds higher levels going forward to protect bullish momentum.

Bitcoin (BTC) saw flash volatility into the May 23 Wall Street open as news headlines liquidated longs.
BTC/USD 1-hour chart. Source: Cointelegraph/TradingView
Bitcoin trips as Trump says EU talks “going nowhere”
Data from Cointelegraph Markets Pro and TradingView showed BTC/USD hitting lows of $107,367 on Bitstamp before rebounding.
This marked daily losses of up to 4% as markets reacted to comments from US President Donald Trump over tariffs on the European Union.
“Our discus…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by William Suberg</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Postgres IDE in VS Code]]></title>
        <id>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/blog/adforpostgresql/announcing-a-new-ide-for-postgresql-in-vs-code-from-microsoft/4414648</id>
        <link href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/blog/adforpostgresql/announcing-a-new-ide-for-postgresql-in-vs-code-from-microsoft/4414648"/>
        <updated>2025-05-23T15:12:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build a Testing Framework for E-Commerce Checkout and Payments]]></title>
        <id>68308f32f4205e3b843cfb37</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-build-a-testing-framework-for-e-commerce-checkout-and-payments/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-23T15:07:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When I first started working on E-commerce applications, I assumed testing checkout flows and payments would be straightforward. My expectation was simple: users select items, provide an address, pay, and receive confirmation. But I quickly learned t...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Venkata Sai Sandeep</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Architecture of Mathematics – And How Developers Can Use it in Code]]></title>
        <id>68308ee8ccde6bc325c82393</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/the-architecture-of-mathematics-and-how-developers-can-use-it-in-code/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-23T15:06:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA["To understand is to perceive patterns." - Isaiah Berlin Math is not just numbers. It is the science of finding complex patterns that shape our world. This means that to truly understand it, we need to see beyond numbers, formulas, and theorems and ...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tiago Capelo Monteiro</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spoiler alert: The future of Web3 is not blockchain]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/future-of-web3-is-not-blockchain</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/future-of-web3-is-not-blockchain?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-23T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Opinion by: Grigore Roșu, founder and chief executive officer of Pi Squared
For some, the audacity of questioning the primacy of blockchain in Web3 is borderline heretical. The idea that decentralization and progress could exist without blockchains seems absurd to those who built careers around Bitcoin, Ethereum, and their descendants. Given blockchain's well-documented scaling limits, however, there is an argument to be made that Web3 doesn't actually need blockchains to thrive. Instead, it requires payment systems and verifiable settlement systems that are super fast. Blockchains are just one way to achieve that, not the only way.
While blockchain solved the double-spending problem, it introduced its own architectural burden: the rigid fixation on total ordering, dictating that every tra…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Grigore Roșu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Who attended Trump’s controversial memecoin dinner?]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/who-attended-trumps-controversial-memecoin-dinner</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/who-attended-trumps-controversial-memecoin-dinner?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-23T14:52:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The top 220 holders of US President Donald Trump’s memecoin met yesterday at the president’s golf course in Virginia for an exclusive dinner and purported meet-and-greet.
Attendees spent a grand total of $148 million for an “ultra-exclusive VIP reception with the president,” which crypto industry advocates and critics alike saw as a potential opportunity to discuss crypto policy with the president. 
The crowd contained a number of foreign crypto executives and influencers who otherwise would not have access to the US president, raising questions around corruption and foreign influence. 
Concerns were further augmented when White House Press Secretary Karoline Leavitt declined to release a list of attendees, stating that the event was a private affair outside of Trump’s presidential duties.…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Aaron Wood</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum price chart targets $4K as transaction fees hit 3-month high]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/ethereum-price-chart-targets-4k-transaction-fees-hit-3-month-highs</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/ethereum-price-chart-targets-4k-transaction-fees-hit-3-month-highs?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-23T14:49:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Key takeaways:

Ethereum is forming a bull flag on the daily chart, with a potential breakout to $4,000.

If Ethereum’s network activity and total value locked continue to grow, ETH price may see further gains.

Ether’s price printed a “bull flag” on the daily chart, a technical chart formation associated with strong upward momentum. Could a strengthening technical setup and increasing transaction fees signal the continuation of ETH’s rally toward $4,000?
Ethereum transaction fees rising is bullish
Marketwide recovery, fueled by Bitcoin’s rise to new all-time highs and improving macroeconomic conditions, saw Ether’s (ETH) price rise by nearly 56% to an eight-week high of $2,734 on May 23, from a low of $1,750 on May 6. 
This strength in price is reflected in onchain activity, with Ethereum…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Nancy Lubale</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[US DOJ seizes $24M in crypto from accused Qakbot malware developer]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/us-seizes-24m-crypto-qakbot-developer</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/us-seizes-24m-crypto-qakbot-developer?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-23T14:29:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The US Department of Justice (DOJ) has filed a civil forfeiture complaint to seize more than $24 million in cryptocurrency from Rustam Rafailevich Gallyamov, a Russian national accused of developing the Qakbot malware.
According to a May 22 announcement, the DOJ unsealed charges against the 48-year-old Moscovite with a federal indictment. Gallyamov is allegedly the malware developer behind the Qakbot botnet. 
“Today’s announcement of the Justice Department’s latest actions to counter the Qakbot malware scheme sends a clear message to the cybercrime community,” said Matthew Galeotti, head of the DOJ’s criminal division.
Screenshot of the indictment. Source: US Department of Justice
Galeotti highlighted that the DOJ is “determined to hold cybercriminals accountable.” He added that the depart…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Adrian Zmudzinski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Caesar's Last Breath]]></title>
        <id>https://charliesabino.com/caesars-last-breath/</id>
        <link href="https://charliesabino.com/caesars-last-breath/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-23T14:22:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is DNS hijacking? How it took down Curve Finance’s website]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/explained/what-is-dns-hijacking-how-it-took-down-curve-finances-website</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/explained/what-is-dns-hijacking-how-it-took-down-curve-finances-website?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-23T14:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Understanding the Curve Finance DNS hijacking            
            
                
On May 12, 2025, at 20:55 UTC, hackers hijacked the “.fi” domain name system (DNS) of Curve Finance after managing to access the registrar. They began sending its users to a malicious website, attempting to drain their wallets. This was the second attack on Curve Finance’s infrastructure in a week.
Users were directed to a website that was a non-functional decoy, designed only to trick users into providing wallet signatures. The hack hadn’t breached the protocol’s smart contracts and was limited to the DNS layer.
The DNS is a critical component of the internet that functions like a phonebook. It allows you to use simple, memorable domain names (such as facebook.com) instead of complex numerical IP addre…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Dilip Kumar Patairya</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Market Sees $300M Liquidations as Trump Tariff Threats Flush Late Bulls]]></title>
        <id>b8f8ab22-fcaf-4344-ab7c-d856c3e58532</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/23/crypto-market-sees-usd300m-liquidations-as-trump-tariff-threats-flush-late-bulls"/>
        <updated>2025-05-23T13:53:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The leverage flush happened as crypto prices quickly dropped on renewed trade war fears, with BTC slipping 3% from near record highs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Krisztian Sandor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Twice lucky? Cetus’ recovery plan on Sui mirrors a Solana blueprint]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/cetus-hack-sui-successful-solana</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/cetus-hack-sui-successful-solana?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-23T13:52:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The bounty offer to recover stolen funds from Sui-based decentralized exchange (DEX) Cetus closely resembles a successful strategy used by a Solana project three years ago.
It turns out that Cetus shares the same development team as Crema Finance, a Solana-based DeFi project that suffered a $9-million hack in 2022 but recovered most of the funds by negotiating with its hacker. Now, Cetus is relying on the same strategy.
Cetus is asking the hacker to return all but $6 million, or 2,324 Ether (ETH), of the stolen funds in exchange for a promise not to pursue legal action. The protocol lost $223 million to an exploit on May 22.
The size of the bounty has sparked backlash from users, with many calling for a formal compensation plan instead. Several community members argue that even if funds ar…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Yohan Yun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Show HN: Samchika – A Java Library for Fast, Multithreaded File Processing]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/MayankPratap/Samchika</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/MayankPratap/Samchika"/>
        <updated>2025-05-23T13:39:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Feature Fridays: dTelecom]]></title>
        <id>682f3eb8646f7c0001399182</id>
        <link href="https://blog.quicknode.com/feature-fridays-dtelecom/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-23T13:37:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[dTelecom is reshaping digital communication with decentralized, AI-powered infrastructure for Web3 developers and businesses.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>QuickNode</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Washington moves on crypto: Stablecoin and blockchain bills signal regulatory momentum]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/washington-moves-on-crypto-stablecoin-and-blockchain-bills-signal-regulatory-momentum</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/washington-moves-on-crypto-stablecoin-and-blockchain-bills-signal-regulatory-momentum?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-23T13:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this week’s episode of Byte-Sized Insight, on Decentralize with Cointelegraph, we break down a pivotal moment for US crypto legislation. 
In a 66–32 procedural vote on May 19, the US Senate advanced the GENIUS Act, a landmark bill aimed at establishing a comprehensive regulatory framework for stablecoins. Meanwhile, across the Capitol, Representative Tom Emmer reintroduced the Blockchain Regulatory Certainty Act, backed by bipartisan support.

Breaking down GENIUS
The GENIUS Act — short for “Guiding and Establishing National Innovation for U.S. Stablecoins Act” — seeks to answer foundational questions around stablecoin issuance and oversight.
“It defines this idea of a payment stablecoin,” explained Rashan Colbert, director of US policy at the Crypto Council for Innovation, in this week…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Savannah Fortis</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use React 19 in Power Apps PCF Components]]></title>
        <id>6830767c62d9a28c0de11007</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-react-19-in-pcf-components/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-23T13:22:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Power Apps Component Framework – PCF for short – lets you create complex custom components using traditional web development tools like HTML, CSS, and JavaScript. When creating a new PCF project, you can choose from two types of controls: standar...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brandon Wozniewicz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Here’s what happened in crypto today]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/what-happened-in-crypto-today</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/what-happened-in-crypto-today?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-23T13:19:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today in crypto, Changpeng Zhao has responded forcefully to The Wall Street Journal’s latest report linking the former Binance CEO’s crypto dealings with the Trump-back decentralized finance platform World Liberty Financial, United States Commodity Futures Trading Commission (CFTC) Commissioner Summer Mersinger said crypto perpetual futures could soon come to the US, and lawmakers plan to amend the GENIUS Act to bar sitting presidents from profiting off stablecoins.
CZ refutes claims in latest WSJ article on Trump-linked crypto dealings
Binance co-founder and former CEO Changpeng “CZ” Zhao has pushed back against a report in The Wall Street Journal, calling it a “hit piece” filled with inaccuracies and negative assumptions. 
In an X post, Zhao criticized the publication’s portrayal of his …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Cointelegraph</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CoinDesk 20 Performance Update: Index Declines 3.2% as All Assets Trade Lower]]></title>
        <id>ee46e543-c59c-4ad8-ba6c-93619e202250</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/coindesk-indices/2025/05/23/coindesk-20-performance-update-index-declines-3-2-as-all-assets-trade-lower"/>
        <updated>2025-05-23T13:13:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sui (SUI) Dropped 6.8% and NEAR Protocol (NEAR) fell  5.8%, leading the index lower from Thursday.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CoinDesk Indices</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Can ChatGPT-powered AI agents really trade crypto for you?]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/can-chatgpt-powered-ai-agents-really-trade-crypto-for-you</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/can-chatgpt-powered-ai-agents-really-trade-crypto-for-you?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-23T13:13:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Key takeaways

ChatGPT-powered AI agents automate trading tasks using natural language prompts and API integrations, improving speed and consistency.

Successes occur when ChatGPT is used as a support tool, not a fully autonomous trading system.

Failures happen when traders over-rely on ChatGPT without real-time data, proper risk management or manual oversight.

Regulatory focus on AI in trading is increasing, with new frameworks emerging to ensure transparency, accountability and compliance.

What if a crypto trader didn’t need to constantly check charts, worry about emotions, or stay up all night watching for sudden price swings? What if those tasks could be handled by an intelligent agent that understands instructions in plain English — and reacts within milliseconds? That’s where Chat…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Callum Reid</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Semler Scientific Bolsters Bitcoin Holdings with $50M Acquisition]]></title>
        <id>d746f167-b10a-4d8e-bf78-26d09f63294c</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/23/semler-scientific-bolsters-bitcoin-holdings-with-usd50m-acquisition"/>
        <updated>2025-05-23T13:04:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The company acquired 455 bitcoin in its third-largest announced purchase.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>James Van Straten</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why enterprise RAG systems fail: Google study introduces ‘sufficient context’ solution]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008684</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/why-enterprise-rag-systems-fail-google-study-introduces-sufficient-context-solution/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-23T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google's "sufficient context" helps refine RAG systems, reduce LLM hallucinations, and boost AI reliability for business applications.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ben Dickson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Lender Ledn Goes Full Bitcoin Maxi as It Seeks to Reduce Client Asset Risk]]></title>
        <id>523aaf44-b3a2-49dc-874e-8bf44fd3ccc7</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2025/05/23/crypto-lender-ledn-goes-full-bitcoin-maxi-as-it-seeks-to-reduce-client-asset-risk"/>
        <updated>2025-05-23T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ledn said the shift is part of its broader strategy to simplify its product and sharpen its focus around bitcoin.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Crawley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ledn ditches ETH, shifts to full custody model for Bitcoin loans]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/ledn-ditches-eth-full-custody-model-bitcoin-loans</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/ledn-ditches-eth-full-custody-model-bitcoin-loans?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-23T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Digital asset lender Ledn is transitioning to fully collateralized Bitcoin lending and discontinuing support for Ethereum, in moves designed to consolidate its BTC-focused business and further safeguard client assets against credit risks.
In adopting a full custody structure for Bitcoin (BTC) loans, Ledn will no longer lend out client assets to generate interest, the company disclosed on May 23. Instead, Bitcoin collateral will remain under full custody by Ledn or one of its designated funding partners. 
“This means assets aren’t rehypothecated, reused, or loaned out to generate yield,” Ledn co-founder and CEO Adam Reeds told Cointelegraph. 
Reeds said the move brings the company back to its roots and aligns more closely with Bitcoin’s founding principles.
“Bitcoin was created as a direct …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Sam Bourgi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[US Bitcoin ETFs near record month after $1.5B inflows in 2 days]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-etfs-record-month-1-5b-inflows-2-days</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-etfs-record-month-1-5b-inflows-2-days?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-23T12:46:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Spot Bitcoin exchange-traded funds (ETFs) in the United States are heading for a record-breaking month, helping push Bitcoin to new all-time highs amid rising institutional demand.
The US-listed spot Bitcoin (BTC) ETFs recorded more than $1.5 billion in combined inflows over a two-day period, with $608 million on May 21 and $934 million on May 22, according to data from Sosovalue.
A repeat performance of the past two days’ inflows would see monthly inflows surge to $6.68 billion, surpassing the monthly record of $6.49 billion from November 2024.
Bitcoin ETF inflows, monthly, all-time chart. Source: Sosovalue
Related: German gov’t missed out on $2.3B profit after selling Bitcoin at $57K
ETF inflows helped Bitcoin rise to a new all-time high of $112,000 on May 22 before retracing to above $1…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Zoltan Vardai</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Good Vibes Shattered as Trump Revives Trade War, Sending Bitcoin Tumbling Below $109K]]></title>
        <id>e6b9f8b7-005e-460f-87a2-463276d1c040</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/23/good-vibes-shattered-as-trump-revives-trade-war-bitcoin-tumbles-below-usd109k"/>
        <updated>2025-05-23T12:14:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The president Friday morning threatened an imminent 50% tariff on all EU imports as well as a 25% levy on imported Apple iPhones.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephen Alpher</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Download: meet Cathy Tie, and Anthropic’s new AI models]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1117399</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/05/23/1117399/the-download-meet-cathy-tie-and-anthropics-new-ai-models/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-23T12:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is today’s edition of The Download, our weekday newsletter that provides a daily dose of what’s going on in the world of technology. Meet Cathy Tie, Bride of “China’s Frankenstein” Since the Chinese biophysicist He Jiankui was released from prison in 2022, he has sought to make a scientific comeback and to repair his reputation after…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rhiannon Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Genius Group resumes Bitcoin buying after US court ruling]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/genius-group-buys-more-bitcoin-after</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/genius-group-buys-more-bitcoin-after?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-23T12:07:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Singapore-based artificial intelligence firm Genius Group has added more Bitcoin to its corporate treasury after being temporarily banned from doing so.
In a May 22 announcement, Genius Group explained that it has resumed accumulating Bitcoin (BTC) following a favorable ruling by the US Court of Appeals. It follows Genius Group being temporarily barred from expanding its Bitcoin treasury after a US court order had banned it from selling shares, raising funds and using investor funds to buy more BTC.
Genius Group announced it increased its Bitcoin Treasury 40% with the purchase of 24.5 BTC, worth around $2.7 million. The company now holds 85.5 BTC acquired for a total of $8.5 million, at an average price of $99,700 per coin.
“We are pleased to be able to begin the task of rebuilding shareho…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Adrian Zmudzinski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CZ refutes claims in latest WSJ article on Trump-linked crypto dealings]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/cz-denies-fixer-claims-wsj-report</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/cz-denies-fixer-claims-wsj-report?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-23T11:53:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Binance co-founder and former CEO Changpeng “CZ” Zhao has pushed back against a report in The Wall Street Journal, calling it a “hit piece” filled with inaccuracies and negative assumptions. 
In an X post, Zhao criticized the publication’s portrayal of his alleged involvement with World Liberty Financial, the decentralized finance project backed by a business entity affiliated with US President Donald Trump. Trump’s sons — Eric and Donald Jr. —are involved in the management of the company.
Zhao said the WSJ article portrayed him as acting as a “fixer” for the WLF team and its co-founder Zach Witkoff during foreign trips. 
The article suggested Zhao facilitated introductions and meetings for WLF leaders during foreign trips, including a visit to Pakistan that reportedly resulted in a memora…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Ezra Reguerra</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Remembering Alasdair MacIntyre]]></title>
        <id>https://www.wordonfire.org/articles/remembering-alasdair-macintyre-1929-2025/</id>
        <link href="https://www.wordonfire.org/articles/remembering-alasdair-macintyre-1929-2025/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-23T11:37:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin&#039;s new all-time high has traders asking: Is BTC price overheating at $111K?]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-new-all-time-high-traders-asking-is-btc-price-overheating</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-new-all-time-high-traders-asking-is-btc-price-overheating?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-23T11:31:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Key takeaways:

Bitcoin hit a new all-time high of $111,970 on May 22, but retraced to $110,700, with analysts noting mixed signals on market overheating.

Funding rates and other metrics suggest a “healthy upward phase.”

Bitcoin’s (BTC) price recorded a new all-time high of $111,970  on May 22. However, BTC price retraced shortly after to trade at $110,700 at the time of writing. 
Despite the correction, there are mixed signals about whether the price rally is overheated or whether this is a healthy pullback. 
Bitcoin “still not overheated” — analyst
Bitcoin is not showing any signs of being overheated despite reaching new all-time highs this week, with several analysts pointing to fundamentals suggesting Bitcoin could rise further.
“Overheating indicators such as the funding rate and sh…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Nancy Lubale</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Daybook Americas: Bitcoin Market Cap Tops $2.2T as Derivatives, Sentiment Signal More Upside]]></title>
        <id>153c2526-d517-492e-9439-65525a732529</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/daybook-us/2025/05/23/crypto-daybook-americas-bitcoin-market-cap-tops-usd2-2t-as-derivatives-sentiment-signal-more-upside"/>
        <updated>2025-05-23T11:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Your day-ahead look for May 23, 2025]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>James Van Straten</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why I no longer have an old-school cert on my HTTPS site]]></title>
        <id>https://rachelbythebay.com/w/2025/05/22/ssl/</id>
        <link href="https://rachelbythebay.com/w/2025/05/22/ssl/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-23T10:56:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Writing A Job Runner (In Elixir) (Again) (10 years later)]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/notactuallytreyanastasio/genstage_tutorial_2025/blob/main/README.md</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/notactuallytreyanastasio/genstage_tutorial_2025/blob/main/README.md"/>
        <updated>2025-05-23T10:41:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Photo Essay: Kingston At Computex 2025]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=353600</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/353600/kingston-computex-2025/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-23T10:34:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kingston is and always has been a mainstay at Computex 2025. This year, the memory maker gave us a brief tour of its achievements, as well as some new products we can expect. Perhaps one of the brand’s proudest achievements was how much its products was being used in the AI and more specifically, the […]
The post Photo Essay: Kingston At Computex 2025 appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John Law</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cetus offers $6M bounty after $220M hack as Sui faces decentralization debate]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/cetus-6m-white-hat-bounty-of-stolen-220m</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/cetus-6m-white-hat-bounty-of-stolen-220m?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-23T10:01:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cetus is offering a $6 million white hat bounty in an effort to recover $220 million in stolen digital assets, while emergency responses from the Sui Network have raised concerns about decentralization.
Sui-native decentralized exchange (DEX) Cetus was exploited for over $220 million worth of cryptocurrency on May 22. However, Cetus managed to freeze $162 million of the stolen funds shortly after.
Cetus has since offered a white hat bounty of up to $6 million for the exploiter for returning the stolen 20,920 Ether (ETH), worth over $55 million, along with the rest of the stolen funds currently frozen on the Sui blockchain.
“In exchange, you can keep 2,324 ETH ($6M) as a bounty, and we will consider the matter closed and will not pursue any further legal, intelligence, or public action,” Ce…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Zoltan Vardai</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Laid off but not afraid with X-senior Microsoft Dev MacKevin Fey [Podcast #173]]]></title>
        <id>68304756ecdb03ab557f3974</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/laid-off-but-not-afraid-with-x-senior-microsoft-dev-mackevin-fey-podcast-173/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-23T10:00:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On this week's episode of the podcast, freeCodeCamp founder Quincy Larson interviews MacKevin Fey. He just got laid off last week from his senior engineering role at Microsoft. We talk about: How Mack's approaching the job search after being laid of...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Xiaomi YU7 Unveiled In China; Comes In 3 Variants]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=353577</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/353577/xiaomi-yu7-unveiled-in-china-comes-in-3-variants/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-23T09:59:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Xiaomi’s second fully electric (EV) model, the YU7 SUV, was unveiled yesterday in conjunction with the company’s 15th-year anniversary. The EV SUV is offered in three configurations: rear-wheel drive (RWD), all-wheel drive (AWD) and Max AWD. As previously reported, the YU7 SUV shares many design elements with the SU7 sedan, including the closed grille, distinctive […]
The post Xiaomi YU7 Unveiled In China; Comes In 3 Variants appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Keran</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Photo Essay: AGi At Computex 2025]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=353596</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/353596/photo-essay-agi-at-computex-2025/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-23T09:42:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’ve said it before and we’ll say it again: AGi isn’t a brand many would be familiar with but the company has been very slowly making a name for itself in the PC memory and storage market. This year, we visited the brand’s booth at Computex 2025 to find out what it’s been doing since […]
The post Photo Essay: AGi At Computex 2025 appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John Law</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Photo Essay: DarkFlash At Computex 2025]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=353236</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/353236/photo-essay-darkflash-at-computex-2025/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-23T09:37:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[DarkFlash was another brand we visited at its booth during Computex 2025. While we’re not entirely familiar with the name, the company does have a reputation of being a manufacturer of components and peripherals. Casings are something of the brand’s speciality, something that it was eager to show off in the form of its all-glass […]
The post Photo Essay: DarkFlash At Computex 2025 appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John Law</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Photo Essay: PNY At Computex 2025]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=353439</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/353439/pny-computex-2025/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-23T09:32:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[During our tour of Computex 2025, we found time to stop by at the PNY booth. As with all GPU makers and given the recent launch of the NVIDIA GeForce RTX 5060 a few days earlier, the brand was presenting its own custom-cooled SKUs, among other things, to the floor. The RTX 5060 series PNY […]
The post Photo Essay: PNY At Computex 2025 appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John Law</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Volkswagen Confirms Golf GTI Will Go Fully Electric]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=353528</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/353528/volkswagen-confirms-golf-gti-will-go-fully-electric/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-23T09:26:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Since its debut in 1976, the Volkswagen Golf GTI has gained a rich history and a legendary status as a performance hatchback in the automaker’s line-up. But, as the automotive world shifts gears towards electrification, even the mighty GTI isn’t immune to change. Behind the scenes, development is already in full swing. Volkswagen’s engineers are […]
The post Volkswagen Confirms Golf GTI Will Go Fully Electric appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Keran</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CFTC’s Plans for Crypto Perpetual Trading Puts Focus on Hyperliquid’s HYPE]]></title>
        <id>780dccef-8a69-4d87-91ae-6203e5ab8d74</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/23/cftcs-plans-for-crypto-perpetual-trading-puts-focus-on-hyperliquids-hype"/>
        <updated>2025-05-23T09:24:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HYPE is up 15% in the past 24 hours, outperforming majors, as developers said they submitted comments to the derivatives agency on using DeFi principles to create better products.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shaurya Malwa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hyperliquid backs 24/7 crypto trading in CFTC comments submission]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/hypehyperliquid-cftc-comments-crypto-derivatives-tradingrliquid</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/hypehyperliquid-cftc-comments-crypto-derivatives-tradingrliquid?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-23T09:09:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hyperliquid, a decentralized perpetuals exchange operating on its own layer-1 blockchain, has submitted formal comments on 24/7 derivatives trading to the United States Commodity Futures Trading Commission (CFTC).
In a May 23 X post, Hyperliquid Labs announced that it has “submitted two comment letters to the [CFTC] in response to its recent Requests for Comment on perpetual derivatives and 24/7 trading.” The team behind the decentralized exchange (DEX) added:
“We commend the CFTC for its proactive engagement on these topics, understanding of which is fundamental to the evolution of global markets.”
Hyperliquid stated that it is committed to the advancement of the decentralized finance (DeFi) space. The team also claimed that its implementation “exemplifies how core DeFi principles can be …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Adrian Zmudzinski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The FDA plans to limit access to covid vaccines. Here’s why that’s not all bad.]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1117329</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/05/23/1117329/fda-limit-access-covid-vaccines/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-23T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This week, two new leaders at the US Food and Drug Administration announced plans to limit access to covid vaccines, arguing that there is not much evidence to support the value of annual shots in healthy people. New vaccines will be made available only to the people who are most vulnerable—namely, those over 65 and…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jessica Hamzelou</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meet Cathy Tie, Bride of “China’s Frankenstein”]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1117373</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/05/23/1117373/cathy-tie-he-jiankui-china-crispr-x-twitter-feed/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-23T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Since the Chinese biophysicist He Jiankui was released from prison in 2022, he has sought to make a scientific comeback and to repair his reputation after a three-year incarceration for illegally creating the world’s first gene-edited children.  While he has bounced between cities, jobs, and meetings with investors, one area of visible success on his…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Caiwei Chen, Antonio Regalado</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Samsung Galaxy Buds Core Appears In Official Support Sites]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=353627</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/353627/samsung-galaxy-buds-core-appears-in-official-support-sites/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-23T08:59:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Samsung Galaxy Buds FE was released back in October of 2023, and the time for a successor may be nigh. Except that it may not be called the Galaxy Buds FE 2, according to reports. New name aside, it may also be close to launch, as its model number has started appearing in support […]
The post Samsung Galaxy Buds Core Appears In Official Support Sites appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ian Chee</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Major U.S. Banks Mull Jointly Launching Stablecoin: WSJ]]></title>
        <id>4c76c31a-f15f-4bf8-af51-2a9c7f7f18bd</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2025/05/23/major-us-banks-mull-jointly-launching-stablecoin-wsj"/>
        <updated>2025-05-23T08:48:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Such a stablecoin, potentially open to other banks, aims to improve transaction speeds and efficiency while fending off competition from crypto firms.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Francisco Rodrigues</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DeFi near-zero onboarding costs can help 1.4B unbanked: 1inch co-founder]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/1inch-cofounder-defi-financial-inclusion-dbw-event</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/1inch-cofounder-defi-financial-inclusion-dbw-event?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-23T08:47:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decentralized finance (DeFi) platforms have a major cost advantage over traditional banks when it comes to onboarding new users, according to Anton Bukov, co-founder of decentralized exchange (DEX) aggregator 1inch.
Speaking at a panel during Dutch Blockchain Week on May 22 in Amsterdam, Bukov said traditional banks spend between $100 and $300 per user to verify documents and set up accounts. Online banks, he said, spend about $20 to $30. In contrast, DeFi requires almost nothing beyond a smartphone and internet access.
“Onboarding to DeFi literally costs zero,” Bukov said. “You don’t need brick-and-mortar infrastructure or lengthy verification processes. Just connect and transact.” 
Bukov said that this gives DeFi an edge over traditional financial institutions in reaching the 1.4 billion…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Ezra Reguerra</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin buyer dominance at $111K suggests &#039;another wave&#039; of gains]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-buyer-dominance-at-111k-suggests-another-wave-of-gains</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-buyer-dominance-at-111k-suggests-another-wave-of-gains?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-23T08:45:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Key points:

Bitcoin buyer interest remains strong at all-time highs, contrasting with the first touch of $100,000 in 2024.

The BTC price uptrend “may continue” as a result, CryptoQuant analysis concludes.

Bitcoin short-term holders are firmly in the black in a further potential bull market boost.

Bitcoin (BTC) buyers remain dominant on exchanges as all-time highs are met with unusual optimism.
Data from onchain analytics platform CryptoQuant shows a 90-day cumulative volume delta (CVD) favoring Bitcoin bulls.

CryptoQuant: BTC price uptrend “may continue”
BTC price all-time highs continue to find support among traders, with buyers staying dominant despite the market surging 50% in under two months.
Analyzing 90-day CVD, CryptoQuant contributor Ibrahim Cosar reveals the extent to which …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by William Suberg</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Tether refuses to comply with MiCA]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/explained/why-tether-refuses-to-comply-with-mica</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/explained/why-tether-refuses-to-comply-with-mica?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-23T08:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Is Tether MiCA compliant?            
            
                
The EU’s new Markets in Crypto-Assets regulation, better known as MiCA, is the first major attempt by a global economic power to create clear, region-wide rules for the crypto space, and stablecoins are a big focus.
MiCA mandates best practices. If a stablecoin is going to be traded in the EU, its issuer has to follow some stringent rules:
1. You need a license
To issue a stablecoin in Europe, you must become a fully authorized electronic money institution (EMI). That’s the same kind of license traditional fintechs need to offer e-wallets or prepaid cards. It’s not cheap and it’s not quick. 
2. Most of your reserves have to sit in European banks
This is one of the most controversial parts of MiCA. If you issue a “significa…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Bradley Peak</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Alcatel 3 Launches; V3 Classic, Pro Releasing on 27 May]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=353565</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/353565/alcatel-3-launches-v3-classic-pro-releasing-27-may/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-23T08:00:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Alcatel is having quite a busy week. Its V3 Ultra 5G just had its specs revealed on a Flipkart page, confirming its 5,010mAh battery. Now, the brand has quietly launched its Alcatel 3 (2025) phone via its official webpage. In addition to that, a listing on Flipkart reveals that the V3 Classic and Pro phones, […]
The post Alcatel 3 Launches; V3 Classic, Pro Releasing on 27 May appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Newsdesk</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Enters Strongest Accumulation Phase Since January as BTC Price Passes $110K]]></title>
        <id>29205afd-ca8c-4683-93b4-3286329cb66c</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/23/bitcoin-enters-strongest-accumulation-phase-since-january-as-btc-price-passes-110k"/>
        <updated>2025-05-23T07:46:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Glassnode data shows all wallet cohorts are now accumulating, with options markets pricing in potential upside beyond $200K in June.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>James Van Straten</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fujifilm Opens Pre-Orders For X Half Camera; Costs RM3,398]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=353560</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/353560/fujifilm-x-half/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-23T06:51:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fujifilm has announced a very unique new digital camera called the X Half, which is inspired by half-frame cameras. The most interesting thing about this camera is, without a doubt, that it shoots stills and videos in a vertical format. The X Half features an 18MP 1-inch 3:4 CMOS sensor with a 10.8mm f/2.8 FUJINON […]
The post Fujifilm Opens Pre-Orders For X Half Camera; Costs RM3,398 appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ikmal Rozlan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[US big banks hold early talks on joint crypto stablecoin: WSJ]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/us-big-banks-in-talks-for-joint-crypto-stablecoin-wsj</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/us-big-banks-in-talks-for-joint-crypto-stablecoin-wsj?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-23T06:27:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Some of the biggest banking companies in the US are reportedly exploring a team-up to launch a crypto stablecoin.
Companies owned by JPMorgan, Bank of America, Citigroup and Wells Fargo have discussed the possibility of jointly issuing a stablecoin, The Wall Street Journal reported on May 22, citing people familiar with the matter.

Other financial institutions linked to the potential stablecoin include Early Warning Services, the parent company of digital payments network Zelle, and the payment network Clearing House.
The discussions are still in the early stages, and a final decision on the project could change depending on the regulatory environment and the demand for stablecoins.
A JPMorgan spokesperson told Cointelegraph the company had no comment. Bank of America, CitiGroup, and Well…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Tarang Khaitan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Justin Sun Defends TRUMP After Presidential Dinner, Says 'Memecoins Have Merit']]></title>
        <id>bc2347ce-4dd2-42f3-afbd-6c99d9881bc9</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/23/justin-sun-defends-trump-after-presidential-dinner-says-memecoins-have-merit"/>
        <updated>2025-05-23T05:45:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tron's Sun sees the President fueling a new American crypto boom.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sam Reynolds</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[XRP Could Rocket to $8 as Focus Shifts to Crypto Majors After Bitcoin's Record Run: Traders]]></title>
        <id>63916677-2e5f-47e3-9059-f526edc85b38</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/23/xrp-could-rocket-to-8-as-focus-shifts-to-crypto-majors-after-bitcoins-record-run-traders"/>
        <updated>2025-05-23T05:33:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Traders are rotating into major altcoins like XRP and Solana’s SOL as bitcoin consolidates near its record highs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shaurya Malwa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[John Carmack talk at Upper Bound 2025]]></title>
        <id>https://twitter.com/ID_AA_Carmack/status/1925710474366034326</id>
        <link href="https://twitter.com/ID_AA_Carmack/status/1925710474366034326"/>
        <updated>2025-05-23T05:14:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[After GPT-4o backlash, researchers benchmark models on moral endorsement—find sycophancy persists across the board]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008691</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/after-gpt-4o-backlash-researchers-benchmark-models-on-moral-endorsement-find-sycophancy-persists-across-the-board/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-22T23:46:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new benchmark can test how much LLMs become sycophants, and found that GPT-4o was the most sycophantic of the models tested.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Emilia David</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Memecoin Moo Deng, MEW Surges After Robinhood Listing]]></title>
        <id>045b859b-4a96-468a-930e-c896c2a17b78</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/22/memecoin-moo-deng-mew-surges-after-robinhood-listing"/>
        <updated>2025-05-22T21:27:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Both tokens jumped on the news, adding to their already large gains this month.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Helene Braun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn Vue.js in This Beginner's Course]]></title>
        <id>682f84537a13a40bfa336307</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-vuejs-in-this-beginners-course/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-22T20:08:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you’ve been meaning to add Vue.js to your front-end toolbelt, today’s your day. We just published a full, 6-hour Vue 3 course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel. Instructor Bhrugen Patel walks you through everything you need to build modern, ...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BlockTrust IRA Brings Quant Trading Tools to Crypto Retirement Accounts]]></title>
        <id>a5315ae8-f5e0-44d7-a384-5068f2df64aa</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/22/blocktrust-ira-brings-quant-trading-tools-to-crypto-retirement-accounts"/>
        <updated>2025-05-22T19:16:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By leveraging trading signals from Animus Technologies, BlockTrust IRA promises to beat benchmark BTC and ETH positions.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tom Carreras</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Anthropic faces backlash to Claude 4 Opus behavior that contacts authorities, press if it thinks you’re doing something ‘egregiously immoral’]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008672</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/anthropic-faces-backlash-to-claude-4-opus-behavior-that-contacts-authorities-press-if-it-thinks-youre-doing-something-immoral/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-22T19:12:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bowman later edited his tweet and the following one in a thread to read as follows, but it still didn't convince the naysayers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carl Franzen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Major Wake-Up Call': How $400M Coinbase Breach Exposes Crypto's Dark Side]]></title>
        <id>6ba27993-c6da-4035-876c-4ecc7282f4c4</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2025/05/22/major-wake-up-call-how-usd400m-coinbase-breach-exposes-crypto-s-dark-side"/>
        <updated>2025-05-22T18:21:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase said 69,461 customers were initially impacted by the breach, but fears remain over the threat of real-world robberies.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Oliver Knight</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Centrifuge Expands Tokenized RWAs to Solana, Starting With $400M Treasury Fund]]></title>
        <id>b7b95f56-2902-4daa-a192-c48b5b4a2397</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/22/centrifuge-expands-tokenized-rwas-to-solana-starting-with-400m-treasury-fund"/>
        <updated>2025-05-22T18:18:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Solana is gaining momentum in the fast-growing tokenized real-world asset space as traditional finance and DeFi gets increasingly intertwined.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Krisztian Sandor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Democrats Threaten Lawsuits, Join Protests Ahead of Trump Memecoin Dinner]]></title>
        <id>f7b1009d-92f3-48ba-bdf1-a1ec95b8d506</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2025/05/22/democrats-threaten-lawsuits-join-protests-ahead-of-trump-memecoin-dinner"/>
        <updated>2025-05-22T18:06:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Democratic lawmakers went through a flurry of actions to highlight concerns that Donald Trump's memecoin dinner is "corrupt."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jesse Hamilton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Anthropic’s new hybrid AI model can work on tasks autonomously for hours at a time]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1117338</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/05/22/1117338/anthropics-new-hybrid-ai-model-can-work-on-tasks-autonomously-for-hours-at-a-time/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-22T16:51:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Anthropic has announced two new AI models that it claims represent a major step toward making AI agents truly useful. AI agents trained on Claude Opus 4, the company’s most powerful model to date, raise the bar for what such systems are capable of by tackling difficult tasks over extended periods of time and responding…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rhiannon Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Anthropic overtakes OpenAI: Claude Opus 4 codes seven hours nonstop, sets record SWE-Bench score and reshapes enterprise AI]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008575</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/anthropic-claude-opus-4-can-code-for-7-hours-straight-and-its-about-to-change-how-we-work-with-ai/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-22T16:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Anthropic's Claude Opus 4 outperforms OpenAI's GPT-4.1 with unprecedented seven-hour autonomous coding sessions and record-breaking 72.5% SWE-bench score, transforming AI from quick-response tool to day-long collaborator.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Nuñez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Major TradFi Institutions to Pursue Tokenization Efforts on Solana]]></title>
        <id>1e9f7d9e-f627-457a-8dda-a93e35c00f69</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2025/05/22/major-tradfi-institutions-to-pursue-tokenization-efforts-on-solana"/>
        <updated>2025-05-22T16:12:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tokenization is one of the principal use cases of blockchain technology attracting the attention and investment of the TradFi world]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Crawley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Justin Sun-Linked Wallet Leading Access to Trump Dinner Tagged as Belonging to HTX]]></title>
        <id>bca545d8-d0c9-4cfa-a211-44f6c0f97575</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2025/05/22/justin-sun-linked-wallet-leading-access-to-trump-dinner-tagged-as-belonging-to-htx"/>
        <updated>2025-05-22T16:05:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sun, a Chinese-born crypto billionaire, is also involved with the Trump-linked ecosystem through a $75 million investment in World Liberty Financial.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Francisco Rodrigues</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Deploy Your FastAPI + PostgreSQL App on Render: A Beginner's Guide]]></title>
        <id>682f4900bcc94cb9bccbf905</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/deploy-fastapi-postgresql-app-on-render/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-22T15:55:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This guide is a comprehensive roadmap for deploying a FastAPI backend connected to a PostgreSQL database using Render, a cloud platform that supports hosting Python web apps and managed PostgreSQL databases.   You can find the complete source code he...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Preston Osoro</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kraken to List Tokenized Version of Nvidia, Apple, Tesla Shares]]></title>
        <id>3b9fba56-daf9-4556-b83f-f6eaa28ad999</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/22/kraken-to-list-tokenized-version-of-nvidia-apple-tesla-shares"/>
        <updated>2025-05-22T15:55:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The tokens will be deployed on Solana and backed by real securities held by Kraken’s partner, Backed Finance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Helene Braun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[First U.S. XRP Futures ETF Begins Trading on Nasdaq]]></title>
        <id>0a64f011-e949-485d-b984-18f3a3d2971d</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/22/first-u-s-xrp-futures-etf-begins-trading-on-nasdaq"/>
        <updated>2025-05-22T15:53:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The fund will invest at least 80% of its assets in XRP futures contracts and shares of other XRP-linked exchange-traded products.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Helene Braun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[An Animated Introduction to Elixir]]></title>
        <id>682f44e3dcb21c615cf1a12d</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/an-animated-introduction-to-elixir/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-22T15:38:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Elixir is a dynamic, functional programming language designed for building scalable and maintainable applications. It leverages the battle-tested Erlang VM, known for running low-latency, distributed, and fault-tolerant systems. Elixir is based on an...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mark Mahoney</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Time Magazine appears to accidentally publish embargoed story confirming new Anthropic model]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008649</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/time-magazine-appears-to-accidentally-publish-embargoed-story-confirming-anthropic-claude-4-opus/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-22T15:26:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Someone also appears to have published a full scrape of the Time article online on the news aggregator app Newsbreak.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carl Franzen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto for Advisors: When Crypto Meets Netflix]]></title>
        <id>7f516d56-430a-487d-90aa-11357443c3c4</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/coindesk-indices/2025/05/21/crypto-for-advisors-when-crypto-meets-netflix"/>
        <updated>2025-05-22T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How Black Mirror’s on-chain experiment is paving the way for the future of entertainment monetization.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shivani Phull</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Global Dollar's USDG Eyes Hundreds of Partners Attracted by Yield, Sees 'Big Names' From TradFi]]></title>
        <id>e068c52f-e6b5-46e8-922b-4e6fa9097240</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2025/05/22/stablecoin-consortium-usdg-will-see-thousands-of-firms-joining-says-kraken"/>
        <updated>2025-05-22T14:11:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Banks and large TradFi firms are preparing to join the Global Dollar network alongside firms like Robinhood, Galaxy and Anchorage, founding member Kraken said.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ian Allison</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trump-Backed World Liberty Financial Buys BUILDon Token, Sending the Price Up 1,340%]]></title>
        <id>e2071d8e-6d14-4cba-a7c9-fcba8dd0ab18</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2025/05/22/trump-backed-crypto-project-buys-buildon-token-sending-prices-up-1-340"/>
        <updated>2025-05-22T14:00:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The token had a market cap of just $40 million before the purchase.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Oliver Knight</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Texas Moves Closer to Setting Up Strategic Bitcoin Reserve as Bill Passes House]]></title>
        <id>dde56905-9e4c-4e9a-b312-d3e487c7dc24</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2025/05/22/texas-moves-closer-to-setting-up-strategic-bitcoin-reserve-as-bill-passes-house"/>
        <updated>2025-05-22T13:39:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The House voted in favor of Senate Bill 121 which would establish a "Texas Strategic Bitcoin Reserve for the purpose of investing in cryptocurrency"]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Crawley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Enchant launches zero-equity accelerator for gaming and AI startups]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008571</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/games/enchant-launches-zero-equity-accelerator-for-gaming-and-ai-startups/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-22T12:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Enchant is launching a new zero-equity accelerator for gaming and AI startups, with applications now open for its three-month program.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dean Takahashi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Download: the desert data center boom, and how to measure Earth’s elevations]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1117300</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/05/22/1117300/the-download-the-desert-data-center-boom-and-how-to-measure-earths-elevations/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-22T12:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is today’s edition of The Download, our weekday newsletter that provides a daily dose of what’s going on in the world of technology. The data center boom in the desert In the high desert east of Reno, Nevada, construction crews are flattening the golden foothills of the Virginia Range, laying the foundations of a data center…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rhiannon Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Machinist and Machine]]></title>
        <id>https://punkx.org/jackdoe/misery.html</id>
        <link href="https://punkx.org/jackdoe/misery.html"/>
        <updated>2025-05-22T10:57:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Three takeaways about AI’s energy use and climate impacts]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1117277</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/05/22/1117277/ai-energy-three-takeaways/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-22T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This week, we published Power Hungry, a package all about AI and energy. At the center of this package is the most comprehensive look yet at AI’s growing power demand, if I do say so myself.  This data-heavy story is the result of over six months of reporting by me and my colleague James O’Donnell…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Casey Crownhart</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A new atomic clock in space could help us measure elevations on Earth]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1117294</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/05/22/1117294/a-new-atomic-clock-in-space-could-help-us-measure-elevations-on-earth/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-22T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In 2003, engineers from Germany and Switzerland began building a bridge across the Rhine River simultaneously from both sides. Months into construction, they found that the two sides did not meet. The German side hovered 54 centimeters above the Swiss side. The misalignment occurred because the German engineers had measured elevation with a historic level…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sophia Chen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[At Google I/O, Sergey Brin makes surprise appearance — and declares Google will build the first AGI]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008490</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/at-google-i-o-sergey-brin-makes-surprise-appearance-and-declares-google-will-build-the-first-agi/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-21T22:20:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google co-founder Sergey Brin makes surprise appearance at Google I/O, declaring "Gemini will be the very first AGI," revealing philosophical tensions with DeepMind CEO Hassabis who urges scientific caution in the high-stakes AI race.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Nuñez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Master Database Management Systems]]></title>
        <id>682e3c04117e792e5f46edc3</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/master-database-management-systems/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-21T20:48:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Understanding how to manage data effectively is a critical skill for anyone pursuing a career in tech. And we just published a course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will teach you all about Database Management Systems (DBMS). This in-de...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Roundtables: A New Look at AI’s Energy Use]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1117287</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/05/21/1117287/roundtables-a-new-look-at-ais-energy-use-2/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-21T19:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Recorded on May 21, 2025 Big Tech’s appetite for energy is growing rapidly as adoption of AI accelerates. But just how much energy does even a single AI query use? And what does it mean for the climate? Hear from MIT Technology Review editor in chief Mat Honan, senior climate reporter Casey Crownhart, and AI reporter James…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>MIT Technology Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Refactor Complex Codebases – A Practical Guide for Devs]]></title>
        <id>682df5a0f2057ab279952dbe</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-refactor-complex-codebases/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-21T15:47:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Developers often see refactoring as a secondary concern that they can delay indefinitely because it doesn’t immediately contribute to revenue or feature development. And managers frequently view refactoring as "not a business need" until it boils ove...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ankur Tyagi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Vibe Coding Won't Destroy Software Engineering]]></title>
        <id>682df55da72360814bcae9ef</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/why-vibe-coding-wont-destroy-software-engineering/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-21T15:46:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AI is disrupting all industries at a pace not seen at any time in history. Technologies and industries that were once dominated by one or two companies or were very much “human-focused” are coming under threat. Google is losing ground to AI search, t...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ben</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OpenAI updates its new Responses API rapidly with MCP support, GPT-4o native image gen, and more enterprise features]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008465</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/programming-development/openai-updates-its-new-responses-api-rapidly-with-mcp-support-gpt-4o-native-image-gen-and-more-enterprise-features/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-21T15:30:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Support for remote Model Context Protocol servers, integration of image generation and Code Interpreter tools, and upgrades to file search...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carl Franzen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mistral AI launches Devstral, powerful new open source SWE agent model that runs on laptops]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008458</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/mistral-ai-launches-devstral-powerful-new-open-source-swe-agent-model-that-runs-on-laptops/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-21T14:57:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Beyond performance and portability, its Apache 2.0 license offers a compelling proposition for commercial applications.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carl Franzen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Download: Google’s AI mission, and America’s reliance on natural gas]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1117249</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/05/21/1117249/the-download-googles-ai-mission-and-americas-reliance-on-natural-gas/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-21T12:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is today’s edition of The Download, our weekday newsletter that provides a daily dose of what’s going on in the world of technology. By putting AI into everything, Google wants to make it invisible If you want to know where AI is headed, this year’s Google I/O has you covered. The company’s annual showcase of next-gen…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rhiannon Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Curious Case of the Pygmy Nuthatch]]></title>
        <id>https://slate.com/culture/2025/05/birds-movies-charlies-angels-2000-pygmy-nuthatch.html</id>
        <link href="https://slate.com/culture/2025/05/birds-movies-charlies-angels-2000-pygmy-nuthatch.html"/>
        <updated>2025-05-21T11:52:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[By putting AI into everything, Google wants to make it invisible]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1117251</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/05/21/1117251/by-putting-ai-into-everything-google-wants-to-make-it-invisible/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-21T11:49:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you want to know where AI is headed, this year’s Google I/O has you covered. The company’s annual showcase of next-gen products, which kicked off yesterday, has all of the pomp and pizzazz, the sizzle reels and celebrity walk-ons, that you’d expect from a multimillion-dollar marketing event. But it also shows us just how…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Will Douglas Heaven</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AMD unveils new Threadripper CPUs and Radeon GPUs for gamers at Computex 2025]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008206</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/games/amd-unveils-new-threadripper-cpus-and-radeon-gpus-for-gamers-at-computex-2025/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-21T03:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AMD held a Computex press event to introduce its Radeon RX 9060 XT graphics cards and Threadripper CPUs for next-gen gaming and workstations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dean Takahashi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google finally launches NotebookLM mobile app at I/O: hands-on, first impressions]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008400</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/google-finally-launches-notebooklm-mobile-app-at-i-o-hands-on-first-impressions/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T19:29:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As NotebookLM matures, its emerging business-tier capabilities suggest growing alignment with the productivity and compliance...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carl Franzen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google just leapfrogged every competitor with mind-blowing AI that can think deeper, shop smarter, and create videos with dialogue]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008346</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/google-just-leapfrogged-every-competitor-with-mind-blowing-ai-that-can-think-deeper-shop-smarter-and-create-videos-with-dialogue/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T17:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google unveiled major AI advancements at I/O 2025, including Gemini 2.5 with Deep Think, AI Mode in Search, Veo 3 for video with audio, and a $249 Ultra plan aimed at power users and enterprises.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Nuñez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google’s Jules aims to out-code Codex in battle for the AI developer stack]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008361</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/googles-jules-aims-to-out-code-codex-in-battle-for-the-ai-developer-stack/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T17:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google released Jules, its coding agent, into beta as autonomous coding agents are quickly gaining market share.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Emilia David</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Inside Google’s AI leap: Gemini 2.5 thinks deeper, speaks smarter and codes faster]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008366</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/inside-google-ai-leap-gemini-2-5-thinks-deeper-speaks-smarter-codes-faster/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T17:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google is moving closer to its goal of autonomous agentic AI with a series of enhancements to Gemini 2.5 Pro and Flash.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Taryn Plumb</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blazing-fast Solana data via gRPC: access the freshest Solana data from Shredstream leaders]]></title>
        <id>68273f14bf73460001094b35</id>
        <link href="https://blog.quicknode.com/yellowstone-grpc/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T15:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Access the fastest Solana data with the Yellowstone Geyser gRPC self-serve add-on or with the premium hybrid dedicated gRPC node.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>QuickNode</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Christopher Hill's History from Below]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thenation.com/article/society/christopher-hill-life-of/</id>
        <link href="https://www.thenation.com/article/society/christopher-hill-life-of/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T05:23:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft just launched an AI that discovered a new chemical in 200 hours instead of years]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008310</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/microsoft-just-launched-an-ai-that-discovered-a-new-chemical-in-200-hours-instead-of-years/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T18:34:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft launches Discovery platform that uses agentic AI to compress years of scientific research into days, transforming R&D across pharmaceuticals, materials science, and semiconductor industries.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Nuñez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Designing type inference for high quality type errors]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.polybdenum.com/2025/02/14/designing-type-inference-for-high-quality-type-errors.html</id>
        <link href="https://blog.polybdenum.com/2025/02/14/designing-type-inference-for-high-quality-type-errors.html"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T18:22:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Is your AI app pissing off users or going off-script? Raindrop emerges with AI-native observability platform to monitor performance]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008299</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/is-your-ai-app-pissing-off-users-or-going-off-script-raindrop-emerges-with-ai-native-observability-platform-to-monitor-performance/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T18:09:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With its rebrand and product expansion, Raindrop is betting that the next generation of software observability will be AI-first by design.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carl Franzen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft just taught its AI agents to talk to each other—and it could transform how we work]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008254</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/microsoft-just-taught-its-ai-agents-to-talk-to-each-other-and-it-could-transform-how-we-work/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T16:01:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft unveils multi-agent systems, WhatsApp integration, and Python-powered analytics for Copilot Studio at Build 2025, transforming how enterprises build and deploy AI solutions.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Nuñez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Microsoft Fabric has already been adopted by 70% of the Fortune 500 — and what’s next]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3007980</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/70-of-the-fortune-500-already-use-microsoft-fabric-and-its-now-getting-even-more-features-including-cosmosdb-support/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft integrates CosmosDB into Fabric, open sources DiskANN vector search, and unifies its data platforms to eliminate integration complexity that has slowed enterprise AI adoption.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sean Michael Kerner</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub Copilot evolves into autonomous agent with asynchronous code testing]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008231</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/github-copilot-evolves-into-autonomous-agent-with-asynchronous-code-testing/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub adds agentic capabilities to its Copilot coding assistant, competing with other more asynchronous coding platforms.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Emilia David</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft announces over 50 AI tools to build the ‘agentic web’ at Build 2025]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008229</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/microsoft-announces-over-50-ai-tools-to-build-the-agentic-web-at-build-2025/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T15:59:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft reveals its ambitious AI agent strategy, showcasing how multi-agent systems with persistent memory will transform enterprise workflows and accelerate development timelines.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Nuñez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Reddit, Webflow, and Superhuman are already customers—now GrowthX has $12M to grow]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008276</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/reddit-webflow-and-superhuman-are-already-customers-now-growthx-has-12m-to-grow/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[GrowthX secures $12M in funding for its "service-as-software" platform that combines AI with human expertise to boost content marketing results by up to 300%.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Nuñez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Quantum Machines launches Qualibrate open source framework to speed quantum computer calibration]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008032</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/games/quantum-machines-launches-qualibrate-open-source-framework-to-speed-quantum-computer-calibration/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Quantum Machines, a provider of advanced hybrid quantum-classical control solutions, announced today the release of Qualibrate.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dean Takahashi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Samsung boosts OLED TV gaming with Nvidia G-Sync compatibility]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008019</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/games/samsung-boosts-oled-tv-gaming-with-nvidia-g-sync-compatibility/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Samsung said its 2025 OLED TV lineup will feature Nvidia G-Sync compatibility, delivering smooth gameplay, low latency, and more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dean Takahashi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Salesforce just unveiled AI ‘digital teammates’ in Slack — and they’re coming for Microsoft Copilot]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008273</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/salesforce-just-unveiled-ai-digital-teammates-in-slack-and-theyre-coming-for-microsoft-copilot/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Salesforce launches Agentforce in Slack, transforming workplace productivity with specialized AI agents that operate as digital teammates, replacing one-size-fits-all AI assistants with purpose-built solutions.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Nuñez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Foxconn builds AI factory in partnership with Taiwan and Nvidia]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008261</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/games/foxconn-builds-ai-factory-in-partnership-with-taiwan-and-nvidia/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T07:14:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nvidia and Foxconn announced they are working with the Taiwan government to build an AI factory supercomputer.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dean Takahashi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nvidia launches AI-first DGX Personal Computing Systems]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008256</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/games/nvidia-launches-ai-first-dgx-personal-computing-systems/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T07:06:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nvidia announced that Taiwan’s leading system manufacturers are set to build Nvidia DGX Spark and DGX Station systems.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dean Takahashi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is Sui: A Comprehensive Guide to Web3 Scalability]]></title>
        <id>6823533984101f00013a5ca4</id>
        <link href="https://blog.quicknode.com/what-is-sui-a-comprehensive-guide-to-web3-scalability/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-15T23:34:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Explore how Sui Network achieves 300,000 TPS through parallel processing, and its applications in gaming, DeFi, and supply chain management.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>QuickNode</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AI Meets Blockchain: Transforming Technology for the Next Era]]></title>
        <id>682354c584101f00013a5cb9</id>
        <link href="https://blog.quicknode.com/ai-and-blockchain-transforming-technology-together/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-15T23:34:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discover how AI and blockchain integration enhances security, efficiency, and innovation in healthcare, supply chains, and financial services.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>QuickNode</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Adventure Layer: AI Native Onchain Games, Unleashed]]></title>
        <id>6824c55abf73460001094973</id>
        <link href="https://blog.quicknode.com/adventure-layer-launches-on-quicknode-raas/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-15T12:04:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Adventure Layer launches layer-2 chain leveraging QuickNode's Rollup-as-a-Service (RaaS) product.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>QuickNode</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[QuickLee V2: An Improved Transparent Look into RPC Provider Latency]]></title>
        <id>680fc8e1f8ae810001969b47</id>
        <link href="https://blog.quicknode.com/quicklee-v2/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-14T13:57:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[View public and real-time dashboards to better understand latency and speed when evaluating RPC providers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>QuickNode</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>