<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2025-05-23T11:11:42.200Z</id>
    <title>AngJianming RSS Feed</title>
    <updated>2025-05-23T11:11:42.200Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Top 7 Microsoft 365 Apps Every Business Should Use in 2025]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/aadarsh_6c0f2d089d67a8a0a/top-7-microsoft-365-apps-every-business-should-use-in-2025-30cp</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/aadarsh_6c0f2d089d67a8a0a/top-7-microsoft-365-apps-every-business-should-use-in-2025-30cp"/>
        <updated>2025-05-23T10:59:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Top 7 Microsoft 365 Apps Every Business Should Use in 2025


In today's fast-moving digital world, businesses need more than just basic tools — they need smart, connected solutions that improve productivity, simplify communication, and ensure data security. That’s where Microsoft 365 Apps for Business comes in.
Packed with powerful apps like Word, Excel, Outlook, Teams, and OneDrive, Microsoft 365 is more than just office software — it’s a complete productivity suite for modern businesses.
In this post, we’ll explore the top 7 Microsoft 365 apps every business should use in 2025 and how they can transform your workflow.
Microsoft Word is still the gold standard for creating professional documents — but in Microsoft 365, it’s taken to the next level:
✍️ Real-time collaboration: Multiple peo…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>aadarsh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Maximizing Efficiency with Fleet Fuel Management: The Smart Move for Modern Fleet Operations]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/hypernym_io/maximizing-efficiency-with-fleet-fuel-management-the-smart-move-for-modern-fleet-operations-47bi</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/hypernym_io/maximizing-efficiency-with-fleet-fuel-management-the-smart-move-for-modern-fleet-operations-47bi"/>
        <updated>2025-05-23T10:59:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In today’s fast-paced transportation landscape, fleet fuel management is more than a cost-saving tactic—it's a strategic pillar of successful fleet operations. As fuel prices fluctuate and sustainability becomes a growing priority, fleet managers are turning to intelligent solutions to manage resources efficiently. At the core of this transformation is the Hypernym Fleet Management System, a powerful platform that puts fleet fuel management and operational control in the palm of your hand.
Let’s explore how Hypernym is changing the game, and why integrated fleet management and telematics are vital to fuel efficiency and long-term success.
Fleet fuel management is the process of monitoring, controlling, and optimizing fuel consumption across a fleet of vehicles. But it's not just about trac…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hypernym_io</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[🎓 How to become a product data expert with Sentric Academy (free and online)]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/irene_beghini/how-to-become-a-product-data-expert-with-sentric-academy-free-and-online-40e4</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/irene_beghini/how-to-become-a-product-data-expert-with-sentric-academy-free-and-online-40e4"/>
        <updated>2025-05-23T10:57:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[💭 Have you ever had to manage dozens of spreadsheets, sync product descriptions across e-commerce, ERPs, catalogs... and not even know where to start?
If you work with structured data, APIs, or integrated systems, you already know: the real skill today is managing information — not just writing code.
This is where Sentric Academy comes in.

A technical training platform created for developers, digital agencies, freelancers, and anyone who wants to truly master product data management.
A free online platform, built by the team behind Sentric, designed to help you:
Understand how the system works

Use it independently

Integrate it into your stack (CMS, PIM, ERP, custom APIs...)
You don’t have to be an expert already: the Academy is also ideal for those just getting started who want to lear…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Irene Beghini</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[🚀 Yo devs, wanna build collab apps that SLAP? Meet Jazz: the Real-Time Collab Framework That’s Straight Fire 🔥]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/vikyw89/yo-devs-wanna-build-collab-apps-that-slap-meet-jazz-the-real-time-collab-framework-thats-23o</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/vikyw89/yo-devs-wanna-build-collab-apps-that-slap-meet-jazz-the-real-time-collab-framework-thats-23o"/>
        <updated>2025-05-23T10:51:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What’s up, code fam? If you’re tired of boring, laggy apps and want your squad to vibe together in real time (securely, obvi), you gotta peep Jazz by Garden Co. This open-source baddie is here to make your next project hit different. Let’s get into it:
✨ Why Jazz is a Whole Mood
Real-Time Sync, No Cap: Your data updates instantly across all devices. No more “wait, did you save?” drama. It’s all live, all the time.
Offline? Still Vibing: Even if your WiFi ghosts you, Jazz keeps your changes safe and syncs up when you’re back online. Resilient AF.
Squad Goals = Collab: Multiple peeps can work together, edit, and see changes in real time. Think Google Docs energy, but for anything you wanna build.
End-to-End Encryption: Your tea stays private. Jazz encrypts everything so haters and hackers ca…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>viky</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MySQL for beginners]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/matheusfrg/mysql-for-beginners-1441</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/matheusfrg/mysql-for-beginners-1441"/>
        <updated>2025-05-23T10:50:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What is MySQL?


MySQL is a relational database management system (RDBMS) that lets you store, organize, and retrieve data using SQL (Structured Query Language). It’s one of the most popular databases in the world — trusted by companies like Facebook, YouTube, and GitHub.
Structured storage with tables, columns, and rows
Powerful queries using SELECT, JOIN, WHERE, and more 
Secure data handling with user privileges and roles
Fast performance, scalability, and reliability
Ideal for real-world applications: from user accounts to e-commerce
Whether you're building a simple web app or a complex system, MySQL gives you full control over your data. It's the perfect first step for any developer.
Here an example of MySQL command:
CREATE TABLE products (
    id INT AUTO_INCREMENT PRIMARY KEY,
    name VARCHAR(100),
    price DECIMAL(10, 2),
    created_at TIMESTAMP DEFAULT CURRENT_TIMESTAMP
);

-- Insert a product
INSERT INTO products (name, price) VALUES ('Laptop', 1499.99);

-- Get all products
SELECT * FROM products;`


💬 If you're just starting with MySQL, here are the fundamentals you should focus on first:
📊 What is a Database & Table
🔑 Primary Keys & Data Types
🛠️ Basic SQL Commands
📋 Filtering Data with WHERE
🔗 Table Relationships (JOINs)
🧩 Indexes & Foreign Keys
📦 Normalization
🔐 User Permissions & Security
🗃️ Backup & Restore
Always know how to export and import your data safely.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matheus Gonçalves</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[🚀 Starting My Dev Journey with Node.js! 🌐]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/s_devworld/starting-my-dev-journey-with-nodejs-2d52</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/s_devworld/starting-my-dev-journey-with-nodejs-2d52"/>
        <updated>2025-05-23T10:48:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[**🚀 Starting My Dev Journey with Node.js! 🟢


Hey devs! 👋**

Node.js isn’t just a runtime — it’s freedom for JavaScript developers. It lets you build fast, scalable network applications using JS on the server-side. Think of it as unlocking the full-stack potential of JavaScript. 🌐✨
Why I love Node.js so far:
⚡ Non-blocking I/O — It's built for speed and efficiency.
📦 NPM ecosystem — There’s a package for nearly everything!
🔁 Event-driven architecture — Perfect for handling real-time data.
🔄 Full-stack sync — Using JS across both frontend & backend feels seamless.
Whether you're building a REST API, a real-time chat app, or a microservice, Node.js has your back.
This is just the beginning — I'm diving deeper into Express.js next and can’t wait to share more as I learn. If you're working with Node.js too, I’d love to hear your favorite tips, tools, or projects! 🛠️💬


  
  
  NodeJS #WebDevelopment #JavaScript #DevJourney #BackendDevelopment]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shivesh Mishra</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[When “Leadership” Becomes Abuse in Disguise]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/formantaudio/when-leadership-becomes-abuse-in-disguise-3lem</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/formantaudio/when-leadership-becomes-abuse-in-disguise-3lem"/>
        <updated>2025-05-23T10:46:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Lately, I’ve been seeing stories that genuinely shock me - managers deliberately sabotaging production, creating chaos, or manipulating deadlines just to see how their devs react under pressure.  
Let’s be clear: this isn’t leadership. This is abuse.  
You don’t build trust or resilience by throwing your team into trauma scenarios. You don’t foster collaboration by making people suffer. And you definitely don’t promote “team skills” by manufacturing stress. That’s not psychological safety - that’s psychological warfare.  
If this happened in any other field - construction, demolition, food service - the manager would be gone. Immediately. Because putting people at risk for the sake of your curiosity or ego is unacceptable.  
Just because developers work at desks doesn’t mean they aren’t affected. Burnout is real. Mental exhaustion is real. People leave not because they’re weak - but because they’re being used as stress test dummies.  
You don’t test loyalty by creating chaos. You earn it by creating clarity.

You don’t build team skills through sabotage. You build them through support.  
We need to stop celebrating toxic “leadership” and start holding it accountable.  
Written by Tyler Johnston-Kent

Check out more work at [https://www.formant.ca]


  
  
  leadership #burnout #mentalhealth #softwareengineering #devlife #workculture]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tyler Johnston-Kent</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pneumocephalus as well as Facial Drop by using an Aircraft: In a situation Document.]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/patchhall71/pneumocephalus-as-well-as-facial-drop-by-using-an-aircraft-in-a-situation-document-209c</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/patchhall71/pneumocephalus-as-well-as-facial-drop-by-using-an-aircraft-in-a-situation-document-209c"/>
        <updated>2025-05-23T10:39:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The research unequivocally demonstrates that TFAP2C warrants consideration as a valuable biomarker for the prevention and treatment of psoriasis. 
Estimated to affect 21 to 67% of children and adolescents, urticaria is a common disorder, which commonly necessitates emergency department admissions. 
In the atopic condition known as allergic rhinitis (AR), the immune system's response to environmental factors manifests as clinical symptoms. Helicobacter pylori's neutrophil-activating protein (HP-NAP), a peptide, acts to reduce Th2 responses and encourage Th1 activity; the mucus-binding cell-surface protein MapA binds to mucosal lining. This study investigated the impact of HP-NAP and MapA, when combined with alumina nanoparticles, on the expression of AR. Alumina nanoparticles were conjugate…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Larsson McGarry</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chanel Boy Small Bag: The Ultimate Guide to This Iconic Handbag]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/anitaterry/chanel-boy-small-bag-the-ultimate-guide-to-this-iconic-handbag-37k0</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/anitaterry/chanel-boy-small-bag-the-ultimate-guide-to-this-iconic-handbag-37k0"/>
        <updated>2025-05-23T10:36:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Chanel Boy Bag marks one of the celebrated design in the history of luxury fashion houses. One of the most remarkable bags in a collection was launched in 2011 by Karl Lagerfeld, who was inspired by Gabrielle Chanel's androgynous style and admiration for practical pieces. Unlike the classic Chanel flap bags, the Boy Bag is bold and edgy, modern, which makes it stand out from the rest, especially amongst trendsetting individuals. It features strong lines, a signature rectangular lock with a chunky strap that displays contemporary appeal while maintaining achingly timeless elegance. View Chanel Boy Small for sale - LuxuryEvermore for More Details
The Chanel Boy Bag comes with Small, Medium, New Medium and Large sizes, each addressing style preferences and differing functional needs. Cost…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Anita Terry</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Smart Way UAE Businesses Are Using Salesforce to Win Customers]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/ameliajohnss/the-smart-way-uae-businesses-are-using-salesforce-to-win-customers-6f</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/ameliajohnss/the-smart-way-uae-businesses-are-using-salesforce-to-win-customers-6f"/>
        <updated>2025-05-23T10:36:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In an era where customer experience drives market dominance, UAE companies are turning to Salesforce as more than just a CRM — it’s becoming a core business enabler.
But unlocking its full potential requires more than implementation. It calls for a tailored strategy that aligns with regional nuances, growth ambitions, and digital maturity.

What it takes:
Customize Salesforce to reflect UAE business culture and customer expectations
Read the full blog here]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>amelia.johnss</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[EmailJS in a Next.js]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/syedmurtjiz/emailjs-in-a-nextjs-application-30k6</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/syedmurtjiz/emailjs-in-a-nextjs-application-30k6"/>
        <updated>2025-05-23T10:34:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[(Step-by-Step Guide)
Create an email account on email.js (https://www.emailjs.com)


Sign up and log in to your account


Connect or link your email with email.js 


Then the following page will be shown



Then click on Gmail when the services open



Then, click on the Connect Account Button to connect your email. After that, click on the create service button



After creation, you will get service from that



Then Click on Email Template 



Then click on the Create New Template Button




Then click on the Create Template button



Then, set the template that you want and click the save button 



Then, go back to the Email Template and get your templateId



Then open the account from the left sidebar and get your public key



After that Install EmailJS in Next.js
npm install @emai…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Murtjiz Naqvi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Photo Essay: Kingston At Computex 2025]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=353600</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/353600/kingston-computex-2025/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-23T10:34:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kingston is and always has been a mainstay at Computex 2025. This year, the memory maker gave us a brief tour of its achievements, as well as some new products we can expect. Perhaps one of the brand’s proudest achievements was how much its products was being used in the AI and more specifically, the […]
The post Photo Essay: Kingston At Computex 2025 appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John Law</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Your Computer Sucks? Blame Your Weak Will (and Maybe Hanish)]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/ladoxer/your-computer-sucks-blame-your-weak-will-and-maybe-hanish-5752</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/ladoxer/your-computer-sucks-blame-your-weak-will-and-maybe-hanish-5752"/>
        <updated>2025-05-23T10:23:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Let's be real, guys. Nothing grinds our gears more than tech that can't keep up. You're trying to crush the competition in that game, or maybe just trying to watch the highlights without buffering every two seconds, and BAM! Frozen screen. You feel that primal rage building, right? That's your inner caveman screaming for efficiency. And if you're anything like my buddy Hanish, his inner caveman goes full berserker. Dude once headbutted his router because Netflix was lagging. True story.
Now, some egghead philosopher named Nietzsche (don't worry, I can barely pronounce it either) had this idea about the "will to power." Basically, it's the manly urge to get better, to dominate challenges, and to generally be more awesome. Think about hitting the gym and pushing yourself to lift more – that'…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Muhammed Labeeb</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cetus offers $6M bounty after $220M hack as Sui faces decentralization debate]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/cetus-6m-white-hat-bounty-of-stolen-220m</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/cetus-6m-white-hat-bounty-of-stolen-220m?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-23T10:01:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cetus is offering a $6 million white hat bounty in an effort to recover $220 million in stolen digital assets, while emergency responses from the Sui Network have raised concerns about decentralization.
Sui-native decentralized exchange (DEX) Cetus was exploited for over $220 million worth of cryptocurrency on May 22. However, Cetus managed to freeze $162 million of the stolen funds shortly after.
Cetus has since offered a white hat bounty of up to $6 million for the exploiter for returning the stolen 20,920 Ether (ETH), worth over $55 million, along with the rest of the stolen funds currently frozen on the Sui blockchain.
“In exchange, you can keep 2,324 ETH ($6M) as a bounty, and we will consider the matter closed and will not pursue any further legal, intelligence, or public action,” Ce…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Zoltan Vardai</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Xiaomi YU7 Unveiled In China; Comes In 3 Variants]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=353577</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/353577/xiaomi-yu7-unveiled-in-china-comes-in-3-variants/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-23T09:59:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Xiaomi’s second fully electric (EV) model, the YU7 SUV, was unveiled yesterday in conjunction with the company’s 15th-year anniversary. The EV SUV is offered in three configurations: rear-wheel drive (RWD), all-wheel drive (AWD) and Max AWD. As previously reported, the YU7 SUV shares many design elements with the SU7 sedan, including the closed grille, distinctive […]
The post Xiaomi YU7 Unveiled In China; Comes In 3 Variants appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Keran</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OpenAI: Scaling PostgreSQL to the Next Level]]></title>
        <id>https://www.pixelstech.net/article/1747708863-openai%3a-scaling-postgresql-to-the-next-level</id>
        <link href="https://www.pixelstech.net/article/1747708863-openai%3a-scaling-postgresql-to-the-next-level"/>
        <updated>2025-05-23T09:54:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Photo Essay: AGi At Computex 2025]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=353596</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/353596/photo-essay-agi-at-computex-2025/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-23T09:42:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’ve said it before and we’ll say it again: AGi isn’t a brand many would be familiar with but the company has been very slowly making a name for itself in the PC memory and storage market. This year, we visited the brand’s booth at Computex 2025 to find out what it’s been doing since […]
The post Photo Essay: AGi At Computex 2025 appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John Law</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Photo Essay: DarkFlash At Computex 2025]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=353236</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/353236/photo-essay-darkflash-at-computex-2025/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-23T09:37:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[DarkFlash was another brand we visited at its booth during Computex 2025. While we’re not entirely familiar with the name, the company does have a reputation of being a manufacturer of components and peripherals. Casings are something of the brand’s speciality, something that it was eager to show off in the form of its all-glass […]
The post Photo Essay: DarkFlash At Computex 2025 appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John Law</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Photo Essay: PNY At Computex 2025]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=353439</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/353439/pny-computex-2025/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-23T09:32:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[During our tour of Computex 2025, we found time to stop by at the PNY booth. As with all GPU makers and given the recent launch of the NVIDIA GeForce RTX 5060 a few days earlier, the brand was presenting its own custom-cooled SKUs, among other things, to the floor. The RTX 5060 series PNY […]
The post Photo Essay: PNY At Computex 2025 appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John Law</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Volkswagen Confirms Golf GTI Will Go Fully Electric]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=353528</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/353528/volkswagen-confirms-golf-gti-will-go-fully-electric/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-23T09:26:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Since its debut in 1976, the Volkswagen Golf GTI has gained a rich history and a legendary status as a performance hatchback in the automaker’s line-up. But, as the automotive world shifts gears towards electrification, even the mighty GTI isn’t immune to change. Behind the scenes, development is already in full swing. Volkswagen’s engineers are […]
The post Volkswagen Confirms Golf GTI Will Go Fully Electric appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Keran</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CFTC’s Plans for Crypto Perpetual Trading Puts Focus on Hyperliquid’s HYPE]]></title>
        <id>780dccef-8a69-4d87-91ae-6203e5ab8d74</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/23/cftcs-plans-for-crypto-perpetual-trading-puts-focus-on-hyperliquids-hype"/>
        <updated>2025-05-23T09:24:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HYPE is up 15% in the past 24 hours, outperforming majors, as developers said they submitted comments to the derivatives agency on using DeFi principles to create better products.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shaurya Malwa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hyperliquid backs 24/7 crypto trading in CFTC comments submission]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/hypehyperliquid-cftc-comments-crypto-derivatives-tradingrliquid</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/hypehyperliquid-cftc-comments-crypto-derivatives-tradingrliquid?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-23T09:09:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hyperliquid, a decentralized perpetuals exchange operating on its own layer-1 blockchain, has submitted formal comments on 24/7 derivatives trading to the United States Commodity Futures Trading Commission (CFTC).
In a May 23 X post, Hyperliquid Labs announced that it has “submitted two comment letters to the [CFTC] in response to its recent Requests for Comment on perpetual derivatives and 24/7 trading.” The team behind the decentralized exchange (DEX) added:
“We commend the CFTC for its proactive engagement on these topics, understanding of which is fundamental to the evolution of global markets.”
Hyperliquid stated that it is committed to the advancement of the decentralized finance (DeFi) space. The team also claimed that its implementation “exemplifies how core DeFi principles can be …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Adrian Zmudzinski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The FDA plans to limit access to covid vaccines. Here’s why that’s not all bad.]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1117329</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/05/23/1117329/fda-limit-access-covid-vaccines/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-23T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This week, two new leaders at the US Food and Drug Administration announced plans to limit access to covid vaccines, arguing that there is not much evidence to support the value of annual shots in healthy people. New vaccines will be made available only to the people who are most vulnerable—namely, those over 65 and…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jessica Hamzelou</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meet Cathy Tie, Bride of “China’s Frankenstein”]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1117373</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/05/23/1117373/cathy-tie-he-jiankui-china-crispr-x-twitter-feed/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-23T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Since the Chinese biophysicist He Jiankui was released from prison in 2022, he has sought to make a scientific comeback and to repair his reputation after a three-year incarceration for illegally creating the world’s first gene-edited children.  While he has bounced between cities, jobs, and meetings with investors, one area of visible success on his…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Caiwei Chen, Antonio Regalado</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Samsung Galaxy Buds Core Appears In Official Support Sites]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=353627</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/353627/samsung-galaxy-buds-core-appears-in-official-support-sites/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-23T08:59:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Samsung Galaxy Buds FE was released back in October of 2023, and the time for a successor may be nigh. Except that it may not be called the Galaxy Buds FE 2, according to reports. New name aside, it may also be close to launch, as its model number has started appearing in support […]
The post Samsung Galaxy Buds Core Appears In Official Support Sites appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ian Chee</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Major U.S. Banks Mull Jointly Launching Stablecoin: WSJ]]></title>
        <id>4c76c31a-f15f-4bf8-af51-2a9c7f7f18bd</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2025/05/23/major-us-banks-mull-jointly-launching-stablecoin-wsj"/>
        <updated>2025-05-23T08:48:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Such a stablecoin, potentially open to other banks, aims to improve transaction speeds and efficiency while fending off competition from crypto firms.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Francisco Rodrigues</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DeFi near-zero onboarding costs can help 1.4B unbanked: 1inch co-founder]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/1inch-cofounder-defi-financial-inclusion-dbw-event</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/1inch-cofounder-defi-financial-inclusion-dbw-event?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-23T08:47:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decentralized finance (DeFi) platforms have a major cost advantage over traditional banks when it comes to onboarding new users, according to Anton Bukov, co-founder of decentralized exchange (DEX) 1inch.
Speaking at a panel during Dutch Blockchain Week on May 22 in Amsterdam, Bukov said traditional banks spend between $100 and $300 per user to verify documents and set up accounts. Online banks, he said, spend about $20 to $30. In contrast, DeFi requires almost nothing beyond a smartphone and internet access.
“Onboarding to DeFi literally costs zero,” Bukov said. “You don’t need brick-and-mortar infrastructure or lengthy verification processes. Just connect and transact.” 
Bukov said that this gives DeFi an edge over traditional financial institutions in reaching the 1.4 billion unbanked p…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Ezra Reguerra</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin buyer dominance at $111K suggests &#039;another wave&#039; of gains]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-buyer-dominance-at-111k-suggests-another-wave-of-gains</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-buyer-dominance-at-111k-suggests-another-wave-of-gains?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-23T08:45:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Key points:

Bitcoin buyer interest remains strong at all-time highs, contrasting with the first touch of $100,000 in 2024.

The BTC price uptrend “may continue” as a result, CryptoQuant analysis concludes.

Bitcoin short-term holders are firmly in the black in a further potential bull market boost.

Bitcoin (BTC) buyers remain dominant on exchanges as all-time highs are met with unusual optimism.
Data from onchain analytics platform CryptoQuant shows a 90-day cumulative volume delta (CVD) favoring Bitcoin bulls.

CryptoQuant: BTC price uptrend “may continue”
BTC price all-time highs continue to find support among traders, with buyers staying dominant despite the market surging 50% in under two months.
Analyzing 90-day CVD, CryptoQuant contributor Ibrahim Cosar reveals the extent to which …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by William Suberg</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Tether refuses to comply with MiCA]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/explained/why-tether-refuses-to-comply-with-mica</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/explained/why-tether-refuses-to-comply-with-mica?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-23T08:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Is Tether MiCA compliant?            
            
                
The EU’s new Markets in Crypto-Assets regulation, better known as MiCA, is the first major attempt by a global economic power to create clear, region-wide rules for the crypto space, and stablecoins are a big focus.
MiCA mandates best practices. If a stablecoin is going to be traded in the EU, its issuer has to follow some stringent rules:
1. You need a license
To issue a stablecoin in Europe, you must become a fully authorized electronic money institution (EMI). That’s the same kind of license traditional fintechs need to offer e-wallets or prepaid cards. It’s not cheap and it’s not quick. 
2. Most of your reserves have to sit in European banks
This is one of the most controversial parts of MiCA. If you issue a “significa…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Bradley Peak</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Alcatel 3 Launches; V3 Classic, Pro Releasing on 27 May]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=353565</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/353565/alcatel-3-launches-v3-classic-pro-releasing-27-may/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-23T08:00:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Alcatel is having quite a busy week. Its V3 Ultra 5G just had its specs revealed on a Flipkart page, confirming its 5,010mAh battery. Now, the brand has quietly launched its Alcatel 3 (2025) phone via its official webpage. In addition to that, a listing on Flipkart reveals that the V3 Classic and Pro phones, […]
The post Alcatel 3 Launches; V3 Classic, Pro Releasing on 27 May appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Newsdesk</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Enters Strongest Accumulation Phase Since January as BTC Price Passes $110K]]></title>
        <id>29205afd-ca8c-4683-93b4-3286329cb66c</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/23/bitcoin-enters-strongest-accumulation-phase-since-january-as-btc-price-passes-110k"/>
        <updated>2025-05-23T07:46:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Glassnode data shows all wallet cohorts are now accumulating, with options markets pricing in potential upside beyond $200K in June.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>James Van Straten</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[College English majors can't read]]></title>
        <id>https://kittenbeloved.substack.com/p/college-english-majors-cant-read</id>
        <link href="https://kittenbeloved.substack.com/p/college-english-majors-cant-read"/>
        <updated>2025-05-23T07:30:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fujifilm Opens Pre-Orders For X Half Camera; Costs RM3,398]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=353560</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/353560/fujifilm-x-half/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-23T06:51:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fujifilm has announced a very unique new digital camera called the X Half, which is inspired by half-frame cameras. The most interesting thing about this camera is, without a doubt, that it shoots stills and videos in a vertical format. The X Half features an 18MP 1-inch 3:4 CMOS sensor with a 10.8mm f/2.8 FUJINON […]
The post Fujifilm Opens Pre-Orders For X Half Camera; Costs RM3,398 appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ikmal Rozlan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[KumoRFM: A Foundation Model for In-Context Learning on Relational Data]]></title>
        <id>https://kumo.ai/company/news/kumo-relational-foundation-model/</id>
        <link href="https://kumo.ai/company/news/kumo-relational-foundation-model/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-23T06:50:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[US big banks hold early talks on joint crypto stablecoin: WSJ]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/us-big-banks-in-talks-for-joint-crypto-stablecoin-wsj</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/us-big-banks-in-talks-for-joint-crypto-stablecoin-wsj?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-23T06:27:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Some of the biggest banking companies in the US are reportedly exploring a team-up to launch a crypto stablecoin.
Companies owned by JPMorgan, Bank of America, Citigroup and Wells Fargo have discussed the possibility of jointly issuing a stablecoin, The Wall Street Journal reported on May 22, citing people familiar with the matter.
Other financial institutions linked to the potential stablecoin include Early Warning Services, the parent company of digital payments network Zelle, and the payment network Clearing House.
The discussions are still in the early stages, and a final decision on the project could change depending on the regulatory environment and the demand for stablecoins.
A JPMorgan spokesperson told Cointelegraph the company had no comment. Bank of America, CitiGroup, and Wells…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Tarang Khaitan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Anthropic’s debuts most powerful AI yet amid ‘whistleblowing’ controversy]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/anthropic-launches-latest-ai-whistleblowing-backlash</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/anthropic-launches-latest-ai-whistleblowing-backlash?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-23T06:13:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Artificial intelligence firm Anthropic has launched the latest generations of its chatbots amid criticism of a testing environment behaviour that could report some users to authorities.
Anthropic unveiled Claude Opus 4 and Claude Sonnet 4 on May 22, claiming that Claude Opus 4 is its most powerful model yet, “and the world’s best coding model,” while Claude Sonnet 4 is a significant upgrade from its predecessor, “delivering superior coding and reasoning.”
The firm added that both upgrades are hybrid models offering two modes — “near-instant responses and extended thinking for deeper reasoning.”
Both AI models can also alternate between reasoning, research and tool use, like web search, to improve responses, it said. 
Anthropic added that Claude Opus 4 outperforms competitors in agentic cod…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Martin Young</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nothing Phone (1) Won’t Get Android 16 Update]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=353547</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/353547/nothing-phone-1-wont-get-android-16-update/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-23T06:06:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As Google prepares to release Android 16 next month, Nothing has confirmed that one of its devices is definitely not going to receive the update. Of course, the device is none other than the company’s very first smartphone, the Nothing Phone (1). A company representative told Android Authority that the Nothing Phone (1) will not […]
The post Nothing Phone (1) Won’t Get Android 16 Update appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nurul Kamil</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hackers using fake Ledger Live app to steal seed phrases and drain crypto]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/hackers-fake-ledger-apps-to-steal-seed-phrases</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/hackers-fake-ledger-apps-to-steal-seed-phrases?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-23T05:58:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cybercriminals are using fake Ledger Live apps to drain macOS users’ crypto through malware that steals seed phrases, a cybersecurity firm warns. 
The malware replaces the legitimate Ledger Live app on victims’ devices and then prompts the user to input their seed phrase through a phony pop-up message, a team from Moonlock said in a May 22 report.
“Initially, attackers could use the clone to steal passwords, notes, and wallet details to get a glimpse of the wallet’s assets, but they had no way to extract the funds,” the Moonlock team said.
“Now, within a year, they have learned to steal seed phrases and empty the wallets of their victims,” it added. 
One way the scammers replace the real Ledger Live app with a clone is through the Atomic macOS Stealer, designed to steal sensitive data, whi…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Stephen Katte</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pictures give glimpse inside Trump’s memecoin holder dinner]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/pictures-give-glimpses-inside-trumps-memecoin-dinner</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/pictures-give-glimpses-inside-trumps-memecoin-dinner?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-23T05:50:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Photos from within US President Donald Trump’s secretive dinner for his top memecoin buyers show attendees were treated to a three-course meal and gift bags as protesters gathered outside the event to accuse Trump of profiting from the presidency.
Pictures posted online by some of the 220 largest holders of the Official Trump (TRUMP) token — one of several crypto ventures critics have said conflicts with Trump’s ethics as president — show attendees were greeted by large posters bearing “Fight Fight Fight,” which also sat atop each table, referencing the company that launched the memecoin.
The White House said it would not publish a guest list of those who attended the dinner, but Tron CEO Justin Sun, Magic Eden CEO Jack Lu and BitMart CEO Sheldon Xia were among those sharing snaps of the d…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Brayden Lindrea</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Justin Sun Defends TRUMP After Presidential Dinner, Says 'Memecoins Have Merit']]></title>
        <id>bc2347ce-4dd2-42f3-afbd-6c99d9881bc9</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/23/justin-sun-defends-trump-after-presidential-dinner-says-memecoins-have-merit"/>
        <updated>2025-05-23T05:45:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tron's Sun sees the President fueling a new American crypto boom.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sam Reynolds</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[XRP Could Rocket to $8 as Focus Shifts to Crypto Majors After Bitcoin's Record Run: Traders]]></title>
        <id>63916677-2e5f-47e3-9059-f526edc85b38</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/23/xrp-could-rocket-to-8-as-focus-shifts-to-crypto-majors-after-bitcoins-record-run-traders"/>
        <updated>2025-05-23T05:33:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Traders are rotating into major altcoins like XRP and Solana’s SOL as bitcoin consolidates near its record highs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shaurya Malwa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin open interest hits record high as BTC slips below $111K]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-open-interest-hits-record-high-btc-below-111</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-open-interest-hits-record-high-btc-below-111?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-23T05:18:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin futures open interest (OI) has hit record levels on crypto derivatives exchanges as traders anticipate the cryptocurrency will continue and reach new all-time highs. 
Bitcoin (BTC) futures open interest reached a peak of just over $80 billion on May 23, according to CoinGlass. It’s an increase of 30% since the start of May as derivatives speculators load up on leverage in anticipation of higher Bitcoin prices.
Open interest is the total number of outstanding futures contracts that allow traders to bet on the future price of Bitcoin, which have not been settled or closed, showing the total amount of current market speculation.
Total Bitcoin futures OI. Source: Coinglass
When OI surges, it indicates massive leveraged positions are built up in the market, with lots of traders holding …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Martin Young</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[John Carmack talk at Upper Bound 2025 – slides and notes]]></title>
        <id>https://twitter.com/ID_AA_Carmack/status/1925710474366034326</id>
        <link href="https://twitter.com/ID_AA_Carmack/status/1925710474366034326"/>
        <updated>2025-05-23T05:14:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trendspotting in crypto: How to discover winning projects before the crowd]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/trendspotting-in-crypto</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/trendspotting-in-crypto?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-23T05:11:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[TL;DR
Spotting the next big crypto project before it explodes demands data, discipline and a sharp eye for real signals. This guide explores how to identify early winners by analyzing onchain metrics, tokenomics, dev activity and community traction while avoiding the common traps of hype-driven pumps and red-flag projects.
Despite the crypto space being crowded, fast-moving and full of noise, some investors manage to consistently find promising projects while they’re still under the radar.
So, how do they do it? 
Crypto trendspotters know how to read onchain data. They understand tokenomics. They read GitHub commits and follow the money. It takes more than jumping on the hype bandwagon ahead of the crowd.
This guide breaks down how to find crypto projects with real potential using lessons …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Bradley Peak</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lockheed Martin and IBM combine quantum computing with HPC in new research]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ibm.com/quantum/blog/lockheed-martin-sqd</id>
        <link href="https://www.ibm.com/quantum/blog/lockheed-martin-sqd"/>
        <updated>2025-05-23T04:46:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Swedish health firm jumps 37% on first Bitcoin buy, China EV seller to buy 1K BTC]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/swedish-health-firm-rises-37-percent-bitcoin-buy</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/swedish-health-firm-rises-37-percent-bitcoin-buy?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-23T03:29:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Shares in Swedish health tech company H100 Group AB rose 37% after it said it purchased Bitcoin for the first time as part of a new strategy, while China’s Jiuzi Holdings revealed its plan to stack 1,000 Bitcoin over the next year.
H100 said on May 22 that it spent 5 million Norwegian krone ($490,830) buying 4.39 Bitcoin (BTC) at an average purchasing price of around $111,785.
The company’s shares closed May 22 trading up 37% to 1.22 Swedish krona ($0.13) on the Nordic Growth Market following its disclosure of its Bitcoin purchase, Bloomberg data shows. 
Source: H100
The strong trading day recovered some losses from the past two months, during which the firm’s shares have fallen by over 46%.
H100’s change in share price so far in 2025. Source: Bloomberg
The firm’s CEO, Sander Andersen, sai…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Brayden Lindrea</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto perp futures coming ‘very soon,’ says CFTC’s Mersinger]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/crypto-perp-futures-coming-very-soon-cftc-s-mersinger</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/crypto-perp-futures-coming-very-soon-cftc-s-mersinger?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-23T02:58:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto perpetual futures contracts could receive regulatory approval in the US “very soon,” says outgoing Commodities and Futures Trading Commission Commissioner Summer Mersinger.
Perpetual crypto futures “can come to market now,” Mersinger told Bloomberg TV on May 22. 
“We’re seeing some applications, and I believe we’ll see some of those products trading live very soon,” she said, adding it would be “great to get that trading back onshore in the United States.” 
Mersinger, who will leave the CFTC at the end of May, said having crypto derivatives trading and regulated in the US would be a “really good thing for these markets and would be really beneficial to the industry broadly.”
Crypto perpetual futures are derivative contracts that allow traders to speculate on the price of cryptocurre…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Martin Young</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘No questions asked’ Bitcoin launderer gets 6 years in prison]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/no-questions-asked-bitcoin-launderer-gets-6-years</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/no-questions-asked-bitcoin-launderer-gets-6-years?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-23T02:38:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A US man operating what prosecutors called a “no questions asked” cash-to-Bitcoin conversion service has been sentenced to six years behind bars and was ordered to hand over millions of dollars. 
Boston federal court Judge Richard Stearns sentenced Trung Nguyen, from Danvers, Massachusetts, to six years in prison followed by three years of supervised release, and ordered him to forfeit $1.5 million, the Boston US Attorney’s Office said on May 22. 
Prosecutors said Nguyen ran an unlicensed money-transmitting business called National Vending between September 2017 and October 2020, which used various techniques he learned in an online course to evade authorities.
As part of the course, Nguyen was taught how to conceal his actual business from banks, crypto exchanges and state authorities by …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Stephen Katte</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Michigan lawmakers file 4 crypto bills on retiree funds, CBDCs, mining]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/michigan-lawmakers-introduce-four-crypto-bills</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/michigan-lawmakers-introduce-four-crypto-bills?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-23T01:14:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Michigan lawmakers have introduced four crypto-related bills covering crypto mining, central bank digital currencies (CBDCs) and crypto in state retirement funds.
Republican state Representative Bill Schuette introduced House Bill 4510 on May 21, which would amend Michigan’s Public Employee Retirement System Investment Act to allow the state treasurer, currently Rachael Eubanks, to invest in cryptocurrencies that have averaged a market cap above $250 million over the last calendar year.
Bitcoin (BTC) and Ether (ETH) are the only cryptocurrencies that currently meet that threshold. The bill adds that any cryptocurrencies must be held in the form of an exchange-traded product issued by a registered investment company.
A similar bill was introduced in February, permitting the state treasurer …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Brayden Lindrea</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Future of Flatpak]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/1020571/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/1020571/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-22T23:51:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[After GPT-4o backlash, researchers benchmark models on moral endorsement—Find sycophancy persists across the board]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008691</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/after-gpt-4o-backlash-researchers-benchmark-models-on-moral-endorsement-find-sycophancy-persists-across-the-board/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-22T23:46:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new benchmark can test how much LLMs become sycophants, and found that GPT-4o was the most sycophantic of the models tested.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Emilia David</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sketchy Calendar]]></title>
        <id>https://www.inkandswitch.com/ink/notes/sketchy-calendar/</id>
        <link href="https://www.inkandswitch.com/ink/notes/sketchy-calendar/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-22T23:19:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[32 bits that changed microprocessor design]]></title>
        <id>https://spectrum.ieee.org/bellmac-32-ieee-milestone</id>
        <link href="https://spectrum.ieee.org/bellmac-32-ieee-milestone"/>
        <updated>2025-05-22T23:18:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Here’s what happened in crypto today]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/what-happened-in-crypto-today</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/what-happened-in-crypto-today?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-22T22:00:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today in crypto, the CFTC’s Summer Mersinger said crypto perpetual futures could soon come to the US, lawmakers will amend the GENIUS Act to bar sitting presidents from profiting off stablecoins, and the decentralized exchange Cetus lost over $200 million in an exploit.
Crypto perp futures coming ‘very soon’ to US: CFTC’s Mersinger
Outgoing Commodities and Futures Trading Commission Commissioner Summer Mersinger said on May 22 that the regulator could greenlight crypto perpetual futures contracts “very soon.”
“We’re seeing some applications, and I believe we’ll see some of those products trading live very soon,” she told Bloomberg TV, adding it would be “great to get that trading back onshore in the United States.” 
Summer Mersinger on Bloomberg TV. Source: YouTube
Crypto perpetual futures…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Cointelegraph</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Show HN: Defuddle, an HTML-to-Markdown alternative to Readability]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/kepano/defuddle</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/kepano/defuddle"/>
        <updated>2025-05-22T21:40:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[US tourist drugged by fake Uber driver and robbed of $123K BTC — Report]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/american-tourist-drugged-fake-uber-driver-robbed-123k-btc</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/american-tourist-drugged-fake-uber-driver-robbed-123k-btc?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-22T21:40:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An American tourist in the United Kingdom was reportedly drugged by an individual posing as a taxi driver, who stole the tourist's $123,000 in Bitcoin (BTC) stored on a cell phone. 
According to a report from My London, Jacob Irwin-Cline went out to a London bar and had several drinks before calling an Uber to take him home.
Cline said that he did not thoroughly check the details of the Uber ride on his phone and left with a random private cab driver resembling the Uber driver at first glance, but driving a different vehicle — a detail Cline would only discover after the incident.

Once inside the vehicle, the US tourist said the driver offered him a cigarette, which Cline said was likely laced with a rare and potent sedative drug called scopolamine. Cline added that the cigarette made him…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Vince Quill</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Senators plan to amend GENIUS Act to address Trump family&#039;s stablecoin]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/senators-amendment-genius-act-world-liberty-financial-stablecoin</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/senators-amendment-genius-act-world-liberty-financial-stablecoin?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-22T21:33:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Though a majority of members of the US Senate voted to advance a bill to regulate payment stablecoins on May 20, high-ranking Democrats are planning to propose an amendment to the legislation to address President Donald Trump’s connections to the cryptocurrency industry.
According to a May 22 Axios report, Senate Minority Leader Chuck Schumer and Senators Elizabeth Warren and Jeff Merkley will file an amendment to the Guiding and Establishing National Innovation for US Stablecoins Act, or GENIUS Act, to block a US president from profiting from stablecoins. The proposed amendment would come after 18 Democrats sided with Republicans in the Senate in voting to advance the bill on May 20 after it failed a procedural vote on May 8.
“Passing the GENIUS Act without our anti-corruption amendment s…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Turner Wright</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Memecoin Moo Deng, MEW Surges After Robinhood Listing]]></title>
        <id>045b859b-4a96-468a-930e-c896c2a17b78</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/22/memecoin-moo-deng-mew-surges-after-robinhood-listing"/>
        <updated>2025-05-22T21:27:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Both tokens jumped on the news, adding to their already large gains this month.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Helene Braun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[XRP price fails to respond to two extremely bullish developments — Here is why]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/xrp-price-fails-to-respond-to-two-extremely-bullish-developments-here-is-why</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/xrp-price-fails-to-respond-to-two-extremely-bullish-developments-here-is-why?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-22T21:09:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Key takeaways:

The SEC’s decision on a spot XRP ETF could ignite a significant rally.

The current $2.2 billion in XRP futures hints at growing institutional investor demand.

The two most bullish events ever imagined by XRP (XRP) advocates happened in 2025, but XRP continues to underperform the cryptocurrency market. On March 6, XRP was listed as a candidate for the United States' “Digital Asset Reserve,” and Ripple Labs settled a years-long complaint with the US Securities and Exchange Commission on May 8.
XRP/USD (blue) vs. crypto market capitalization. Source: TradingView / Cointelegraph
XRP fell 6% in the three months leading up to May 22, while overall crypto market capitalization rose 10%. Traders remain hopeful for a 45% rally to $3.50, with derivatives metrics signaling rising co…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Marcel Pechman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn Vue.js in This Beginner's Course]]></title>
        <id>682f84537a13a40bfa336307</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-vuejs-in-this-beginners-course/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-22T20:08:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you’ve been meaning to add Vue.js to your front-end toolbelt, today’s your day. We just published a full, 6-hour Vue 3 course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel. Instructor Bhrugen Patel walks you through everything you need to build modern, ...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sui validators freeze majority of stolen funds in $220M Cetus hack]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/sui-validators-freeze-majority-stolen-funds-220m-cetus-hack</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/sui-validators-freeze-majority-stolen-funds-220m-cetus-hack?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-22T19:32:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cetus, a decentralized crypto exchange (DEX) built atop the Sui blockchain network, said $162 million of over $220 million stolen in a May 22 hack has been frozen.
According to the Cetus team, the DEX is working with the Sui Foundation and other entities within the ecosystem to recover the remainder of the funds. The Sui Foundation also confirmed:
"A large number of validators identified the addresses with the stolen funds and are ignoring transactions on those addresses until further notice. The Cetus team is exploring paths to recover those funds and return them to the community."
The Cetus hack is the latest in a string of such incidents impacting crypto and Web3 in the first half of 2025. Cybersecurity continues to be a major issue in crypto, with many industry executives calling for t…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Vince Quill</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BlockTrust IRA Brings Quant Trading Tools to Crypto Retirement Accounts]]></title>
        <id>a5315ae8-f5e0-44d7-a384-5068f2df64aa</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/22/blocktrust-ira-brings-quant-trading-tools-to-crypto-retirement-accounts"/>
        <updated>2025-05-22T19:16:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By leveraging trading signals from Animus Technologies, BlockTrust IRA promises to beat benchmark BTC and ETH positions.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tom Carreras</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Anthropic faces backlash to Claude 4 Opus behavior that contacts authorities, press if it thinks you’re doing something ‘egregiously immoral’]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008672</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/anthropic-faces-backlash-to-claude-4-opus-behavior-that-contacts-authorities-press-if-it-thinks-youre-doing-something-immoral/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-22T19:12:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bowman later edited his tweet and the following one in a thread to read as follows, but it still didn't convince the naysayers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carl Franzen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Does Earth have two high-tide bulges on opposite sides? (2014)]]></title>
        <id>http://physics.stackexchange.com/questions/121830/does-earth-really-have-two-high-tide-bulges-on-opposite-sides</id>
        <link href="http://physics.stackexchange.com/questions/121830/does-earth-really-have-two-high-tide-bulges-on-opposite-sides"/>
        <updated>2025-05-22T18:58:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OpenAI plans to ship 100 million pocket-sized AI devices for everyday use]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/openai-100-million-pocket-sized-ai-devices-everyday-use</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/openai-100-million-pocket-sized-ai-devices-everyday-use?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-22T18:43:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[OpenAI is planning to develop AI “companion” devices that will integrate artificial intelligence capabilities with everyday life, potentially opening the door to a new high-tech innovation used alongside laptops and smartphones.
In an interview with The Wall Street Journal, OpenAI CEO Sam Altman said he and former Apple chief design officer Jony Ive are developing these secret devices for mass consumption, with plans to ship 100 million units upon launch.
Ive joined OpenAI after his startup, io, was acquired by Altman’s company in a $6.5 billion deal, the Journal reported on May 21. 
Neither Altman nor Ives specified what these companion devices would look like or how they would operate. Ives simply referred to them as a “new design movement” that would be similar to Apple’s family of hard…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Sam Bourgi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Solana price fractal targets rally to $260, but one thing must happen first — Analysts]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/solana-price-fractal-targets-rally-to-260-but-one-thing-must-happen-first-analysts</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/solana-price-fractal-targets-rally-to-260-but-one-thing-must-happen-first-analysts?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-22T18:41:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Key takeaways:

Solana’s bull flag pattern projects a rally to $260, but low spot buy volumes have analysts advising caution.

After briefly dropping to $160 from $184, Solana (SOL) is attempting to reclaim a position above its key resistance at $180 for a second consecutive week. With Bitcoin (BTC) hitting an all-time high, market speculators are banking on eventual capital rotation, which could pump major altcoins like SOL toward new highs.
Solana shows promising signs on the daily chart, forming a textbook bull flag pattern after a strong uptrend. While SOL prices currently trade under $180, a breakout above this level could propel SOL toward its first target at $200, with further upside potential to $220 if momentum sustains.
Solana 1-day chart. Source: Cointelegraph/TradingView
The tr…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Biraajmaan Tamuly</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to cheat at settlers by loading the dice (2017)]]></title>
        <id>https://izbicki.me/blog/how-to-cheat-at-settlers-of-catan-by-loading-the-dice-and-prove-it-with-p-values.html</id>
        <link href="https://izbicki.me/blog/how-to-cheat-at-settlers-of-catan-by-loading-the-dice-and-prove-it-with-p-values.html"/>
        <updated>2025-05-22T18:25:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Major Wake-Up Call': How $400M Coinbase Breach Exposes Crypto's Dark Side]]></title>
        <id>6ba27993-c6da-4035-876c-4ecc7282f4c4</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2025/05/22/major-wake-up-call-how-usd400m-coinbase-breach-exposes-crypto-s-dark-side"/>
        <updated>2025-05-22T18:21:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase said 69,461 customers were initially impacted by the breach, but fears remain over the threat of real-world robberies.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Oliver Knight</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Centrifuge Expands Tokenized RWAs to Solana, Starting With $400M Treasury Fund]]></title>
        <id>b7b95f56-2902-4daa-a192-c48b5b4a2397</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/22/centrifuge-expands-tokenized-rwas-to-solana-starting-with-400m-treasury-fund"/>
        <updated>2025-05-22T18:18:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Solana is gaining momentum in the fast-growing tokenized real-world asset space as traditional finance and DeFi gets increasingly intertwined.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Krisztian Sandor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kraken to offer tokenized US stocks to non-US clients]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/kraken-tokenized-us-stocks-international-clients-report</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/kraken-tokenized-us-stocks-international-clients-report?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-22T18:12:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto exchange Kraken is planning to offer non-US customers the option of trading tokenized US stocks, part of the company’s push to offer more traditional assets via tokenization.
The products will be offered through Backed, a new Kraken partner, according to a statement shared with Cointelegraph. Tokens representing the stocks will be stored on the Solana blockchain due to its “unmatched performance, low latency and thriving global ecosystem,” the statement said.
“The whole point of crypto is that we're able to see things very transparently,” Kraken co-CEO Arjun Sethi said during Solana's Accelerate event on May 22. ”It's decentralized. It is open-source. You can innovate as quickly as possible, and there's no reason why companies like us can't morph to do that."
The decision to incorpo…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Christopher Tepedino</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Loading Pydantic models from JSON without running out of memory]]></title>
        <id>https://pythonspeed.com/articles/pydantic-json-memory/</id>
        <link href="https://pythonspeed.com/articles/pydantic-json-memory/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-22T18:06:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Democrats Threaten Lawsuits, Join Protests Ahead of Trump Memecoin Dinner]]></title>
        <id>f7b1009d-92f3-48ba-bdf1-a1ec95b8d506</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2025/05/22/democrats-threaten-lawsuits-join-protests-ahead-of-trump-memecoin-dinner"/>
        <updated>2025-05-22T18:06:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Democratic lawmakers went through a flurry of actions to highlight concerns that Donald Trump's memecoin dinner is "corrupt."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jesse Hamilton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[We’ll be ending web hosting for your apps on Glitch]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.glitch.com/post/changes-are-coming-to-glitch/</id>
        <link href="https://blog.glitch.com/post/changes-are-coming-to-glitch/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-22T17:16:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[US lawmaker introduces anti-corruption bill ahead of Trump&#039;s dinner]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/donald-trump-crypto-corruption-bill-memecoin-dinner</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/donald-trump-crypto-corruption-bill-memecoin-dinner?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-22T17:16:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[California Representative Maxine Waters, ranking member of the US House Financial Services Committee, has announced plans to introduce legislation “to block [Donald] Trump’s memecoin and stop his crypto corruption.”
In a May 22 notice, Waters said the Stop Trading, Retention, and Unfair Market Payoffs (TRUMP) in Crypto Act of 2025 bill would be aimed at blocking the US president, vice president, members of Congress and their families from engaging in “crypto crime.” 
The US lawmaker referred to Trump and his wife, Melania, issuing personal memecoins in January, his family launching a stablecoin, USD1, through the crypto platform World Liberty Financial, and the president attempting to establish a national Bitcoin (BTC) reserve as his sons back a BTC mining venture.
“Donald Trump is prepari…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Turner Wright</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Anthropic’s new hybrid AI model can work on tasks autonomously for hours at a time]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1117338</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/05/22/1117338/anthropics-new-hybrid-ai-model-can-work-on-tasks-autonomously-for-hours-at-a-time/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-22T16:51:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Anthropic has announced two new AI models that it claims represent a major step toward making AI agents truly useful. AI agents trained on Claude Opus 4, the company’s most powerful model to date, raise the bar for what such systems are capable of by tackling difficult tasks over extended periods of time and responding…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rhiannon Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Anthropic overtakes OpenAI: Claude Opus 4 codes seven hours nonstop, sets record SWE-Bench score and reshapes enterprise AI]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008575</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/anthropic-claude-opus-4-can-code-for-7-hours-straight-and-its-about-to-change-how-we-work-with-ai/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-22T16:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Anthropic's Claude Opus 4 outperforms OpenAI's GPT-4.1 with unprecedented seven-hour autonomous coding sessions and record-breaking 72.5% SWE-bench score, transforming AI from quick-response tool to day-long collaborator.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Nuñez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Claude 4]]></title>
        <id>https://www.anthropic.com/news/claude-4</id>
        <link href="https://www.anthropic.com/news/claude-4"/>
        <updated>2025-05-22T16:34:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mozilla to shut down Pocket and Fakespot]]></title>
        <id>https://support.mozilla.org/en-US/kb/future-of-pocket</id>
        <link href="https://support.mozilla.org/en-US/kb/future-of-pocket"/>
        <updated>2025-05-22T16:30:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Major TradFi Institutions to Pursue Tokenization Efforts on Solana]]></title>
        <id>1e9f7d9e-f627-457a-8dda-a93e35c00f69</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2025/05/22/major-tradfi-institutions-to-pursue-tokenization-efforts-on-solana"/>
        <updated>2025-05-22T16:12:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tokenization is one of the principal use cases of blockchain technology attracting the attention and investment of the TradFi world]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Crawley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BTC price eyes $112K as risk assets &#039;ignore bad news&#039; on unemployment]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/btc-price-eyes-112k-risk-assets-ignore-bad-news-unemployment</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/btc-price-eyes-112k-risk-assets-ignore-bad-news-unemployment?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-22T16:07:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Key points:

Mixed results for US jobless claims fail to dent risk-asset enthusiasm.

Despite concerns over the bond market, Bitcoin and stocks enjoy stability at the start of the Wall Street trading session.

BTC price expectations remain lofty amid low volatility and a curious lack of profit-taking.

Bitcoin (BTC) focused on $111,000 around the May 22 Wall Street open as record highs met mixed US unemployment data.
BTC/USD 1-hour chart. Source: Cointelegraph/TradingView
Bitcoin, stocks brush off jobs uncertainty
Data from Cointelegraph Markets Pro and TradingView showed BTC price volatility cooling in line with stocks.
The latest US macroeconomic data painted a conflicting picture of labor market resilience to inflation trends.
Initial jobless claims came in below expectations at 227,000…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by William Suberg</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Justin Sun-Linked Wallet Leading Access to Trump Dinner Tagged as Belonging to HTX]]></title>
        <id>bca545d8-d0c9-4cfa-a211-44f6c0f97575</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2025/05/22/justin-sun-linked-wallet-leading-access-to-trump-dinner-tagged-as-belonging-to-htx"/>
        <updated>2025-05-22T16:05:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sun, a Chinese-born crypto billionaire, is also involved with the Trump-linked ecosystem through a $75 million investment in World Liberty Financial.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Francisco Rodrigues</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin could go much higher due to lack of FOMO and futures market euphoria — Analysts]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-could-go-much-higher-due-to-lack-of-fomo-and-futures-market-euphoria-analysts</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-could-go-much-higher-due-to-lack-of-fomo-and-futures-market-euphoria-analysts?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-22T15:58:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Key takeaways:

Bitcoin’s rally to new price highs happened as funding rates and trading sentiment remained unusually subdued.

Rising stablecoin supply and global M2 growth indicate untapped liquidity and the potential for further price increases.

Long-term holders are not aggressively selling, reflecting their expectation for continued Bitcoin price appreciation.

Bitcoin (BTC) hit a new all-time high on May 21, with prices rising to $111,860 on Binance on May 22, but the markets lack the state of frenzy associated with new highs. Economist and crypto commentator Alex Krüger noted that “this is the least euphoric new all-time highs” for Bitcoin, after highlighting subdued funding rates for Bitcoin across crypto exchanges.
Bitcoin price and aggregated funding rate. Source: Coinalyze
The …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Biraajmaan Tamuly</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Deploy Your FastAPI + PostgreSQL App on Render: A Beginner's Guide]]></title>
        <id>682f4900bcc94cb9bccbf905</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/deploy-fastapi-postgresql-app-on-render/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-22T15:55:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This guide is a comprehensive roadmap for deploying a FastAPI backend connected to a PostgreSQL database using Render, a cloud platform that supports hosting Python web apps and managed PostgreSQL databases.   You can find the complete source code he...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Preston Osoro</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Carmaker DeLorean tokenizes EV reservations on Sui]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/delorean-tokenizes-ev-reservations-on-sui</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/delorean-tokenizes-ev-reservations-on-sui?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-22T15:55:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[DeLorean launched an onchain reservation system and non-fungible token (NFT) marketplace for its upcoming electric vehicle launch, introducing a new blockchain-based approach for reserving and reselling cars.
According to DeLorean, its Build Slot NFT collection grants holders priority access to purchase DeLorean’s upcoming electric car, Alpha 5 EV. The model is the carmaker’s first vehicle in over 40 years, inspired by the iconic flux capacitor from the movie Back to the Future.
The company created an exclusive marketplace for its NFT holders, in which users can buy or trade the NFTs using the USDC (USDC) stablecoin on the Sui network and will be able to earn rewards.
DeLorean says that each vehicle’s history and performance data will be recorded onchain through the FLUX protocol, includin…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Lyne Qian</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kraken to List Tokenized Version of Nvidia, Apple, Tesla Shares]]></title>
        <id>3b9fba56-daf9-4556-b83f-f6eaa28ad999</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/22/kraken-to-list-tokenized-version-of-nvidia-apple-tesla-shares"/>
        <updated>2025-05-22T15:55:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The tokens will be deployed on Solana and backed by real securities held by Kraken’s partner, Backed Finance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Helene Braun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[First U.S. XRP Futures ETF Begins Trading on Nasdaq]]></title>
        <id>0a64f011-e949-485d-b984-18f3a3d2971d</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/22/first-u-s-xrp-futures-etf-begins-trading-on-nasdaq"/>
        <updated>2025-05-22T15:53:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The fund will invest at least 80% of its assets in XRP futures contracts and shares of other XRP-linked exchange-traded products.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Helene Braun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[That fractal that's been up on my wall for years]]></title>
        <id>https://chriskw.xyz/2025/05/21/Fractal/</id>
        <link href="https://chriskw.xyz/2025/05/21/Fractal/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-22T15:50:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[An Animated Introduction to Elixir]]></title>
        <id>682f44e3dcb21c615cf1a12d</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/an-animated-introduction-to-elixir/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-22T15:38:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Elixir is a dynamic, functional programming language designed for building scalable and maintainable applications. It leverages the battle-tested Erlang VM, known for running low-latency, distributed, and fault-tolerant systems. Elixir is based on an...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mark Mahoney</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Time Magazine appears to accidentally publish embargoed story confirming new Anthropic model]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008649</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/time-magazine-appears-to-accidentally-publish-embargoed-story-confirming-anthropic-claude-4-opus/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-22T15:26:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Someone also appears to have published a full scrape of the Time article online on the news aggregator app Newsbreak.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carl Franzen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Launch HN: WorkDone (YC X25) – AI Audit of Medical Charts]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=44063000</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=44063000"/>
        <updated>2025-05-22T15:23:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto for Advisors: When Crypto Meets Netflix]]></title>
        <id>7f516d56-430a-487d-90aa-11357443c3c4</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/coindesk-indices/2025/05/21/crypto-for-advisors-when-crypto-meets-netflix"/>
        <updated>2025-05-22T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How Black Mirror’s on-chain experiment is paving the way for the future of entertainment monetization.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shivani Phull</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Semiconductor exemptions don’t matter when it comes to tariffs]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/semiconductor-exemptions-don-t-matter</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/semiconductor-exemptions-don-t-matter?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-22T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Opinion by: Ahmad Shadid of O.xyz
Semiconductors scored a rare exemption from US President Donald Trump’s aggressive reciprocal tariffs, but the relief is symbolic at best. Most semiconductors enter the US embedded in servers, GPUs, laptops, and smartphones. 
The finished goods remain heavily tariffed, some with duties reaching up to 49%. The exemption looks good politically but delivers little practical benefit. Nvidia’s DGX systems, crucial for training advanced AI models, do not fall under the exempted HTS codes. Nvidia could pay effective tariffs nearing 40% on these vital components. Such costs threaten to stall critical AI infrastructure projects across the country. 
Semiconductor tariffs may compromise the goal of the CHIPS Act. The act promised tens of billions of dollars in subsid…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Ahmad Shadid</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Global Dollar's USDG Eyes Hundreds of Partners Attracted by Yield, Sees 'Big Names' From TradFi]]></title>
        <id>e068c52f-e6b5-46e8-922b-4e6fa9097240</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2025/05/22/stablecoin-consortium-usdg-will-see-thousands-of-firms-joining-says-kraken"/>
        <updated>2025-05-22T14:11:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Banks and large TradFi firms are preparing to join the Global Dollar network alongside firms like Robinhood, Galaxy and Anchorage, founding member Kraken said.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ian Allison</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[I Built My Own Audio Player]]></title>
        <id>https://nexo.sh/posts/why-i-built-a-native-mp3-player-in-swiftui/</id>
        <link href="https://nexo.sh/posts/why-i-built-a-native-mp3-player-in-swiftui/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-22T14:09:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fast Allocations in Ruby 3.5]]></title>
        <id>https://railsatscale.com/2025-05-21-fast-allocations-in-ruby-3-5/</id>
        <link href="https://railsatscale.com/2025-05-21-fast-allocations-in-ruby-3-5/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-22T14:01:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trump-Backed World Liberty Financial Buys BUILDon Token, Sending the Price Up 1,340%]]></title>
        <id>e2071d8e-6d14-4cba-a7c9-fcba8dd0ab18</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2025/05/22/trump-backed-crypto-project-buys-buildon-token-sending-prices-up-1-340"/>
        <updated>2025-05-22T14:00:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The token had a market cap of just $40 million before the purchase.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Oliver Knight</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Which senators invest in crypto? 11 lawmakers have blockchain-related investments]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/senators-invest-crypto-blockchain-related-investments</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/senators-invest-crypto-blockchain-related-investments?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-22T13:54:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As the question of stablecoin regulation heats up in the US Senate, so has the issue of which members are personally invested in cryptocurrencies and cryptocurrency firms. 
On May 19, the Senate voted to invoke cloture and move ahead with the GENIUS Act, which would provide a regulatory framework for stablecoins. The measure passed 66-32, with 16 Democrats supporting the bill.
Democratic concerns over corruption and politicians’ ties to cryptocurrency firms made the bipartisan move controversial. After the vote was finished, Colorado Senator Michael Bennet introduced the STABLE GENIUS Act. The bill would prevent members of Congress from issuing or investing in digital currency and require them to put their crypto in a blind trust while in office.
Bills to prevent members of Congress from i…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Aaron Wood</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Texas Moves Closer to Setting Up Strategic Bitcoin Reserve as Bill Passes House]]></title>
        <id>dde56905-9e4c-4e9a-b312-d3e487c7dc24</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2025/05/22/texas-moves-closer-to-setting-up-strategic-bitcoin-reserve-as-bill-passes-house"/>
        <updated>2025-05-22T13:39:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The House voted in favor of Senate Bill 121 which would establish a "Texas Strategic Bitcoin Reserve for the purpose of investing in cryptocurrency"]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Crawley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Exponential currency debasement: ‘You don’t own enough crypto, NFTs’]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/currency-debasement-own-enough-crypto-nfts</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/currency-debasement-own-enough-crypto-nfts?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-22T13:39:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cryptocurrencies and non-fungible tokens (NFTs) can help investors protect their eroding purchasing power during an era of exponential currency debasement, according to analysts and industry leaders.
Investing in digital assets is becoming increasingly important in the “world of the exponential age and currency debasement,” according to Raoul Pal, founder and CEO of Global Macro Investor.
“You don’t own enough crypto. When you do, you don’t own enough NFT’s, as art is upstream of wealth. Both will never be this cheap again,” Pal said.
NFTs are “the single best long term store of wealth I know and you get to buy it before network effects kick in,” he added in another response.
Source: Raoul Pal
“There is some validity to the statement that NFTs, and in extension art, become a vehicle for th…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Zoltan Vardai</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CoinDesk 20 Performance Update: Index Gains 4.5% with All Assets Trading Higher]]></title>
        <id>aaca5697-10bc-4e9d-b21d-caacf85b7e33</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/coindesk-indices/2025/05/22/coindesk-20-performance-update-index-gains-45-with-all-assets-trading-higher"/>
        <updated>2025-05-22T13:36:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Avalanche (AVAX) Surged 11.2% while NEAR Protocol (NEAR) jumped 7.9%, leading the index higher.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CoinDesk Indices</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Show HN: SQLite JavaScript - extend your database with JavaScript]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/sqliteai/sqlite-js</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/sqliteai/sqlite-js"/>
        <updated>2025-05-22T13:25:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What You Didn’t Know About Laszlo Hanyecz, the Bitcoin Pizza Day Legend]]></title>
        <id>28e94138-acbd-43b0-98c5-c2d5c0806857</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/tech/2025/05/22/what-you-didnt-know-about-laszlo-hanyecz-the-bitcoin-pizza-day-legend"/>
        <updated>2025-05-22T13:06:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When Laszlo Hanyecz purchased two large Papa John’s pizzas with 10,000 BTC on May 22, 2010, he became a legend. But how much do you really know about the man behind Bitcoin Pizza Day?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Colin Harper, Blockspace Media</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Project Roxom Global Raises $17.9M to Build BTC Treasury, Create Media Network]]></title>
        <id>37051a57-792a-41a8-b141-b91362c60f5b</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2025/05/22/roxom-global-raises-179m-to-build-btc-treasury-back-247-media-network"/>
        <updated>2025-05-22T13:00:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[RoxomTV is being built as a media network backed by a 100% bitcoin treasury and currently holds 84.72 BTC]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Crawley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[U.S. Stablecoin Bill Approval Could Trigger a Long-Term Crypto Bull Market: Bitwise]]></title>
        <id>f3d27af1-e50b-422a-ae80-55962691b564</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/22/us-stablecoin-bill-approval-could-trigger-a-long-term-crypto-bull-market-bitwise"/>
        <updated>2025-05-22T12:55:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The passage of a U.S. stablecoin bill could be one of the most important regulatory developments in the history of crypto, the report said.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Will Canny</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Strategy Plans $2.1B Sale of Its Perpetual Strife Preferred Stock]]></title>
        <id>89ebea90-364a-433a-8330-e4540056cd89</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/22/strategy-plans-21b-sale-of-its-perpetual-strife-preferred-stock"/>
        <updated>2025-05-22T12:37:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Proceeds to support corporate initiatives including bitcoin acquisitions and working capital.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>James Van Straten</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Enchant launches zero-equity accelerator for gaming and AI startups]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008571</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/games/enchant-launches-zero-equity-accelerator-for-gaming-and-ai-startups/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-22T12:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Enchant is launching a new zero-equity accelerator for gaming and AI startups, with applications now open for its three-month program.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dean Takahashi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Download: the desert data center boom, and how to measure Earth’s elevations]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1117300</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/05/22/1117300/the-download-the-desert-data-center-boom-and-how-to-measure-earths-elevations/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-22T12:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is today’s edition of The Download, our weekday newsletter that provides a daily dose of what’s going on in the world of technology. The data center boom in the desert In the high desert east of Reno, Nevada, construction crews are flattening the golden foothills of the Virginia Range, laying the foundations of a data center…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rhiannon Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Improving performance of rav1d video decoder]]></title>
        <id>https://ohadravid.github.io/posts/2025-05-rav1d-faster/</id>
        <link href="https://ohadravid.github.io/posts/2025-05-rav1d-faster/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-22T11:59:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sui's Biggest Liquidity Provider Hacked for $223M, Causing Sui-Based Tokens to Plummet]]></title>
        <id>32730c6a-9f4c-4852-a38b-c3184ae2079d</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/22/sui-networks-cetus-protocol-hit-in-apparent-hack-sending-token-prices-down-90"/>
        <updated>2025-05-22T11:54:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cetus is Sui’s biggest liquidity provider and decentralized exchange.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shaurya Malwa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Are Bitcoin Traders Aggressively Shorting as BTC Hits New Record High?]]></title>
        <id>a641ed4a-06c2-4968-9065-f371462385a4</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/22/why-are-bitcoin-traders-aggressively-shorting-as-btc-hits-new-record-high"/>
        <updated>2025-05-22T11:39:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The move comes as the long/short ratio is at its lowest point since September 2022.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Oliver Knight</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Three takeaways about AI’s energy use and climate impacts]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1117277</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/05/22/1117277/ai-energy-three-takeaways/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-22T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This week, we published Power Hungry, a package all about AI and energy. At the center of this package is the most comprehensive look yet at AI’s growing power demand, if I do say so myself.  This data-heavy story is the result of over six months of reporting by me and my colleague James O’Donnell…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Casey Crownhart</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A new atomic clock in space could help us measure elevations on Earth]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1117294</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/05/22/1117294/a-new-atomic-clock-in-space-could-help-us-measure-elevations-on-earth/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-22T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In 2003, engineers from Germany and Switzerland began building a bridge across the Rhine River simultaneously from both sides. Months into construction, they found that the two sides did not meet. The German side hovered 54 centimeters above the Swiss side. The misalignment occurred because the German engineers had measured elevation with a historic level…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sophia Chen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ancient law requires a bale of straw to hang from Charing Cross rail bridge]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ianvisits.co.uk/articles/ancient-law-requires-a-bale-of-hay-to-hang-from-charing-cross-rail-bridge-81318/</id>
        <link href="https://www.ianvisits.co.uk/articles/ancient-law-requires-a-bale-of-hay-to-hang-from-charing-cross-rail-bridge-81318/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-22T08:52:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[At Google I/O, Sergey Brin makes surprise appearance — and declares Google will build the first AGI]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008490</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/at-google-i-o-sergey-brin-makes-surprise-appearance-and-declares-google-will-build-the-first-agi/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-21T22:20:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google co-founder Sergey Brin makes surprise appearance at Google I/O, declaring "Gemini will be the very first AGI," revealing philosophical tensions with DeepMind CEO Hassabis who urges scientific caution in the high-stakes AI race.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Nuñez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Master Database Management Systems]]></title>
        <id>682e3c04117e792e5f46edc3</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/master-database-management-systems/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-21T20:48:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Understanding how to manage data effectively is a critical skill for anyone pursuing a career in tech. And we just published a course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will teach you all about Database Management Systems (DBMS). This in-de...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Roundtables: A New Look at AI’s Energy Use]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1117287</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/05/21/1117287/roundtables-a-new-look-at-ais-energy-use-2/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-21T19:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Recorded on May 21, 2025 Big Tech’s appetite for energy is growing rapidly as adoption of AI accelerates. But just how much energy does even a single AI query use? And what does it mean for the climate? Hear from MIT Technology Review editor in chief Mat Honan, senior climate reporter Casey Crownhart, and AI reporter James…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>MIT Technology Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Refactor Complex Codebases – A Practical Guide for Devs]]></title>
        <id>682df5a0f2057ab279952dbe</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-refactor-complex-codebases/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-21T15:47:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Developers often see refactoring as a secondary concern that they can delay indefinitely because it doesn’t immediately contribute to revenue or feature development. And managers frequently view refactoring as "not a business need" until it boils ove...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ankur Tyagi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Vibe Coding Won't Destroy Software Engineering]]></title>
        <id>682df55da72360814bcae9ef</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/why-vibe-coding-wont-destroy-software-engineering/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-21T15:46:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AI is disrupting all industries at a pace not seen at any time in history. Technologies and industries that were once dominated by one or two companies or were very much “human-focused” are coming under threat. Google is losing ground to AI search, t...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ben</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OpenAI updates its new Responses API rapidly with MCP support, GPT-4o native image gen, and more enterprise features]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008465</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/programming-development/openai-updates-its-new-responses-api-rapidly-with-mcp-support-gpt-4o-native-image-gen-and-more-enterprise-features/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-21T15:30:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Support for remote Model Context Protocol servers, integration of image generation and Code Interpreter tools, and upgrades to file search...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carl Franzen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How JavaScript Lint Rules Work (and Why Abstract Syntax Trees Matter)]]></title>
        <id>682def7ddd9c9fdc3dae95cf</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-javascript-lint-rules-work-and-why-abstract-syntax-trees-matter/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-21T15:21:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Before I started to contribute to eslint-plugin-react, I didn’t think too deeply about the linters I used every day while writing code. Like many developers, I installed them at the start of a project, appreciated the red underlines or auto-fixes, an...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tilda Udufo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mistral AI launches Devstral, powerful new open source SWE agent model that runs on laptops]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008458</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/mistral-ai-launches-devstral-powerful-new-open-source-swe-agent-model-that-runs-on-laptops/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-21T14:57:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Beyond performance and portability, its Apache 2.0 license offers a compelling proposition for commercial applications.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carl Franzen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Download: Google’s AI mission, and America’s reliance on natural gas]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1117249</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/05/21/1117249/the-download-googles-ai-mission-and-americas-reliance-on-natural-gas/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-21T12:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is today’s edition of The Download, our weekday newsletter that provides a daily dose of what’s going on in the world of technology. By putting AI into everything, Google wants to make it invisible If you want to know where AI is headed, this year’s Google I/O has you covered. The company’s annual showcase of next-gen…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rhiannon Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[By putting AI into everything, Google wants to make it invisible]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1117251</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/05/21/1117251/by-putting-ai-into-everything-google-wants-to-make-it-invisible/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-21T11:49:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you want to know where AI is headed, this year’s Google I/O has you covered. The company’s annual showcase of next-gen products, which kicked off yesterday, has all of the pomp and pizzazz, the sizzle reels and celebrity walk-ons, that you’d expect from a multimillion-dollar marketing event. But it also shows us just how…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Will Douglas Heaven</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A South Korean grand master on the art of the perfect soy sauce]]></title>
        <id>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2025/may/21/without-time-there-is-no-flavour-a-south-korean-grand-master-on-the-art-of-the-perfect-soy-sauce</id>
        <link href="https://www.theguardian.com/world/2025/may/21/without-time-there-is-no-flavour-a-south-korean-grand-master-on-the-art-of-the-perfect-soy-sauce"/>
        <updated>2025-05-21T11:19:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Satellites Spotting Depth]]></title>
        <id>https://tech.marksblogg.com/depth-anything-v2-maxar-ai-detection.html</id>
        <link href="https://tech.marksblogg.com/depth-anything-v2-maxar-ai-detection.html"/>
        <updated>2025-05-21T10:12:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AMD unveils new Threadripper CPUs and Radeon GPUs for gamers at Computex 2025]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008206</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/games/amd-unveils-new-threadripper-cpus-and-radeon-gpus-for-gamers-at-computex-2025/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-21T03:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AMD held a Computex press event to introduce its Radeon RX 9060 XT graphics cards and Threadripper CPUs for next-gen gaming and workstations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dean Takahashi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google finally launches NotebookLM mobile app at I/O: hands-on, first impressions]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008400</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/google-finally-launches-notebooklm-mobile-app-at-i-o-hands-on-first-impressions/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T19:29:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As NotebookLM matures, its emerging business-tier capabilities suggest growing alignment with the productivity and compliance...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carl Franzen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google just leapfrogged every competitor with mind-blowing AI that can think deeper, shop smarter, and create videos with dialogue]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008346</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/google-just-leapfrogged-every-competitor-with-mind-blowing-ai-that-can-think-deeper-shop-smarter-and-create-videos-with-dialogue/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T17:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google unveiled major AI advancements at I/O 2025, including Gemini 2.5 with Deep Think, AI Mode in Search, Veo 3 for video with audio, and a $249 Ultra plan aimed at power users and enterprises.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Nuñez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google’s Jules aims to out-code Codex in battle for the AI developer stack]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008361</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/googles-jules-aims-to-out-code-codex-in-battle-for-the-ai-developer-stack/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T17:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google released Jules, its coding agent, into beta as autonomous coding agents are quickly gaining market share.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Emilia David</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Inside Google’s AI leap: Gemini 2.5 thinks deeper, speaks smarter and codes faster]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008366</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/inside-google-ai-leap-gemini-2-5-thinks-deeper-speaks-smarter-codes-faster/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T17:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google is moving closer to its goal of autonomous agentic AI with a series of enhancements to Gemini 2.5 Pro and Flash.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Taryn Plumb</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blazing-fast Solana data via gRPC: access the freshest Solana data from Shredstream leaders]]></title>
        <id>68273f14bf73460001094b35</id>
        <link href="https://blog.quicknode.com/yellowstone-grpc/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T15:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Access the fastest Solana data with the Yellowstone Geyser gRPC self-serve add-on or with the premium hybrid dedicated gRPC node.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>QuickNode</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn LangGraph and Build Conversational AI with Python]]></title>
        <id>682ca2c574938e5428551845</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-langgraph-and-build-conversational-ai-with-python/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T15:41:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you're building conversational AI and tired of messy logic or hard-to-scale workflows, LangGraph makes it easier. It uses graphs to manage dialogue flow, so your bots stay organized even as they get more complex. Great for anything from support ag...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Download: introducing the AI energy package]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1117051</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/05/20/1117051/the-download-introducing-the-ai-energy-package/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T12:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is today’s edition of The Download, our weekday newsletter that provides a daily dose of what’s going on in the world of technology. We did the math on AI’s energy footprint. Here’s the story you haven’t heard. It’s well documented that AI is a power-hungry technology. But there has been far less reporting on the extent…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rhiannon Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Formal Mathematical Investigation on the Validity of Kellogg's Glaze Claims]]></title>
        <id>https://old.reddit.com/r/theydidthemath/comments/1iljmig/_/</id>
        <link href="https://old.reddit.com/r/theydidthemath/comments/1iljmig/_/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T23:44:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Richard Garwin’s role in designing the hydrogen bomb was obscured]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nytimes.com/2025/05/19/science/richard-garwin-hydrogen-bomb.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.nytimes.com/2025/05/19/science/richard-garwin-hydrogen-bomb.html"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T19:09:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft just launched an AI that discovered a new chemical in 200 hours instead of years]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008310</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/microsoft-just-launched-an-ai-that-discovered-a-new-chemical-in-200-hours-instead-of-years/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T18:34:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft launches Discovery platform that uses agentic AI to compress years of scientific research into days, transforming R&D across pharmaceuticals, materials science, and semiconductor industries.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Nuñez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Is your AI app pissing off users or going off-script? Raindrop emerges with AI-native observability platform to monitor performance]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008299</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/is-your-ai-app-pissing-off-users-or-going-off-script-raindrop-emerges-with-ai-native-observability-platform-to-monitor-performance/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T18:09:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With its rebrand and product expansion, Raindrop is betting that the next generation of software observability will be AI-first by design.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carl Franzen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft just taught its AI agents to talk to each other—and it could transform how we work]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008254</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/microsoft-just-taught-its-ai-agents-to-talk-to-each-other-and-it-could-transform-how-we-work/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T16:01:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft unveils multi-agent systems, WhatsApp integration, and Python-powered analytics for Copilot Studio at Build 2025, transforming how enterprises build and deploy AI solutions.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Nuñez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Microsoft Fabric has already been adopted by 70% of the Fortune 500 — and what’s next]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3007980</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/70-of-the-fortune-500-already-use-microsoft-fabric-and-its-now-getting-even-more-features-including-cosmosdb-support/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft integrates CosmosDB into Fabric, open sources DiskANN vector search, and unifies its data platforms to eliminate integration complexity that has slowed enterprise AI adoption.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sean Michael Kerner</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub Copilot evolves into autonomous agent with asynchronous code testing]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008231</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/github-copilot-evolves-into-autonomous-agent-with-asynchronous-code-testing/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub adds agentic capabilities to its Copilot coding assistant, competing with other more asynchronous coding platforms.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Emilia David</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft announces over 50 AI tools to build the ‘agentic web’ at Build 2025]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008229</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/microsoft-announces-over-50-ai-tools-to-build-the-agentic-web-at-build-2025/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T15:59:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft reveals its ambitious AI agent strategy, showcasing how multi-agent systems with persistent memory will transform enterprise workflows and accelerate development timelines.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Nuñez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Turbocharged' Mitochondria Power Birds' Epic Migratory Journeys]]></title>
        <id>https://www.quantamagazine.org/turbocharged-mitochondria-power-birds-epic-migratory-journeys-20250519/</id>
        <link href="https://www.quantamagazine.org/turbocharged-mitochondria-power-birds-epic-migratory-journeys-20250519/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T15:47:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Reddit, Webflow, and Superhuman are already customers—now GrowthX has $12M to grow]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008276</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/reddit-webflow-and-superhuman-are-already-customers-now-growthx-has-12m-to-grow/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[GrowthX secures $12M in funding for its "service-as-software" platform that combines AI with human expertise to boost content marketing results by up to 300%.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Nuñez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Cybercriminals Crack Your Passwords (And How to Stay One Step Ahead)]]></title>
        <id>682b3930e99a22ce9f9199c8</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-cybercriminals-crack-your-passwords-and-how-to-stay-one-step-ahead/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T13:59:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Passwords are the keys to your digital life  –  email, bank accounts, social media, and even your workplace systems. Unfortunately, they’re also one of the weakest links in cybersecurity.  Every year, billions of credentials are stolen and sold on th...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Manish Shivanandhan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Quantum Machines launches Qualibrate open source framework to speed quantum computer calibration]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008032</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/games/quantum-machines-launches-qualibrate-open-source-framework-to-speed-quantum-computer-calibration/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Quantum Machines, a provider of advanced hybrid quantum-classical control solutions, announced today the release of Qualibrate.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dean Takahashi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Samsung boosts OLED TV gaming with Nvidia G-Sync compatibility]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008019</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/games/samsung-boosts-oled-tv-gaming-with-nvidia-g-sync-compatibility/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Samsung said its 2025 OLED TV lineup will feature Nvidia G-Sync compatibility, delivering smooth gameplay, low latency, and more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dean Takahashi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Salesforce just unveiled AI ‘digital teammates’ in Slack — and they’re coming for Microsoft Copilot]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008273</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/salesforce-just-unveiled-ai-digital-teammates-in-slack-and-theyre-coming-for-microsoft-copilot/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Salesforce launches Agentforce in Slack, transforming workplace productivity with specialized AI agents that operate as digital teammates, replacing one-size-fits-all AI assistants with purpose-built solutions.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Nuñez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Airport for DuckDB]]></title>
        <id>https://airport.query.farm/</id>
        <link href="https://airport.query.farm/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T11:25:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tallest Wooden Wind Turbine]]></title>
        <id>https://modvion.com/</id>
        <link href="https://modvion.com/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T07:58:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Foxconn builds AI factory in partnership with Taiwan and Nvidia]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008261</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/games/foxconn-builds-ai-factory-in-partnership-with-taiwan-and-nvidia/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T07:14:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nvidia and Foxconn announced they are working with the Taiwan government to build an AI factory supercomputer.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dean Takahashi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nvidia launches AI-first DGX Personal Computing Systems]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008256</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/games/nvidia-launches-ai-first-dgx-personal-computing-systems/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T07:06:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nvidia announced that Taiwan’s leading system manufacturers are set to build Nvidia DGX Spark and DGX Station systems.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dean Takahashi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nvidia-powered supercomputer to enable quantum leap for Taiwan’s research]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008257</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/games/nvidia-powered-supercomputer-to-enable-quantum-leap-for-taiwans-research/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T06:58:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nvidia is powering a supercomputer at Taiwan’s National Center for High-Performance Computing that’s set to deliver over eight times more AI performance than before.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dean Takahashi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nvidia powers world’s largest quantum research supercomputer]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008248</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/games/nvidia-powers-worlds-largest-quantum-research-supercomputer/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T06:48:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nvidia announced the opening of the Global Research and Development Center for Business by Quantum-AI Technology.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dean Takahashi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nvidia provides Omniverse Blueprint for AI factory digital twins]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008243</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/games/nvidia-provides-omniverse-blueprint-for-ai-factory-digital-twins/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T06:34:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nvidia today announced a significant expansion of the Nvidia Omniverse Blueprint for AI factory digital twins, now available as a preview.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dean Takahashi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[When a team is too big]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.alexewerlof.com/p/when-a-team-is-too-big</id>
        <link href="https://blog.alexewerlof.com/p/when-a-team-is-too-big"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T04:31:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Extend Power Apps with Reusable Components]]></title>
        <id>682779afad5694b25984f6b1</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/powerapps-component-crash-course/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-16T17:45:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you have experience in traditional software development, low-code tools may feel a bit sparse at first. But to many people’s surprise, traditional techniques often translate quite well to low-code development. Not always one-for-one – but usually ...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brandon Wozniewicz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is Sui: A Comprehensive Guide to Web3 Scalability]]></title>
        <id>6823533984101f00013a5ca4</id>
        <link href="https://blog.quicknode.com/what-is-sui-a-comprehensive-guide-to-web3-scalability/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-15T23:34:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Explore how Sui Network achieves 300,000 TPS through parallel processing, and its applications in gaming, DeFi, and supply chain management.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>QuickNode</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AI Meets Blockchain: Transforming Technology for the Next Era]]></title>
        <id>682354c584101f00013a5cb9</id>
        <link href="https://blog.quicknode.com/ai-and-blockchain-transforming-technology-together/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-15T23:34:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discover how AI and blockchain integration enhances security, efficiency, and innovation in healthcare, supply chains, and financial services.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>QuickNode</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Adventure Layer: AI Native Onchain Games, Unleashed]]></title>
        <id>6824c55abf73460001094973</id>
        <link href="https://blog.quicknode.com/adventure-layer-launches-on-quicknode-raas/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-15T12:04:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Adventure Layer launches layer-2 chain leveraging QuickNode's Rollup-as-a-Service (RaaS) product.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>QuickNode</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[QuickLee V2: An Improved Transparent Look into RPC Provider Latency]]></title>
        <id>680fc8e1f8ae810001969b47</id>
        <link href="https://blog.quicknode.com/quicklee-v2/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-14T13:57:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[View public and real-time dashboards to better understand latency and speed when evaluating RPC providers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>QuickNode</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>