<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2025-05-21T13:48:35.927Z</id>
    <title>AngJianming RSS Feed</title>
    <updated>2025-05-21T13:48:35.927Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to setup the Nuxt starter template on Appwrite Sites]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/appwrite/how-to-setup-the-nuxt-starter-template-on-appwrite-sites-a6g</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/appwrite/how-to-setup-the-nuxt-starter-template-on-appwrite-sites-a6g"/>
        <updated>2025-05-21T13:47:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Building web applications requires both front-end expertise and back-end infrastructure. Appwrite Sites simplifies this process by providing a platform for deploying, hosting, and scaling web applications.
To ease this process even further, Appwrite Sites offers a variety of starter kits for popular frameworks like Next.js, React, Vue, Nuxt, Angular, SvelteKit, and Flutter. In this blog, you will learn how to set up the Nuxt starter template and deploy it to Appwrite Sites.
Nuxt is a framework built on top of Vue.js that makes it easy to develop server-rendered, statically generated, or single-page applications with features like routing, SEO optimization, and modular architecture out of the box.
Appwrite's Nuxt starter template includes:
A clean, single-page UI
Integration with Appwrite's…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Aditya Oberai</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[** Unlocking Efficiency: Advanced Qualities in SAP Ariba Sourcing AR121-- Part 2 **.<br>]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/rayonchance7/-unlocking-efficiency-advanced-qualities-in-sap-ariba-sourcing-ar121-part-2--4cob</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/rayonchance7/-unlocking-efficiency-advanced-qualities-in-sap-ariba-sourcing-ar121-part-2--4cob"/>
        <updated>2025-05-21T13:39:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In today's fast-paced purchase environment, leveraging sophisticated features in SAP Ariba Sourcing can be a game-changer for effectiveness and performance. Acting on Part 1, this short article dives deeper into advanced capabilities in SAP Ariba Sourcing AR121, providing understandings into exactly how experts can improve sourcing processes, boost collaboration, and drive impactful savings. 
** Dynamic Approval Processes *: SAP Ariba Sourcing enables extremely personalized authorization operations. With automated policies, teams can set up conditional approval processes, minimizing bottlenecks and hands-on interventions. * Template-Based RFX Management **: Advanced customers can harness personalized RFX themes to quicken repeated sourcing events. This attribute not only saves time yet lik…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Fisker Justice</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[🌍 7 Online Document Translation Tools Developers & Tech Teams Can Trust in 2025]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/shruti_saraswat_c258d5934/7-online-document-translation-tools-developers-tech-teams-can-trust-in-2025-1dlh</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/shruti_saraswat_c258d5934/7-online-document-translation-tools-developers-tech-teams-can-trust-in-2025-1dlh"/>
        <updated>2025-05-21T13:38:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Whether you're handling software documentation, multilingual reports, or scanned PDFs, translating documents accurately — without breaking formatting — is a challenge that developers, researchers, and product teams often run into.
As teams become more distributed and projects go global, the need for accurate, secure, and layout-preserving translation tools has grown.
This post covers 7 reliable platforms that support document translation across different formats (like PDF, DOCX, Excel, subtitles, etc.) and offer developer-friendly features like OCR, context-aware AI, or multilingual file support.
When working with documents like:
    User guides and manuals
    Legal contracts or compliance files
    Research papers or educational content
    Localized project documentation
…it’s not just …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shruti Saraswat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ruby: Uma Linguagem Puramente Orientada a Objetos]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/marcosfernandesdev/ruby-uma-linguagem-puramente-orientada-a-objetos-225n</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/marcosfernandesdev/ruby-uma-linguagem-puramente-orientada-a-objetos-225n"/>
        <updated>2025-05-21T13:37:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ruby é frequentemente descrita como uma linguagem elegante, expressiva e com uma sintaxe que prioriza a legibilidade e produtividade do desenvolvedor. Mas o que realmente destaca Ruby no universo das linguagens de programação é seu compromisso total com o paradigma orientado a objetos. Vamos explorar o que isso significa e como isso molda a experiência de programação em Ruby.
Diferentemente de outras linguagens que se dizem orientadas a objetos como Java, JavaScript e Python, em Ruby absolutamente tudo é um objeto. Não existem tipos primitivos ou básicos que se comportam de maneira diferente.
Números, strings, booleanos, até mesmo o valor nil (equivalente ao null de outras linguagens) - todos são objetos completos com seus próprios métodos e comportamentos. Isso significa que você pode faz…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Marcos Fernandes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cypress vs Selenium: Which testing framework is better?]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/mailosaur_/cypress-vs-selenium-which-testing-framework-is-better-4h33</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/mailosaur_/cypress-vs-selenium-which-testing-framework-is-better-4h33"/>
        <updated>2025-05-21T13:36:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What are testing frameworks used for?
In general, testing frameworks are used to set up and run automated tests for web applications. It allows for elements like password reset systems, automated emails, forms for user input, and other key parts that work together to be tested, creating a reliable online application. Web apps can include a lot of categories like online stores, websites, email providers, and other tools;, and in order to make sure they work how they’re expected, they have to undergo some form of testing.
Testing frameworks come in many shapes and sizes. Some, like Selenium and Cypress, are open-source and free to use. Others require paid subscriptions and offer perks like low and no-code testing. The right option will depend a lot on what testing plans you have, and what re…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mailosaur</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Application Layer: Where Data Meets Your Favorite Apps (and Memes)]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/aniruddhaadak_/application-layer-where-data-meets-your-favorite-apps-and-memes-21m0</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/aniruddhaadak_/application-layer-where-data-meets-your-favorite-apps-and-memes-21m0"/>
        <updated>2025-05-21T13:36:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome to the Application Layer—the flashy, user-friendly face of networking. This is where data transforms into your TikTok feed, Netflix streams, and those late-night emails you regret sending. Let’s dive into how this layer keeps your digital life spicy.  
What Is the Application Layer?


Imagine the internet as a fancy restaurant. The Application Layer is the menu, the waiter, and the chef—all rolled into one. It’s what you see and use: browsers, email clients, streaming apps, and more.  
"The Application Layer: Where data finally grows up and becomes something useful—like cat videos or productivity tools."  
Protocols You Already Know (But Didn’t Realize)



  
  
  HTTP/HTTPS: The Internet’s Waiter




HTTP: HyperText Transfer Protocol. It’s how websites load when you type “google.c…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ANIRUDDHA ADAK</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Entendendo a Arquitetura MVC no Ruby on Rails: A Base para Aplicações Web Robustas]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/marcosfernandesdev/entendendo-a-arquitetura-mvc-no-ruby-on-rails-a-base-para-aplicacoes-web-robustas-4jl9</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/marcosfernandesdev/entendendo-a-arquitetura-mvc-no-ruby-on-rails-a-base-para-aplicacoes-web-robustas-4jl9"/>
        <updated>2025-05-21T13:34:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Se você está começando no desenvolvimento web com Ruby on Rails, ou mesmo se já tem alguma experiência, entender profundamente a arquitetura MVC (Model-View-Controller) é fundamental para criar aplicações organizadas, escaláveis e fáceis de manter. Neste artigo, vamos desvendar como o Rails implementa esse padrão de design e por que ele é tão poderoso.
A arquitetura MVC é um padrão de design que separa uma aplicação em três componentes principais:
Model (Modelo): Gerencia os dados e a lógica de negócios
View (Visão): Exibe as informações ao usuário
Controller (Controlador): Orquestra a aplicação, recebendo eventos do mundo externo e coordenando o modelo e a visão
Este "triunvirato" — modelo, visão e controlador — trabalha em conjunto para criar uma separação clara de responsabilidades, res…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Marcos Fernandes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[🎙️We have prepared a lot of new things in HMPL.js for developers!]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/hmpljs/we-have-prepared-a-lot-of-new-things-in-hmpljs-for-developers-31dn</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/hmpljs/we-have-prepared-a-lot-of-new-things-in-hmpljs-for-developers-31dn"/>
        <updated>2025-05-21T13:32:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Within a month and a half since version 3, the template language has been expanded with new functionality and ecosystem modules.
All of this is great for web app development because sometimes people make new features and you never need them. It's not entirely correct, but imagine you have a phone and they add a widget or something that you would never put on your home screen. That's not the case here.
Here everything was prepared simply by the most obvious needs.
Well, let's see what's there now!
One of the main innovations is the integration of HMPL with Vite.js. Now, you can include a plugin that processes files with the .hmpl extension in your projects.
vite.config.mjs
import { defineConfig } from "vite";
import hmplPlugin from "vite-plugin-hmpl";

export default defineConfig({
  plugin…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Anthony Max</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Burn: The Next-Gen Deep Learning Framework That Will Blow Your Mind]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/githubopensource/burn-the-next-gen-deep-learning-framework-that-will-blow-your-mind-136i</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/githubopensource/burn-the-next-gen-deep-learning-framework-that-will-blow-your-mind-136i"/>
        <updated>2025-05-21T13:28:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Quick Summary: 📝


Burn is a deep learning framework written in Rust that prioritizes flexibility, efficiency, and portability. It achieves high performance through features like automatic kernel fusion and asynchronous execution. The framework's thread-safe design and cross-platform support enable multi-device training and deployment on various backends, including CUDA, Metal, and WebGPU.
✅ Blazing-fast performance thanks to automatic kernel fusion and asynchronous execution.


✅ Improved developer experience with a clean, intuitive API and excellent documentation.


✅ Enhanced scalability with thread-safe building blocks for effortless multi-device training.


✅ Built in Rust for memory safety and speed.


✅ Flexibility and portability across various backends




  
  
  Project Statist…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GitHubOpenSource</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Contributing to Elixir Documentation: My Journey with PR #14501]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/abreujp/contributing-to-elixir-documentation-my-journey-with-pr-14501-41do</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/abreujp/contributing-to-elixir-documentation-my-journey-with-pr-14501-41do"/>
        <updated>2025-05-21T13:23:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Have you ever been bitten by a silent nil in Elixir? I have—and it led me to submit a PR to Elixir's documentation. What started as a frustrating debugging session turned into a valuable learning experience about both Elixir and effective technical writing.
While reading the Elixir documentation and exploring its ecosystem, I found an opportunity to improve the documentation about an important anti-pattern - non-assertive map access. This article shares my experience submitting PR #14501 and the valuable lessons I learned about effective documentation through collaboration with Elixir's core team.
In Elixir, accessing map values can be done in two main ways:
Static access (map.key): Used when a key is expected to exist. If missing, it raises a KeyError.
Dynamic access (map[:key]): Used for…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>João Paulo Abreu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why is a Communication & Stakeholder Management Plan essential in projects?]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/writegenic/why-is-a-communication-stakeholder-management-plan-essential-in-projects-1i56</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/writegenic/why-is-a-communication-stakeholder-management-plan-essential-in-projects-1i56"/>
        <updated>2025-05-21T13:20:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A Communication & Stakeholder Management Plan plays a critical role in the success of any project. It ensures that every stakeholder is kept informed, aligned, and engaged throughout the project lifecycle. Here's a breakdown of its key benefits:
The plan sets a clear communication strategy for sharing information with all stakeholders. It defines what will be communicated, by whom, how often, and through which channels. This eliminates guesswork and promotes consistent, timely updates.
Without a structured communication plan, stakeholders may receive conflicting or outdated information. This can lead to misunderstandings and delays. A well-organized plan prevents these issues by providing a single source of truth for project communications.

When stakeholders are consistently informed and …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Writegenic AI</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why walking is the most underrated form of exercise (2017)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nbcnews.com/better/health/why-walking-most-underrated-form-exercise-ncna797271</id>
        <link href="https://www.nbcnews.com/better/health/why-walking-most-underrated-form-exercise-ncna797271"/>
        <updated>2025-05-21T13:20:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GENIUS Act ‘legitimizes’ stablecoins for global institutional adoption]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/genius-act-legitimizes-stablecoins-institutional-adoption</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/genius-act-legitimizes-stablecoins-institutional-adoption?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-21T13:19:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Stablecoin adoption among institutions could surge as the United States Senate prepares to debate a key piece of legislation aimed at regulating the sector.  
After failing to gain support from key Democrats on May 8, the Guiding and Establishing National Innovation for US Stablecoins (GENIUS) Act passed the US Senate in a 66–32 procedural vote on May 20 and is now heading to a debate on the Senate floor.
The bill seeks to set clear rules for stablecoin collateralization and mandate compliance with Anti-Money Laundering laws.
Related: German gov’t missed out on $2.3B profit after selling Bitcoin at $57K
“This act doesn’t just regulate stablecoins, it legitimizes them,” said Andrei Grachev, managing partner at DWF Labs and Falcon Finance.
“It sets clear rules, and with clarity comes confide…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Zoltan Vardai</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google I/O Keynote 2025 Summary: Gemini Deep Think, Search AI Mode, Android XR, Jules]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/justdetermined/google-io-keynote-2025-summary-gemini-deep-think-search-ai-mode-android-xr-jules-3g1b</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/justdetermined/google-io-keynote-2025-summary-gemini-deep-think-search-ai-mode-android-xr-jules-3g1b"/>
        <updated>2025-05-21T13:19:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google I/O Keynote 2025 Summary: Advancements in AI, Search, and XR. 
Ironwood 7th Generation TPU(Tensor Processing Unit): Designed to power thinking and inference at scale with 10X performance over previous generation. Coming to Google Cloud customers later this year. 

Update: Gemini Now Has over 400M monthly users.
Gemini 2.5 Pro: Optimized for quality and complex tasks. It includes an enhanced reasoning mode called Deep Think 
Gemini 2.5 Flash: optimized for speed and cost-efficiency, particularly for high-volume applications.
Jules: Google's AI Coding Agent. Jules autonomously reads your code performs tasks like writing tests and fixing bugs. 
Gemini Live: This feature, leveraging Project Astra, rolled out on Android and iOS already, allowing real-time conversations with Gemini about …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Just Determined</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CoinDesk 20 Performance Update: Uniswap (UNI) Gains 7.2% as Index Climbs Higher]]></title>
        <id>ad29cf5b-4af5-4c15-9808-7efbdca30ec3</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/coindesk-indices/2025/05/21/coindesk-20-performance-update-uniswap-uni-gains-7-2-as-index-climbs-higher"/>
        <updated>2025-05-21T13:15:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Avalanche (AVAX) was also among the top performers, rising 3.5% from Tuesday.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CoinDesk Indices</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Building an agentic image generator that improves itself]]></title>
        <id>https://simulate.trybezel.com/research/image_agent</id>
        <link href="https://simulate.trybezel.com/research/image_agent"/>
        <updated>2025-05-21T13:12:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Guatemala's Largest Bank Adopts Stablecoin Rails for U.S. Remittance Payments]]></title>
        <id>26ded7a7-350b-40d8-a3ef-b0084eb1aef2</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2025/05/21/guatemalas-largest-bank-adopts-stablecoin-rails-for-us-remittance-payments"/>
        <updated>2025-05-21T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SukuPay will allow Guatemalans to receive funds from the U.S. for a flat 99 cent fee, using only a phone number within their Banco National mobile app Zigi.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Crawley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Hedge Fund Temple Capital Hires TradFi Execs as Institutional Demand Grows]]></title>
        <id>43c08df8-fc59-4375-a314-524b86c4a1d8</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2025/05/21/crypto-hedge-fund-temple-capital-hires-tradfi-execs-as-institutional-demand-grows"/>
        <updated>2025-05-21T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Richard Murray, former CEO of crypto asset manager Hilbert Capital, has recently joined Temple Capital as a partner of the firm.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Will Canny</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Mining Startup Sangha Sees $42M Revenue as It Breaks Ground on West Texas Pilot Project]]></title>
        <id>86ad5dff-8a62-4543-921d-c68e49e2034a</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/21/bitcoin-mining-startup-sangha-breaks-ground-on-west-texas-pilot-project"/>
        <updated>2025-05-21T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The firm expects its 19.9 MW bitcoin mine to be running by the end of July.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tom Carreras</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Guatemala’s largest bank integrates blockchain for cross-border payments]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/guatemala-largest-bank-integrates-blockchain-cross-border-payments</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/guatemala-largest-bank-integrates-blockchain-cross-border-payments?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-21T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Guatemala’s largest bank, Banco Industrial, has integrated crypto infrastructure provider SukuPay into its mobile banking app, allowing locals to more easily receive remittances powered by blockchain technology. 
SukuPay’s infrastructure has been fully embedded inside the Zigi payment app, allowing Guatemalans to receive funds from the United States instantly for a $0.99 flat fee, the company disclosed on May 21. 
Users of the Zigi app do not need a crypto wallet or an International Bank Account Number (IBAN) to receive the funds, the company said. 
SukuPay CEO Yonathan Lapchik told Cointelegraph that the “key to mainstream adoption of blockchain technology is making it invisible to the end-user” so that there are no technical barriers. 
“That’s the only way we’ll scale blockchain to billi…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Sam Bourgi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hong Kong passes stablecoin bill, set to open licensing by year-end]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/hong-kong-passes-stablecoin-bill-opens-licensing-by-year-end</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/hong-kong-passes-stablecoin-bill-opens-licensing-by-year-end?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-21T12:58:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hong Kong’s Legislative Council passed the Stablecoin Bill, paving the way for a regulated framework that could position the region as a global leader in digital assets and Web3 development.  
In a May 21 post on X, Legislative Council member Johnny Ng Kit-Chong said the bill had passed its third reading, clearing the final hurdle for adoption.
“It is expected that by the end of this year, major institutions will be able to apply to the Hong Kong Monetary Authority to become licensed stablecoin issuers,” Ng said.
Image of the legislative assembly session. Source: Johnny Ng Kit-Chong
According to the new Hong Kong legislation, stablecoins must be backed by fiat currency as underlying assets. Ng said Hong Kong is welcoming “global enterprises and institutions interested in issuing stablecoin…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Adrian Zmudzinski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Mining Profitability Fell in April as Network Hashrate Rose: Jefferies]]></title>
        <id>e9310bf0-1eaa-44b4-b9e2-76930d6f2ed7</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/21/bitcoin-mining-profitability-fell-in-april-as-network-hashrate-rose-jefferies"/>
        <updated>2025-05-21T12:53:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[U.S.-listed miners also produced fewer bitcoin last month than in March.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Will Canny</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[XRP-BTC Pair Flashes First Golden Cross, Hinting at Major Bull Run for XRP]]></title>
        <id>b8451b15-3742-401a-99c3-c6de919be37b</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/21/xrp-btc-pair-flashes-first-golden-cross-hinting-at-major-bull-run-for-xrp"/>
        <updated>2025-05-21T12:41:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The pattern has raised the probability of ratio breaking out of its prolonged sideways trend in a sign of major XRP uptrend.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Omkar Godbole</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[5 Boring Things That Have a Bigger Impact Than AI Assistants on Dev Productivity]]></title>
        <id>https://codemanship.wordpress.com/2025/05/21/five-boring-things-that-have-a-bigger-impact-than-a-i-coding-assistants-on-dev-team-productivity/</id>
        <link href="https://codemanship.wordpress.com/2025/05/21/five-boring-things-that-have-a-bigger-impact-than-a-i-coding-assistants-on-dev-team-productivity/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-21T12:39:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Download: Google’s AI mission, and America’s reliance on natural gas]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1117249</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/05/21/1117249/the-download-googles-ai-mission-and-americas-reliance-on-natural-gas/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-21T12:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is today’s edition of The Download, our weekday newsletter that provides a daily dose of what’s going on in the world of technology. By putting AI into everything, Google wants to make it invisible If you want to know where AI is headed, this year’s Google I/O has you covered. The company’s annual showcase of next-gen…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rhiannon Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Overlap (YC S24) Is Hiring]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ycombinator.com/companies/overlap/jobs/Z8IbFjD-product-engineer</id>
        <link href="https://www.ycombinator.com/companies/overlap/jobs/Z8IbFjD-product-engineer"/>
        <updated>2025-05-21T12:01:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Property Testing Finds Bugs Unit Testing Does Not (2021)]]></title>
        <id>https://buttondown.com/hillelwayne/archive/why-property-testing-finds-bugs-unit-testing-does/</id>
        <link href="https://buttondown.com/hillelwayne/archive/why-property-testing-finds-bugs-unit-testing-does/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-21T11:49:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[By putting AI into everything, Google wants to make it invisible]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1117251</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/05/21/1117251/by-putting-ai-into-everything-google-wants-to-make-it-invisible/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-21T11:49:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you want to know where AI is headed, this year’s Google I/O has you covered. The company’s annual showcase of next-gen products, which kicked off yesterday, has all of the pomp and pizzazz, the sizzle reels and celebrity walk-ons, that you’d expect from a multimillion-dollar marketing event. But it also shows us just how…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Will Douglas Heaven</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Infinix GT 30 Pro Now Official In Malaysia From RM1,299]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=352678</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/352678/infinix-gt-30-pro-official-malaysia-from-rm1299/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-21T11:25:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Infinix previously shared that it will be launching the GT 30 Pro today, and sure enough, the phone has gotten its official unveiling. With the launch, we get its confirmed spec sheet, as well as its asking price in the market, but we’ll get to that in a bit. The Infinix GT 30 Pro has […]
The post Infinix GT 30 Pro Now Official In Malaysia From RM1,299 appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ian Chee</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Yield-bearing stablecoins surge to $11B, now 4.5% of market: Report]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/yield-bearing-stablecoins-hit-11b-pendle-dominates-growth</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/yield-bearing-stablecoins-hit-11b-pendle-dominates-growth?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-21T11:19:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Yield-bearing stablecoins have soared to $11 billion in circulation, representing 4.5% of the total stablecoin market, a steep climb from just $1.5 billion and a 1% market share at the start of 2024.
One of the biggest winners is Pendle, a decentralized protocol that enables users to lock in fixed yields or speculate on variable interest rates. Pendle now accounts for 30% of all yield-bearing stablecoin total value locked (TVL), roughly $3 billion, the firm said in a report shared with Cointelegraph.  
Pendle noted that stablecoins make up 83% of its $4 billion total value locked, a sharp rise from less than 20% just a year ago. In contrast, assets such as Ether (ETH), which historically contributed 80%–90% of Pendle’s TVL, have shrunk to less than 10%.
Traditional stablecoins like USDt (U…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Amin Haqshanas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Daybook Americas: Bitcoin Eyes New High as MetaPlanet Mania Builds]]></title>
        <id>e3ecc3a9-0ff1-4c7c-965c-34d52e53e922</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/daybook-us/2025/05/21/crypto-daybook-americas-bitcoin-eyes-new-high-as-metaplanet-mania-builds"/>
        <updated>2025-05-21T11:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Your day-ahead look for May 21, 2025]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>James Van Straten</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Roto: A Compiled Scripting Language for Rust]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.nlnetlabs.nl/introducing-roto-a-compiled-scripting-language-for-rust/</id>
        <link href="https://blog.nlnetlabs.nl/introducing-roto-a-compiled-scripting-language-for-rust/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-21T11:10:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Watching AI drive Microsoft employees insane]]></title>
        <id>https://old.reddit.com/r/ExperiencedDevs/comments/1krttqo/my_new_hobby_watching_ai_slowly_drive_microsoft/</id>
        <link href="https://old.reddit.com/r/ExperiencedDevs/comments/1krttqo/my_new_hobby_watching_ai_slowly_drive_microsoft/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-21T10:57:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[2026 Toyota RAV4 Debuts With HEV, PHEV Models]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=352667</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/352667/2026-toyota-rav4-debuts-with-hev-phev-models/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-21T10:56:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Toyota RAV4 has been in a staple in the compact SUV scene and for 2026, it takes the form of plug-in hybrid (PHEV) and hybrid (HEV). The car comes in three trims – the Core, Adventure and GR Sport. At first glance, the new RAV4 has a Land Cruiser-esque square look to it, with […]
The post 2026 Toyota RAV4 Debuts With HEV, PHEV Models appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Keran</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bold Technologies and My Aion launch $2.5B smart city AI platform]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/abu-dhabi-bold-technologies-my-aion-launch-aion-sentia-ai-smart-city-platform</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/abu-dhabi-bold-technologies-my-aion-launch-aion-sentia-ai-smart-city-platform?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-21T10:55:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Abu Dhabi-based Bold Technologies, a subsidiary of conglomerate Bold Holdings, has partnered with international artificial intelligence company My Aion to launch a $2.5 billion smart-city initiative aimed at transforming urban infrastructure through AI.
The companies announced the development of a platform called Aion Sentia Cognitive City, which manages complex urban systems. The platform will be powered by Maia, an AI core engine developed by My Aion, and aims to optimize and manage systems across mobility, energy, education, healthcare and digital services. 
My Aion CEO Daniele Marinelli said the AI will know the user well enough to “recommend the perfect place for your anniversary dinner and book it for you without you lifting a finger.”
The project will debut in Abu Dhabi before expan…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Ezra Reguerra</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MSI Unveils New Claw A8 BZ2EM With AMD Ryzen Z2 Extreme At Computex 2025]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=352680</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/352680/msi-unveils-new-claw-a8-bz2em-computex-2025/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-21T10:37:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[MSI has introduced a new entry to its handheld gaming PC lineup with the Claw A8 BZ2EM at Computex 2025. Marking a notable departure from its previous Intel-powered models, this latest version is equipped with AMD’s Ryzen Z2 Extreme processor – confirming earlier rumours ahead of the reveal. The MSI Claw A8 BZ2EM retains the […]
The post MSI Unveils New Claw A8 BZ2EM With AMD Ryzen Z2 Extreme At Computex 2025 appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Heirul Kamel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How high can Bitcoin price go?]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/how-high-can-bitcoin-price-go</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/how-high-can-bitcoin-price-go?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-21T10:15:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Key takeaways:

Bitcoin gained 14% since May 5, breaking $108,000  for the first time since January.

Targets of $140,000 and even $200,000 are increasingly discussed for 2025.

Bitcoin (BTC) price has climbed by more than 14% since May 5, rallying to $107,000 on May 21.
Data from Cointelegraph Markets Pro and TradingView shows that the price of Bitcoin rose 3.6% to a four-month high of $108,000 on May 21 from a low of $104,200 the previous day. 
The last time BTC/USD traded above this level was on Jan. 20, when President Donald Trump’s inauguration fueled BTC’s price rally to $109,350 all-time high.
BTC/USD daily chart. Source: TradingView
Bitcoin’s price rise coincides with a marketwide rally, with the global crypto market capitalization rising above $3.36 trillion for the first time sin…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Nancy Lubale</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Suisse eyes UAE expansion with regulatory nod in Abu Dhabi]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-suisse-in-principle-approval-in-abu-dhabi</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-suisse-in-principle-approval-in-abu-dhabi?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-21T10:12:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Suisse secured an in-principle approval (IPA) from the Financial Services Regulatory Authority (FSRA) of the Abu Dhabi Global Market (ADGM), marking a major step in the Swiss crypto firm’s expansion beyond the European Union.
The Swiss crypto financial service provider received the in-principle approval through its subsidiary BTCS (Middle East), according to a May 21 news release.
The IPA is a precursor to a full financial services license, which would allow Bitcoin Suisse to provide regulated crypto financial services such as digital asset trading, crypto securities and derivatives offerings, as well as custody solutions.
The approval reflects the firm’s “strong commitment to maintaining the highest standards of transparency, security, and regulatory compliance,” according to Ceyd…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Zoltan Vardai</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Hawk Tuah Girl' Hailey Welch Claims SEC, FBI Cleared Her for the HAWK Memecoin Disaster]]></title>
        <id>c07c876e-6d0a-46a5-a94f-91e4d34703cb</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2025/05/21/hawk-tuah-girl-hailey-welch-claims-sec-fbi-cleared-her-for-the-hawk-memecoin-disaster"/>
        <updated>2025-05-21T09:48:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Haliey Welch says she “didn’t know enough about crypto” — despite previously claiming she’d “learned so much” ahead of her failed token launch.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shaurya Malwa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Redmi K80 Ultra Gets CMIIT Certification; Official Release Soon]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=352635</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/352635/redmi-k80-ultra-gets-cmiit-certification-official-release-soon/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-21T09:46:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Xiaomi released its Redmi K80 smartphone series last year, which currently consists of a base and Pro model. Now, Xpertpick reports that an Ultra model is on its way, having been MIIT (Ministry of Industry and Information Technology)-certified in China. The Redmi K80 Ultra is listed under model number 25060RK16C in the MIIT database. As […]
The post Redmi K80 Ultra Gets CMIIT Certification; Official Release Soon appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Newsdesk</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[These Six Charts Explain Why Bitcoin's Recent Move to Over $100K May Be More Durable Than January's Run]]></title>
        <id>aed18392-5758-471b-9869-7261253ffc7a</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/21/these-six-charts-explain-why-bitcoin-s-recent-move-to-over-usd100k-may-be-more-durable-than-january-s-run"/>
        <updated>2025-05-21T09:38:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Financial conditions, stablecoin flows and other key metrics point to stronger foundation compared to the December-January twin peaks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Omkar Godbole</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Strive Eyes $7.9B Distressed Mt. Gox Bitcoin Claims to Accumulate Discounted BTC]]></title>
        <id>97d35fbb-556b-4470-870d-46b9f1583f40</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2025/05/21/strive-eyes-79b-distressed-mt-gox-bitcoin-claims-to-accumulate-discounted-btc"/>
        <updated>2025-05-21T09:28:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The goal is to gain exposure to bitcoin at a discount, with the aim of beating BTC's price performance in the long run.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Francisco Rodrigues</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto.com secures EU license to launch crypto financial derivatives]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/crypto-com-secures-eu-license</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/crypto-com-secures-eu-license?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-21T09:23:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mobile-first crypto exchange and payment platform Crypto.com secured a license allowing it to offer cryptocurrency financial derivatives in the European Economic Area.
According to a May 21 announcement, Crypto.com secured a Markets in Financial Instruments Directive (MiFID) license.
“We have already expanded our brand presence in Europe since receiving our MiCA licence and we now look forward to providing customers across the region even more ways to engage with our platform through these new offerings,” said Crypto.com’s co-founder and CEO, Kris Marszalek.
Source: Crypto.com
The announcement followed Crypto.com receiving in-principle approval to operate across the European Union under a Markets in Crypto-Assets (MiCA) license in mid-January. The company received regulatory approval for i…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Adrian Zmudzinski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google Adds Gemini AI To Chrome For Paying Users In The US]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=352621</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/352621/google-adds-gemini-ai-to-chrome-for-paying-users-in-the-us/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-21T09:14:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google has announced that it is adding its Gemini AI assistant to its Chrome browser. For now, Gemini will only be available on the desktop version, and only for AI Pro and AI Ultra subscribers in the US who use English as their Chrome language. It is unclear whether a global rollout of this feature […]
The post Google Adds Gemini AI To Chrome For Paying Users In The US appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nurul Kamil</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin &#039;blow-off top&#039; set at $128K with new all-time highs in sight]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-blow-off-top-128k-new-all-time-highs-sight</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-blow-off-top-128k-new-all-time-highs-sight?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-21T09:12:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Key points:

Bitcoin tags $108,000 for the first time since the day of its current all-time highs in January.

Traders and analysts mention support extending toward $90,000, but the probability of a retest is fading.

Near-term upside targets include a “blow-off top” at $128,000.

Bitcoin (BTC) spiked to more than $108,000 on May 21, marking new four-month highs. Where will BTC/USD go next?
Crypto traders and analysts are lining up their forecasts with BTC price action less than 1.5% away from new all-time highs.

BTC price support test now “less likely”
Bitcoin continues to coil below what is now its most significant psychological resistance barrier, January’s all-time highs.
BTC/USD 1-day chart. Source: Cointelegraph/TradingView
At $109,356 on Bitstamp, per data from Cointelegraph Market…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by William Suberg</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DOGE Holds Bullish Structure as Whales Shed $40M Ahead of Possible Breakout]]></title>
        <id>1e00d85b-231c-4c0b-8868-546ac72e00b1</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/21/doge-holds-bullish-structure-as-whales-shed-usd40m-ahead-of-possible-breakout"/>
        <updated>2025-05-21T09:11:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dogecoin consolidates below $0.26 as whales unload $40M in tokens. Analysts eye a potential breakout toward $0.35–$0.45 amid bullish chart setup.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>AI Boost</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Days to Cover mNAV,' Emerges as the New Standard for Evaluating Bitcoin Equities]]></title>
        <id>8b8e2338-aab2-4886-92e5-c18165e7a361</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/21/days-to-cover-mnav-the-new-standard-for-evaluating-bitcoin-equities"/>
        <updated>2025-05-21T09:10:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A data driven metric reveals which companies are truly stacking sats and which are lagging behind the valuations investors are giving them.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>James Van Straten</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SIB Enters EV Battery Component Sector With ZZ Tech Partnership]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=352571</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/352571/sib-enters-ev-battery-component-sector-with-zz-tech-partnership/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-21T08:54:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Malaysian automotive component manufacturer, Sapura Industrial Berhad (SIB), has announced a joint venture with China’s Zhejiang Zhongze Precision Technology Co. Ltd (ZZ Tech) to produce battery components. More specifically, the team up focuses on the production of “high-precision storage battery casings”. This joint venture marks the entry of SIB into the energy storage and battery […]
The post SIB Enters EV Battery Component Sector With ZZ Tech Partnership appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Keran</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Australian Securities Regulator Wants to Appeal High Court's Decision on Block Earner]]></title>
        <id>fe752bc1-ef8a-47f9-8b5d-bb9834b0f55c</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2025/05/21/australian-securities-regulator-wants-to-appeal-high-courts-decision-on-block-earner"/>
        <updated>2025-05-21T08:50:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The High Court in March 2024 dismissed ASIC's allegations that Block Earner had engaged in unlicensed financial services by offering its DeFi product Access]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Crawley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SEC’s Peirce says NFT royalties do not make tokens securities]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/nft-royalties-not-securities-sec-peirce</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/nft-royalties-not-securities-sec-peirce?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-21T08:38:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[United States Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) Commissioner Hester Peirce said many non-fungible tokens (NFTs), including those with mechanisms to pay creator royalties, likely fall outside the purview of federal securities laws.
In a recent speech, Peirce said NFTs that allow artists to earn resale revenue do not automatically qualify as securities. Unlike stocks, NFTs are programmable assets that distribute proceeds to developers or artists. The SEC official said that mirrors how streaming platforms compensate musicians and filmmakers. 
“Just as streaming platforms pay royalties to the creator of a song or video each time a user plays it, an NFT can enable artists to benefit from the appreciation in the value of their work after its initial sale,” Peirce said. 
Peirce added that …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Ezra Reguerra</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SHIB Spikes Then Reverses Sharply as Whale Activity Turns Bearish]]></title>
        <id>b6c78903-13ad-48f0-8132-86c8d4db4d7c</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/21/shib-spikes-then-reverses-sharply-as-whale-activity-turns-bearish"/>
        <updated>2025-05-21T08:35:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Shiba Inu’s price swings reveal quick gains and sharp reversals, while on-chain data shows whales reducing exposure, hinting at short-term bearish pressure.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>AI Boost</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[South Korea to Let Non-Profits, Exchanges Sell Crypto Under New FSC Rules]]></title>
        <id>4add5a52-ccd1-4459-bddc-879b833571d2</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2025/05/21/south-korea-to-let-non-profits-exchanges-sell-crypto-under-new-fsc-rules"/>
        <updated>2025-05-21T08:32:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Non-profits will need to meet strict conditions such as five years of audited operations and internal committees to vet donations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Francisco Rodrigues</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[South Korea tightens crypto rules ahead of institutional market entry]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/south-korea-tightens-kyc-rules-ahead-of-institutional-crypto-entry</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/south-korea-tightens-kyc-rules-ahead-of-institutional-crypto-entry?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-21T08:27:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[South Korea is tightening rules around digital asset transactions as it prepares to allow institutional players into its crypto market, introducing new guidelines for nonprofit crypto sales and stricter listing standards for exchanges.
On May 20, the Financial Services Commission (FSC) of South Korea said during its fourth Virtual Asset Committee meeting that it had finalized sweeping new measures.
Set to take effect in June, the updated rules allow both nonprofit organizations and virtual asset exchanges to sell cryptocurrencies, but under new compliance standards.
Nonprofit entities must have at least five years of audited financial history to be permitted to receive and sell virtual asset donations. They will also need to establish internal Donation Review Committees to assess the appro…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Amin Haqshanas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mickey Mouse Gets A Formula 1 Car For 2026]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=352439</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/352439/mickey-mouse-gets-formula-1-car-2026/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-21T08:25:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Formula 1 is one of the biggest names in motorsports, and Mickey Mouse is the most iconic character in Disney’s lineup. But what if these two giants teamed up? Well, you don’t have to imagine anymore — F1 and Disney have officially struck a partnership! Starting next year, fans will see Mickey Mouse and his […]
The post Mickey Mouse Gets A Formula 1 Car For 2026 appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Keran</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Photo Essay: Zotac At Computex 2025]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=352349</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/352349/photo-essay-zotac-at-computex-2025/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-21T08:22:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We paid a visit to Zotac’s booth on the first day of Computex 2025. Located at Hall 1 of the Nangang Exhibition Centre and like all brands on the floor, the brand had its portfolio on site for us to see. One of the first things I made a beeline for was Zotac’s refreshed Zone […]
The post Photo Essay: Zotac At Computex 2025 appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John Law</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google Adds Live Translation To Meet; Starting With English, Spanish]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=352546</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/352546/google-adds-live-translation-to-meet-starting-with-english-spanish/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-21T08:08:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Among the various announcements made during the annual I/O event was the introduction of Live Translation in Google Meet. Releasing to subscribers of its AI Premium plans, users communicating on Meet will have their speech live translated into another language when the feature is turned on. The current languages supported are English and Spanish, with […]
The post Google Adds Live Translation To Meet; Starting With English, Spanish appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Newsdesk</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Solana Could Soon Witness Its Largest Consensus Change as Developer Proposes 'Alpenglow']]></title>
        <id>0a0c47d3-5b70-47ee-b3dc-de9f6ea6310c</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/tech/2025/05/21/solana-could-soon-witness-its-largest-consensus-change-as-developer-proposes-alpenglow"/>
        <updated>2025-05-21T08:01:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“We believe that the release of Alpenglow will be a turning point for Solana,” developers wrote in a blog Monday.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shaurya Malwa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why crypto transfers can fail and what you must check before sending]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/explained/why-crypto-transfers-can-fail-and-what-you-must-check-before-sending</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/explained/why-crypto-transfers-can-fail-and-what-you-must-check-before-sending?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-21T07:35:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Why crypto transfers can fail and what you must check before sending            
            
                
Crypto transfers fail more often than most people realize, but user attentiveness can stop most losses.
What’s often marketed as a seamless, borderless system can become frustrating when transfers fail, with no customer service hotline to call and no easy recourse to reverse mistakes. In the crypto universe, the burden of getting it right falls squarely on the shoulders of the user.
But here’s the encouraging part: Most failures are preventable. Understanding why crypto transfers fail can help users avoid costly missteps, navigate the quirks of different networks and send funds with far greater confidence. With a little preparation, you can sidestep common pitfalls and take contro…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Sasha Shilina</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CME's XRP Futures Have Pulled In Nearly $30M Since Debut, Fueling XRP ETF Hopes]]></title>
        <id>f25a9c10-54e8-4841-a1ff-ba26641bb381</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/21/cmes-xrp-futures-have-pulled-in-nearly-30m-since-debut-fueling-xrp-etf-hopes"/>
        <updated>2025-05-21T07:11:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Strong institutional interest in CME’s new XRP futures contracts is reviving hopes for a U.S.-listed spot XRP ETF, as the token gains traction in regulated markets.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shaurya Malwa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Theta Capital raises $175M to back early-stage blockchain startups]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/theta-raises-175m-to-back-crypto-vc-firms-as-sector-rebounds</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/theta-raises-175m-to-back-crypto-vc-firms-as-sector-rebounds?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-21T07:09:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Amsterdam-based Theta Capital Management raised over $175 million for its latest fund-of-funds, aimed at supporting early-stage blockchain startups through specialized venture capital (VC) firms.
The new vehicle, Theta Blockchain Ventures IV, will channel capital into crypto-native VC firms with a track record of backing blockchain innovation, Theta’s managing partner and chief investment officer Ruud Smets told Bloomberg.
Smets said the strategy focuses on specialist managers who can outperform generalist investors in the earliest funding rounds.
“We’ve always been looking for areas where specialization and active management provide a sustainable edge,” Smets noted. He said that the experience and positioning of dedicated crypto VCs “has compounded over time,” creating barriers for less f…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Amin Haqshanas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[LG Introduces xboom Audio Lineup With will.i.am]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=352548</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/352548/lg-xboom-will-i-am/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-21T07:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[LG has announced a new audio lineup called xboom, in collaboration with American artist will.i.am. The lineup is currently made up of three portable Bluetooth speakers and one pair of wireless earbuds. The most affordable of the bunch is the xboom Buds, which are compact earbuds with tiny wing tips for a more snug fit. […]
The post LG Introduces xboom Audio Lineup With will.i.am appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ikmal Rozlan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Futures Open Interest Zoom as BTC Inches Towards All-Time High; DOGE, ADA, XRP Add 4%]]></title>
        <id>3cd24ae6-677e-4605-a57d-dfc5290ca55e</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/21/bitcoin-futures-open-interest-zoomas-btc-inches-towards-all-time-high-doge-ada-xrp-add-4"/>
        <updated>2025-05-21T06:36:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Buoyant sentiment and calm volatility are fueling leveraged bets as BTC consolidates above $100,000 — setting up what traders say could be a clean move to new highs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shaurya Malwa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Overview of the Ada Computer Language Competition (1979)]]></title>
        <id>https://iment.com/maida/computer/redref/</id>
        <link href="https://iment.com/maida/computer/redref/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-21T06:18:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SEC delays decision on Ether staking and XRP ETFs, as analysts expected]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/sec-delays-ether-staking-xrp-etfs-expected-analyst</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/sec-delays-ether-staking-xrp-etfs-expected-analyst?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-21T06:13:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The US Securities and Exchange Commission has delayed its decision on Bitwise’s application to add staking to its Ether exchange-traded fund and on Grayscale’s XRP ETF bid, which analysts had expected.
The SEC said on May 20 that it needed to extend its decision on Bitwise’s application by 45 days to “consider the proposed rule change and the issues raised therein.” The agency needed to either decide or punt its decision by May 22.
The agency also delayed deciding on Grayscale’s XRP (XRP) tracking ETF and Bitwise’s Solana (SOL) tracking fund while it seeks public comments and begins “proceedings to allow for additional analysis” of the proposals to ensure they meet regulatory standards.
Bloomberg ETF analyst James Seyffart said on X that both delays were expected because the SEC “typically…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Stephen Katte</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[KindlyMD shareholders OK merger with Trump-linked Bitcoin firm]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/kindlymd-shareholders-ok-merger-with-trump-linked-bitcoin-firm</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/kindlymd-shareholders-ok-merger-with-trump-linked-bitcoin-firm?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-21T06:01:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Shareholders of the healthcare services provider KindlyMD, Inc have approved a proposed merger with Bitcoin holding company Nakamoto Holdings, founded by US President Donald Trump’s crypto adviser, David Bailey.
KindlyMD and Nakamoto Holdings, a newly formed company that focuses on creating a network of Bitcoin-related entities, will both file information statements with the Securities and Exchange Commission, KindlyMD said in a May 20 statement.
The merger is expected to take place 20 days after both companies have shared the information statement with KindlyMD’s shareholders, with the transaction expected to be finalized in the third quarter of 2025.
Google Finance shows shares in KindlyMD (KDLY) closed the May 20 trading session up 9% at $15.22 and gained another 4.8% after the bell as …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Tarang Khaitan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Sets Record Daily Close With $110K as the Next Level to Watch for BTC]]></title>
        <id>77e476d9-5a46-4072-8996-39f0786cb6ed</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/21/bitcoin-sets-record-daily-close-with-usd110k-as-the-next-level-to-watch-for-btc"/>
        <updated>2025-05-21T05:21:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The next significant price level for Bitcoin is $110,000, where market dynamics could amplify price movements.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Omkar Godbole</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blackstone buys $1M worth of Bitcoin ETF in first crypto bet]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/blackstone-buys-1-million-blackrock-bitcoin-etf-ibit</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/blackstone-buys-1-million-blackrock-bitcoin-etf-ibit?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-21T05:16:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Blackstone, which bills itself as the “the world’s largest alternative asset manager,” disclosed its first-ever crypto-related purchase, buying shares in BlackRock’s spot Bitcoin exchange-traded fund.
However, Blackstone’s investment, reported in a May 20 filing with the US Securities and Exchange Commission, only totaled around $1.08 million — a fraction of the asset manager’s $1.2 trillion portfolio.
Blackstone reported holding 23,094 shares of BlackRock’s iShares Bitcoin Trust ETF (IBIT) as of March 31.
The IBIT shares were added to Blackstone’s Alternative Multi-Strategy Fund (BTMIX), which holds $2.63 billion worth of assets, Google Finance data shows.
The filing shows Blackstone also bought 4,300 shares in crypto ATM operator Bitcoin Depot Inc. (BTM) for a total cost of $6,300 and sp…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Brayden Lindrea</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Convolutions, Polynomials and Flipped Kernels]]></title>
        <id>https://eli.thegreenplace.net/2025/convolutions-polynomials-and-flipped-kernels/</id>
        <link href="https://eli.thegreenplace.net/2025/convolutions-polynomials-and-flipped-kernels/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-21T04:35:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘Hawk tuah girl’ Haliey Welch says FBI probed her ‘memecoin disaster’]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/hawk-tuah-girl-haliey-welch-fbi-probed-over-hawk-memecoin</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/hawk-tuah-girl-haliey-welch-fbi-probed-over-hawk-memecoin?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-21T04:03:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Haliey Welch, better known as the “Hawk tuah girl,” says the Federal Bureau of Investigation briefly probed her after her “memecoin disaster” — the failed launch of a token in her image that she promoted. 
Welch said in a May 21 episode of her “Talk Tuah” podcast that the FBI showed up at her grandmother’s house looking to speak to her over the Hawk Tuah (HAWK) crypto token, which many crypto commentators have called an exit scam.
“After the coin launch, the feds came to granny’s house and knocked on her door, and she called me, having a heart attack, saying: ‘The FBI is here after you, what have you done?’”
Welch said she handed over her phone to the FBI and met with agents who “interrogated me, asking me questions and everything else related to crypto.”
“They cleared me, I was good to go…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Brayden Lindrea</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AMD unveils new Threadripper CPUs and Radeon GPUs for gamers at Computex 2025]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008206</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/games/amd-unveils-new-threadripper-cpus-and-radeon-gpus-for-gamers-at-computex-2025/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-21T03:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AMD held a Computex press event to introduce its Radeon RX 9060 XT graphics cards and Threadripper CPUs for next-gen gaming and workstations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dean Takahashi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Secret Trove of Rare Guitars Heads to the Met]]></title>
        <id>https://www.newyorker.com/magazine/2025/05/26/a-secret-trove-of-rare-guitars-heads-to-the-met</id>
        <link href="https://www.newyorker.com/magazine/2025/05/26/a-secret-trove-of-rare-guitars-heads-to-the-met"/>
        <updated>2025-05-21T02:13:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NYC Mayor Eric Adams launches crypto advisory council]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/nyc-mayor-eric-adams-launches-crypto-taskforce</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/nyc-mayor-eric-adams-launches-crypto-taskforce?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-21T01:37:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New York City Mayor Eric Adams says he will create a digital advisory council to attract jobs and investment to the Big Apple and position it as the “crypto capital of the globe.”
“This is not about chasing memes or trends,” Adams told the inaugural New York City Crypto Summit on May 20. “We want to use the technology of tomorrow to better serve New Yorkers today.”
“We have experts right here, and they are going to help us navigate solutions that serve our city,” he added. “The age of tokenization, which includes crypto and blockchain and other fintech innovations, that age is here, and we’re going to continue to move forward with it.”
Adams didn’t share further details on the advisory group, but said a council chair and key policy recommendations would follow in the next few weeks.

We're…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Stephen Katte</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SEC Charges Unicoin, Top Executives With $100M ‘Massive Securities Fraud’]]></title>
        <id>52b6a53a-ba17-4896-aa11-65abbba3d283</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2025/05/20/sec-charges-unicoin-top-executives-with-100m-massive-securities-fraud"/>
        <updated>2025-05-21T01:29:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Unicoin’s CEO announced last month that he’d rejected the SEC’s offer to negotiate a settlement.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nikhilesh De</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SEC charges Unicoin crypto platform over alleged $100 million fraud]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/sec-charges-unicoin-100-million-fraud</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/sec-charges-unicoin-100-million-fraud?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-21T01:13:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Update May 21, 4:32 am UTC: This article has been updated to add more information from the SEC’s complaint.
The US Securities and Exchange Commission has sued crypto investment platform Unicoin and three of its executives, alleging they made false and misleading statements about their crypto assets that raised over $100 million from investors.
The SEC said on May 20 that it charged Unicoin CEO Alex Konanykhin, board member Silvina Moschini and former investment chief Alex Dominguez with misleading over 5,000 investors about certificates that conveyed rights to receive Unicoin tokens and stock.
SEC Division of Enforcement associate director Mark Cave claimed that starting in 2022, the trio “exploited thousands of investors with fictitious promises that its tokens, when issued, would be back…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Stephen Katte</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Strive targets 75,000 Bitcoin from Mt. Gox claims to build Bitcoin treasury]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/strive-targets-75000-bitcoin-in-mt-gox-claims</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/strive-targets-75000-bitcoin-in-mt-gox-claims?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-21T00:49:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Vivek Ramaswamy’s Strive is looking to build its Bitcoin holdings by purchasing distressed Bitcoin claims at a discount, starting with claims tied to 75,000 Bitcoin at the bankrupt crypto exchange Mt. Gox.
Strive said in a May 20 regulatory filing that it partnered with 117 Castell Advisory Group LLC to target claims to Bitcoin (BTC) that have received definitive legal rulings but are still awaiting distribution.
The company said buying the claims would allow it to purchase Bitcoin at a discount and grow its Bitcoin per share ratio ahead of its planned reverse merger with Asset Entities — which is expected to be completed sometime mid this year.
Strive hasn’t disclosed any Bitcoin holdings but claims it will face fewer restrictions on purchasing Bitcoin than companies going public through …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Brayden Lindrea</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[“ZLinq”, a Zero-Allocation LINQ Library for .NET]]></title>
        <id>https://neuecc.medium.com/zlinq-a-zero-allocation-linq-library-for-net-1bb0a3e5c749</id>
        <link href="https://neuecc.medium.com/zlinq-a-zero-allocation-linq-library-for-net-1bb0a3e5c749"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T22:29:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Here’s what happened in crypto today]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/what-happened-in-crypto-today</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/what-happened-in-crypto-today?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T22:02:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today in crypto, DWF Labs’ Andrei Grachev said the US GENIUS Act would legitimize stablecoins for institutional adoption and set a precedent for other global jurisdictions, the US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) filed a $100 million fraud suit against Unicoin and its executives, and Javier Milei shut down a task force investigating the fallout from the LIBRA token scandal.
GENIUS Act “legitimizes” stablecoins for global institutional adoption
Stablecoin adoption among institutions could surge as the United States Senate prepares to debate a key piece of legislation aimed at regulating the sector.
After failing to gain support from key Democrats on May 8, the Guiding and Establishing National Innovation for US Stablecoins (GENIUS) Act passed the US Senate in a 66–32 procedural vote…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Cointelegraph</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Apex Group Buys Majority Stake in Tokenization Specialist Tokeny as RWA Trend Soars]]></title>
        <id>dcd8f748-4310-41a1-ad35-ee2944196b19</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2025/05/20/apex-group-buys-majority-stake-in-tokenization-specialist-tokeny-as-rwa-trend-soars"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T22:00:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Apex Group said it plans to fold Tokeny’s team and tech into its services as it pushes tokenized finance to the mainstream.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Krisztian Sandor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Justin Sun to attend Trump&#039;s dinner with memecoin backers]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/justin-sun-attend-trump-dinner-with-memecoin-backers</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/justin-sun-attend-trump-dinner-with-memecoin-backers?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T20:54:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After weeks of speculation among crypto enthusiasts and news outlets, Tron founder Justin Sun has claimed he owns the wallet that purchased the largest amount of Donald Trump’s memecoin, allowing him to qualify for a dinner and reception with the US president.
In a May 19 X post, Sun said he had received an invitation to attend Trump’s dinner at his golf club outside Washington, DC, as part of a reward for the top 220 memecoin holders. The Tron founder claimed he controlled the top wallet on the TRUMP token leaderboard under the username “Sun,” which held roughly $19 million worth of the memecoin at a price of $13.20.
According to Sun, he plans to network at the May 22 memecoin dinner, “talk crypto,” and “discuss the future” of the industry. It’s unclear why the Tron founder chose to annou…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Turner Wright</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sell in May? Bitcoin Tops $107K, Could Hit Record Highs This Summer Say Analysts]]></title>
        <id>42110d25-971e-4561-b01b-abc1c39cb570</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/20/sell-in-may-bitcoin-tops-107k-could-hit-record-highs-this-summer-say-analysts"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T20:43:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Regulatory tailwinds, persistent ETF and corporate buying, Fed rate decisions and Trump's looming tariff deadline are setting the crypto market up for an eventful next few months.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Krisztian Sandor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin open interest hits record high as bulls stampede toward new BTC price highs]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-open-interest-hits-record-high-as-bulls-stampede-toward-new-btc-price-highs</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-open-interest-hits-record-high-as-bulls-stampede-toward-new-btc-price-highs?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T20:32:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Key takeaways:

Bitcoin futures open interest hit a record $72 billion, signaling rising use of leverage among institutional investors.

$1.2 billion in shorts at $107,000 to $108,000 are at risk of liquidation, boosting BTC’s breakout odds.

The aggregate open interest in Bitcoin (BTC) futures surged to a record high on May 20, raising questions about whether bearish positions are now at risk. Despite repeated failures to break above the $107,000 level since May 18, the sheer volume of leveraged positions could propel Bitcoin to a new all-time high.
Bitcoin futures aggregate open interest, USD. Source: CoinGlass
The total open interest in BTC futures climbed to $72 billion on May 20, marking an 8% increase from $66.6 billion just a week earlier. Institutional demand continues to be a majo…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Marcel Pechman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Litestream: Revamped]]></title>
        <id>https://fly.io/blog/litestream-revamped/</id>
        <link href="https://fly.io/blog/litestream-revamped/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T19:58:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum price gained 90% the last time this indicator turned bullish]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/ethereum-price-gained-90-the-last-time-this-indicator-turned-bullish</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/ethereum-price-gained-90-the-last-time-this-indicator-turned-bullish?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T19:44:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Key Takeaways:

Ethereum is forming a bull flag on the daily chart, with a potential breakout above $3,600.

If ETH reclaims the 2-week Gaussian Channel mid-line, a 90% rally could occur.

Ether (ETH) price is consolidating between $2,400 and $2,750 on its daily chart, forming a bull flag pattern with sights on the $3,000 to $3,100 resistance zone. A bull flag is a continuation pattern that follows a sharp rally (black flagpole) to $2,730 from $1,900, with the current range forming the flag. 
Ethereum 1-day chart. Source: Cointelegraph/TradingView
A bullish breakout above $2,600 could target $3,600, which is calculated by adding the flagpole height to the breakout point, but the immediate key area of interest remains between the resistance range at $3,100-$3,000. 
The 200-day exponential m…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Biraajmaan Tamuly</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NYC Mayor Eric Adams Is Creating a Crypto Advisory Council]]></title>
        <id>266b251b-2d78-4859-822b-d03736b6ea13</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2025/05/20/nyc-mayor-eric-adams-creating-crypto-advisory-council"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T19:38:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA["We want to use technology of tomorrow to better serve New Yorkers today," said the mayor at a summit on Tuesday.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cheyenne Ligon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google finally launches NotebookLM mobile app at I/O: hands-on, first impressions]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008400</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/google-finally-launches-notebooklm-mobile-app-at-i-o-hands-on-first-impressions/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T19:29:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As NotebookLM matures, its emerging business-tier capabilities suggest growing alignment with the productivity and compliance...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carl Franzen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bancor files patent infringement lawsuit against Uniswap over DEX tech]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/bancor-files-patent-infringement-lawsuit-against-uniswap-over-dex-tech</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/bancor-files-patent-infringement-lawsuit-against-uniswap-over-dex-tech?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T19:20:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bancor, the creator of a smart contract-based automated market maker, is suing Uniswap for patent infringement, alleging the decentralized finance exchange has used its technology without permission and profited significantly from it.
According to the May 20 announcement of the lawsuit, Bancor designed the technology in 2016 and patented it in January 2017. The technology underpins the “constant product automated market maker,” which involves using mathematics to add or withdraw resources from a liquidity pool. The application subsequently led to two issued patents.
Bancor alleges that Uniswap used the invention to create its protocol, launched in November 2018. The two organizations are considered competitors in the sector of decentralized finance (DeFi).
“When an organization continuousl…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Christopher Tepedino</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Securitize’s Tokenized Credit Fund Set for Solana DeFi Debut as RWA Trend Expands]]></title>
        <id>dd6c31b9-61fb-4c38-a037-82c330292bb5</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2025/05/20/apollos-tokenized-credit-fund-set-for-solana-defi-debut-as-rwa-trend-expands"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T18:52:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kamino Finance and Steakhouse Financial are teaming up to bring Securitize's ACRED token to the fast-growing Solana DeFi ecosystem.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Krisztian Sandor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The NSA Selector]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/wenzellabs/the_NSA_selector</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/wenzellabs/the_NSA_selector"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T18:30:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Red Programming Language]]></title>
        <id>https://www.red-lang.org/p/about.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.red-lang.org/p/about.html"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T18:14:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin ready to ‘vaporize’ shorts once price discovery above $110K begins]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-ready-to-vaporize-shorts-once-price-discovery-above-110k-begins</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-ready-to-vaporize-shorts-once-price-discovery-above-110k-begins?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T18:05:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Key takeaways:

An end-of-month Bitcoin price close above $102,400 would set the highest monthly close ever, proving the bull market continues at a rapid pace.

Over $3 billion in Bitcoin short positions are vulnerable above $107,000, creating a “liquidation magnet” that could send BTC price to new highs.

Bitcoin (BTC) is 11 days from potentially setting its highest monthly candle close in history. After achieving a record weekly close of $106,407 on May 18, BTC could secure a new monthly high by closing above $102,400 this month.
Bitcoin 1-month chart. Source: Cointelegraph/TradingView
With respect to its current market trend, Bitcoin is inches away from a “price discovery” period, as noted by crypto trader Jelle.
Price discovery in this context refers to the process where buyers and sel…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Biraajmaan Tamuly</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gemma 3n preview: Mobile-first AI]]></title>
        <id>https://developers.googleblog.com/en/introducing-gemma-3n/</id>
        <link href="https://developers.googleblog.com/en/introducing-gemma-3n/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T18:03:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase CEO&#039;s journey from no &#039;political causes&#039; to hiring DOGE staff]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/brian-armstrong-coinbase-political-journey</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/brian-armstrong-coinbase-political-journey?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Five years ago, Brian Armstrong wanted employees of his cryptocurrency exchange to refrain from expressing political views at work. Now, the Coinbase CEO seems to be open to involvement with Republican figures, including members of US President Donald Trump’s inner circle.
In a May 13 X post, Armstrong said members of the Department of Government Efficiency (DOGE) team, spearheaded by Elon Musk, though not set up as an actual department, would be welcome to implement cost-cutting changes at Coinbase after leaving the US government. 
Armstrong offered to set up an accelerated onboarding process with the exchange, responding to an interview in which at least one DOGE staffer felt ostracized from Harvard University, where he had been enrolled.
“If you are looking for your next mission after s…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Turner Wright</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Veo 3 and Imagen 4, and a new tool for filmmaking called Flow]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.google/technology/ai/generative-media-models-io-2025/</id>
        <link href="https://blog.google/technology/ai/generative-media-models-io-2025/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T17:46:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google just leapfrogged every competitor with mind-blowing AI that can think deeper, shop smarter, and create videos with dialogue]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008346</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/google-just-leapfrogged-every-competitor-with-mind-blowing-ai-that-can-think-deeper-shop-smarter-and-create-videos-with-dialogue/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T17:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google unveiled major AI advancements at I/O 2025, including Gemini 2.5 with Deep Think, AI Mode in Search, Veo 3 for video with audio, and a $249 Ultra plan aimed at power users and enterprises.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Nuñez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google’s Jules aims to out-code Codex in battle for the AI developer stack]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008361</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/googles-jules-aims-to-out-code-codex-in-battle-for-the-ai-developer-stack/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T17:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google released Jules, its coding agent, into beta as autonomous coding agents are quickly gaining market share.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Emilia David</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Inside Google’s AI leap: Gemini 2.5 thinks deeper, speaks smarter and codes faster]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008366</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/inside-google-ai-leap-gemini-2-5-thinks-deeper-speaks-smarter-codes-faster/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T17:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google is moving closer to its goal of autonomous agentic AI with a series of enhancements to Gemini 2.5 Pro and Flash.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Taryn Plumb</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Validation Cloud Debuts Mavrik-1 AI Engine on Hedera to Democratize DeFi Data Analysis and Web3]]></title>
        <id>aa892120-4788-4a32-b30a-3103c605d77a</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/press-release/2025/05/20/emb-13-00-est-validation-cloud-debuts-mavrik-1-ai-engine-on-hedera-to-democratize-defi-data-analysis-and-web3"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T17:00:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mavrik-1 aims to lower the barrier to DeFi adoption by allowing users to access complex data without technical expertise.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Omkar Godbole</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Validation Cloud deploys Web3 AI engine on Hedera]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/validation-cloud-deploys-web3-ai-engine-hedera</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/validation-cloud-deploys-web3-ai-engine-hedera?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Artificial intelligence platform Validation Cloud has launched a new large language model on the Hedera network, potentially giving decentralized finance users the ability to reach blockchain data in a more accessible way.
The Mavrik-1 AI engine has been deployed on Hedera, with several other planned integrations expected during a public rollout later this year, Validation Cloud’s team told Cointelegraph. 
The AI engine is designed to allow users to interact with DeFi protocols and access blockchain data through natural language queries without needing technical expertise or knowledge. 
Mavrik-1 uses live onchain data trained for DeFi, stablecoins and other blockchain applications. 
Hedera DeFi metrics, including total value locked (TVL), decentralized exchange volume and stablecoin activi…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Sam Bourgi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SEC crypto task force to release first report &#039;in the next few months&#039;]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/sec-chair-paul-atkins-report-crypto-months</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/sec-chair-paul-atkins-report-crypto-months?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T16:49:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) Chair Paul Atkins appeared before lawmakers in one of his first hearings since taking the reins at the financial regulator, addressing questions about his plans for the cryptocurrency industry.
In a May 20 hearing discussing oversight of the SEC, Atkins reiterated his pledge to make regulating digital assets a “key priority” while chair. In response to questions from North Carolina Representative Chuck Edwards, the SEC chair did not directly answer how much of the regulator’s funds were used to support the crypto task force headed by Commissioner Hester Peirce, and said its findings were “still under development.”
“We should be having something here in the next few months with proposed steps forward,” said Atkins, referring to the task force’s fi…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Turner Wright</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Argentina&#039;s Milei shuts down task force investigating LIBRA scandal]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/javier-milei-shuts-down-task-force-investigating-libra-scandal</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/javier-milei-shuts-down-task-force-investigating-libra-scandal?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T16:19:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Argentine President Javier Milei has dissolved a task force established to investigate the fallout from LIBRA, the scandalous cryptocurrency project the head of state promoted on his social media channel before it crashed to zero. 
The Investigative Task Force (ITU) was dissolved via a May 19 decree signed by Milei and Justice Minister Mariano Cúneo Libarona, government documents revealed. 
“The Research Task Unit is dissolved” after completing its mandate, the translated version of the decree read.
The task force is being dissolved despite pressure from opposition groups, which are seeking to activate an investigative commission as soon as May 20, local media outlet Clarin reported. 
A screenshot of Milei’s tweet endorsing LIBRA. Source: TRM Labs
Government officials established the UTI o…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Sam Bourgi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blazing-fast Solana data via gRPC: access the freshest Solana data from Shredstream leaders]]></title>
        <id>68273f14bf73460001094b35</id>
        <link href="https://blog.quicknode.com/yellowstone-grpc/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T15:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Access the fastest Solana data with the Yellowstone Geyser gRPC self-serve add-on or with the premium hybrid dedicated gRPC node.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>QuickNode</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn LangGraph and Build Conversational AI with Python]]></title>
        <id>682ca2c574938e5428551845</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-langgraph-and-build-conversational-ai-with-python/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T15:41:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you're building conversational AI and tired of messy logic or hard-to-scale workflows, LangGraph makes it easier. It uses graphs to manage dialogue flow, so your bots stay organized even as they get more complex. Great for anything from support ag...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Show HN: A Tiling Window Manager for Windows, Written in Janet]]></title>
        <id>https://agent-kilo.github.io/jwno/</id>
        <link href="https://agent-kilo.github.io/jwno/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T15:08:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Show HN: 90s.dev – Game maker that runs on the web]]></title>
        <id>https://90s.dev/blog/finally-releasing-90s-dev.html</id>
        <link href="https://90s.dev/blog/finally-releasing-90s-dev.html"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T14:58:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Deep Learning Is Applied Topology]]></title>
        <id>https://theahura.substack.com/p/deep-learning-is-applied-topology</id>
        <link href="https://theahura.substack.com/p/deep-learning-is-applied-topology"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T13:54:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Clojuring the web application stack: Meditation One]]></title>
        <id>https://www.evalapply.org/posts/clojure-web-app-from-scratch/index.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.evalapply.org/posts/clojure-web-app-from-scratch/index.html"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T13:15:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Download: introducing the AI energy package]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1117051</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/05/20/1117051/the-download-introducing-the-ai-energy-package/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T12:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is today’s edition of The Download, our weekday newsletter that provides a daily dose of what’s going on in the world of technology. We did the math on AI’s energy footprint. Here’s the story you haven’t heard. It’s well documented that AI is a power-hungry technology. But there has been far less reporting on the extent…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rhiannon Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why does the U.S. always run a trade deficit?]]></title>
        <id>https://libertystreeteconomics.newyorkfed.org/2025/05/why-does-the-u-s-always-run-a-trade-deficit/</id>
        <link href="https://libertystreeteconomics.newyorkfed.org/2025/05/why-does-the-u-s-always-run-a-trade-deficit/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T11:42:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AI's energy footprint]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/05/20/1116327/ai-energy-usage-climate-footprint-big-tech/</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/05/20/1116327/ai-energy-usage-climate-footprint-big-tech/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T10:07:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AI could keep us dependent on natural gas for decades to come]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1116272</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/05/20/1116272/ai-natural-gas-data-centers-energy-power-plants/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The thousands of sprawling acres in rural northeast Louisiana had gone unwanted for nearly two decades. Louisiana authorities bought the land in Richland Parish in 2006 to promote economic development in one of the poorest regions in the state. For years, they marketed the former agricultural fields as the Franklin Farm mega site, first to…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Rotman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AI’s energy impact is still small—but how we handle it is huge]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1116274</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/05/20/1116274/opinion-ai-energy-use-data-centers-electricity/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With seemingly no limit to the demand for artificial intelligence, everyone in the energy, AI, and climate fields is justifiably worried. Will there be enough clean electricity to power AI and enough water to cool the data centers that support this technology? These are important questions with serious implications for communities, the economy, and the…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Costa Samaras, Emma Strubell, Ramayya Krishnan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The data center boom in the desert]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1116287</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/05/20/1116287/ai-data-centers-nevada-water-reno-computing-environmental-impact/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the high desert east of Reno, Nevada, construction crews are flattening the golden foothills of the Virginia Range, laying the foundations of a data center city. Google, Tract, Switch, EdgeCore, Novva, Vantage, and PowerHouse are all operating, building, or expanding huge facilities within the Tahoe Reno Industrial Center, a business park bigger than the…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>James Temple</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[We did the math on AI’s energy footprint. Here’s the story you haven’t heard.]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1116327</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/05/20/1116327/ai-energy-usage-climate-footprint-big-tech/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The emissions from individual AI text, image, and video queries seem small—until you add up what the industry isn’t tracking and consider where it’s heading next.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>James O'Donnell, Casey Crownhart</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Everything you need to know about estimating AI’s energy and emissions burden]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1116331</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/05/20/1116331/ai-energy-demand-methodology/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When we set out to write a story on the best available estimates for AI’s energy and emissions burden, we knew there would be caveats and uncertainties to these numbers. But, we quickly discovered, the caveats are the story too.  This story is a part of MIT Technology Review’s series “Power Hungry: AI and our…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>James O'Donnell, Casey Crownhart</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Four reasons to be optimistic about AI’s energy usage]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1116337</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/05/20/1116337/ai-energy-use-optimism/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The day after his inauguration in January, President Donald Trump announced Stargate, a $500 billion initiative to build out AI infrastructure, backed by some of the biggest companies in tech. Stargate aims to accelerate the construction of massive data centers and electricity networks across the US to ensure it keeps its edge over China. This…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Will Douglas Heaven</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Can nuclear power really fuel the rise of AI?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1116339</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/05/20/1116339/ai-nuclear-power-energy-reactors/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the AI arms race, all the major players say they want to go nuclear.   Over the past year, the likes of Meta, Amazon, Microsoft, and Google have sent out a flurry of announcements related to nuclear energy. Some are about agreements to purchase power from existing plants, while others are about investments looking to…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Casey Crownhart</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft just launched an AI that discovered a new chemical in 200 hours instead of years]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008310</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/microsoft-just-launched-an-ai-that-discovered-a-new-chemical-in-200-hours-instead-of-years/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T18:34:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft launches Discovery platform that uses agentic AI to compress years of scientific research into days, transforming R&D across pharmaceuticals, materials science, and semiconductor industries.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Nuñez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Is your AI app pissing off users or going off-script? Raindrop emerges with AI-native observability platform to monitor performance]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008299</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/is-your-ai-app-pissing-off-users-or-going-off-script-raindrop-emerges-with-ai-native-observability-platform-to-monitor-performance/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T18:09:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With its rebrand and product expansion, Raindrop is betting that the next generation of software observability will be AI-first by design.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carl Franzen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Writing into Uninitialized Buffers in Rust]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.sunfishcode.online/writingintouninitializedbuffersinrust/</id>
        <link href="https://blog.sunfishcode.online/writingintouninitializedbuffersinrust/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T17:56:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft just taught its AI agents to talk to each other—and it could transform how we work]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008254</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/microsoft-just-taught-its-ai-agents-to-talk-to-each-other-and-it-could-transform-how-we-work/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T16:01:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft unveils multi-agent systems, WhatsApp integration, and Python-powered analytics for Copilot Studio at Build 2025, transforming how enterprises build and deploy AI solutions.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Nuñez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Microsoft Fabric has already been adopted by 70% of the Fortune 500 — and what’s next]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3007980</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/70-of-the-fortune-500-already-use-microsoft-fabric-and-its-now-getting-even-more-features-including-cosmosdb-support/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft integrates CosmosDB into Fabric, open sources DiskANN vector search, and unifies its data platforms to eliminate integration complexity that has slowed enterprise AI adoption.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sean Michael Kerner</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub Copilot evolves into autonomous agent with asynchronous code testing]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008231</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/github-copilot-evolves-into-autonomous-agent-with-asynchronous-code-testing/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub adds agentic capabilities to its Copilot coding assistant, competing with other more asynchronous coding platforms.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Emilia David</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft announces over 50 AI tools to build the ‘agentic web’ at Build 2025]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008229</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/microsoft-announces-over-50-ai-tools-to-build-the-agentic-web-at-build-2025/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T15:59:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft reveals its ambitious AI agent strategy, showcasing how multi-agent systems with persistent memory will transform enterprise workflows and accelerate development timelines.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Nuñez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Reddit, Webflow, and Superhuman are already customers—now GrowthX has $12M to grow]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008276</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/reddit-webflow-and-superhuman-are-already-customers-now-growthx-has-12m-to-grow/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[GrowthX secures $12M in funding for its "service-as-software" platform that combines AI with human expertise to boost content marketing results by up to 300%.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Nuñez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Cybercriminals Crack Your Passwords (And How to Stay One Step Ahead)]]></title>
        <id>682b3930e99a22ce9f9199c8</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-cybercriminals-crack-your-passwords-and-how-to-stay-one-step-ahead/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T13:59:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Passwords are the keys to your digital life  –  email, bank accounts, social media, and even your workplace systems. Unfortunately, they’re also one of the weakest links in cybersecurity.  Every year, billions of credentials are stolen and sold on th...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Manish Shivanandhan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Quantum Machines launches Qualibrate open source framework to speed quantum computer calibration]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008032</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/games/quantum-machines-launches-qualibrate-open-source-framework-to-speed-quantum-computer-calibration/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Quantum Machines, a provider of advanced hybrid quantum-classical control solutions, announced today the release of Qualibrate.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dean Takahashi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Samsung boosts OLED TV gaming with Nvidia G-Sync compatibility]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008019</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/games/samsung-boosts-oled-tv-gaming-with-nvidia-g-sync-compatibility/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Samsung said its 2025 OLED TV lineup will feature Nvidia G-Sync compatibility, delivering smooth gameplay, low latency, and more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dean Takahashi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Salesforce just unveiled AI ‘digital teammates’ in Slack — and they’re coming for Microsoft Copilot]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008273</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/salesforce-just-unveiled-ai-digital-teammates-in-slack-and-theyre-coming-for-microsoft-copilot/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Salesforce launches Agentforce in Slack, transforming workplace productivity with specialized AI agents that operate as digital teammates, replacing one-size-fits-all AI assistants with purpose-built solutions.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Nuñez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Foxconn builds AI factory in partnership with Taiwan and Nvidia]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008261</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/games/foxconn-builds-ai-factory-in-partnership-with-taiwan-and-nvidia/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T07:14:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nvidia and Foxconn announced they are working with the Taiwan government to build an AI factory supercomputer.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dean Takahashi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nvidia launches AI-first DGX Personal Computing Systems]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008256</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/games/nvidia-launches-ai-first-dgx-personal-computing-systems/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T07:06:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nvidia announced that Taiwan’s leading system manufacturers are set to build Nvidia DGX Spark and DGX Station systems.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dean Takahashi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nvidia-powered supercomputer to enable quantum leap for Taiwan’s research]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008257</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/games/nvidia-powered-supercomputer-to-enable-quantum-leap-for-taiwans-research/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T06:58:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nvidia is powering a supercomputer at Taiwan’s National Center for High-Performance Computing that’s set to deliver over eight times more AI performance than before.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dean Takahashi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nvidia powers world’s largest quantum research supercomputer]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008248</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/games/nvidia-powers-worlds-largest-quantum-research-supercomputer/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T06:48:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nvidia announced the opening of the Global Research and Development Center for Business by Quantum-AI Technology.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dean Takahashi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nvidia provides Omniverse Blueprint for AI factory digital twins]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008243</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/games/nvidia-provides-omniverse-blueprint-for-ai-factory-digital-twins/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T06:34:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nvidia today announced a significant expansion of the Nvidia Omniverse Blueprint for AI factory digital twins, now available as a preview.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dean Takahashi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nvidia charges ahead with humanoid robotics aided by the cloud]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008144</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/games/nvidia-charges-ahead-with-humanoid-robotics-aided-by-the-cloud/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T06:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nvidia said it is racing ahead with humanoid robotics technology, providing more Blackwell systems to accelerate humanoid robot development.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dean Takahashi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What makes a good engineer also makes a good engineering organization (2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://moxie.org/2024/09/23/a-good-engineer.html</id>
        <link href="https://moxie.org/2024/09/23/a-good-engineer.html"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T05:26:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The lack of a good command line way to sort IPv6 addresses]]></title>
        <id>https://utcc.utoronto.ca/~cks/space/blog/unix/SortingIPv6Addresses</id>
        <link href="https://utcc.utoronto.ca/~cks/space/blog/unix/SortingIPv6Addresses"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T04:04:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Using unwrap() in Rust is Okay (2022)]]></title>
        <id>https://burntsushi.net/unwrap/</id>
        <link href="https://burntsushi.net/unwrap/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-18T22:41:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[From dot-com to dot-AI: How we can learn from the last tech transformation (and avoid making the same mistakes)]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3007969</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/from-dot-com-to-dot-ai-how-we-can-learn-from-the-last-tech-transformation-and-avoid-making-the-same-mistakes/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-18T19:05:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The AI winners won’t be the ones slapping “AI” on a landing page — they’ll be creating products enterprises can't live without.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kailiang Fu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Building my own solar power system]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/@joe_5312/pg-e-sucks-or-how-i-learned-to-stop-worrying-and-love-building-my-own-solar-system-acf0c9f03f3b</id>
        <link href="https://medium.com/@joe_5312/pg-e-sucks-or-how-i-learned-to-stop-worrying-and-love-building-my-own-solar-system-acf0c9f03f3b"/>
        <updated>2025-05-18T18:07:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Someone got an LLM running on a Commodore 64 from 1982, and it runs as well]]></title>
        <id>https://www.xda-developers.com/llm-running-commodore-64/</id>
        <link href="https://www.xda-developers.com/llm-running-commodore-64/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-18T17:47:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Adopting agentic AI? Build AI fluency, redesign workflows, don’t neglect supervision]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3007933</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/adopting-agentic-ai-build-ai-fluency-redesign-workflows-dont-neglect-supervision/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-17T19:05:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How can organizations decide how to use human-in-the-loop mechanisms and collaborative frameworks with AI agents?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Imran Aftab, 10Pearls</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Withnail and I (2001)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.criterion.com/current/posts/122-withnail-and-i</id>
        <link href="https://www.criterion.com/current/posts/122-withnail-and-i"/>
        <updated>2025-05-17T16:59:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[My favourite fonts to use with LaTeX (2022)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lfe.pt/latex/fonts/typography/2022/11/21/latex-fonts-part1.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.lfe.pt/latex/fonts/typography/2022/11/21/latex-fonts-part1.html"/>
        <updated>2025-05-17T02:53:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google’s AlphaEvolve: The AI agent that reclaimed 0.7% of Google’s compute – and how to copy it]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3007997</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/googles-alphaevolve-the-ai-agent-that-reclaimed-0-7-of-googles-compute-and-how-to-copy-it/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-17T00:31:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google's AlphaEvolve is the epitome of a best-practice AI agent orchestration. It offers a lesson in production-grade agent engineering. Discover its architecture & essential takeaways for your enterprise AI strategy.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matt Marshall</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Shrink exploit windows, slash MTTP: Why ring deployment is now a must for enterprise defense]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3007233</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/security/slash-mttp-block-exploits-ring-deployment-now-essential/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-16T20:48:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ring deployment slashes MTTP and legacy CVE risk. Learn how Ivanti and Southstar Bank are modernizing patch strategy with real-time intel.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Louis Columbus</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Extend Power Apps with Reusable Components]]></title>
        <id>682779afad5694b25984f6b1</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/powerapps-component-crash-course/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-16T17:45:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you have experience in traditional software development, low-code tools may feel a bit sparse at first. But to many people’s surprise, traditional techniques often translate quite well to low-code development. Not always one-for-one – but usually ...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brandon Wozniewicz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Write Math Equations in Google Docs]]></title>
        <id>68275cf15ed8a1db0cf8769b</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/write-math-equations-in-google-docs/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-16T15:42:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Math equations are a critical part of academic papers, research reports, and technical documentation. While LaTeX is widely used for professional typesetting, Google Docs offers a robust set of features for inserting and formatting math equations and...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Vikram Aruchamy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OpenAI launches research preview of Codex AI software engineering agent for developers — with parallel tasking]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3007915</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/programming-development/openai-launches-research-preview-of-codex-ai-software-engineering-agent-for-developers-with-parallel-tasking/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-16T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Starting today it will be available as a research preview for ChatGPT Pro, Enterprise, and Team users, with support later for Plus and Edu.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carl Franzen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Acer unveils AI-powered wearables at Computex 2025]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3007872</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/games/acer-unveils-ai-powered-wearables-at-computex-2025/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-16T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Acer Gadget, a subsidiary of Acer, unveiled AI-powered wearables at the Computex 2025 trade show in Taiwan.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dean Takahashi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to make Developer Friends When You Don't Live in Silicon Valley, with Iraqi Engineer Code;Life [Podcast #172]]]></title>
        <id>68271ae2c90fa4a071c44a2b</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-make-developer-friends-when-you-dont-live-in-silicon-valley-with-iraqi-engineer-codelife-podcast-172/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-16T11:00:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On this week's episode of the podcast, freeCodeCamp founder Quincy Larson interviews software engineer and live coding streamer Code;Life.   For those of you watching the video version of this interview, she lives in Iraq and she uses a 3D avatar to ...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elon Musk’s xAI tries to explain Grok’s South African race relations freakout the other day]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3007876</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/elon-musks-xai-tries-to-explain-groks-south-african-race-relations-freakout-the-other-day/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-16T02:47:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With its prompts now public and a team of human babysitters on call, Grok is supposedly back on script. But the incident underscores...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carl Franzen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn A1 Level Spanish]]></title>
        <id>68269a8eb0cc91a6c87a682d</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-a1-level-spanish/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-16T01:53:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learning a new language can open doors to new cultures, connections, and opportunities, and Spanish is one of the most widely spoken languages in the world. Whether you're dreaming of traveling to Spanish-speaking countries, connecting with Spanish-s...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Software engineering-native AI models have arrived: What Windsurf’s SWE-1 means for technical decision-makers]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3007851</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/software-engineering-native-ai-models-have-arrived-what-windsurfs-swe-1-means-for-technical-decision-makers/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-16T00:30:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Windsurf's new SWE-1 AI models tackle the complete software engineering workflow, potentially reducing development cycles and technical debt.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sean Michael Kerner</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is Sui: A Comprehensive Guide to Web3 Scalability]]></title>
        <id>6823533984101f00013a5ca4</id>
        <link href="https://blog.quicknode.com/what-is-sui-a-comprehensive-guide-to-web3-scalability/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-15T23:34:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Explore how Sui Network achieves 300,000 TPS through parallel processing, and its applications in gaming, DeFi, and supply chain management.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>QuickNode</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AI Meets Blockchain: Transforming Technology for the Next Era]]></title>
        <id>682354c584101f00013a5cb9</id>
        <link href="https://blog.quicknode.com/ai-and-blockchain-transforming-technology-together/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-15T23:34:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discover how AI and blockchain integration enhances security, efficiency, and innovation in healthcare, supply chains, and financial services.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>QuickNode</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Adventure Layer: AI Native Onchain Games, Unleashed]]></title>
        <id>6824c55abf73460001094973</id>
        <link href="https://blog.quicknode.com/adventure-layer-launches-on-quicknode-raas/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-15T12:04:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Adventure Layer launches layer-2 chain leveraging QuickNode's Rollup-as-a-Service (RaaS) product.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>QuickNode</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How DNS Works: A Guide to Understanding the Internet's Address Book]]></title>
        <id>6824f1ac04a60b4a58654ddc</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-dns-works-the-internets-address-book/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-14T19:40:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Domain Name System (DNS) translates domain names (like example.com) into IP addresses (like 192.0.2.1) so we can easily access websites. In this guide, you’ll learn how DNS resolution starts, its step-by-step process, how caching works, and the r...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dhruv Prajapati</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Load Balancing with Azure Application Gateway and Azure Load Balancer – When to Use Each One]]></title>
        <id>6824f10a7d203c180e5ea4b2</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/load-balancing-with-azure-application-gateway-and-azure-load-balancer/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-14T19:37:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You’ve probably heard someone mention load balancing when talking about cloud apps. Maybe even names like Azure Load Balancer, Azure Application Gateway, or something about Virtual Machines and Scale Sets. 😵‍💫 It all sounds important...but also a l...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Prince Onukwili</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build Slim and Fast Docker Images with Multi-Stage Builds]]></title>
        <id>6824b1638a2b26e9d2d0fe86</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-slim-fast-docker-images-with-multi-stage-builds/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-14T15:06:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Apps don’t stay simple forever. More features mean more dependencies, slower builds, and heavier Docker images. That’s where things start to hurt. Docker helps, but without the right setup, your builds can quickly get bloated. Multi-stage builds make...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniel Adeboye</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn Vite for a Better Web Development Workflow]]></title>
        <id>6824ae178a2b26e9d2d0fe4c</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-vite-for-a-better-web-development-workflow/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-14T14:52:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Speed and simplicity are at the heart of modern web development. As applications grow more complex and the demand for rapid iteration increases, developers are constantly searching for tools that minimize friction and maximize productivity. Tradition...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[QuickLee V2: An Improved Transparent Look into RPC Provider Latency]]></title>
        <id>680fc8e1f8ae810001969b47</id>
        <link href="https://blog.quicknode.com/quicklee-v2/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-14T13:57:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[View public and real-time dashboards to better understand latency and speed when evaluating RPC providers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>QuickNode</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Breathe lands $21M Series B to predict battery performance]]></title>
        <id>https://techcrunch.com/?p=3003769</id>
        <link href="https://techcrunch.com/2025/05/07/breathe-lands-21m-series-b-to-predict-battery-performance/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-07T12:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Breathe has developed a suite of tools that it says helps automakers and others get the most out of their batteries.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tim De Chant</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>