<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2025-04-30T17:12:10.584Z</id>
    <title>AngJianming RSS Feed</title>
    <updated>2025-04-30T17:12:10.584Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Local cosmetics sector can be launchpad to position Malaysia as innovation-led economy: Sirim chief tech officer]]></title>
        <id>f3d9620891e0882d2a66ea582395ca3a</id>
        <link href="https://thesun.my/business-news/local-cosmetics-sector-can-be-launchpad-to-position-malaysia-as-innovation-led-economy-sirim-chief-tech-officer-AH14020110"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T17:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SHAH ALAM: The Malaysian cosmetics sector can serve as a launchpad to position the nation as an innovation-led economy, said Sirim Bhd chief technolog...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hayatun Razak</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Grayscale launches Bitcoin adopters exchange-traded fund]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/grayscale-launches-grayscale-bitcoin-adopters-etf</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/grayscale-launches-grayscale-bitcoin-adopters-etf?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T17:08:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Asset manager Grayscale launched the Grayscale Bitcoin Adopters exchange-traded fund (ETF), an investment vehicle that tracks companies employing a Bitcoin (BTC) treasury, or holding strategy.
According to the April 30 announcement, the ETF will provide exposure to companies across seven business sectors, including Bitcoin mining firms, automotive companies, and energy.
Some of the most notable firms in the ETF include Michael Saylor's Strategy, mining company MARA, automotive manufacturer Tesla, BTC treasury company Metaplanet, and aerospace energy firm KULR Technology Group.
Grayscale's Bitcoin Adopters ETF highlights the growing trend of Bitcoin acquisition companies using the scarce digital asset to drive up shareholder prices and to protect their corporate financial reserves against t…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Vince Quill</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin drops under $93K after US GDP data shows shrinking economy, raising recession alarms]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-drops-under-93-k-after-us-gdp-data-shows-shrinking-economy-raising-recession-alarm</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-drops-under-93-k-after-us-gdp-data-shows-shrinking-economy-raising-recession-alarm?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T17:01:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Key points: 

US GDP shrank in Q1, raising recession alarms while also prompting calls for Fed rate cuts.

Bitcoin dropped to $92,910 as GDP figures were released, but sustained buy-side demand could provide support. 

Today’s crypto derisking is likely transitory; market fundamentals remain strong.

Bitcoin (BTC) price took an abrupt tumble as data showed the US gross domestic product (GDP) retracting by 0.3% in Q1, raising alarms among analysts anticipating a recession. Following the news, BTC price dropped to an intra-day low of $92,910, while the DOW and S&P 500 fell by 1% and 1.3% respectively. 
While the GDP figures are shocking at face value, CNBC pointed out that the drop was primarily due to “a surge in imports ahead of President Donald Trump’s tariffs.” Imports are subtracted fro…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Big Smokey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Archil (YC F24) Is Hiring a Distributed Systems Engineer (In-Person, SF)]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=43848007</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=43848007"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T17:01:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bugs Fuel Open-Source Community]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/fzambia/bugs-fuel-open-source-community-1cp6</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/fzambia/bugs-fuel-open-source-community-1cp6"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T16:46:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Note: this post is kind of a satire. Kind of.
During the last 10 years I was driving the development of Centrifugo, an open-source real-time messaging server. I've spent years building, maintaining, and obsessing over this project — and in that time, a thought has kept creeping into my brain:
What if... having more bugs actually leads to a better community?
Here’s where it gets real. Let me point to a recent story from the folks behind NATS, a popular open-source messaging system. They announced plans to move to the BUSL license, and in doing so, they shared this quote that really stuck with me:
“Paradoxically, improved stability, extensive documentation, and exemplary reference architectures have led some organizations to discontinue financial support, even when relying heavily on the sof…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alexander Emelin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[I've been planning to do a platform for researchers. I would love to get feedback and recommendation from the dev community here.]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/naratech/ive-been-planning-to-do-a-platform-for-researchers-i-would-love-to-get-feedback-and-6ca</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/naratech/ive-been-planning-to-do-a-platform-for-researchers-i-would-love-to-get-feedback-and-6ca"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T16:41:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dashboard for Researchers & Geneticists: Functional Requirements [System Design]
Sanjeewa Narayana ・ Apr 20
#geneticists
        #devops
        #systemdesign
        #cloudcomputing]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sanjeewa Narayana</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[10 Lightweight API Gateways for Your Next Project]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/nordicapis/10-lightweight-api-gateways-for-your-next-project-1ha3</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/nordicapis/10-lightweight-api-gateways-for-your-next-project-1ha3"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T16:40:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A vendor-neutral take on the leading API gateways out there for developers in 2025.
If you're building an API, you'll need an API gateway. It's just considered best practice nowadays. API gateways ensure your APIs aren't abused, helping with rate limiting, traffic routing, authentication, authorization, and more. They're also helpful for observability and compliance, too. Whether you're exposing public APIs or managing internal microservices, an API gateway helps protect, scale, and productize your services.
Below, we'll quickly review some of the lightweight, developer-friendly API gateways on the market, including both open-source and commercial options. These are all either inherently lightweight or flexible enough without heavy enterprise overhead. We'll highlight some of the pros, con…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nordic APIs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[𝗨𝗻𝗹𝗼𝗰𝗸𝗶𝗻𝗴 𝗠𝗼𝗱𝗲𝗿𝗻 𝗦𝗲𝗰𝘂𝗿𝗶𝘁𝘆: 𝗪𝗵𝘆 𝗢𝗔𝘂𝘁𝗵 𝗠𝗮𝘁𝘁𝗲𝗿𝘀 𝗶𝗻 𝗧𝗼𝗱𝗮𝘆’𝘀 𝗝𝗮𝘃𝗮 & 𝗦𝗽𝗿𝗶𝗻𝗴 𝗕𝗼𝗼𝘁 𝗔𝗽𝗽𝗹𝗶𝗰𝗮𝘁𝗶𝗼𝗻𝘀]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/thiago_souza_1510/--17fm</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/thiago_souza_1510/--17fm"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T16:39:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the ever-evolving world of backend development, security is no longer just a checkbox-it’s a critical pillar of every successful application. As Java and Spring Boot continue to power enterprise systems, the adoption of OAuth has become essential for protecting APIs and user data in a scalable, flexible way.
OAuth isn’t just another security protocol. It’s a robust framework that empowers secure authorization, enabling applications to access resources without exposing user credentials. This is especially important as we move toward microservices architectures and cloud-native environments, where traditional security models often fall short.
With Spring Boot’s seamless integration of OAuth, developers can implement secure authentication and authorization flows with minimal friction. This not only enhances user experience but also ensures compliance with modern security standards.
But here’s the real question: How are you leveraging OAuth in your Java projects? Are you facing challenges with token management, user consent, or integrating with third-party providers? Or have you discovered best practices that make your security architecture shine?
Let’s spark a conversation! Share your experiences, challenges, and insights about implementing OAuth with Java and Spring Boot. Your input could help others navigate the complex world of application security.
What’s been your biggest win-or challenge-with OAuth in your projects? Let’s discuss!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Thiago Souza</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS -Elastic Network Interfaces (ENI)]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/skillboosttrainer/aws-elastic-network-interfaces-eni-10kh</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/skillboosttrainer/aws-elastic-network-interfaces-eni-10kh"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T16:36:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Elastic Network Interfaces (ENIs) are logical networking components within a Virtual Private Cloud (VPC) in AWS. They function as virtual network cards, providing network connectivity for EC2 instances and other AWS services.
Each ENI must have a primary private IPv4 address from the VPC’s IPv4 address range.
ENIs can have one or more secondary private IPv4 addresses. This is useful for applications requiring multiple IP addresses on a single instance.
You can associate one or more Elastic IP addresses (IPv4) with a primary or secondary private IP address on the ENI.
ENIs can also have IPv6 addresses if your VPC supports IPv6.
Each ENI has a unique MAC address, which is crucial for network communication.
ENIs can have one or more security groups attached. Security groups act as virtual…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SkillBoostTrainer</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The best part is how actionable this is. It’s not just theory, it’s what actually works.]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/alexbenshoof/the-best-part-is-how-actionable-this-is-its-not-just-theory-its-what-actually-works-2l8p</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/alexbenshoof/the-best-part-is-how-actionable-this-is-its-not-just-theory-its-what-actually-works-2l8p"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T16:32:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Hard Truth About Why Digital Campaigns Underperform
Anthony James ・ Apr 30
#marketing
        #startup
        #b2b
        #growth]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alessandra Benshoof</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Love how this focuses on value and timing instead of pressure tactics. More people need to hear this.]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/alexbenshoof/love-how-this-focuses-on-value-and-timing-instead-of-pressure-tactics-more-people-need-to-hear-1g0</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/alexbenshoof/love-how-this-focuses-on-value-and-timing-instead-of-pressure-tactics-more-people-need-to-hear-1g0"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T16:31:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What Sales Teams Can Teach Product Builders About Process (From Ashkan Rajaee’s Perspective)
Matt Johnson ・ Apr 22
#ashkanrajaee
        #closethedeal
        #salestips
        #strategicthinking]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alessandra Benshoof</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[💻 Mastering Java OOP: Understanding Classes, Objects, and the Four Pillars]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/saif_uddin/mastering-java-oop-understanding-classes-objects-and-the-four-pillars-3706</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/saif_uddin/mastering-java-oop-understanding-classes-objects-and-the-four-pillars-3706"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T16:30:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[🔍 Description:
This post introduces Java’s Object-Oriented Programming model by breaking down the four fundamental principles — Encapsulation, Inheritance, Polymorphism, and Abstraction — with real-world analogies and simple code examples. It also walks through how classes and objects work in Java, making it easy for readers to apply the concepts in their own projects.
🔐 Encapsulation
Encapsulation is the concept of hiding internal data and only exposing what’s necessary through methods. It protects an object's state and promotes modular code.
🧬 Inheritance
Inheritance allows a class (subclass) to acquire properties and behaviors from another class (superclass), promoting code reuse and hierarchy.
🌀 Polymorphism
Polymorphism lets one interface or method behave differently based on the object that calls it. It supports method overloading and overriding.
🧩 Abstraction
Abstraction is about hiding complex implementation details and showing only the essential features of an object. Achieved through abstract classes and interfaces.
See More...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Saif Uddin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Unlocking the Power of Async Programming in FastAPI (and Flask!)]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/eod-stock-api/unlocking-the-power-of-async-programming-in-fastapi-and-flask-4o0p</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/eod-stock-api/unlocking-the-power-of-async-programming-in-fastapi-and-flask-4o0p"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T16:29:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Unlocking the Power of Async Programming


As Python developers, we often face the challenge of handling concurrent requests efficiently. FastAPI, a modern web framework built on Python's async capabilities, is a great solution. It allows us to handle large numbers of requests simultaneously without blocking, improving performance and responsiveness.

In this article, we’ll explore how to leverage async programming, covering key concepts and practical tips that will help you make the most of this powerful feature. We’ll also see how async programming is utilized in real-world projects like my job listing platform, JobFinders.site, which uses Flask with async support.
Async programming allows us to run tasks concurrently rather than sequentially, making it possible to handle multiple tasks …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>mobius-crypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[B2B vs B2C Gaming License Types: Choosing the Right Framework for Your iGaming Business]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/lisa72/b2b-vs-b2c-gaming-license-types-choosing-the-right-framework-for-your-igaming-business-2ejn</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/lisa72/b2b-vs-b2c-gaming-license-types-choosing-the-right-framework-for-your-igaming-business-2ejn"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T16:25:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The iGaming industry operates on a foundation of regulatory compliance where choosing between B2B (Business-to-Business) and B2C (Business-to-Consumer) gaming licenses represents a critical strategic decision. These distinct licensing frameworks determine operational capabilities, compliance requirements, cost structures, and market access. Understanding the nuanced differences between these license types is essential for operators and software providers seeking to establish or expand their presence in regulated markets worldwide.

The selection between these license types significantly impacts a company's operational scope, regulatory burden, and capital requirements. Many successful iGaming businesses strategically leverage both license types to maximize market opportunities while optimi…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lisa Ash</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[5 Essential Java Profiling Tools for Diagnosing Performance Bottlenecks]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/aaravjoshi/5-essential-java-profiling-tools-for-diagnosing-performance-bottlenecks-1hkj</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/aaravjoshi/5-essential-java-profiling-tools-for-diagnosing-performance-bottlenecks-1hkj"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T16:24:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As a best-selling author, I invite you to explore my books on Amazon. Don't forget to follow me on Medium and show your support. Thank you! Your support means the world! 
Performance optimization remains a critical aspect of Java application development. As applications grow in complexity, identifying bottlenecks becomes increasingly challenging. In this article, I'll explore five powerful profiling tools that can help diagnose performance issues in Java applications.
Java performance profiling is essential for creating responsive and efficient applications. Through years of optimizing Java systems, I've found that the right profiling tools can drastically reduce the time spent hunting for performance issues. Let's examine five tools that have proven invaluable in my work.
JProfiler stands…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Aarav Joshi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build a Mobile App for Apartment Cleaning with React Native"]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/giovany_osorio_707759bc6b/how-to-build-a-mobile-app-for-apartment-cleaning-with-react-native-4oae</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/giovany_osorio_707759bc6b/how-to-build-a-mobile-app-for-apartment-cleaning-with-react-native-4oae"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T16:23:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Build a Mobile App for Apartment Cleaning with React Native
Mobile apps are transforming the way service industries operate—and the cleaning sector is no exception. In this guide, we’ll show you how to develop a cross-platform mobile app for apartment cleaning services using React Native. We'll include real code examples, a clean structure for SEO, and smart keyword placement to avoid being flagged for spam.
Why React Native?
React Native allows you to build mobile apps for both iOS and Android using a single JavaScript codebase. It’s perfect for startups and businesses looking to save time and money without compromising user experience.
Benefits:
One codebase for multiple platforms
Strong community and third-party libraries
Easy integration with backend services
Native-like performance
Ap…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Giovany Osorio</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DeepSeek-Prover-V2]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/deepseek-ai/DeepSeek-Prover-V2</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/deepseek-ai/DeepSeek-Prover-V2"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T16:23:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Young people aren't as happy as they used to be [Global Flourishing Study]]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nytimes.com/2025/04/30/well/mind/happiness-flourishing-young-adult-study.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.nytimes.com/2025/04/30/well/mind/happiness-flourishing-young-adult-study.html"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T16:19:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AI-Powered Court System Is Coming to Crypto With GenLayer]]></title>
        <id>df94e6f3-f82a-4505-8d89-de84c57517e8</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/tech/2025/04/30/ai-powered-court-system-is-coming-to-crypto-with-genlayer"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T16:04:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[YeagerAI is building a protocol that uses AI models as judges, with the goal of providing reliable, neutral, third-party arbitration in record time.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tom Carreras</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Show HN: Create your own finetuned AI model using Google Sheets]]></title>
        <id>https://promptrepo.com/finetune/</id>
        <link href="https://promptrepo.com/finetune/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T15:53:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Show HN: ART – a new open-source RL framework for training agents]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/OpenPipe/ART</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/OpenPipe/ART"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T15:35:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Alpha-Generating Digital Asset Strategies Will Reshape Alternative Investing]]></title>
        <id>17ae8139-dd24-4790-8dcd-6afeb437e729</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/coindesk-indices/2025/04/30/how-alpha-generating-digital-asset-strategies-will-reshape-alternative-investing"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T15:30:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Now that returns that simply mirror the broader crypto market are easily attainable, investors are looking for more ways to potentially exceed the market, says Lionsoul Global’s Gregory Mall.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gregory Mall</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AI Crypto Agents Are Ushering in a New Era of ‘DeFAI’]]></title>
        <id>f5a3afe9-ab7b-4133-8420-7a13ab9156ec</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/coindesk-indices/2025/04/30/ai-crypto-agents-are-ushering-in-a-new-era-of-defai"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T15:29:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The use of autonomous agents to analyze market trends, balance portfolios and even manage liquidity across decentralized exchanges is a revolution you can’t afford to ignore, says the HBAR Foundation’s Gregg Bell.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gregg Bell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Get User Model in Django – A Simple Guide With Examples]]></title>
        <id>68123f859249b83d2215937d</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-get-user-model-in-django/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T15:19:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When I’m working with Django, one of the first things I often need to do is work with users – like getting the logged-in user, creating a new one, or extending the default user model to add more information. Now, Django has a built-in User model, but...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Udemezue John</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Someone at YouTube needs glasses]]></title>
        <id>https://jayd.ml/2025/04/30/someone-at-youtube-needs-glasses.html</id>
        <link href="https://jayd.ml/2025/04/30/someone-at-youtube-needs-glasses.html"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T15:18:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Oracle ERP Test Automation Guide – Examples and Best Practices]]></title>
        <id>68123ef3b70ffa1e4ce467ae</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/oracle-erp-test-automation-guide/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T15:17:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Oracle Enterprise Resource Planning helps businesses manage finance and supply chains. It also supports human resources and brings different functions together. Many growing businesses rely on it to handle complex tasks, as system failures or errors ...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nazneen Ahmad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OpenAI rolls back ChatGPT’s sycophancy and explains what went wrong]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3006053</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/openai-rolls-back-chatgpts-sycophancy-and-explains-what-went-wrong/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T15:14:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Many organizations may also begin shifting toward open-source alternatives that they can host and tune themselves.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carl Franzen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase Leaps Into Supreme Court Case in Defense of User Data Going to IRS]]></title>
        <id>1fdbaa1e-a5e3-4332-a0a0-78b9de537e9a</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2025/04/30/coinbase-leaps-into-supreme-court-case-in-defense-of-user-data-going-to-irs"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The U.S. crypto exchange filed a brief in a longstanding privacy battle over records the tax agency sought on customers' crypto transactions.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jesse Hamilton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[EU digital product passports won’t solve food fraud, but blockchain can]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/blockchain-can-solve-food-fraud</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/blockchain-can-solve-food-fraud?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Opinion by: Fraser Edwards, co-founder and CEO, Cheqd
Brutal honesty has its place, especially when confronting discomfort, so here’s one that can’t be sweetened with honey: 96% of imported honey in the UK is fake! Tests found that 24 of 25 jars were suspicious or didn’t meet regulatory standards. 
Self-sovereign identity (SSI) can fix this. 
The UK Food Standards Agency and the European Commission both urge reform to tackle this concern by creating a robust traceability database within supply chain networks to ensure consumer transparency and trust. Data, however, is not the problem. The issue is people tampering with it. 
This is not the first time products have been revealed to be inauthentic, with the Honey Authenticity Network highlighting that one-third of all honey products were fak…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Fraser Edwards</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Joining Sun Microsystems – 40 years ago (2022)]]></title>
        <id>https://akapugs.blog/2022/05/03/674/</id>
        <link href="https://akapugs.blog/2022/05/03/674/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T14:57:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin price recovers, Ethereum RWA value up 20%: April in charts]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-price-recovers-ethereum-rwa-value-up-april-2025</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-price-recovers-ethereum-rwa-value-up-april-2025?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T14:37:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[April 2025 witnessed crypto markets rocked by more tariffs at the direction of US President Donald Trump — controversial policies that could have influenced the outcome of Canada’s elections on April 28. 
On April 2, Trump levied “discounted reciprocal tariffs” on 185 countries and territories. The Dow Jones Industrial Average dropped 2,200 points on April 4, while the S&P 500 dropped nearly 6%, its largest decline since March 2020. Bitcoin (BTC) went along for the ride but broke from stocks as it recovered toward the end of the month. 
Blockchain adoption metrics for Ethereum are looking good, as the network now boasts 60% real-world asset (RWA) tokenization value. Major firms like BlackRock are sure the blockchain will be the standard for RWAs, but other observers believe that scaling is…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Aaron Wood</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why can't Ivies cope with losing a few hundred million?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.economist.com/briefing/2025/04/10/why-cant-stinking-rich-ivies-cope-with-losing-a-few-hundred-million</id>
        <link href="https://www.economist.com/briefing/2025/04/10/why-cant-stinking-rich-ivies-cope-with-losing-a-few-hundred-million"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T14:36:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Banks Must Adopt Crypto or 'Be Extinct in 10 Years,' Eric Trump Says]]></title>
        <id>3ac4b718-389d-4e22-8aad-98a97adbf2bd</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2025/04/30/banks-must-adopt-crypto-or-be-extinct-in-10-years-eric-trump-says"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T14:32:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The son of U.S. President Donald Trump said the current financial system is broken and blockchain technology is the fix.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Helene Braun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Coalition Tells SEC Staking Is 'Essential Good,' Not a Security]]></title>
        <id>a61ece06-5e37-4cc3-9eee-c83a72a4a8eb</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2025/04/28/crypto-coalition-tells-sec-staking-is-essential-good-not-a-security"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Industry entities led by the Crypto Council for Innovation argued in a letter to the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission that it shouldn't regulate staking.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jesse Hamilton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Here’s what happened in crypto today]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/what-happened-in-crypto-today</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/what-happened-in-crypto-today?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T13:58:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today in crypto, an elderly US individual is reportedly the victim of a recent $330 million Bitcoin social engineering attack, a US judge ruled that Tornado Cash can’t be sanctioned again, and the US Securities and Exchange Commission delayed its decision on Dogecoin and XRP exchange-traded funds.
$330 million Bitcoin social engineering theft victim is elderly US citizen
An elderly US individual is reportedly the victim of a devastating $330 million Bitcoin heist, now ranked as the fifth-largest crypto hack in history.
The attacker used advanced social engineering tactics to gain access to the victim’s wallet, onchain investigator ZachXBT said in an April 30 update on X.
The hack took place on April 28, 2025, when ZachXBT flagged a suspicious transfer involving 3,520 Bitcoin (BTC), valued …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Cointelegraph</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[China’s DeepSeek launches new open-source AI after R1 took on OpenAI]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/china-s-deep-seek-launches-new-open-source-ai-after-its-r1-took-on-open-ai</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/china-s-deep-seek-launches-new-open-source-ai-after-its-r1-took-on-open-ai?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T13:47:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Chinese artificial intelligence development company DeepSeek has released a new open-weight large language model (LLM).
DeepSeek uploaded its newest model, Prover V2, to the hosting service Hugging Face on April 30. The latest model, released under the permissive open-source MIT license, aims to tackle math proof verification.
 DeepSeek-Prover-V2 HuggingFace repository. Source: HuggingFace
Prover V2 has 671 billion parameters, making it significantly larger than its predecessors, Prover V1 and Prover V1.5, which were released in August 2024. The paper accompanying the first version explained that the model was trained to translate math competition problems into formal logic using the Lean 4 programming language — a tool widely used for proving theorems.  
The developers say Prover V2 compr…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Adrian Zmudzinski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA["AI-first" is the new Return To Office]]></title>
        <id>https://www.anildash.com//2025/04/19/ai-first-is-the-new-return-to-office/</id>
        <link href="https://www.anildash.com//2025/04/19/ai-first-is-the-new-return-to-office/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T13:38:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vitalik Buterin outlines vision as Ethereum ecosystem addresses hit new high]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/vitalik-shares-ethereum-vision-as-addresses-hit-record-high</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/vitalik-shares-ethereum-vision-as-addresses-hit-record-high?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T13:34:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum co-founder Vitalik Buterin released another update on what he believes the future of the network should entail.
In an April 30 post on blockchain-based social media platform Farcaster, Buterin outlined his personal areas of focus for Ethereum development this year. These include investigating changes to the network infrastructure to achieve single-slot finality, updates to smart contract execution and enhancements to privacy.
The post comes as the Ethereum network hits a new milestone. GrowThePie data shows that the weekly number of unique addresses interacting with the Ethereum ecosystem reached a new high of over 15.4 million, with nearly 13.45 million on layer-2 protocols.
Weekly chart of unique active addresses in the Ethereum ecosystem. Source: GrowThePie
Buterin recently arg…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Adrian Zmudzinski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Stagflationary Data Puts Pressure on Bitcoin, Stocks Early in U.S. Day]]></title>
        <id>3c744e3b-2623-4d12-9ee3-371eda918810</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/04/30/stagflationary-data-puts-pressure-on-bitcoin-stocks-early-in-u-s-day"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T13:34:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[U.S. GDP turned negative in the first quarter, while prices rose more than forecast; ADP jobs data was the weakest in nearly one year.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephen Alpher</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trump's Crypto Sherpa Bo Hines Says Crypto Legislation on Target for Quick Completion]]></title>
        <id>4faa7f7a-b9c4-4d0c-9168-a7dd151d1185</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/consensus-toronto-2025-coverage/2025/04/30/trumps-crypto-sherpa-bo-hines-says-crypto-legislation-on-target-for-quick-completion"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T13:28:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The head of the Presidential Council of Advisers for Digital Assets says new laws could be set by August, and Trump's own crypto interests aren't a factor.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jesse Hamilton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[$330M Bitcoin social engineering theft victim is elderly US citizen]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/elderly-us-victim-loses-330m-bitcoin-in-social-engineering-theft</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/elderly-us-victim-loses-330m-bitcoin-in-social-engineering-theft?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T13:18:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An elderly US individual is reportedly the victim of a devastating $330 million Bitcoin heist, now ranked as the fifth-largest crypto hack in history.
The attacker used advanced social engineering tactics to gain access to the victim’s wallet, onchain investigator ZachXBT said in an April 30 update on X.
The hack took place on April 28, 2025, when ZachXBT flagged a suspicious transfer involving 3,520 Bitcoin (BTC), valued at $330.7 million.
Following the transfer, the stolen stash was quickly laundered through over six instant exchanges and swapped into privacy-focused cryptocurrency Monero (XMR).
Onchain data shows that the victim had held over 3,000 BTC since 2017, with no prior history of large-scale transactions.
ZachXBT confirming the victim of the hack. Source: ZachXBT
Once stolen, t…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Amin Haqshanas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CoinDesk 20 Performance Update: Index Declines 2% as Nearly All Assets Trade Lower]]></title>
        <id>c1cd9dad-e07b-4abe-9187-978f1d043b24</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/coindesk-indices/2025/04/30/coindesk-20-performance-update-index-declines-2-as-nearly-all-assets-trade-lower"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T13:12:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Aave (AAVE) fell 4.7% and Ripple (XRP) dropped 4%, leading the index lower from Tuesday.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CoinDesk Indices</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Port of Los Angeles says shipping volume will plummet 35% next week]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cnbc.com/2025/04/29/port-of-los-angeles-sees-shipping-volume-down-35percent-next-week-as-tariffs-bite.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.cnbc.com/2025/04/29/port-of-los-angeles-sees-shipping-volume-down-35percent-next-week-as-tariffs-bite.html"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T13:07:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Show HN: Kexa.io – Open-Source IT Security and Compliance Verification]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=43844665</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=43844665"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T13:04:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The open source debate: Is crypto losing its soul?]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/open-source-debate-crypto-losing-soul</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/open-source-debate-crypto-losing-soul?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T13:03:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto was born from an open-source ethos, where code was shared publicly, accessible for review and shaped by community contributions. Transparency and verifiability are foundational principles that enable trust in Bitcoin.
But as the space matured, some disadvantages of open source surfaced. Innovative smart contract platforms and decentralized finance (DeFi) applications were forked to create direct competitors — from the wave of Uniswap clones to Ethereum forks — which prioritized speed and lower fees over decentralization.
As a result, some projects opted for closed-source development to protect proprietary designs and reduce the risk of exploits, hoping to delay or deter malicious actors by making the code harder to analyze. This approach is often criticized as “security through obsc…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Yohan Yun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto hackers hit DeFi for $92M in April as attacks double from March]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/crypto-hackers-steal-92-m-april-hacked-funds-1-7-b-2025</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/crypto-hackers-steal-92-m-april-hacked-funds-1-7-b-2025?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T13:00:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency hackers stole more than $90 million in April, dealing another blow to the industry’s mainstream reputation despite ongoing efforts to improve cybersecurity.
Hackers made off with $92 million of digital assets across 15 incidents in April, according to an April 30 research report by blockchain cybersecurity firm Immunefi.
The total marks a 124% month-over-month increase from March, when hackers stole $41 million.
Crypto stole in April 2025. Source: Immunefi
The month’s largest hack on open-source platform UPCX accounted for most of the damage in April, with over $70 million in losses, while KiloEx lost $7.5 million as April’s second-largest hack.
The KiloEx exploiter returned the stolen funds just days after the attack occurred.
All of April’s reported attacks targeted decent…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Zoltan Vardai</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Structify raises $4.1M seed to turn unstructured web data into enterprise-ready datasets]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3006010</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/structify-raises-4-1m-seed-to-turn-unstructured-web-data-into-enterprise-ready-datasets/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Brooklyn-based Structify emerges from stealth with $4.1 million in seed funding to transform how businesses prepare data for AI, promising to save data scientists from the task that consumes 80% of their time.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Nuñez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mantra links OM token crash to risky crypto exchange policies]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/mantra-om-token-crash-exchange-risk-policies</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/mantra-om-token-crash-exchange-risk-policies?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T12:34:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Update (April 30, 4:10 pm UTC): This article has been updated to add a comment from Mantra CEO John Mullin.
Decentralized finance (DeFi) platform Mantra has called for industry-wide cooperation to reduce investor risks in the aftermath of its OM token crash.
On April 30, Mantra published its latest update since the sudden collapse of its OM token, claiming that the incident was “bigger than Mantra.”
“Liquidation cascades could happen to any project in the crypto industry,” Mantra CEO John Mullin warned in the post, pointing to the role of “aggressive leverage positions” on exchanges as a broader threat to investor safety.
Mantra’s industry-wide call to action is the biggest section in the latest OM crash update. Source: Mantra
“We’re cooperating with major exchanges to improve market stabi…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Helen Partz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OCaml's Wings for Machine Learning]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/raven-ml/raven</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/raven-ml/raven"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T12:31:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tokenized Apollo Credit Fund Makes DeFi Debut With Levered-Yield Strategy by Securitize, Gauntlet]]></title>
        <id>677307ee-e3e4-4cc2-bf42-97ffd9c4e6fd</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/04/30/tokenized-apollo-credit-fund-makes-defi-debut-with-levered-yield-strategy-by-securitize-gauntlet"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T12:17:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The offering aims to make real-world asset tokens competitive with stablecoins for DeFi yield strategies, Securitize's Reid Simon said.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Krisztian Sandor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin macro indicator that predicted 2022 bottom flashes &#039;buy signal&#039;]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-macro-indicator-predicted-2022-bottom-flashes-buy</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-macro-indicator-predicted-2022-bottom-flashes-buy?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T12:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Key takeaways:

Macro Chain Index issues first buy signal since 2022, hinting at a new Bitcoin bull run.

RSI crossover on the MCI aligns with past cycle bottoms that preceded 500%+ BTC rallies.

Bitcoin price recovers from $74K to $95K amid rising open interest and positive funding rates.

A key Bitcoin (BTC) indicator that accurately signaled the 2022 market bottom has just flashed another buy signal, suggesting the cryptocurrency may be entering a new bull phase.
Bitcoin metric hints at “absolute bottom”
Dubbed the Macro Chain Index (MCI), the indicator is a composite of several long-term on-chain and macroeconomic metrics. 
It analyzes factors such as accumulation behavior, network activity, and supply trends, helping identify whether Bitcoin is undervalued or overvalued relative to it…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Yashu Gola</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FIFA shifts NFT platform to new Ethereum-compatible blockchain]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/fifa-collect-nfts-move-to-evm-blockchain</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/fifa-collect-nfts-move-to-evm-blockchain?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T12:12:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Federation Internationale de Football Association (FIFA) plans to launch a new blockchain network to support its non-fungible token (NFT) collectibles, the organization announced on April 30.
FIFA will launch its “FIFA Blockchain,” with Ethereum Virtual Machine (EVM) compatibility and aims to provide “better performance, future features, and improved scalability.”
As part of the move, FIFA Collect — its official NFT collection — will migrate from the Algorand blockchain to the new FIFA Blockchain. The migration is scheduled to begin no earlier than May 20, FIFA said.  
FIFA announces new blockchain for FIFA collection migration. Source: collect.fifa.com

“At this stage, no immediate action is required. When the migration process begins, we will provide clear, step-by-step instructions …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Zoltan Vardai</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Download: stereotypes in AI models, and the new age of coding]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1115952</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/04/30/1115952/the-download-stereotypes-in-ai-models-and-the-new-age-of-coding/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T12:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is today’s edition of The Download, our weekday newsletter that provides a daily dose of what’s going on in the world of technology. This data set helps researchers spot harmful stereotypes in LLMs What’s new? AI models are riddled with culturally specific biases. A new data set, called SHADES, is designed to help developers combat the…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rhiannon Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mastercard Introduces Agent Pay, A New System For AI-Led Commerce]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=350185</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/350185/mastercard-introduces-agent-pay/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T12:04:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mastercard has introduced a new technology called “Agent Pay”, aimed at powering secure and intelligent payments in a world increasingly shaped by artificial intelligence. Developed with companies including Microsoft and other leading AI platforms, the system is designed to allow AI agents – such as virtual assistants, chatbots, or autonomous shopping tools – to initiate […]
The post Mastercard Introduces Agent Pay, A New System For AI-Led Commerce appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Heirul Kamel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vanar Chain tackles AWS-style outages with AI-powered data storage]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/vanar-chain-launches-neutron-ai-onchain-compression</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/vanar-chain-launches-neutron-ai-onchain-compression?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T11:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Vanar Chain, a layer-1 blockchain network, has launched a new artificial intelligence-powered compression and data authentication layer designed to address the industry’s longstanding issue with onchain storage.
Vanar Chain is launching Neutron, an AI-native blockchain layer with data compression ratios of up to 500:1, which can reduce a standard 25 megabyte file to just 50 kilobytes, transforming it into a “Neutron Seed” that can be stored on the blockchain ledger.
The new blockchain compression layer aims to solve the industry’s data storage issue, with traditional blockchains lacking the capacity to store data, only to reference it.
This design introduces potential single points of failure. Vanar's Neutron aims to solve this by enabling fully onchain, verifiable data storage.
Neutron is…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Zoltan Vardai</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Retailers will soon have only about 7 weeks of full inventories left]]></title>
        <id>https://fortune.com/article/retailers-weeks-of-inventory-left-trump-china-trade-war/</id>
        <link href="https://fortune.com/article/retailers-weeks-of-inventory-left-trump-china-trade-war/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T11:42:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lessons from the Lebanese Space Program – Kasurian]]></title>
        <id>https://kasurian.com/p/lebanese-space-program</id>
        <link href="https://kasurian.com/p/lebanese-space-program"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T11:41:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Daybook Americas: Robinhood Earnings to Preview Trump's 'Damage']]></title>
        <id>0b8f55d6-8763-4cc6-9352-6bfcb3db8bab</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/daybook-us/2025/04/30/crypto-daybook-americas-biggest-tokens-show-restraint-for-now-but-damage-has-already-been-done"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T11:17:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Your day-ahead look for April 30, 2025]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Francisco Rodrigues</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin traders predict BTC price gains ahead of $96K liquidity clash]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-traders-predict-btc-price-gains-ahead-of-96k-liquidity-clash</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-traders-predict-btc-price-gains-ahead-of-96k-liquidity-clash?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T11:11:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Key points:

Bitcoin consolidates after upside momentum stalls, but traders are confident that upside breakout will result.

Major risk-asset volatility is expected as US macro data precedes the monthly candle close.

April BTC price performance is on track to be the best since 2020.

Bitcoin (BTC) spent another day around $95,000 on April 30 as volatility waited in the wings.
BTC/USD 1-hour chart. Source: Cointelegraph/TradingView
Bitcoin enjoys the calm before the storm
Data from Cointelegraph Markets Pro and TradingView showed calm trading conditions with hours to go until the monthly close and key US macro data.
The latter comes in the form of Q1 GDP and the March print of the Personal Consumption Expenditures (PCE) index, known as the Federal Reserve’s “preferred” inflation gauge.
The…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by William Suberg</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nasdaq Seeks SEC Approval to List 21Shares Dogecoin ETF]]></title>
        <id>11f6cfaa-74d7-43a5-b5cd-081a49c73d92</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/04/30/nasdaq-seeks-sec-approval-to-list-21shares-dogecoin-etf"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T11:06:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase Custody Trust will hold the fund’s tokens and serve as the official custodian for the ETF.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shaurya Malwa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Inside Movement’s Token-Dump Scandal: Secret Contracts, Shadow Advisors and Hidden Middlemen]]></title>
        <id>ca25f2fb-f887-4098-86ec-a0104210e64e</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/tech/2025/04/30/inside-movement-s-token-dump-scandal-secret-contracts-shadow-advisors-and-hidden-middlemen"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Movement, backed by Trump's World Liberty Financial, says it was duped into an agreement that experts say incentivized price manipulation.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sam Kessler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Week In Gaming: EA Cancels Titanfall Game, Borderlands 4 Gets New Release Date, And More]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=350162</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/350162/this-week-in-gaming/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T10:53:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’re halfway through the week, and in the world of gaming, some things have happened but not in such a major fashion that it would make waves. That being said, their occurrence is still important enough to warrant a report and as such, here’s a quick list of them. EA Lays Off Hundreds Of Staff, […]
The post This Week In Gaming: EA Cancels Titanfall Game, Borderlands 4 Gets New Release Date, And More appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John Law</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[KuCoin Commits $2B to 'Trust Project' Focusing on Crypto Security, Transparency]]></title>
        <id>2a3c88da-cd66-4d75-8f07-1dbedc9e3cc9</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2025/04/30/kucoin-commits-usd2-billion-to-trust-project-focusing-on-crypto-security-and-transparency"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T10:08:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[KuCoin’s native token, KCS, will play a more pivotal role in the ecosystem.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Omkar Godbole</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin volatility lowest in 563 days, Hayes predicts $1M BTC by 2028]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-volatility-563-day-low-hayes-predicts-1-m-btc-2028</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-volatility-563-day-low-hayes-predicts-1-m-btc-2028?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T10:02:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin is showing signs of maturity as a global financial asset, with price volatility dropping to its lowest level in more than 500 days, according to new research.
Volatility refers to the degree of variation of a trading price over time, which indicates the uncertainty about the size of changes in an asset’s value.
Bitcoin (BTC) weekly volatility hit a 563-day low on April 30, said Vetle Lunde, the head of research at K33 Research.
Source: Vetle Lunde
Bitcoin’s decreasing volatility suggests BTC is maturing as a global financial asset, leading to a more stable price trajectory.
Bitcoin has become the seventh-largest asset globally by market capitalization, reaching $1.87 trillion. It now ranks above Silver, Meta and Saudi Aramco, according to Companiesmarketcap.
Top 10 global assets by…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Zoltan Vardai</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Samsung One UI 8 Might Bring AI Video Summarisation]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=350177</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/350177/samsung-one-ui-8-might-bring-ai-video-summarisation/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T09:50:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Samsung will reportedly bring an AI video summarisation tool in its One UI 8 based on Android 16. As reported by SammyGuru, the tool will be able to analyse a video, based on speech, visuals, and captions. A multi-modal AI model will then summarise the main points of the video. The feature will apparently be […]
The post Samsung One UI 8 Might Bring AI Video Summarisation appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Newsdesk</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This data set helps researchers spot harmful stereotypes in LLMs]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1115946</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/04/30/1115946/this-data-set-helps-researchers-spot-harmful-stereotypes-in-llms/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T09:41:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AI models are riddled with culturally specific biases. A new data set, called SHADES, is designed to help developers combat the problem by spotting harmful stereotypes and other kinds of discrimination that emerge in AI chatbot responses across a wide range of languages. Margaret Mitchell, chief ethics scientist at AI startup Hugging Face, led the…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rhiannon Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Finland Bans Smartphones in Schools]]></title>
        <id>https://yle.fi/a/74-20158886</id>
        <link href="https://yle.fi/a/74-20158886"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T09:17:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chery Tiggo Cross HEV To Get Malaysian Appearance In May]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=350155</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/350155/chery-tiggo-cross-hev-to-get-malaysian-appearance-in-may/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T09:04:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This year’s edition of the Malaysia Auto Show is scheduled to happen in May as it usually does, but it looks like Chery may have a hybrid car to showcase during the event. This may come in the form of the Tiggo Cross, which may be known instead as the Tiggo 4 elsewhere. Paul Tan […]
The post Chery Tiggo Cross HEV To Get Malaysian Appearance In May appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ian Chee</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Circle taps Onafriq to cut Africa’s cross-border payment costs with USDC]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/circle-onafriq-partner-to-cut-africa-payment-costs-with-usdc</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/circle-onafriq-partner-to-cut-africa-payment-costs-with-usdc?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Stablecoin issuer Circle has partnered with Onafriq, Africa’s largest payments gateway, to reduce the high cost of cross-border payments across the continent using USDC.
According to a press release shared with Cointelegraph, Circle aims to pilot USDC (USDC) settlements within Onafriq’s vast network, which connects over 500 wallets and 200 million bank accounts in more than 40 countries.
“By integrating USDC, we aim to simplify financial transactions for institutions and individuals, reduce costs and strengthen trust,” Onafriq founder and CEO Dare Okoudjou said.
He added that the integration of USDC will simplify transactions and boost trust in digital financial services.
Currently, over 80% of intra-African transactions are routed through correspondent banks outside the continent and sett…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Amin Haqshanas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Xiaomi Debuts Its Own AI Model]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=350157</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/350157/xiaomi-debuts-its-own-ai-model/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T08:57:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Xiaomi has recently unveiled MiMo, its in-house open source AI model with reasoning capabilities. With the release of the large language model, the company has joined the ranks of China’s tech firms, hoping to gain a foothold in the AI industry. According to Xiaomi, MiMo was developed by Core, a specialised AI task force. The […]
The post Xiaomi Debuts Its Own AI Model appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nurul Kamil</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Xiaomi MiMo Reasoning Model]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/XiaomiMiMo/MiMo</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/XiaomiMiMo/MiMo"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T08:48:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Debate on Looser Data Limits Brings to Mind the Divisive Ordinals Controversy]]></title>
        <id>6feae542-2b1a-4681-be27-d67fdf8e8d0f</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/tech/2025/04/30/bitcoin-debate-on-looser-data-limits-brings-to-mind-the-divisive-ordinals-controversy"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T08:44:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Removing the blockchain's OP_RETURN size controls would allow more data to be embedded in transactions. Critics say this will only be used for spam.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sam Reynolds</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin May Evolve Into Low-Beta Equity Play Reflexively, BlackRock's Mitchnik Says]]></title>
        <id>74f0300a-3daa-4fd9-a866-5e9ec9ac6149</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2025/04/30/bitcoin-may-evolve-into-low-beta-equity-play-blackrocks-mitchnik-says"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T08:39:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA["It makes no fundamental sense, and yet when it's repeated enough, it can actually become a little self-fulfilling,” Mitchnik said.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Omkar Godbole</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Is Bitcoin a hedge against inflation in 2025?]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/explained/is-bitcoin-a-hedge-against-inflation</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/explained/is-bitcoin-a-hedge-against-inflation?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T08:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Understanding inflation and the need for hedges            
            
                
Bitcoin’s supply-and-demand dynamics, in addition to growing institutional adoption, position it as a potential hedge against inflation in 2025. However, its high volatility and centralization concerns mean it remains a speculative asset rather than a guaranteed safeguard against inflation.
What is inflation? 
Inflation refers to the general increase in the prices of goods and services in an economy over time, leading to a decrease in the purchasing power of money. As prices rise, each unit of currency buys fewer goods and services. Inflation is typically measured by indexes such as the Consumer Price Index (CPI), which tracks the average change in the prices paid by consumers for a basket of goods an…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Dilip Kumar Patairya</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trump Administration Could Alter Biden-Era AI Chip Rule]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=350146</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/350146/trump-administration-could-alter-biden-era-ai-chip-rule/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T08:24:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[US President Trump and his administration could be looking to bring back a Biden-era rule regarding the export of AI chips to other countries. Supposedly, it’s planning on making a few tweaks to the rule and, in conjunction, do away with its current way of segregating recipient countries into three tiers. According to sources close […]
The post Trump Administration Could Alter Biden-Era AI Chip Rule appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John Law</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Where and how to sell Pi Coin: A step-by-step guide]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/where-and-how-to-sell-pi-coin</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/where-and-how-to-sell-pi-coin?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T08:21:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Key takeaways

Set up your Pi Wallet and secure it with a 24-word seed phrase before transferring your coins.

KYC is often required on both CEXs and P2P platforms to transfer and sell Pi Coins.

You can sell Pi through CEXs or P2P platforms, each offering different security, speed and control.

Always do your own research (DYOR) before selling or holding, as expert opinions on Pi’s future vary.

If you’re here, you probably already know what Pi Coin is and just want to figure out how to sell it. However, a recap awaits, in case you need one. 
While the project pitches itself as a way to democratize crypto access through mobile mining, there are some major concerns that have been hard to ignore:

Pi claims over 60 million users, but blockchain explorers show only about 9.11 million wallets…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Bradley Peak</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Apple Watch SE 3 Display Leaked, May Come In Two Sizes]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=350132</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/350132/apple-watch-se-3-display-leaked-two-sizes/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T08:13:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There is a chance that Apple might be releasing its Watch SE 3 soon, possibly this year, as reported by 9to5Mac. The original model of the watch was released back in 2020, with the 2nd generation being launched two years later in 2022. Like the two preceding models, the third generation may also come in […]
The post Apple Watch SE 3 Display Leaked, May Come In Two Sizes appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ian Chee</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Leaderboard Illusion]]></title>
        <id>https://arxiv.org/abs/2504.20879</id>
        <link href="https://arxiv.org/abs/2504.20879"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T07:58:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Is Bitcoin price going to crash again?]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/is-bitcoin-price-going-to-crash-again</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/is-bitcoin-price-going-to-crash-again?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T07:56:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Key takeaways:

Bitcoin's 28% rebound from $75,000 faces resistance at $95,000, risking a bull trap.

Strong spot price momentum and ETF inflows support a potential $100,000 push.

Bull flag pattern suggests a $108,300 target if BTC breaks the $95,000 resistance.

Bitcoin (BTC) price has rebounded by 28% from its five-month low below $75,000 reached on April 9. However, its failure to break above the $95,000 resistance level decisively has sparked concerns that the latest recovery may trap bulls.
BTC/USD daily price chart. Source: Cointelegraph/TradingView
Bitcoin ETF flows provide a “more solid foundation”
But another big crash may be averted as BTC price momentum is backed by elevated spot Bitcoin ETF inflows in recent days. 
This provides Bitcoin a “more solid foundation” to surge forwa…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Nancy Lubale</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Banks must adopt crypto or be extinct in 10 years, Eric Trump says]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/bank-must-adopt-crypto-or-be-extinct-eric-trump</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/bank-must-adopt-crypto-or-be-extinct-eric-trump?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T07:51:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Eric Trump, executive vice president of the Trump Organization and son of US President Donald Trump, has delivered a warning to global banks regarding cryptocurrency adoption.
“The modern financial system is broken, it’s slow, it’s expensive,” Trump said in a CNBC interview on April 30, adding that the existing banking system “favors the ultra-wealthy.”
“It forced me into the crypto world,” he continued, adding: “And I’m telling you, if the banks don’t watch what’s coming, they’re going to be extinct in 10 years.”
SWIFT is an “absolute disaster”
While emphasizing the need for banks to closely monitor developments in the crypto industry, Trump highlighted the benefits of cryptocurrency’s underlying blockchain technology for the financial system.
He slammed the existing cross-border transact…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Helen Partz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[realme 14T Set To Land In Malaysia On 16 May]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=350149</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/350149/realme-14t-16-may/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T07:51:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hot on the heels of its recent launch of the 14 series, realme has revealed that it will be launching the 14T next month. The upcoming device has been listed on the brand’s official Shopee page with an arrival date of 16 May 2025. Aside from the first sale date, the listing also reveals that […]
The post realme 14T Set To Land In Malaysia On 16 May appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ikmal Rozlan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[I created Perfect Wiki and reached $250k in annual revenue without investors]]></title>
        <id>https://habr.com/en/articles/905812/</id>
        <link href="https://habr.com/en/articles/905812/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T07:45:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TON’s Broxus launches blockchain app scalability platform TON Factory]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/telegram-ton-factory-scalability-launch</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/telegram-ton-factory-scalability-launch?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T06:16:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Open Network (TON) ecosystem participant Broxus has unveiled TON Factory, a new platform designed to accelerate the development and scalability of high-throughput applications like decentralized exchanges (DEXs) and blockchain-based games.
In an April 30 post on Telegram, the project said TON Factory aims to help developers rapidly build and scale projects with modular components, integration tools, and hands-on expert support.
“For OGs already building on TON, TON Factory helps you scale further,” the announcement stated.
The initiative is backed by a team of over 150 engineers with experience delivering production-ready infrastructure in the TON ecosystem, per the announcement. 
Source: TON
“TON Factory will help developers focusing on L2/appchains with TVM tech and ensuring connecti…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Amin Haqshanas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BlackRock Looking to Tokenize Shares of Its $150B Treasury Trust Fund, SEC Filing Shows]]></title>
        <id>c3e9da3d-b1ba-4d10-99bf-07ac25dd1351</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/04/30/sec-filing-shows-blackrock-preparing-150-billion-tokenized-treasury-trust-offering"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T06:15:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BlackRock will work with BNY Mellon in creating a new class of Distributed Ledger Technology shares for the fund.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sam Reynolds</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Samsung To Add Direct Access To Gemini For Galaxy A Series]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=350134</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/350134/samsung-adds-direct-access-gemini-for-galaxy-a-series/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T06:10:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Samsung has announced that it is adding a feature to select Galaxy A series devices that allows users to directly access Gemini using the side button. With this feature, which is already available on the company’s Galaxy S series, users can simply press and hold the side button to activate the AI assistant. The upcoming […]
The post Samsung To Add Direct Access To Gemini For Galaxy A Series appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nurul Kamil</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum ETF staking will have little impact without multimonth rally: Analyst]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/ether-etf-staking-impact-on-inflows-little-price-rally-eric-balchunas</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/ether-etf-staking-impact-on-inflows-little-price-rally-eric-balchunas?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T06:04:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Key takeaways

Approving staking for spot Ether exchange-traded funds (ETFs) in the US may have a minimal impact on inflows unless Ether sees a sustained rally, says Eric Balchunas

ETH dropped significantly in price after the launch of the ETFs last year, unlike spot Bitcoin ETFs, which saw new all-time highs just two months after launching.

Balchunas said that for inflows to increase again, ETH would need a multimonth run and a strong narrative.

Spot Ethereum ETFs being able to stake a portion of the tokens under their control may not help garner inflows without a more sustained rally in the token’s price, says Bloomberg ETF analyst Eric Balchunas.
Balchunas said on an April 29 episode of the New Era Finance Podcast that staking being approved for Ether (ETH) ETFs would have “a little”…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Ciaran Lyons</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Telegram’s TON Takes On Real World Assets With Libre’s $500M Tokenized Bond Fund]]></title>
        <id>ebe6875e-7c61-4b31-9f2e-03a0d9648aa6</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2025/04/30/telegram-s-ton-takes-on-real-world-assets-with-libre-s-usd500m-tokenized-bond-fund"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T06:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Libre’s Telegram Bond Fund ($TBF) will offer accredited investors institutional-grade yield products that will also be available as collateral for on-chain borrowing and product development on TON,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ian Allison</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google’s “Audio Overviews” Feature For NotebookLM Now Supports Bahasa Malaysia]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=350138</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/350138/google-audio-overviews-now-supports-bahasa-malaysia/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T05:59:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google has updated its AI-powered learning tool, NotebookLM, by introducing support for more than 50 languages in its Audio Overviews feature. With this update, users can now generate podcast-style summaries of their submitted content in languages beyond English — including Bahasa Malaysia. According to a recent blog post, Google says the expansion is part of […]
The post Google’s “Audio Overviews” Feature For NotebookLM Now Supports Bahasa Malaysia appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Heirul Kamel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SEC drops investigation into PayPal’s stablecoin]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/sec-drops-investigation-into-paypal-s-stablecoin</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/sec-drops-investigation-into-paypal-s-stablecoin?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T05:46:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[PayPal says the US Securities and Exchange Commission has abandoned its investigation into the payment giant’s US-dollar stablecoin.
PayPal said in an April 29 regulatory filing that the SEC concluded its investigation into PayPal USD (PYUSD) and wouldn’t be taking any action.
The company said it received a subpoena from the SEC’s Division of Enforcement over its stablecoin in November 2023. 
“The subpoena requests the production of documents. We are cooperating with the SEC in connection with this request,” PayPal stated at the time.
In its latest filing, the firm said the SEC notified it in February that the agency “was closing this inquiry without enforcement action.”
PayPal has said its stablecoin is 100% redeemable for US dollars and “fully backed” by dollar deposits, including short-…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Martin Young</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FTX sues NFT Stars and Kurosemi in push to recover tokens]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/ftx-sues-nft-stars-and-kurosemi-in-push-to-recover-tokens</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/ftx-sues-nft-stars-and-kurosemi-in-push-to-recover-tokens?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T05:31:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bankrupt crypto exchange FTX has filed lawsuits against the non-fungible token marketplace NFT Stars and the blockchain gaming firm Kurosemi, which operates as Delysium, accusing them of withholding tokens they owed.
The lawsuits, both filed in the Delaware bankruptcy court, alleged that NFT Stars and Delysium failed to deliver all the tokens paid for by FTX despite repeated attempts to resolve the matter.
FTX claimed in an April 28 statement that it made “numerous unanswered attempts” to engage with both firms, and it would be “contacting numerous other token and coin issuers regarding FTX assets and will be filing additional suits against non-responsive parties.”
Source: FTX
As part of the complaint against Delysium, FTX claimed its defunct trading arm, Alameda Research, paid $1 million …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Stephen Katte</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SEC Delays Dogecoin and XRP ETF Decisions]]></title>
        <id>6bb80abf-8034-42d9-991c-6a51ab9ce9a3</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/04/30/sec-delays-dogecoin-and-xrp-etf-decisions"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T05:25:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The delays are expected as most ETF filings have final deadlines in October or beyond, one analyst pointed out.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shaurya Malwa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BlackRock files to create digital shares tracking one of its money market funds]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/blackrock-files-digital-shares-money-market-fund</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/blackrock-files-digital-shares-money-market-fund?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T05:18:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Asset manager BlackRock has filed to create digital ledger technology shares from one of the firm’s money market funds, which will leverage blockchain technology to maintain a mirror record of share ownership for investors.
The DLT shares will track BlackRock’s BLF Treasury Trust Fund (TTTXX), which may only be purchased from BlackRock Advisors and The Bank of New York Mellon (BNY), the firm said in its April 29 Form N-1A filing with the Securities and Exchange Commission.
The money market fund holds over $150 million worth of assets, invested almost entirely in US Treasury bills and cash.
BlackRock said that the shares “are expected to be purchased and held through BNY, which intends to use blockchain technology to maintain a mirror record of share ownership for its customers.”
Unlike the…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Brayden Lindrea</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[US Treasury’s OFAC can’t restore Tornado Cash sanctions, judge rules]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/us-treasury-ofac-cant-restore-tornado-cash-sanctions</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/us-treasury-ofac-cant-restore-tornado-cash-sanctions?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T04:14:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The US Treasury Department’s Office of Foreign Assets Control can’t restore or reimpose sanctions against the crypto mixing service Tornado Cash, a US federal court has ruled.
Austin federal court judge Robert Pitman said in an April 28 judgment that OFAC’s sanctions on Tornado Cash were unlawful and that the agency was “permanently enjoined from enforcing” sanctions.
Tornado Cash users led by Joseph Van Loon had sued the Treasury, arguing that OFAC’s addition of the platform’s smart contract addresses to its Specially Designated Nationals and Blocked Persons (SDN) list was “not in accordance with law.” 
OFAC had sanctioned Tornado Cash in August 2022, accusing the protocol of helping launder crypto stolen by the North Korean hacking collective, the Lazarus Group.
The agency dropped the pl…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Martin Young</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Strategy’s Bitcoin buys should be ‘super careless’ to pump price — Exec]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/michael-saylor-strategy-bitcoin-buying-approach-super-careless-idea-richard-byworth</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/michael-saylor-strategy-bitcoin-buying-approach-super-careless-idea-richard-byworth?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T03:48:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Key takeaways:

Richard Byworth says Michael Saylor’s Strategy could ramp up its Bitcoin buys by acquiring cash-rich companies and converting their cash into Bitcoin.

He says that Strategy should consider accelerating purchases as the Bitcoin supply on exchanges continues to decline.

Byworth argues that aggressively increasing Bitcoin holdings would boost Strategy’s mNAV, benefiting shareholders.

Michael Saylor’s Strategy should take a more aggressive approach to buying Bitcoin by acquiring companies to use their cash holdings to fund purchases and do away with over-the-counter buys, a crypto executive says.
“Saylor’s strategy so far has been the right one,” Syz Capital partner and Jan3 adviser Richard Byworth said on an April 29 podcast.
Strategy should try “super aggressive” buying
Ho…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Ciaran Lyons</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Linux in Excel]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/NSG650/LinuxInExcel</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/NSG650/LinuxInExcel"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T03:08:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sycophancy in GPT-4o]]></title>
        <id>https://openai.com/index/sycophancy-in-gpt-4o/</id>
        <link href="https://openai.com/index/sycophancy-in-gpt-4o/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T03:06:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What It Takes to Defend a Cybersecurity Company from Today's Adversaries]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sentinelone.com/labs/top-tier-target-what-it-takes-to-defend-a-cybersecurity-company-from-todays-adversaries/</id>
        <link href="https://www.sentinelone.com/labs/top-tier-target-what-it-takes-to-defend-a-cybersecurity-company-from-todays-adversaries/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T02:53:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Malaysia attracts US$3.7 billion in digital investments, solidifying]]></title>
        <id>b95e1bfb983c9cc102bc4266d362a8c2</id>
        <link href="https://www.digitalnewsasia.com/digital-economy/malaysia-attracts-us37-billion-digital-investments-solidifying-position-aseans-tech"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T02:31:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Malaysia’s digital economy continues to go from strength to strength, emerging as a strategic engine of growth that creates jobs, opens new opportunities, and fosters local innovation for businesses]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>@DigitalNewsAsia</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Australia’s finance watchdog to crack down on dormant crypto exchanges]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/australia-finance-agency-austrac-dormant-crypto-exchange-blitz</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/australia-finance-agency-austrac-dormant-crypto-exchange-blitz?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T02:24:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Australia’s financial intelligence agency has told inactive registered crypto exchanges to withdraw their registrations or risk having them canceled over fears that the dormant firms could be used for scams.
There are currently 427 crypto exchanges registered with the Australian Transaction Reports and Analysis Centre (AUSTRAC), but the agency said on April 29 that it suspects a significant number are inactive and possibly vulnerable to being bought and co-opted by criminals.
The agency is contacting any so-called digital currency exchanges (DCEs) that appear to no longer be trading, and AUSTRAC CEO Brendan Thomas said they’ll be told to “use it or lose it.”
“Businesses registered with AUSTRAC are required to keep their details up to date; this includes details about services that are no l…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Stephen Katte</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MDV powers Malaysia's tech innovation with over RM13bil financing]]></title>
        <id>d3f5fdc4ea236d719dc3a9d352d4620c</id>
        <link href="https://www.nst.com.my/business/corporate/2025/04/1209375/mdv-powers-malaysias-tech-innovation-over-rm13bil-financing"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T01:56:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[KUALA LUMPUR: Malaysia Debt Ventures Bhd (MDV) has emerged as a key enabler of the nation’s innovation and digital transformation agenda, with more than RM13 billion channelled into over 1,000 high-impact, technology-driven projects.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bernama</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ledger scammers are sending letters to steal seed phrases]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/ledger-scammers-send-letters-steal-recovery-seed-phrases</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/ledger-scammers-send-letters-steal-recovery-seed-phrases?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T01:50:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Scammers are mailing physical letters to the owners of Ledger crypto hardware wallets asking them to validate their private seed phrases in a bid to access the wallets to clean them out.
In an April 29 X post, tech commentator Jacob Canfield shared a scam letter sent to his home via post that appeared to be from Ledger claiming he needed to immediately perform a “critical security update” on his device. 
The letter, which uses Ledger’s logo, business address, and a reference number to feign legitimacy, asks to scan a QR code and enter the wallet’s private recovery phrase under the guise of validating the device.
The letter threatens that “failure to complete this mandatory validation process may result in restricted access to your wallet and funds.”
Source: Jacob Canfield
A seed phrase, or…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Brayden Lindrea</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[You Wouldn't Download a Hacker News]]></title>
        <id>https://www.jasonthorsness.com/25</id>
        <link href="https://www.jasonthorsness.com/25"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T01:26:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Author of Crypto Bills Now Being Rehashed Predicts 'Wicked Hot Summer' in Congress]]></title>
        <id>efd65f86-4255-4797-861a-23f03284b564</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2025/04/29/author-of-crypto-bills-now-being-rehashed-predicts-wicked-hot-summer-in-congress"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T22:49:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Patrick McHenry, the ex-lawmaker who championed last year's crypto legislation, also said he expects a role to be found for Tether in the U.S. stablecoin field.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jesse Hamilton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[No more window switching: Mastercard’s Agent Pay transforms how enterprises use AI search]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3005997</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/no-more-window-switching-mastercards-agent-pay-transforms-how-enterprises-use-ai-search/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T22:24:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mastercard is working with AI companies and banks to allow AI platforms and agents to facilitate transactions.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Emilia David</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trump's Truth Social Mulls Launching Token for Subscriptions in Latest Crypto Push]]></title>
        <id>38806852-3f69-4584-a468-6c835ffce78f</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2025/04/29/trump-s-truth-social-mulls-launching-token-for-subscriptions-in-further-crypto-push"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T21:39:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The company also plans to forge ahead with its ETFs, which will include cryptocurrencies.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tom Carreras</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Edges Above $95K, U.S. Stocks Remain Strong as Analyst Warns of 'Blind' Market]]></title>
        <id>0b77b062-fd9e-4a51-9e8c-b2f07d34ab15</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/04/29/bitcoin-edges-up-to-usd95k-u-s-stocks-remain-strong-as-analyst-warns-of-blind-market"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T20:11:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Secretary of Commerce Howard Lutnick announced that the White House was finalizing a trade deal with an unnamed country.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tom Carreras</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meta unleashes Llama API running 18x faster than OpenAI: Cerebras partnership delivers 2,600 tokens per second]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3005976</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/meta-unleashes-llama-api-running-18x-faster-than-openai-cerebras-partnership-delivers-2600-tokens-per-second/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T20:02:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Meta partners with Cerebras to launch its new Llama API, offering developers AI inference speeds up to 18 times faster than traditional GPU solutions, challenging OpenAI and Google in the fast-growing AI services market.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Nuñez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Researchers are studying how to minimize human impact on public lands]]></title>
        <id>https://undark.org/2025/04/28/keep-wild-places-wild/</id>
        <link href="https://undark.org/2025/04/28/keep-wild-places-wild/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T19:45:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SoFi Plans Major Push Into Crypto Amid New Regulatory Environment]]></title>
        <id>2f3ada3b-e97d-4f16-8191-76362479c063</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2025/04/29/sofi-will-allow-clients-to-invest-in-crypto-again-after-suspending-service-in-2023-plans-major-push"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T19:11:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There's been a “fundamental shift” in the crypto landscape in the U.S., CEO Anthony Noto said on Wednesday.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Helene Braun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tornado Cash Can’t Be Sanctioned Again, Texas Judge Rules]]></title>
        <id>fc5b1370-af53-43a5-b5da-ec4d7b6197e9</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2025/04/29/tornado-cash-can-t-be-sanctioned-again-texas-judge-rules"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T18:43:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In December, a U.S. appeals court ruled that the U.S. Treasury’s Office of Foreign Asset Control (OFAC) exceeded its statutory authority in sanctioning Tornado Cash.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cheyenne Ligon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meta’s first dedicated AI app is here with Llama 4 — but it’s more consumer than productivity or business oriented]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3005961</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/metas-first-dedicated-ai-app-is-here-with-llama-4-but-its-more-consumer-than-productivity-or-business-oriented/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T18:19:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This mainstream exposure will likely accelerate a shift in what people expect not just from consumer apps, but from workplaces...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carl Franzen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chain of Recursive Thoughts: Make AI think harder by making it argue with itself]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/PhialsBasement/Chain-of-Recursive-Thoughts</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/PhialsBasement/Chain-of-Recursive-Thoughts"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T17:19:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Samourai Wallet Prosecutors Are Considering Dropping Charges Under New DOJ Crypto Enforcement Priorities: Filing]]></title>
        <id>9b36b910-d4ee-462e-9886-3535208b8bf1</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2025/04/29/samourai-wallet-prosecutors-are-considering-dropping-charges-under-new-doj-crypto-enforcement-priorities-filing"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T16:46:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The co-founders are each facing up to 25 years in prison for alleged money laundering and unlicensed money transmitting.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cheyenne Ligon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Create Accessible and User-Friendly Forms in React]]></title>
        <id>6810f59e8deee87383c1bc46</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-create-accessible-and-user-friendly-forms-in-react/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T15:51:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When designing web applications, you’ll often be asked the age old question “How accessible is your website” and “Does it offer the best user experience?”. These are both very valid questions, but they are often overlooked in favour of rich or fancy ...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Grant Riordan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn College Calculus and Implement with Python]]></title>
        <id>6810eebd43aa3d16a14700eb</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-college-calculus-and-implement-with-python/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T15:22:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Calculus is one of the cornerstones of higher mathematics and a powerful tool for understanding change, motion, and growth across countless disciplines. But for many students, Calculus can seem intimidating or abstract. What if you could learn it ste...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Register Models in Django Admin]]></title>
        <id>6810e5a2dc9845a2ab207f06</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-register-models-in-django-admin/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T14:43:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When you're building a website or an app with Django, one of the most exciting moments is when your database models finally come to life. But to manage your data easily – adding, editing, or deleting entries – you need Django’s Admin panel. Now, here...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Udemezue John</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Jepsen: Amazon RDS for PostgreSQL 17.4]]></title>
        <id>https://jepsen.io/analyses/amazon-rds-for-postgresql-17.4</id>
        <link href="https://jepsen.io/analyses/amazon-rds-for-postgresql-17.4"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T14:30:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tripp launches Kōkua AI as mental wellness coach across multiple platforms]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3005798</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/games/tripp-launches-kokua-ai-as-mental-wellness-coach-across-multiple-platforms/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T13:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tripp launched Kōkua AI, a mental wellness guide designed to deliver real-time, personalized emotional support across multiple platforms.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dean Takahashi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[xMEMS extends micro cooling fan-on-a-chip tech to AI data centers]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3005879</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/game-development/xmems-extends-micro-cooling-fan-on-a-chip-tech-to-ai-data-centers/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[xMEMS Labs, a pioneer of MEMS-based chips, announced that its innovative µCooling fan-on-a-chip tech will be expanded to AI data centers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dean Takahashi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New atomic fountain clock joins group that keeps the world on time]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nist.gov/news-events/news/2025/04/new-atomic-fountain-clock-joins-elite-group-keeps-world-time</id>
        <link href="https://www.nist.gov/news-events/news/2025/04/new-atomic-fountain-clock-joins-elite-group-keeps-world-time"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T12:39:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Is "Induced Atmospheric Vibration"?]]></title>
        <id>https://physics.stackexchange.com/questions/848666/what-is-induced-atmospheric-vibration</id>
        <link href="https://physics.stackexchange.com/questions/848666/what-is-induced-atmospheric-vibration"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T12:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Download: the AI Hype Index, and “normal” AI]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1115932</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/04/29/1115932/the-download-the-ai-hype-index-and-normal-ai/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T12:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is today’s edition of The Download, our weekday newsletter that provides a daily dose of what’s going on in the world of technology. The AI Hype Index: AI agent cyberattacks, racing robots, and musical models Separating AI reality from hyped-up fiction isn’t always easy. That’s why we’ve created the AI Hype Index—a simple, at-a-glance summary of…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rhiannon Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The AI Hype Index: AI agent cyberattacks, racing robots, and musical models]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1115918</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/04/29/1115918/the-ai-hype-index-ai-agent-cyberattacks-racing-robots-and-musical-models/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Separating AI reality from hyped-up fiction isn’t always easy. That’s why we’ve created the AI Hype Index—a simple, at-a-glance summary of everything you need to know about the state of the industry. AI agents are the AI industry’s hypiest new product—intelligent assistants capable of completing tasks without human supervision. But while they can be theoretically…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Editors</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Web3j Six Month Project Update]]></title>
        <id>68109495670a1300013504c2</id>
        <link href="https://blog.web3labs.com/web3j-six-month-project-update/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T09:10:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[November 2024 - April 2025
This report summarizes the activities and accomplishments of Web3j, an LF Decentralized Trust project, from November 2024 to April 2025. During this period, the project made significant strides in improving the framework’s functionality, enhancing user engagement, and bolstering overall community interaction. 
Key]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>George Tebrean</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[We need to start thinking of AI as “normal”]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1115928</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/04/29/1115928/is-ai-normal/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Right now, despite its ubiquity, AI is seen as anything but a normal technology. There is talk of AI systems that will soon merit the term “superintelligence,” and the former CEO of Google recently suggested we control AI models the way we control uranium and other nuclear weapons materials. Anthropic is dedicating time and money…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>James O'Donnell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[My sourdough starter has twins]]></title>
        <id>https://brainbaking.com/post/2025/04/my-sourdough-starter-has-twins/</id>
        <link href="https://brainbaking.com/post/2025/04/my-sourdough-starter-has-twins/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T08:20:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Alibaba launches open source Qwen3 model that surpasses OpenAI o1 and DeepSeek R1]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3005880</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/alibaba-launches-open-source-qwen3-model-that-surpasses-openai-o1-and-deepseek-r1/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-28T23:56:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Qwen3’s open-weight release under an accessible license marks an important milestone, lowering barriers for developers and organizations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carl Franzen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[I use zip bombs to protect my server]]></title>
        <id>https://idiallo.com/blog/zipbomb-protection</id>
        <link href="https://idiallo.com/blog/zipbomb-protection"/>
        <updated>2025-04-28T22:28:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ex-OpenAI CEO and power users sound alarm over AI sycophancy and flattery of users]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3005850</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/ex-openai-ceo-and-power-users-sound-alarm-over-ai-sycophancy-and-flattery-of-users/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-28T21:49:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crucially, the turbulence also nudges many organizations to explore open-source models they can host, monitor, and fine-tune themselves.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carl Franzen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Beyond A2A and MCP: How LOKA’s Universal Agent Identity Layer changes the game]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3005824</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/beyond-a2a-and-mcp-how-lokas-universal-agent-identity-layer-changes-the-game/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-28T20:35:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The LOKA protocol, a proposed standard for AI agents from Carnegie Mellon University researchers, will give identities and intentions to agents.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Emilia David</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build a Production-Ready DevOps Pipeline with Free Tools]]></title>
        <id>680fe1e69418a1165cb184a2</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-build-a-production-ready-devops-pipeline-with-free-tools/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-28T20:15:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A few months ago, I dove into DevOps, expecting it to be an expensive journey requiring costly tools and infrastructure. But I discovered you can build professional-grade pipelines using entirely free resources. If DevOps feels out of reach because y...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Opaluwa Emidowojo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[30 seconds vs. 3: The d1 reasoning framework that’s slashing AI response times]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3005393</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/30-seconds-vs-3-the-d1-reasoning-framework-thats-slashing-ai-response-times/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-28T19:31:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[d1 framework changes boosts diffusion LLMs with novel reinforcement learning, unlocking efficient, problem-solving AI possibilities.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ben Dickson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build a Website from Scratch – Start to Finish Walkthrough]]></title>
        <id>680fd51ef631538076304a73</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-build-a-website-from-scratch-start-to-finish-walkthrough/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-28T19:21:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, fellow developers! Building a website can feel overwhelming at first – especially when you're staring at a blank HTML file, wondering how it ever turns into a real website on the internet. If you're new to web development, you've probably asked y...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kunal Nalawade</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Writer releases Palmyra X5, delivers near GPT-4.1 performance at 75% lower cost]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3005734</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/writer-releases-palmyra-x5-delivers-near-gpt-4-performance-at-75-lower-cost/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-28T17:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Writer unveils Palmyra X5: The enterprise AI model that processes 1,500 pages at once, costs 75% less than GPT-4, and enables affordable autonomous agents for businesses seeking automation ROI.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Nuñez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[QuickNode: Building the Infrastructure for the Next Generation of Blockchain]]></title>
        <id>6807d5787fb8500001c39b99</id>
        <link href="https://blog.quicknode.com/quicknode-building-the-infrastructure-for-the-next-generation-of-blockchain/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-28T16:02:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Join QuickNode co-founder Dmitry Shklovsky as he discusses blockchain infrastructure, building decentralized applications, and the future of Web3 development on TheCube's Crypto Trailblazer Series.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>QuickNode</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Enable CORS in Django]]></title>
        <id>680fa40e9096ceb5eeedd90e</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-enable-cors-in-django/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-28T15:51:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you've ever tried to connect your frontend app to your Django backend and suddenly hit an error that looks something like "has been blocked by CORS policy", you're not alone. It’s frustrating, especially when your code seems fine. So what’s going ...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Udemezue John</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Turn Ubuntu 24.04 into a KVM Hypervisor – Quick Setup with Web Management]]></title>
        <id>680fa285102a9fb019d4fa34</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/turn-ubuntu-2404-into-a-kvm-hypervisor/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-28T15:45:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Virtualization lets you run multiple operating systems on one machine. It’s perfect for testing apps, hosting servers, or learning DevOps. A hypervisor is the software that lets you run multiple virtual machines on a single physical machine, and the ...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shamsuddoha Ranju</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Automate Mobile Testing: Strategies for Reliable, Scalable Tests]]></title>
        <id>680fa2440e43e5b002c3c7f4</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-automate-mobile-testing-strategies/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-28T15:44:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mobile test automation uses tools and frameworks to test mobile applications automatically. It replicates user interactions to evaluate the app's functions and detect possible issues early on. This automated approach is helpful since it accelerates t...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nazneen Ahmad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Download: China’s manufacturers’ viral moment, and how AI is changing creativity]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1115909</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/04/28/1115909/the-download-chinas-manufacturers-viral-moment-and-how-ai-is-changing-creativity/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-28T12:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is today’s edition of The Download, our weekday newsletter that provides a daily dose of what’s going on in the world of technology. Why Chinese manufacturers are going viral on TikTok Since the video was posted earlier this month, millions of TikTok users have watched as a young Chinese man in a blue T-shirt sits beside…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rhiannon Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Does RAG make LLMs less safe?  Bloomberg research reveals hidden dangers]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3005592</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/does-rag-make-llms-less-safe-bloomberg-research-reveals-hidden-dangers/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-28T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[RAG is supposed to make enterprise AI more accurate, but it could potentially also make it less safe according to new research.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sean Michael Kerner</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Chinese manufacturers are going viral on TikTok]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1115876</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/04/28/1115876/why-chinese-manufacturers-are-going-viral-on-tiktok/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-28T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Since the video was posted earlier this month, millions of TikTok users have watched as a young Chinese man in a blue T-shirt sits beside a traditional tea set and speaks directly to the camera in accented English: “Let’s expose luxury’s biggest secret.”  He stands and lifts what looks like an Hermès Birkin bag, one…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Caiwei Chen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[UPDATED] Malaysia and Maldives explore new ties in solar, defence, and digital tech [WATCH]]]></title>
        <id>2ff00997f9c35cff9b55bf1c234d9fd9</id>
        <link href="https://www.nst.com.my/news/nation/2025/04/1208426/updated-malaysia-and-maldives-explore-new-ties-solar-defence-and-digital"/>
        <updated>2025-04-28T04:17:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[PUTRAJAYA: Malaysia is eager to explore new avenues of cooperation with the Maldives, including floating solar energy, defence, and digital technology, says Datuk Seri Anwar Ibrahim.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hakim Mahari</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Retail & E-Commerce Innovation Marketing & Tech Summit: Malaysia 2025]]></title>
        <id>cd2a0d19be53d9723fc0475f09d0da2d</id>
        <link href="https://marketech-apac.com/conference/retail-e-commerce-innovation-marketing-tech-summit-malaysia-2025/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-28T01:58:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Retail & E-Commerce Innovation Marketing & Tech Summit: Malaysia 2025]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Zyra Kate Capilastique</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Is your AI product actually working? How to develop the right metric system]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3005642</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/is-your-ai-product-actually-working-how-to-develop-the-right-metric-system/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-27T19:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Metrics are critical for determining AI product performance. But where to begin? Here's a framework to apply across various use cases.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sharanya Rao, Intuit</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bits + Bytes: A Miscellany Of Technology]]></title>
        <id>92c9e6ae0de9449f2a2cd9808d52c95a</id>
        <link href="https://theedgemalaysia.com/node/752832"/>
        <updated>2025-04-27T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[NEWS

Malaysia sees tech salary surge in 2025, led by system engineers

Tech salaries in Malaysia have risen significantly this year, with system engineers recording the highest increase at 8%, according to NodeFlair’s Tech Salary Report 2...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Edge Malaysia</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FORKLIFTACTION, B2B news service and business platform about forklifts and materials handling]]></title>
        <id>20065c212264065b824a3328d06be4fc</id>
        <link href="https://www.forkliftaction.com/pagenotfound.aspx"/>
        <updated>2025-04-27T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[FORKLIFTACTION, B2B news service and business platform about forklifts and materials handling]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Forkliftaction</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DeepSeek’s success shows why motivation is key to AI innovation]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3005636</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/deepseeks-success-shows-why-motivation-is-key-to-ai-innovation/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-26T19:55:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How did DeepSeek attain such cost-savings while American companies could not? Let's dive into the technical details.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Debasish Ray Chawdhuri, Talentica Software</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The True Size Of]]></title>
        <id>https://thetruesize.com/</id>
        <link href="https://thetruesize.com/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-26T15:41:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Malaysia remains 9th largest global exporter of high-tech products]]></title>
        <id>ec83e12fc9489689eba3a736f7c0fd4e</id>
        <link href="https://e.vnexpress.net/news/tech/tech-news/malaysia-remains-9th-largest-global-exporter-of-high-tech-products-4878750.html"/>
        <updated>2025-04-26T02:41:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Malaysia successfully maintained its position as the ninth-largest exporter of high-tech goods out of 143 economies in 2023, the highest recognition it has achieved in the past decade, Bernama has reported.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>VnExpress</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Liquid AI is revolutionizing LLMs to work on edge devices like smartphones with new ‘Hyena Edge’ model]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3005611</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/liquid-ai-is-revolutionizing-llms-to-work-on-edge-devices-like-smartphones-with-new-hyena-edge-model/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-25T22:02:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hyena Edge’s success positions Liquid AI as one of the emerging players to watch in the evolving AI model landscape.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carl Franzen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The new AI calculus: Google’s 80% cost edge vs. OpenAI’s ecosystem]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3005571</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/the-new-ai-calculus-googles-80-cost-edge-vs-openais-ecosystem/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-25T20:26:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Explore the Google vs OpenAI AI ecosystem battle post-o3. Deep dive into Google's huge cost advantage (TPU vs GPU), agent strategies & model risks for enterprise]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matt Marshall</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Malaysia remains 9th largest global exporter of high-tech products]]></title>
        <id>e1054193ac5220fd5f3cf3fb0ac3fcbd</id>
        <link href="https://en.vietnamplus.vn/malaysia-remains-9th-largest-global-exporter-of-high-tech-products-post318075.vnp"/>
        <updated>2025-04-25T18:11:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Malaysia’s high-tech exports increased by 2 billion USD to reach 127 billion USD in 2023. He said high-tech exports comprised 58.69% of total manufacturing exports in 2023, up from 52.48% recorded in 2022.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Vietnam+ (VietnamPlus)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[UK agrees to assist Malaysia in technology, new energy]]></title>
        <id>9bba1ab03b6cc59e6474a313d3bc9d9c</id>
        <link href="https://theedgemalaysia.com/node/753068"/>
        <updated>2025-04-25T15:31:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The UK has agreed to collaborate with Malaysia in various fields, including technology and new energy management, said Deputy Prime Minister Datuk Seri Fadillah Yusof.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Edge Malaysia</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Download: how Trump’s tariffs will affect US manufacturing, and AI architecture]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1115868</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/04/25/1115868/the-download-how-trumps-tariffs-will-affect-us-manufacturing-and-ai-architecture/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-25T12:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is today’s edition of The Download, our weekday newsletter that provides a daily dose of what’s going on in the world of technology. Sweeping tariffs could threaten the US manufacturing rebound Despite the geopolitical chaos and market collapses triggered by President Trump’s announcement of broad tariffs on international goods, some supporters still hope the strategy will…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rhiannon Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Need to embrace technological advancements, sustainable practices discussed at country's premier real estate event]]></title>
        <id>13ba8e804fd9567fa951b4f7cc51bead</id>
        <link href="https://theedgemalaysia.com/node/753073"/>
        <updated>2025-04-25T12:00:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Industry leaders, policymakers, investors and experts explored the future of Malaysia's real estate landscape at the National Real Estate Convention (NREC) 2025 held here recently.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Edge Malaysia</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sweeping tariffs could threaten the US manufacturing rebound]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1115827</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/04/25/1115827/sweeping-tariffs-could-threaten-the-us-manufacturing-rebound/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-25T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Despite the geopolitical chaos and market collapses triggered by President Trump’s announcement of broad tariffs on international goods, some supporters still hope the strategy will produce a “golden age” of American industry. Trump himself insists, “Jobs and factories will come roaring back into our country.” While it’s possible that very targeted tariffs could help protect…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Rotman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Is that really your boss calling? Jericho Security raises $15M to stop deepfake fraud that’s cost businesses $200M in 2025 alone]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3005473</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/is-that-really-your-boss-calling-jericho-security-raises-15m-to-stop-deepfake-fraud-thats-cost-businesses-200m-in-2025-alone/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-24T22:18:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Pentagon-backed Jericho Security raises $15 million to combat deepfake fraud that has already cost North American businesses $200 million in 2025, using AI to detect increasingly convincing voice and video impersonations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Nuñez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Intel’s new CEO signals streamlining efforts but does not spell out exact layoff numbers]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3005456</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/games/intels-new-ceo-signals-streamlining-efforts-but-does-not-spell-out-exact-layoff-numbers/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-24T21:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Lip-Bu Tan, the new CEO of Intel, sent out a blunt message to employees saying the company has to reorganize to be more efficient.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dean Takahashi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Zencoder buys Machinet to challenge GitHub Copilot as AI coding assistant consolidation accelerates]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3005445</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/zencoder-buys-machinet-to-challenge-github-copilot-as-ai-coding-assistant-consolidation-accelerates/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-24T20:36:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Zencoder acquires Machinet to strengthen its position in the rapidly consolidating AI coding assistant market, expanding its JetBrains ecosystem integration while outperforming competitors like GitHub Copilot with innovative features such as Repo Grokking and Coffee Mode.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Nuñez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethically trained AI startup Pleias releases new small reasoning models optimized for RAG with built-in citations]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3005435</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/ethically-trained-ai-startup-pleias-releases-new-small-reasoning-models-optimized-for-rag-with-built-in-citations/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-24T17:03:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Pleias emphasizes the models’ suitability for integration into search-augmented assistants, educational tools, and user support systems.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carl Franzen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Evil Geniuses and Theta Labs launch AI chatbot based on esports mascot Meesh]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3005327</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/games/evil-geniuses-and-theta-labs-launch-ai-chatbot-based-on-esports-mascot-meesh/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-24T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Evil Geniuses, the well-known esports organization and brand, has launched its Meesh AI chatbot in a partnership with Theta Labs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dean Takahashi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Driving business value by optimizing the cloud]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1115716</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/04/24/1115716/driving-business-value-by-optimizing-the-cloud/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-24T13:56:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Organizations are deepening their cloud investments at an unprecedented pace, recognizing its fundamental role in driving business agility and innovation. Synergy Research Group reports that companies spent $84 billion worldwide on cloud infrastructure services in the third quarter of 2024, a 23% rise over the third quarter of 2023 and the fourth consecutive quarter in…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>MIT Technology Review Insights</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google adds more AI tools to its Workspace productivity apps]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3005313</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/google-adds-more-ai-tools-to-its-workspace-productivity-apps/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-23T22:43:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google expanded Gemini's features, adding the popular podcast-style feature Audio Overviews to the platform.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Emilia David</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Former DeepSeeker and collaborators release new method for training reliable AI agents: RAGEN]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3005302</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/former-deepseeker-and-collaborators-release-new-method-for-training-reliable-ai-agents-ragen/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-23T20:04:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[RAGEN stands out not just as a technical contribution but as a conceptual step toward more autonomous, reasoning-capable AI agents.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carl Franzen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon’s SWE-PolyBench just exposed the dirty secret about your AI coding assistant]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3005166</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/amazon-swe-polybench-just-exposed-the-dirty-secret-about-your-ai-coding-assistant/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-23T19:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon launches SWE-PolyBench, a groundbreaking multi-language benchmark that exposes critical limitations in AI coding assistants across Python, JavaScript, TypeScript, and Java while introducing new metrics beyond simple pass rates for real-world development tasks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Nuñez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OpenAI makes ChatGPT’s image generation available as API]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3005253</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/openai-makes-chatgpts-image-generation-available-as-api/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-23T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Enterprises can now make Studio Ghibli-inspired images through OpenAI's API.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Emilia David</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[From friction to flow: Why Swissport scrapped its VPN maze for Cato’s SASE platform]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3004830</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/security/from-friction-to-flow-why-swissport-scrapped-its-vpn-maze-for-catos-sase-platform/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-23T16:53:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Swissport ditches legacy tech, deploying a global SASE architecture with Cato Networks securing 26,000 users, unlocking real-time control.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Louis Columbus</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft just launched powerful AI ‘agents’ that could completely transform your workday — and challenge Google’s workplace dominance]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3005118</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/microsoft-just-launched-powerful-ai-agents-that-could-completely-transform-your-workday-and-challenge-googles-workplace-dominance/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-23T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft unveils new AI reasoning agents and Copilot features to transform workplace productivity, with Chief Product Officer Aparna Chennapragada sharing exclusive insights on the company's vision for human-agent collaboration.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Nuñez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cooperations with China continue to drive Malaysia's tech ambitions: experts]]></title>
        <id>7cf31983f27357e33a7e7403d769042c</id>
        <link href="https://english.news.cn/20250423/23952d602d384abe9a3be2f40797fa2d/c.html"/>
        <updated>2025-04-23T09:33:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cooperations with China continue to drive Malaysia's tech ambitions: experts-]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>english.news.cn</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[IBM Tech Innovation Summit]]></title>
        <id>eb7b875c351e513c2d4750bb29a0ab40</id>
        <link href="https://www.malaysiakini.com/news/741130"/>
        <updated>2025-04-23T02:44:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Seats are limited. Register now!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Malaysiakini Team</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[$42.1 million poured into startup offering energy-efficient solutions for costly and unwieldy operational data and AI workloads]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3005163</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/data-infrastructure/42-1-million-poured-into-startup-offering-energy-efficient-solutions-for-costly-and-unwieldy-operational-data-and-ai-workloads/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-23T02:28:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The funding infusion sharpens a mission to make hyperscale analytics radically cheaper and greener at the very moment enterprises fear ballooning data‑center power bills.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ujas Patel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Alabama’s Pursell Agri-Tech teams with Wastech on fertilizer venture in Malaysia]]></title>
        <id>af0a46cec4f3cf8c521e3bd5a58cb6d6</id>
        <link href="https://www.madeinalabama.com/2025/04/alabamas-pursell-agri-tech-teams-with-wastech-on-fertilizer-venture-in-malaysia/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-21T18:21:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Pursell and Wastech Group are establishing a state-of-the-art facility in Malaysia to producte advanced controlled release fertilizers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jerry Underwood</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>