<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2025-05-14T16:17:22.831Z</id>
    <title>AngJianming RSS Feed</title>
    <updated>2025-05-14T16:17:22.831Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Track LLM User Feedback to Improve Your AI Applications]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/lina_lam_9ee459f98b67e9d5/how-to-track-llm-user-feedback-to-improve-your-ai-applications-1a08</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/lina_lam_9ee459f98b67e9d5/how-to-track-llm-user-feedback-to-improve-your-ai-applications-1a08"/>
        <updated>2025-05-14T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In today's AI-driven landscape, learning how to effectively track LLM user feedback is crucial for improving performance and driving higher user satisfaction. 
Every user interaction provides valuable insights that can help you refine your AI's responses to better serve your customers' needs.

In this article, we will show you how to use LLM feedback tracking tools like Helicone to collect, analyze, and implement user feedback for continuous improvement of your AI applications.
Why is Tracking User Feedback Critical for LLM Applications?
The Feedback Collection Framework
Turning User Feedback into Training Datasets
Implementation Best Practices
Useful Resources
Creating a continuous user feedback loop is essential for any successful software application. This applies to LLM applications as…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lina Lam</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Internship Completed]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/ritesh_thakur_4a4301a95a1/internship-completed-257g</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/ritesh_thakur_4a4301a95a1/internship-completed-257g"/>
        <updated>2025-05-14T15:58:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[✅ Excited to share that I’ve successfully completed One month my virtual internship with Uber, in collaboration with MentorMind and Tangible!
During this experience, I worked on predicting ride fare amounts using regression analysis, a valuable hands-on opportunity to apply machine learning techniques to real-world data.
A heartfelt thank you to Alok Khatri Sir for the constant guidance and motivation throughout the journey. Huge thanks to MentorMind and Tangible for creating such a well-structured and impactful program.
This experience has truly boosted my confidence in data science and analytics.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ritesh Thakur</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Optimizing Lambda Performance with AWS Lambda Power Tuning]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/marciojc/optimizing-lambda-performance-with-aws-lambda-power-tuning-2m2o</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/marciojc/optimizing-lambda-performance-with-aws-lambda-power-tuning-2m2o"/>
        <updated>2025-05-14T15:55:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Lambda Power Tuning is a solution provided by AWS that uses Step Functions to test your Lambda function across different memory configurations, helping you determine the optimal power setting for best cost/performance ratio.
Here’s how it works:
A Step Function runs your Lambda with different memory sizes (128MB → 10GB).
It collects duration, cost, and performance metrics.
You get a visual report to decide the best setting.
AWS CLI configured


AWS SAM CLI installed


Node.js Lambda function ready


Deploy the Lambda Power Tuning Step Function




  
  
  🧪 Step 1: Deploy Lambda Power Tuning


Clone and deploy using the AWS Serverless Application Repository or SAM:
git clone https://github.com/alexcasalboni/aws-lambda-power-tuning.git
cd aws-lambda-power-tuning
sam deploy --guided

After deploy, take note of the Step Function ARN (e.g. arn:aws:states:us-east-1:123456789012:stateMachine:PowerTuningStateMachine)
Use the AWS Console or invoke the Step Function programmatically:
{
  "lambdaARN": "arn:aws:lambda:us-east-1:123456789012:function:MyFunction",
  "powerValues": [128, 256, 512, 1024, 2048],
  "num": 10,
  "payload": "{}",
  "parallelInvocation": true,
  "strategy": "cost"
}

Replace with your actual Lambda ARN.
You can start the state machine using AWS Console or CLI:
aws stepfunctions start-execution \
  --state-machine-arn arn:aws:states:us-east-1:123456789012:stateMachine:PowerTuningStateMachine \
  --input file://input.json

Once completed, the Step Function execution will provide:
Cost vs performance graphs


Recommendations for optimal memory setting


JSON result with metrics



You’ll be able to visually compare:
Execution time


Memory size


Cost (ms × GB × price)



💡 Bonus Tip: Tune for Strategy
Lambda Power Tuning supports different strategies:
cost – minimize price
speed – minimize duration
balanced – tradeoff
balanced-v2 – improved balanced strategy
Try different strategies depending on your workload.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Márcio Coelho</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin breakout to $120K on radar as markets forget Fed July rate cut]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-breakout-120k-on-radar-markets-forget-fed-july-rate-cut</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-breakout-120k-on-radar-markets-forget-fed-july-rate-cut?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-14T15:54:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Key points: 

Bitcoin continues to range around $103,000 as bulls struggle to keep upside momentum going.

Traders favor short-term BTC price gains eventually returning, while overall faith in the bull market varies.

Fed rate cuts seem increasingly far off despite encouraging inflation data.

Bitcoin (BTC) hugged familiar territory around the May 14 Wall Street open as traders awaited fresh US macro cues.
BTC/USD 1-hour chart. Source: Cointelegraph/TradingView
Trader: BTC needs $108,000 reclaim for breakout
Data from Cointelegraph Markets Pro and TradingView showed $103,000 remaining a BTC price magnet.
Bulls had managed another trip to $105,000 the day prior, with momentum nonetheless lacking after brisk gains throughout the first half of the month.
Now, traders eyed consolidation prior …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by William Suberg</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Unveiling Educational Community License 2.0: A Comprehensive Overview]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/ahmmrizv9/unveiling-educational-community-license-20-a-comprehensive-overview-1694</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/ahmmrizv9/unveiling-educational-community-license-20-a-comprehensive-overview-1694"/>
        <updated>2025-05-14T15:53:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Abstract


This post offers an in-depth exploration of the Educational Community License 2.0 (ECL 2.0). We begin with a concise overview, then discuss the background and context that led to its creation. We outline core concepts, features, and real-world use cases, and also analyze challenges, limitations, and the future outlook for open source licensing in the education ecosystem. Using clear language and technical insights, this article is designed for developers, educators, and open source enthusiasts alike. Our discussion is enhanced by tables, bullet lists, and curated external references, ensuring that both humans and search engine crawlers can easily parse and appreciate the content.
In today’s digital education era, open source licensing plays a crucial role in protecting intellect…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ahmend Riss</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Launch HN: Jazzberry (YC X25) – AI agent for finding bugs]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=43985994</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=43985994"/>
        <updated>2025-05-14T15:52:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Server That Wasn't Meant to Exist]]></title>
        <id>https://it-notes.dragas.net/2025/05/13/the_server_that_wasnt_meant_to_exist/</id>
        <link href="https://it-notes.dragas.net/2025/05/13/the_server_that_wasnt_meant_to_exist/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-14T15:50:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Descubra o Modo Agente do GitHub Copilot]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/pachicodes/descubra-o-modo-agente-do-github-copilot-54j2</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/pachicodes/descubra-o-modo-agente-do-github-copilot-54j2"/>
        <updated>2025-05-14T15:49:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Se você já usa o GitHub Copilot no dia a dia, prepare-se para conhecer o modo mais poderoso dessa ferramenta: o** modo Agente**. Ainda pouco explorado por muita gente, esse recurso é capaz de planejar tarefas, navegar por arquivos, executar comandos e editar código de forma autônoma, tudo a partir de um único prompt.
Neste post, quero te mostrar como o modo Agente funciona e como ele pode transformar sua rotina de desenvolvimento, especialmente em projetos novos ou mais complexos.
O modo Agente permite que você envie um prompt de alto nível, como por exemplo “crie uma página de login com autenticação”, e o Copilot faz o resto. Ele traça um plano, identifica os arquivos relevantes, escreve o código necessário, executa comandos no terminal e repete o ciclo até concluir a tarefa.
É normal que…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pachi 🥑</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Generating swaggers at compile time]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/lexplt/generating-swaggers-at-compile-time-1m4c</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/lexplt/generating-swaggers-at-compile-time-1m4c"/>
        <updated>2025-05-14T15:48:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At work, we've been generating code from swaggers and publishing said generated code. Alas, this requires us to remember to generate the swagger(s), as well as fixing versions of libraries (which means you need to upgrade versions in the server, publish updated generated code, then update your client), see this examples from eikek/sbt-openapi-schema:
import com.github.eikek.sbt.openapi._

val CirceVersion = "0.14.1"
libraryDependencies ++= Seq(
  "io.circe" %% "circe-generic" % CirceVersion,
  "io.circe" %% "circe-parser"  % CirceVersion
)

openapiSpec := (Compile/resourceDirectory).value/"test.yml"
openapiTargetLanguage := Language.Scala
Compile/openapiScalaConfig := ScalaConfig()
    .withJson(ScalaJson.circeSemiauto)
    .addMapping(CustomMapping.forType({ case TypeDef("LocalDateTime", …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lex Plt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['$500K Bitcoin Would Seal It': Scaramucci Says Crypto Is on the Cusp of Becoming an Asset Class]]></title>
        <id>1873ddf3-ea62-4b1f-bb78-a58ac91757b4</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/consensus-toronto-2025-coverage/2025/05/14/usd500k-bitcoin-would-seal-it-scaramucci-says-crypto-is-on-the-cusp-of-becoming-an-asset-class-for-tradfi"/>
        <updated>2025-05-14T15:46:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At Consensus 2025, top asset managers say bitcoin is close to being recognized as a full-fledged asset class — but institutional acceptance still hinges on education, infrastructure, and maturity.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Helene Braun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Monitoring & It's 4 Golden Signals 🏆]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/tohemt/monitoring-its-4-golden-signals-400</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/tohemt/monitoring-its-4-golden-signals-400"/>
        <updated>2025-05-14T15:45:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Monitoring is a critical part of SRE practices to manage and ensure systems and services reliability. 4 Golden Signals is key metrics that used to monitor the health of your service and underlying systems effectively.
Monitoring is the process of collecting, processing, aggregating, and displaying real-time quantitative data about a system.
Here are few benefits of doing monitoring:
Analyzing Long-Term Trends  📈📉



This historical data supports better technical and business decision-making.
Monitoring helps track the growth and usage patterns of applications over time. You can observe metrics like database size or daily active user count.
Alerting  🚨‼️



Monitoring enables the system to notify you when something is broken or about to break.
When the system can't self-heal, alerts help…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Theo Millard</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Alias Bash Commands in Git Bash for Windows?]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/generatecodedev/how-to-alias-bash-commands-in-git-bash-for-windows-11mi</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/generatecodedev/how-to-alias-bash-commands-in-git-bash-for-windows-11mi"/>
        <updated>2025-05-14T15:45:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction
If you're using Git Bash on Windows and want to create more efficient command line experiences, one of the most useful features you can take advantage of is the ability to alias commands. Aliasing allows you to create shortcuts for longer command sequences, making your workflow smoother. This article will guide you through the process of aliasing Bash commands specifically within Git Bash, focusing on your needs on Windows 7.
Understanding Aliases in Bash
Aliases in Bash are essentially shortcuts you set to run a command or a group of commands quickly. For instance, if you find yourself frequently typing ls -l, you can create an alias called ll that executes this command on your behalf. Understanding how to correctly set up these aliases is important for maximizing your produc…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Generatecode</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New York Finance Watchdog Harris Says State's BitLicense Is Still a Global Standard]]></title>
        <id>6b896256-a3dc-4e21-9739-f74cd8c0c925</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/consensus-toronto-2025-coverage/2025/05/14/new-york-finance-watchdog-harris-says-state-s-bitlicense-is-still-a-global-standard"/>
        <updated>2025-05-14T15:44:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Adrienne Harris, superintendent of the New York Department of Financial Services, said her state's crypto licensing regime is tough, but effective.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jesse Hamilton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[I Built a VS Code Extension to Instantly Highlight TODOs and Custom Tags — No More Missed Comments]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/samiran_rai_7a0e7184d8958/i-built-a-vs-code-extension-to-instantly-highlight-todos-and-custom-tags-no-more-missed-comments-26el</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/samiran_rai_7a0e7184d8958/i-built-a-vs-code-extension-to-instantly-highlight-todos-and-custom-tags-no-more-missed-comments-26el"/>
        <updated>2025-05-14T15:41:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Problem:


We all write TODOs, FIXMEs, or // BUG comments — and we all forget them. Buried in files. Out of sight, out of mind.
I created Glyph Tool — a dead-simple VS Code extension to:
Auto-highlight task comments (even custom ones)

Show them in a sidebar (like a to-do list)

Let you mark done, delete, or filter
No config needed — works instantly
Custom tags & colors
Fully compatible with light/dark themes
Support all languages
🔗 Install it Free on VS Code Marketplace

🚀 Stop losing track. Stay focused. Let Glyph do the remembering.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Samiran Rai</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Uber to introduce fixed-route shuttles in major US cities designed for commuters]]></title>
        <id>https://techcrunch.com/2025/05/14/uber-to-introduce-fixed-route-shuttles-in-major-us-cities-other-ways-to-save/</id>
        <link href="https://techcrunch.com/2025/05/14/uber-to-introduce-fixed-route-shuttles-in-major-us-cities-other-ways-to-save/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-14T15:40:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Class Free Object Oriented JS]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/kooiinc/class-free-object-oriented-js-174l</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/kooiinc/class-free-object-oriented-js-174l"/>
        <updated>2025-05-14T15:39:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An example of Class Free Object Oriented (CFOO) JS-code.


The last years my JS contains almost exclusively CFOO (actually the revealing module pattern). It's a very elegant and relative simple and robust way to create 'constructors' without the need for this or class syntax (aka class sugar). I'd like to share the idea here.
Constructors are created using factory functions, which return frozen objects. Factory functions may include ('inherit') other factory instances. Variable privacy is guaranteed via closures.
The basic pattern is (note: variables/types are not checked here)
const helloWorld = myConstructorFactory(myOtherConstructorFactory());
const universe = helloWorld("universe");

console.log(String(universe));
// 'hello world'
console.log(String(universe.setWorld("universe")));
// 'hello universe'
console.log(String(universe.setHello("Hi")));
// 'Hi universe'
console.log(universe.name);
// 'universe'

universe.name = "nothing"; 
// TypeError: Cannot set property name of [object Object] 
// which has only a getter
universe.instanceName = "nothing";
// TypeError: Cannot add property instanceName, object is not extensible

function myConstructorFactory(inherits) {
  let {hello, world} = inherits;

  return function(instanceName) {
      const instance = {
      get name() { return instanceName; },
      toString() {return hello + " " + world; },
      setWorld(value) { world = value; return instance; },
      setHello(value) { hello = value; return instance; }
    };

    return Object.freeze(instance);
  }
}

function myOtherConstructorFactory(hi, wrld) {
  return Object.freeze( {
    hello: hi || "hello", 
    world: wrld || "world" } );
}

I created a simple, but more complete example @ stackblitz. Feel free to tinker with it.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>KooiInc</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Memecoins worth investing in 2025]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/merehead2015/memecoins-worth-investing-in-in-2025-4c80</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/merehead2015/memecoins-worth-investing-in-in-2025-4c80"/>
        <updated>2025-05-14T15:39:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Currently, you can consider buying digital assets - memecoins. They combine a trend in pop culture and cryptocurrency. The investment tool was created as a reflection of the reaction to some aspects of life and did not have much value. I want to draw your attention to the fact that this is not investment advice and you yourself bear the risks for your actions. In addition, trading memecoins has a high risk and it is best to trade cryptocurrency for beginners that is less volatile and is in the TOP 10 by capitalization.
Recently, more and more people are starting to take this crypto seriously and are considering it for their investments. They will not be as popular as Bitcoin or Ethereum, but they can become part of an investment portfolio. Therefore, it is worth considering the more popula…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yuri Musienko</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Unveiling the Common Public License 1.0: A Deep Dive into Open Source Fair Code Licensing]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/jennythomas498/unveiling-the-common-public-license-10-a-deep-dive-into-open-source-fair-code-licensing-2mil</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/jennythomas498/unveiling-the-common-public-license-10-a-deep-dive-into-open-source-fair-code-licensing-2mil"/>
        <updated>2025-05-14T15:37:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Abstract:

This post explores the Common Public License 1.0 summary in depth. We examine its history, core concepts, and features while detailing its applications, challenges, and future outlook in the open source licensing ecosystem. By integrating comparisons with other licenses and industry insights, this article offers a holistic view of how the CPL balances legal clarity with developer fairness. Links to authoritative resources such as license-token.com, the Open Source Initiative, and discussions on Hacker News support our detailed analysis.
Open source licensing is at the core of collaborative software development. A key player in this landscape is the Common Public License 1.0 (CPL). This license aims to strike a balance between safeguarding the rights of developers and enabling vi…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>JennyThomas498</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Stablecoins Bring 'Meaningful Innovation for Global Payments,' Ripple Exec Says]]></title>
        <id>b9746d1f-f84e-4231-8af8-d89c1eb4f285</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2025/05/14/stablecoins-bring-meaningful-innovation-for-global-payments-ripple-exec-says"/>
        <updated>2025-05-14T15:33:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ripple and Kraken executives said at Consensus 2025 that stablecoin adoption is at a tipping point to become an integral part of the global payment system.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Krisztian Sandor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CFTC Commissioner will step down to become Blockchain Association CEO]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/cftc-commissioner-summer-mersinger-blockchain-association</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/cftc-commissioner-summer-mersinger-blockchain-association?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-14T15:19:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Summer Mersinger, one of four commissioners currently serving at the US financial regulatory body Commodity Futures Trading Commission (CFTC), will become the next CEO of the digital asset advocacy group the Blockchain Association (BA). 
In a May 14 notice, the Blockchain Association said its current CEO, Kristin Smith, would be stepping down for Mersinger on May 16, allowing an interim head of the group to work until the CFTC commissioner assumes the role on June 2. Though her term at the CFTC was expected to last until April 2028, the BA said Mersinger is set to leave the agency on May 30.
The departure of Mersinger, who has served in one of the CFTC’s Republican seats since 2022, opens the way for President Donald Trump to nominate another member to the financial regulator. Rules requir…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Turner Wright</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Show HN: Lumier – Run macOS VMs in a Docker]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/trycua/cua/tree/main/libs/lumier</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/trycua/cua/tree/main/libs/lumier"/>
        <updated>2025-05-14T15:19:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Show HN: CSV GB+ by Data.olllo – Open and Process CSVs Locally]]></title>
        <id>https://apps.microsoft.com/detail/9pfcrwp46v22?hl=en-US&amp;gl=US</id>
        <link href="https://apps.microsoft.com/detail/9pfcrwp46v22?hl=en-US&amp;gl=US"/>
        <updated>2025-05-14T15:12:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AlphaEvolve: A Gemini-powered coding agent for designing advanced algorithms]]></title>
        <id>https://deepmind.google/discover/blog/alphaevolve-a-gemini-powered-coding-agent-for-designing-advanced-algorithms/</id>
        <link href="https://deepmind.google/discover/blog/alphaevolve-a-gemini-powered-coding-agent-for-designing-advanced-algorithms/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-14T15:10:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cardano (ADA) Surges 22% in One Week After Brave Browser Boosts User Exposure]]></title>
        <id>ed438ba7-7ef3-404a-b6ae-95ec8fc7c1f5</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/14/cardano-ada-surges-22-in-one-week-after-brave-browser-boosts-user-exposure"/>
        <updated>2025-05-14T15:06:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cardano's integration with Brave browser exposes it to 86 million potential new users amid institutional accumulation.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>AI Boost</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lyft Taps Solana’s Hivemapper for Real-Time, Crowdsourced Mapping Upgrade]]></title>
        <id>1bbb7506-4128-4f0f-8e9f-dc87c86e7f35</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/tech/2025/05/14/lyft-taps-solanas-bee-maps-for-real-time-crowdsourced-mapping-upgrade"/>
        <updated>2025-05-14T15:00:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The move underscores the growing role of crowdsourced geospatial intelligence in the transportation industry.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Margaux Nijkerk</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Pre-Consensus Lift Amidst Lingering Recession Whispers]]></title>
        <id>5b4a4a8e-5de3-46d2-9aa9-7f130ffc1178</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/coindesk-indices/2025/05/14/a-pre-consensus-lift-amidst-lingering-recession-whispers"/>
        <updated>2025-05-14T15:00:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Following weeks of turbulence, a shift in sentiment sparked a notable crypto rally coinciding with CoinDesk's Consensus conference in Toronto, creating an atmosphere of optimism and good vibes, says CoinDesk Indices’ Andy Baehr.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andy Baehr</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google DeepMind’s new AI agent uses large language models to crack real-world problems]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1116438</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/05/14/1116438/google-deepminds-new-ai-uses-large-language-models-to-crack-real-world-problems/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-14T15:00:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google DeepMind has once again used large language models to discover new solutions to long-standing problems in math and computer science. This time the firm has shown that its approach can not only tackle unsolved theoretical puzzles, but improve a range of important real-world processes as well. Google DeepMind’s new tool, called AlphaEvolve, uses the…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Will Douglas Heaven</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meet AlphaEvolve, the Google AI that writes its own code—and just saved millions in computing costs]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3007538</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/meet-alphaevolve-the-google-ai-that-writes-its-own-code-and-just-saved-millions-in-computing-costs/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-14T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google DeepMind's AlphaEvolve AI system breaks a 56-year-old mathematical record by discovering a more efficient matrix multiplication algorithm that had eluded human mathematicians since Strassen's 1969 breakthrough.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Nuñez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chainproof Combats Ethereum ‘Slashing’ Losses With Guaranteed Yearly Yields]]></title>
        <id>03f9ba1b-92cc-4a4e-a747-82a39ce9af0b</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/14/chainproof-combats-ethereum-slashing-losses-with-guaranteed-yearly-yields"/>
        <updated>2025-05-14T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Slashing, while rare, is a big concern for Ethereum stakers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tim Craig</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The facet of TradFi most ripe for disruption is equities]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/trad-fi-equities-defi</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/trad-fi-equities-defi?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-14T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Opinion by: Mike Cahill, co-founder and CEO of Douro Labs
Despite the institutional frenzy around crypto and the ubiquitous narrative of democratized access to investing, most of the world population is still barred from traditional wealth-building. 
Take the US, for example — here, the top 10% of earners own more than 90% of all stocks. On a global scale, it gets even worse: Billions of individuals don’t have the financial literacy, digital tools or minimum funds required to even access the most basic investment opportunities. 
Traditional institutions must do more than just invest in crypto to ameliorate this disparity — they must start employing digital assets for new use cases altogether. 
The facet of TradFi that is most ripe for disruption is equities. Investing in shares of private …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Mike Cahill</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Proven Bitcoin Momentum Indicator Flashes Green, Supporting Analyst $140K-$200K Price Predictions]]></title>
        <id>4f686803-9365-46c3-ba52-e1f8289feff4</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/14/proven-bitcoin-momentum-indicator-flashes-green-supporting-analysts-usd140k-usd200k-price-predictions"/>
        <updated>2025-05-14T14:55:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A positive flip in the indicator has preceded every major rally since 2020.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Omkar Godbole</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Thai Government to Issue $150M Worth of Digital Investment Tokens]]></title>
        <id>6c0121ce-57c8-4ee1-bf21-8329418e45c0</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2025/05/14/thai-government-to-issue-150m-worth-of-digital-investment-tokens"/>
        <updated>2025-05-14T14:44:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The initial 5 billion baht offering is meant to "test the market," Finance Minister Pichai Chunhavajira said Tuesday at a briefing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Camomile Shumba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Telegram Cracks Down on Suspected $8B Chinese Crypto Crime Marketplace Set Up in Colorado]]></title>
        <id>8a41fd02-c678-420f-8265-a311c3b33f83</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2025/05/14/telegram-cracks-down-on-suspected-8b-chinese-crypto-crime-marketplace-set-up-in-colorado"/>
        <updated>2025-05-14T14:32:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Illicit marketplaces are a key part of the growing global cyberscams industry, with Southeast Asia being among the hubs for such activity.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tim Craig</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[French minister to meet crypto firms after kidnapping attempt]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/france-crypto-security-talks-kidnap-paymium</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/france-crypto-security-talks-kidnap-paymium?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-14T14:28:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The French interior minister reportedly plans to meet cryptocurrency professionals in the aftermath of a violent kidnapping attempt on the family of a crypto exchange executive in Paris.
According to a May 14 France24 report, Interior Minister Bruno Retailleau has invited crypto professionals to meet him after a brazen attempt to kidnap the daughter and grandson of Pierre Noizat, the co-founder and CEO of French crypto exchange Paymium.
”I will assemble businesspeople working in cryptocurrencies, and we have a few of those in France, at the interior ministry to work with them on their security,” Retailleau reportedly told the Europe 1/CNews broadcaster.
On May 13, three masked men attacked Noizat’s daughter while she was walking in Paris’ 11th district with a man and her son. The attackers…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Adrian Zmudzinski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Solana (SOL) Surges 5% on Heavy Volume and Strengthening DeFi Metrics]]></title>
        <id>d066be9c-1fa6-4dd8-9baf-6b32552f1e70</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/14/solana-sol-surges-5-on-heavy-volume-and-strengthening-defi-metrics"/>
        <updated>2025-05-14T14:26:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Institutional investors appear to be flocking to SOL as DeFi metrics show remarkable growth, creating a strong technical foundation for further gains.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>AI Boost</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JPMorgan’s Kinexys Connects With Public Blockchain on Ondo Chain Testnet Debut]]></title>
        <id>0ce5d7ae-f003-4f3b-bc8e-13e401654c24</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2025/05/14/jpmorgans-kinexys-connects-with-public-blockchain-on-ondo-chain-testnet-debut"/>
        <updated>2025-05-14T14:14:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The testnet deal links JPMorgan’s Kinexys payments network to Ondo Chain using Chainlink’s cross-chain tech]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Francisco Rodrigues</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CFTC Commissioner Mersinger to Be CEO at Blockchain Association]]></title>
        <id>4031bbc6-1fd0-4680-bf38-eddffc98d9a9</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2025/05/14/cftc-commissioner-mersinger-to-be-ceo-at-blockchain-association"/>
        <updated>2025-05-14T14:03:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Republican commissioner at the U.S. commodities regulator will be jumping into the industry just as major pieces of crypto legislation are brewing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jesse Hamilton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[QuickLee V2: An Improved Transparent Look into RPC Provider Latency]]></title>
        <id>680fc8e1f8ae810001969b47</id>
        <link href="https://blog.quicknode.com/quicklee-v2/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-14T13:57:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[View public and real-time dashboards to better understand latency and speed when evaluating RPC providers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>QuickNode</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Here’s what happened in crypto today]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/what-happened-in-crypto-today</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/what-happened-in-crypto-today?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-14T13:57:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today in crypto, banking giant UBS says its high-net-worth clients in Asia are pivoting from US dollar assets toward gold, crypto and Chinese markets, Twenty One Capital received a $458.7 million worth of Bitcoin injection from Tether, and VanEck is launching its first tokenized fund backed by US Treasurys.
Asia’s wealthy shifting from US dollar to crypto, gold, China: UBS
High-net-worth clients across Asia are gradually pivoting away from US dollar-based investments, favoring gold, cryptocurrencies and Chinese assets instead, according to financial services giant UBS Group.
“Gold is getting very popular,” Amy Lo, the Swiss bank’s co-head of wealth management for Asia, said during Bloomberg’s New Voices event held in Hong Kong on May 13.
She cited rising geopolitical uncertainty and persis…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Cointelegraph</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TRON's TRX Surges 5% as It Overtakes Ethereum in USDT Circulation]]></title>
        <id>fb2e668a-4ebd-447a-b436-bdfe0c5b5c75</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/14/tron-s-trx-surges-5-as-it-overtakes-ethereum-in-usdt-circulation"/>
        <updated>2025-05-14T13:49:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bullish momentum continues as TRON achieves significant milestone in the stablecoin ecosystem while benefiting from easing global trade tensions.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>AI Boost</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum retakes 10% market share, but ETH bulls shouldn&#039;t celebrate yet]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/ethereum-retakes-10-market-share-eth-bulls-shouldnt-celebrate</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/ethereum-retakes-10-market-share-eth-bulls-shouldnt-celebrate?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-14T13:38:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Key takeaways:

Ethereum’s market dominance has hit overbought RSI levels not seen since May 2021, historically followed by major pullbacks.

ETH/USD is showing a bearish divergence on the four-hour chart, hinting at a potential 10–15% price correction.

Despite the near-term risks, some analysts view a pullback as a “buy-the-dip” setup before a possible move toward $3,500–$3,800.

Ether (ETH) has surged over 50% month-to-date in May, vastly outperforming the broader crypto market’s 15.25% gain. The rally has pushed Ethereum’s market dominance (ETH.D) toward the critical 10% threshold for the first time since March.
But the rising dominance accompanies signs of overheating, indicating that Ethereum bulls should not celebrate the rally just yet.
Ether’s RSI most overextended since May 2021
…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Yashu Gola</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Top South Korean presidential hopefuls support legalizing Bitcoin ETFs]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/south-korean-presidential-candidates-support-bitcoin-etfs</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/south-korean-presidential-candidates-support-bitcoin-etfs?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-14T13:30:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[South Korea could soon follow Hong Kong in legalizing spot Bitcoin exchange-traded funds (ETFs), as the country’s top presidential candidates have expressed pro-crypto positions. 
Still, some industry observers remain cautious about the likelihood of near-term regulatory change.
“All three major South Korean presidential candidates support #Bitcoin ETFs and institutional investment,”  Ki Young Ju, the founder and CEO of onchain data platform CryptoQuant, wrote in a May 14 X post.
Currently, Bitcoin ETFs and institutional crypto investments are banned in South Korea, meaning that “100% [of the] volume comes from retail,” Ju added.
From left: Democratic Party of Korea presidential candidate Lee Jae-myung, People Power Party presidential candidate Kim Moon-soo and New Reform Party presidentia…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Zoltan Vardai</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase CEO Brian Armstrong Invites Ex-DOGE Staff to Join Crypto Exchange]]></title>
        <id>736f4165-72fe-4bc1-a9f3-a1da4d1b1a6c</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2025/05/14/coinbase-ceo-brian-armstrong-invites-ex-doge-staff-to-join-crypto-exchange"/>
        <updated>2025-05-14T13:30:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The move comes after a former DOGE staffer, Ethan Shaotran, praised the team’s mission and work ethic despite the backlash he faced.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Francisco Rodrigues</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SMS 2FA is not just insecure, it's also hostile to mountain people]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.stillgreenmoss.net/sms-2fa-is-not-just-insecure-its-also-hostile-to-mountain-people</id>
        <link href="https://blog.stillgreenmoss.net/sms-2fa-is-not-just-insecure-its-also-hostile-to-mountain-people"/>
        <updated>2025-05-14T13:28:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The U.S. Nuclear Base Hidden Under Greenland's Ice for Decades]]></title>
        <id>https://www.wsj.com/world/greenland-us-camp-century-nuclear-base-91e8abea</id>
        <link href="https://www.wsj.com/world/greenland-us-camp-century-nuclear-base-91e8abea"/>
        <updated>2025-05-14T13:27:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CoinDesk 20 Performance Update: Uniswap (UNI) Drops 6.8% as Index Declines]]></title>
        <id>3f028f9e-4a0c-4cdb-9e1c-11977a94be94</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/coindesk-indices/2025/05/14/coindesk-20-performance-update-uniswap-uni-drops-6-8-as-index-declines"/>
        <updated>2025-05-14T13:17:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Aptos (APT) joined Uniswap (UNI) as an underperformer, falling 4.6% from Tuesday.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CoinDesk Indices</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How the economics of multitenancy work]]></title>
        <id>https://www.blacksmith.sh/blog/the-economics-of-operating-a-ci-cloud</id>
        <link href="https://www.blacksmith.sh/blog/the-economics-of-operating-a-ci-cloud"/>
        <updated>2025-05-14T13:08:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Patronus AI debuts Percival to help enterprises monitor failing AI agents at scale]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3007592</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/patronus-ai-debuts-percival-to-help-enterprises-monitor-failing-ai-agents-at-scale/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-14T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Patronus AI introduces Percival, a real-time monitoring platform that helps enterprises detect, debug, and prevent failures in autonomous AI agents to improve reliability, safety, and scalability.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Nuñez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The A.I. Radiologist Will Not Be with You Soon]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nytimes.com/2025/05/14/technology/ai-jobs-radiologists-mayo-clinic.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.nytimes.com/2025/05/14/technology/ai-jobs-radiologists-mayo-clinic.html"/>
        <updated>2025-05-14T12:52:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Is HDR, Anyway?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lux.camera/what-is-hdr/</id>
        <link href="https://www.lux.camera/what-is-hdr/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-14T12:46:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The first US hub for experimental medical treatments is coming]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1116428</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/05/14/1116428/first-us-hub-for-experimental-medical-treatments/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-14T12:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A bill that allows medical clinics to sell unproven treatments has been passed in Montana.  Under the legislation, doctors can apply for a license to open an experimental treatment clinic and recommend and sell therapies not approved by the Food and Drug Administration (FDA) to their patients. Once it’s signed by the governor, the law…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jessica Hamzelou</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The VentureBeat AI survey is back: Are you ready for the agentic AI future?]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3007483</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/the-venturebeat-ai-survey-is-back-are-you-ready-for-the-agentic-ai-future/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-14T12:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AI is a critical competitive advantage — and it’s time to find out how your company stacks up. The annual VentureBeat AI survey is back. The survey is brought to you by ActiveFence, a leader in expert-driven gen AI safety and security solutions, and returns alongside Transform 2025 in SF this June 24 and 25. […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>VB Staff</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Decentralized OORT AI data hits top ranks on Google Kaggle]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/oort-decentralized-ai-dataset-climbs-kaggle-rankings</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/oort-decentralized-ai-dataset-climbs-kaggle-rankings?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-14T12:18:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An artificial intelligence training image data set developed by decentralized AI solution provider OORT has seen considerable success on Google’s platform Kaggle.
OORT’s Diverse Tools Kaggle data set listing was released in early April; since then, it has climbed to the first page in multiple categories. Kaggle is a Google-owned online platform for data science and machine learning competitions, learning and collaboration. 
Ramkumar Subramaniam, core contributor at crypto AI project OpenLedger, told Cointelegraph that “a front-page Kaggle ranking is a strong social signal, indicating that the data set is engaging the right communities of data scientists, machine learning engineers and practitioners.“
Max Li, founder and CEO of OORT, told Cointelegraph that the firm “observed promising enga…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Adrian Zmudzinski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Surge in XRP, Dogecoin Futures Bets Signals Speculative Froth]]></title>
        <id>42f6714e-f3b7-4f4b-94ea-d21139e4b025</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/14/surge-in-xrp-dogecoin-futures-bets-signals-speculative-froth"/>
        <updated>2025-05-14T12:18:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Rising open interest despite cooling prices suggests traders are leaning into volatility, or overexposing themselves to risk.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shaurya Malwa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Download: taking the temperature of snow, and the future of privacy]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1116426</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/05/14/1116426/the-download-taking-the-temperature-of-snow-and-the-future-of-privacy/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-14T12:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is today’s edition of The Download, our weekday newsletter that provides a daily dose of what’s going on in the world of technology. Why climate researchers are taking the temperature of mountain snow The Sierra’s frozen reservoir provides about a third of California’s water and most of what comes out of the faucets, shower heads, and…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rhiannon Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Boom Likely as Bond Yields Surge - Yes, You Read That Correctly]]></title>
        <id>2d953515-0d9c-40df-a08f-332b9e7ae971</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/14/bitcoin-boom-likely-as-bond-yields-harden-yes-you-read-that-correctly"/>
        <updated>2025-05-14T12:03:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Elevated Treasury yields are driven by factors that are bullish for bitcoin.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Omkar Godbole</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[E-COM: The $40M USPS project to send email on paper]]></title>
        <id>https://buttondown.com/blog/the-e-com-story</id>
        <link href="https://buttondown.com/blog/the-e-com-story"/>
        <updated>2025-05-14T11:59:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FlowG – Distributed Systems without raft (part 2)]]></title>
        <id>https://david-delassus.medium.com/distributed-systems-without-raft-part-2-81ca31eae4db</id>
        <link href="https://david-delassus.medium.com/distributed-systems-without-raft-part-2-81ca31eae4db"/>
        <updated>2025-05-14T11:52:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin more of a ‘diversifier’ than safe-haven asset: Report]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-stock-correlation-safe-haven-portfolio-diversifier</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-stock-correlation-safe-haven-portfolio-diversifier?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-14T11:52:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin’s fluctuating correlation with US equities is raising questions about its role as a global safe-haven asset during periods of financial stress.
Bitcoin (BTC) exhibited a strong negative correlation with the US stock market when analyzing the short-term, seven-day trailing correlation, according to new research from blockchain data provider RedStone Oracles, shared exclusively with Cointelegraph.
Bitcoin, S&P 500, 7-day rolling correlation. Source: Redstone Oracles
However, RedStone said that the 30-day indicator signals a “variable correlation” between Bitcoin price and the S&P 500 index, with the correlation coefficient ranging from -0.2 to 0.4.
This fluctuating correlation suggests that Bitcoin “doesn’t consistently function as a true hedge for equities” due to its lack of a stro…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Zoltan Vardai</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin May Be Headed Towards a 2021-Like Double Top]]></title>
        <id>2f04d76a-42a4-49e2-91a1-3b55189334a1</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/14/bitcoin-may-be-headed-towards-a-2021-like-double-top"/>
        <updated>2025-05-14T11:40:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Several on-chain metrics are pointing toward waning momentum as bitcoin attempts to reach its January record just above $109,000.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Oliver Knight</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to spot a fake crypto investment platform: 10 red flags]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/how-to-spot-a-fake-crypto-investment-platform-10-red-flags</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/how-to-spot-a-fake-crypto-investment-platform-10-red-flags?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-14T11:39:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Key takeaways

Fake crypto investment platforms give themselves away in a few obvious ways.

Many use fake reviews, incorrect contact information and unrealistic promises to lure you in.

The best approach is a healthy dose of skepticism. Watching for these red flags will keep you safe while investing.

The burgeoning cryptocurrency market, with its lack of centralized authority and a constant flow of inexperienced users, makes digital assets a prime target for scammers. Fake crypto investment platforms are a common scam method, masquerading as useful services for crypto traders.
Before signing up for any crypto investment platform, it’s essential to learn the telltale signs of a scam. 
This article will detail what to watch out for and how to verify if a crypto investment platform is legi…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Max Moeller</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Cryptography Behind Passkeys]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.trailofbits.com/2025/05/14/the-cryptography-behind-passkeys/</id>
        <link href="https://blog.trailofbits.com/2025/05/14/the-cryptography-behind-passkeys/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-14T11:22:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Daybook Americas: Altcoins Rally as ‘Complacent’ Bitcoin Points to Renewed Volatility]]></title>
        <id>b5ef954e-3936-4dbc-a877-ea3bdb781f54</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/daybook-us/2025/05/14/crypto-daybook-americas-altcoins-rally-as-complacent-bitcoin-points-to-renewed-volatility"/>
        <updated>2025-05-14T11:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Your day-ahead look for May 14, 2025]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Omkar Godbole</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HONOR 400 Series To Officially Launch On 22 May 2025]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=351657</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/351657/honor-400-series-to-officially-launch-on-22-may-2025/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-14T11:13:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HONOR has confirmed that its upcoming 400 Series smartphones will launch on 22 May 2025 at 3pm local time. As previously reported, the upcoming event, which will be held in Malaysia, will also mark its debut to the global market. In its recent announcement, the brand has revealed that the HONOR 400 Series will come […]
The post HONOR 400 Series To Officially Launch On 22 May 2025 appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Heirul Kamel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Strategy will beat all public equities with Bitcoin, analyst says]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-strategy-number-one-publicly-traded-equity-analyst</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-strategy-number-one-publicly-traded-equity-analyst?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-14T10:58:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Michael Saylor’s Strategy, the world’s largest corporate holder of Bitcoin, may become the top publicly traded equity one day, according to a Strategy analyst.
Strategy will be the “number one publicly traded equity in the entire market” because of its future financial strength enabled with Bitcoin (BTC), Strategy analyst Jeff Walton predicted in the new Financial Times documentary, Michael Saylor’s $40 billion Bitcoin bet.
The company currently holds about 568,840 Bitcoin, worth roughly $59 billion, and Walton said that advantage could push it past all other publicly listed firms in the future.  
“Strategy holds more of the best assets and the most pristine collateral on the entire planet than any other company, by multiples,” Walton said.
Strategy raised $12 billion in 50 days
The analys…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Helen Partz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kazakhstan to become ‘Central Asia’s crypto hub’ with reforms: Minister]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/kazakhstan-eyes-central-asia-crypto-hub-status-with-reforms</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/kazakhstan-eyes-central-asia-crypto-hub-status-with-reforms?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-14T10:36:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kazakhstan has the potential to become a leading crypto hub in Central Asia if regulatory restrictions are eased, according to Kanysh Tuleushin, the country’s first vice minister of digital development, innovation and aerospace industry.
In a recent op-ed for the Kazakhstanskaya Pravda newspaper, Tuleushin said digital mining and smart policy shifts could position Kazakhstan as a regional leader in blockchain innovation.
“If all restrictions were lifted and digital asset trading was allowed across Kazakhstan, the impact could be significant,” he wrote.  
“Kazakhstan might become Central Asia’s crypto hub,” Tuleushin added, suggesting that broader legalization and taxation could add hundreds of billions of the country’s tenge currency to the national budget.
He called for nationwide crypto …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Amin Haqshanas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MARii Introduces NxGV Labelling Scheme]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=351633</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/351633/marii-intros-nxgv-labelling-scheme/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-14T10:27:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At the Malaysian Auto Show (MAS 2025) last week, the Malaysia Automotive, Robotics and IoT Institute (MARii) has introduced the Voluntary Next Generation Vehicle (NxGV) Labelling Scheme. It is a label on new vehicles that indicates the model name, level of autonomy, fuel consumption, and carbon emissions. It is referred to as a milestone effort […]
The post MARii Introduces NxGV Labelling Scheme appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Keran</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SEC delays Solana ETF as decisions for Polkadot, XRP loom]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/sol-ltc-etf-delayed-polkadot-xrp-etfs-june-deadline</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/sol-ltc-etf-delayed-polkadot-xrp-etfs-june-deadline?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-14T10:13:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) has pushed back its decision on a proposed spot Solana exchange-traded fund (ETF), with the cryptocurrency industry now looking to the deadlines for the Polkadot and XRP-based ETFs in June.
The SEC pushed its decision on listing Grayscale’s spot Solana (SOL) Trust ETF on the New York Stock Exchange (NYSE) to October 2025, according to a May 13 filing by the securities regulator.
Delay on Grayscale’s Solana ETF. Source: SEC
The decision came the week after the SEC delayed its ruling on Canary Capital’s Litecoin (LTC) ETF, Bloomberg Intelligence analyst James Seyffart wrote in a May 5 X post.
Source: James Seyffart
Spot ETFs are viewed as key drivers of liquidity and institutional adoption for digital assets. For Bitcoin (BTC), the US spot Bitc…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Zoltan Vardai</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Huawei Launching Nova 14 Series On 19 May, Some Specs Leak]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=351597</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/351597/huawei-launching-nova-14-series-on-19-may-some-specs-leak/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-14T10:11:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Huawei has just revealed via Weibo that it will be releasing its Nova 14 phone series. While the official lineup is currently unclear, the posts indicate that there will be at least an Ultra model. The phones are stated to receive a launch in China on 19 May at 2:30pm, according to a machine translation […]
The post Huawei Launching Nova 14 Series On 19 May, Some Specs Leak appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Newsdesk</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Databricks and Neon]]></title>
        <id>https://www.databricks.com/blog/databricks-neon</id>
        <link href="https://www.databricks.com/blog/databricks-neon"/>
        <updated>2025-05-14T10:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[U Mobile Assures Its Existing 5G Services Are Unaffected By DNB Deal Exit]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=351636</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/351636/u-mobile-assures-its-existing-5g-services-are-unaffected-by-dnb-deal-exit/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-14T10:02:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[U Mobile is assuring customers that its existing 5G services would not be impacted by its shareholders’ agreement (SHA) exit with Digital National Berhad (DNB). In a statement, the orange telco says it will maintain a 5G wholesale Access Agreement with the company, enabling it to continue offering commercial 5G services while deploying its own […]
The post U Mobile Assures Its Existing 5G Services Are Unaffected By DNB Deal Exit appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Heirul Kamel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NVIDIA Announces Partnership With HUMAIN; Will Build AI Factories In Saudi Arabia]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=351630</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/351630/nvidia-partnership-humain/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-14T09:59:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[NVIDIA announced that it has entered into a strategic partnership with Saudi Arabia’s Public Investment Fund, to invest in the latter’s HUMAIN AI value chain subsidiary. The GPU brand will provide the hardware needed for the AI computing infrastructure, as well as to help Saudi Arabia to become a global leader in the AI and […]
The post NVIDIA Announces Partnership With HUMAIN; Will Build AI Factories In Saudi Arabia appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John Law</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Asia’s wealthy shifting from US dollar to crypto, gold, China: UBS]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/ubs-asia-wealthy-invest-bitcoin-gold-china-dollar-diversification</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/ubs-asia-wealthy-invest-bitcoin-gold-china-dollar-diversification?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-14T09:47:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[High-net-worth clients across Asia are gradually pivoting away from US dollar-based investments, favoring gold, cryptocurrencies and Chinese assets instead, according to financial services giant UBS Group.
“Gold is getting very popular,” Amy Lo, the Swiss bank’s co-head of wealth management for Asia, said during Bloomberg’s New Voices event held in Hong Kong on May 13.
She cited rising geopolitical uncertainty and persistent market volatility as primary factors behind the shift. Investors, traditionally concentrated in US-centric assets, are now seeking broader exposure across alternative asset classes, including crypto, commodities and other currencies.
Lo said “volatility is definitely here to stay,” prompting clients to rebalance toward perceived safe havens and growth opportunities in …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Amin Haqshanas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Standard Chartered Will Provide Banking Services for FalconX to Enhance Cross-Border Settlement]]></title>
        <id>21f90f20-0c36-4dae-b0b1-37afca9fd02c</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2025/05/14/standard-chartered-will-provide-banking-services-for-falconx-to-enhance-cross-border-settlement"/>
        <updated>2025-05-14T08:52:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[FalconX is seeking to bridge the gap between traditional finance and crypto through bringing its service up to the level one would find at a TradFi institution]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Crawley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Synthetix Considers Purchase of Options Platform Derive in $27M Token-Swap Deal]]></title>
        <id>378bad5e-ff00-4250-9b76-b2e3b2628bdf</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2025/05/14/synthetix-considers-purchase-of-options-platform-derive-in-27m-token-swap-deal"/>
        <updated>2025-05-14T08:36:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If approved, the uncommon token swap deal would reunite two previously split protocols as Synthetix expands its derivatives suite.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shaurya Malwa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[$20K Bounty Offered for Optimizing Rust Code in Rav1d AV1 Decoder]]></title>
        <id>https://www.memorysafety.org/blog/rav1d-perf-bounty/</id>
        <link href="https://www.memorysafety.org/blog/rav1d-perf-bounty/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-14T08:32:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin miners halt sales as BTC gains 20% since hash ribbon ‘buy’ signal]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-miners-halt-sales-btc-gains-20-hash-ribbon-buy-signal</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-miners-halt-sales-btc-gains-20-hash-ribbon-buy-signal?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-14T08:24:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Key points:

Bitcoin miners have stopped selling their BTC in what may signal the end of a lengthy distribution streak.

Over the past month, miner wallet balances have increased by around 2,700 BTC.

Hash Ribbons data shows good times continuing for both miners and BTC price strength.

Bitcoin (BTC) accumulation by miners is back as network participants swap selling for hodling at $75,000 lows.
Data from onchain analytics firm Glassnode shows that miners are now actively adding to their BTC reserves.
Bitcoin miners buck months of selling
Bitcoin hitting multimonth lows in April sparked a sea change in miner behavior, with a lengthy selling streak reversing into significant accumulation.
Glassnode shows that shortly after BTC/USD bottomed just below $75,000, the balance in miner wallets it…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by William Suberg</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Infinix GT 30 Pro To Launch In Malaysia On 21 May 2025]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=351605</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/351605/infinix-gt-30-pro-to-launch-in-malaysia-on-21-may-2025/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-14T08:13:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Infinix has announced that the latest addition to its GT series and successor of the GT 20 Pro, the GT 30 Pro, is set to launch in Malaysia soon. The gaming smartphone’s debut will be streamed on the company’s official Facebook and TikTok accounts on Wednesday, 21 May 2025 at 3PM. As you may recall, […]
The post Infinix GT 30 Pro To Launch In Malaysia On 21 May 2025 appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nurul Kamil</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Standard Chartered scales institutional crypto banking with FalconX]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/standard-chartered-institutional-crypto-falconx</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/standard-chartered-institutional-crypto-falconx?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-14T08:11:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Global bank Standard Chartered has beefed up its banking support to the cryptocurrency industry by inking a new partnership with the crypto prime broker FalconX.
Standard Chartered will provide a comprehensive suite of banking services to FalconX’s global institutional clients following the strategic partnership announced on May 14.
As part of the collaboration, FalconX will initially integrate Standard Chartered’s banking infrastructure and access to a range of diverse currency pairs for its institutional clients.
The partnership ultimately aims to include a broader range of offerings and mutual opportunities, the announcement noted.
Crypto support beyond banking
The partnership is expected to “expand beyond banking” into additional products and services designed to meet evolving crypto d…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Helen Partz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ex-SEC Chair Gary Gensler privately supported crypto — McHenry]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/gary-gensler-privately-backed-crypto-mchenry-claims</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/gary-gensler-privately-backed-crypto-mchenry-claims?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-14T08:06:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Former US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) Chair Gary Gensler may not have been as hostile to crypto behind closed doors as he appeared to be in public, according to former US Representative Patrick McHenry.
In a May 13 appearance on the Crypto in America podcast, McHenry revealed that during private meetings with Gensler, the former regulator expressed a far more nuanced view of digital assets.
“Did he come across, or was he as anti-crypto in private as he did in public?” McHenry was asked. His response: “No… Nope.”
McHenry noted that Gensler “saw the value of digital assets” and acknowledged the potential of blockchain technology during his time at the Massachusetts Institute of Technology.
Gerald Gallagher, general counsel at Sei Labs, also noted that Gensler played a role in de…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Amin Haqshanas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why climate researchers are taking the temperature of mountain snow]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1116395</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/05/14/1116395/why-climate-researchers-are-taking-the-temperature-of-mountain-snow/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-14T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On a crisp morning in early April, Dan McEvoy and Bjoern Bingham cut clean lines down a wide run at the Heavenly Ski Resort in South Lake Tahoe, then ducked under a rope line cordoning off a patch of untouched snow.  They side-stepped up a small incline, poled past a row of Jeffrey pines, then…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>James Temple</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nissan Confirms New Skyline Model Amid Financial Struggles]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=351608</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/351608/nissan-confirms-new-skyline-model-amid-financial-struggles/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-14T07:59:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Amid challenging financial times for Japanese automaker Nissan, its CEO Ivan Espinosa has confirmed that an all-new Skyline is in development. The announcement was made during the company’s 2024 fiscal year financial report. However, before you get too hyped up – no, this isn’t a new GT-R. The Skyline and GT-R may share a history, […]
The post Nissan Confirms New Skyline Model Amid Financial Struggles appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Keran</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Q-Day Prize challenge, explained: Can quantum computers really break Bitcoin?]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/explained/the-q-day-prize-challenge-explained-can-quantum-computers-really-break-bitcoin</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/explained/the-q-day-prize-challenge-explained-can-quantum-computers-really-break-bitcoin?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-14T07:50:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What is the Q-Day prize?            
            
                
The Q-Day Prize is a challenge to make the Bitcoin network quantum resistant.
On April 16, 2025, quantum computing-focused company Project 11 announced the “Q-Day Prize,” a competition to break a “toy version” of Bitcoin’s cryptography with a quantum computer. Contestants must complete the Q-Day Prize challenge by April 5, 2026.
Their reward? 1 Bitcoin (BTC).

The “Q” in Q-Day refers to quantum computing, the potential threat to many existing cryptographic security measures. 
But can quantum computers break Bitcoin? Let’s find out.
Quantum computing and the threat to Bitcoin
Bitcoin utilizes the SHA-256 hashing algorithm, a National Security Agency (NSA)-developed encryption algorithm. SHA-256 prevents brute force attacks a…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Max Moeller</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kima joins Mastercard sandbox to enable stablecoin card top-ups]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/kima-integrates-with-mastercard-sandbox-to-enable-stablecoin-card-top-ups</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/kima-integrates-with-mastercard-sandbox-to-enable-stablecoin-card-top-ups?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-14T07:47:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decentralized settlement protocol Kima has integrated into Mastercard’s sandbox program, enabling stablecoin-powered top-ups for prepaid cards directly from self-custody wallets.
According to an announcement shared with Cointelegraph, Mastercard partners can now rely on Kima’s settlement infrastructure to enable their prepaid cards to be topped up with stablecoins, including USDC (USDC) and Tether’s USDt (USDT), from self-custody wallets across more than 10 blockchains. 
Kima CEO Eitan Katz said the integration shows that stablecoins can be practical for everyday use, removing friction and intermediaries from crypto-to-fiat conversions while expanding crypto usability.
“Our goal at Kima is to eliminate barriers between digital assets and traditional finance,” Katz said.
Related: Mastercard…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Adrian Zmudzinski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kingston Launches Fury Renegade G5 PCIe 5.0 SSD]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=351599</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/351599/kingston-launches-fury-renegade-g5-pcie-5-0-ssd/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-14T07:42:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kingston recently launched its new Fury Renegade G5 NVMe SSD. The SSD is the memory maker’s latest PCIe 5.0 SSD and offers ultra-fast average sequential speeds. Specs-wise, the Fury Renegade G5 can achieve average sequential read and write speeds of up to 14,800MB/s and 14,000MB/s respectively, depending on the storage configuration. On that note, Kingston […]
The post Kingston Launches Fury Renegade G5 PCIe 5.0 SSD appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John Law</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OnePlus Nord 5, Nord CE5 Appear On SIRIM Ahead Of Unveiling]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=351613</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/351613/oneplus-nord-5-nord-ce5-sirim/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-14T07:26:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[OnePlus is reportedly close to unveiling two new mid-range smartphones, namely the Nord 5 and the Nord CE5. While we have yet to hear anything official from the brand, the upcoming devices have made their way to the SIRIM database, indicating a nearing launch for the Malaysian market. The Nord 5 and Nord CE5 were […]
The post OnePlus Nord 5, Nord CE5 Appear On SIRIM Ahead Of Unveiling appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ikmal Rozlan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Alarm bells ring in US over OpenAI’s crypto project World]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/alarm-bells-us-openai-world-privacy-concerns</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/alarm-bells-us-openai-world-privacy-concerns?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-14T07:11:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[World Network, the digital identity and crypto project of Sam Altman’s OpenAI, has alarmed privacy activists ahead of its United States launch, with observers concerned over its data collection and protection practices.
World “is the opposite of privacy. It’s a trap,” said Nick Almond, CEO of FactoryDAO, on X. While the project claims to protect user privacy in the age of proliferating AI, it’s faced a slew of regulatory concerns across the globe.
Formerly known as “Worldcoin,” the iris-scanning technology and its crypto token payout scheme are being probed by authorities in India, South Korea, Italy, Colombia, Argentina, Portugal, Kenya and Indonesia. In Spain, Hong Kong and Brazil, it’s outright banned.
World’s latest foray into the US could prove to be CEO Sam Altman’s biggest challenge…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Aaron Wood</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto VC deals drop in Q1, but funding more than doubles: PitchBook]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/crypto-venture-funding-doubles-q1-deal-count-drops-pitchbook</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/crypto-venture-funding-doubles-q1-deal-count-drops-pitchbook?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-14T07:09:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto venture capital deals in the first quarter of 2025 saw deal values jump even as the number of deals sank from the same quarter a year ago, says PitchBook.
The venture research firm said in its May 14 Crypto VC Trends report for Q1 that 405 deals were made in the quarter, down 39.5% from the 670 deals made in Q1 2024, but slightly up from the 372 made in Q4 last year.
However, the total value of deals in Q1 more than doubled from a year ago, jumping to $6 billion compared to $2.6 billion in the first quarter of 2024 and doubling from $3 billion in Q4 2024.
PitchBook's senior crypto research analyst Robert Le said that despite macroeconomic turmoil over the quarter, “capital continued to seek crypto’s core utility rails.”
VCs poured nearly $2.55 billion across 16 deals into businesses…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Brayden Lindrea</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto swapper eXch shows signs of life after post-Bybit shutdown]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/crypto-exch-signs-life-bybit-shutdown</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/crypto-exch-signs-life-bybit-shutdown?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-14T07:07:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Once a go-to swapper for hackers and drainers, eXch was shut down by German police in April — but continued activity suggests the story isn’t over.
Without Know Your Customer (KYC) checks, eXch wasn’t your typical crypto exchange. It acted more like an instant swapper, allowing bad actors and cybercriminals to fly under the radar for years.
Among its clients was the Lazarus Group. The North Korean state-backed hacking unit thrust eXch into the spotlight back in February, when it used the platform to funnel some of the $1.4 billion it stole from Bybit. When Bybit traced its stolen funds to eXch, it requested assistance — but the platform refused.
This led to a fierce discussion over privacy versus security, but ultimately, eXch announced it would close its doors on April 17; on April 30, Ge…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Yohan Yun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build a Smartwatch: Picking a Chip]]></title>
        <id>https://ericmigi.com/blog/how-to-build-a-smartwatch-picking-a-chip/</id>
        <link href="https://ericmigi.com/blog/how-to-build-a-smartwatch-picking-a-chip/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-14T07:02:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ex-Cred execs plead guilty to wire fraud over $150M crypto collapse]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/former-execs-crypto-lender-cred-plead-guilty-wire-fraud</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/former-execs-crypto-lender-cred-plead-guilty-wire-fraud?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-14T06:32:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Two former executives of the bankrupt crypto lending service Cred have pleaded guilty to wire fraud connected to the company’s collapse.
Former Cred CEO Daniel Schatt and chief financial officer Joseph Podulka admitted to wire fraud as part of a plea deal with prosecutors, according to a May 13 text filing in a California District Court.
District Judge William Alsup accepted the plea deals and set a sentencing hearing for Aug. 26. Wire fraud can carry up to 20 years in prison and $250,000 in fines for individuals and $500,00 for businesses.
After accepting the defendant's guilty plea, Judge William Alsup set a sentencing hearing for August. Source: PACER
Law360 reported that as part of the plea agreement, Schatt and Podulka admitted to selectively presenting positive “information [while] f…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Stephen Katte</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Semler Scientific sees after-hours stock slump as Q1 revenue plunges]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/semler-scientific-after-hours-stock-drop-q1-results</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/semler-scientific-after-hours-stock-drop-q1-results?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-14T06:22:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin-buying medical device firm Semler Scientific has seen its share price drop after the bell as its first-quarter revenues fell and losses deepened from the year-ago quarter.
In its Q1 earnings report released May 13, Semler reported its total revenues fell 44% from the year-ago quarter to $8.8 million, with its net losses hitting $64.7 million compared to a net income of $6.1 million in the first quarter of 2024.
Shares in Semler Scientific (SMLR) closed the May 13 trading session up over 5% but fell 1.91% to $36 after the bell with its earnings announcement, according to Google Finance. Semler’s stock is down over 32% so far this year.
Semler fell nearly 2% after announcing its Q1 results on May 13. Source: Google Finance
The company said it purchased 894 Bitcoin (BTC) over Q1 and h…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Tarang Khaitan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ether Nears $2.7K, Dogecoin Zooms 9% as Crypto Market Remains Cheery]]></title>
        <id>515e1db8-9c62-4f84-a557-851d9e8d118f</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/14/ether-nears-usd2-7k-dogecoin-zooms-9-as-crypto-market-remains-cheery"/>
        <updated>2025-05-14T06:12:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto market cap dips slightly, but positive sentiment and inflows persist amid bullish altcoin moves.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shaurya Malwa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Synthetix makes $27M bid to re-acquire crypto options platform Derive]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/synthetix-27-million-bid-reacquire-derive</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/synthetix-27-million-bid-reacquire-derive?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-14T06:11:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decentralized finance platform Synthetix is planning to venture further into crypto derivatives with plans to re-acquire the crypto options platform Derive.
Synthetix said in a May 14 blog post that it plans to acquire Derive in a token exchange deal, pricing 1 SNX token to 27 DRV tokens, which would value Derive at around $27 million. 
The transaction is subject to approval from both the Synthetix and Derive communities, which will take a vote on the proposal, called SIP-415, next week.
If approved, the acquisition will combine Derive’s front-end and real-world asset (RWA) expertise with Synthetix’s derivatives infrastructure.
Derive originally launched as Lyra in 2021, having spun out from the Synthetix ecosystem. Synthetix said the acquisition is part of a broader strategy that includes…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Martin Young</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Apple Music Adds Sound Therapy; Features Universal Music Songs]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=351570</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/351570/apple-music-adds-sound-therapy-features-universal-music-songs/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-14T06:09:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Apple and Universal Music Group have announced that the former is adding Sound Therapy to Apple Music, using songs from the latter. Or more specifically, “extended, instrumental, and reimagined versions of popular tracks from acclaimed artists” like Imagine Dragons and Katy Perry. The idea is that these songs are specifically modified, and sorted into three […]
The post Apple Music Adds Sound Therapy; Features Universal Music Songs appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ian Chee</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The recently lost file upload feature in the Nextcloud app for Android]]></title>
        <id>https://nextcloud.com/blog/nextcloud-android-file-upload-issue-google/</id>
        <link href="https://nextcloud.com/blog/nextcloud-android-file-upload-issue-google/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-14T05:38:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Thailand to tokenize $150M government bonds for retail investors: Report]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/thailand-tokenize-150-million-government-bonds</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/thailand-tokenize-150-million-government-bonds?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-14T05:10:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Thailand’s Ministry of Finance reportedly plans to issue $150 million worth of digital investment tokens, allowing retail investors to buy government bonds.
The Bangkok Post reported on May 13 that Finance Minister Pichai Chunhavajira announced the initiative at a briefing after the cabinet endorsed the plan. He added that the tokens will be launched within the next two months.
The so-called “G-tokens” will be used to raise funds from the public under the current budget borrowing plan, said Patchara Anuntasilpa, director-general of the Public Debt Management Office. He added that these were not debt instruments.
“One big selling point of the token is that it allows more retail investors to become part of the digital economy,” he said, adding that for as little as $3, “they can invest in go…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Martin Young</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[eToro IPO raises $620M after pricing shares above range at $52]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/etoro-prices-ipo-above-range-52-share-raise-620-million</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/etoro-prices-ipo-above-range-52-share-raise-620-million?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-14T04:56:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto and stock trading platform eToro has boosted the size of its initial public offering to $620 million by pricing its shares above its previously suggested range.
The platform and its backers sold over 11.92 million shares for $52 each, which are slated to start trading on the Nasdaq Global Select Market on May 14 under the ticker symbol ETOR, eToro said in a May 13 press release.
Initially, the firm aimed to raise $500 million by offering 10 million shares priced between $46 to $50 each.
The share offering will remain open until at least May 15 and consists of more than 5.9 million shares sold by eToro and 5.9 million shares sold by specific existing shareholders.
The Israel-based eToro will go public as a rival to Robinhood Markets Inc. (HOOD), which went public in July 2021 and who…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Stephen Katte</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bus stops here: Shanghai lets riders design their own routes]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sixthtone.com/news/1017072</id>
        <link href="https://www.sixthtone.com/news/1017072"/>
        <updated>2025-05-14T04:33:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Writing that changed how I think about programming languages]]></title>
        <id>https://bernsteinbear.com/blog/pl-writing/</id>
        <link href="https://bernsteinbear.com/blog/pl-writing/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-14T04:19:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Illicit $8B crypto market Xinbi incorporated in Colorado: Elliptic]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/crypto-black-market-xinbi-colorado-based-firm</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/crypto-black-market-xinbi-colorado-based-firm?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-14T03:49:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A Colorado-incorporated firm has been linked to a Chinese illicit marketplace that has served scammers in Southeast Asia and has been used to channel billions of dollars worth of crypto.
The marketplace, called Xinbi Guarantee, has received $8.4 billion, primarily in Tether (USDT) stablecoin transactions to date, blockchain security firm Elliptic reported on May 13. 
Merchants on the Chinese-language, Telegram-based marketplace sell technology, personal data, and money laundering services to Southeast Asian scammers who target victims using pig butchering scams. 
On its website, Xinbi describes itself as an “investment and capital guarantee group company” and claims to operate through Xinbi Co. Ltd, a Colorado-incorporated company incorporated in 2022. 
Screenshots showing Xinbi Co. Ltd’s …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Martin Young</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto exchange CEO’s daughter fights off brazen kidnappers in Paris]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/crypto-exchange-ceo-daughter-fights-kidnappers-paris</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/crypto-exchange-ceo-daughter-fights-kidnappers-paris?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-14T02:07:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Disclaimer: This article contains a video that may be disturbing for some readers.
A brazen attempt to kidnap the daughter and grandson of Pierre Noizat, the co-founder and CEO of French crypto exchange Paymium, was foiled after the daughter and passersby reportedly fought off the kidnappers.
Three masked men attacked Noizat’s daughter and a male partner on May 13 while she was walking with her son in Paris’ 11th district. The assailants tried to force Noizat’s daughter and her son into a waiting van, the French state-owned media outlet France24 reported on May 13.
The accompanying male partner was assaulted when he tried to intervene, but Noizat’s daughter resisted and managed to take one of the guns off an assailant in a scuffle and throw it away, police said.

En plein Paris, un homme a…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Stephen Katte</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Slow Blockchain Governance Leaves Crypto Exposed to Quantum Threats]]></title>
        <id>74a5f48b-0c0a-46d9-beb0-0281ea4d8583</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/consensus-toronto-2025-coverage/2025/05/13/slow-blockchain-governance-leaves-crypto-exposed-to-quantum-threats"/>
        <updated>2025-05-14T00:30:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Securing a whole chain will take too long, so why not go piece by piece with the largest whales putting their stash in quantum vaults first.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sam Reynolds</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tether buys $459M Bitcoin for Twenty One Capital]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/tether-459-million-bitcoin-twenty-one-capital</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/tether-459-million-bitcoin-twenty-one-capital?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-14T00:29:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Stablecoin issuer Tether bought $458.7 million worth of Bitcoin for Twenty One Capital, a Bitcoin investment firm it backed that’s awaiting the completion of a Special Purpose Acquisition Company (SPAC) merger with Cantor Equity Partners.
Tether snapped up 4,812.2 Bitcoin (BTC) at $95,319 each and transferred it to an escrow wallet on May 9, Cantor Equity Partners disclosed in a May 13 filing with the US Securities and Exchange Commission.
It brings Twenty One’s total Bitcoin holdings to 36,312 BTC, as Cantor Equity Partners holds 31,500 BTC on behalf of the firm, which will trade under the ticker XXI once the SPAC merger is complete.
Twenty One’s CEO, Jack Mallers, said on May 13 that they’re already in the approval process of the merger, but didn’t give an exact estimate on when the tran…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Brayden Lindrea</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[eToro Goes Public at $52 a Share, Far Exceeding Marketed Range]]></title>
        <id>76998bde-9b46-43f9-8464-315e5f1ae3b5</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/13/etoro-goes-public-at-52-a-share-far-exceeding-marketed-range"/>
        <updated>2025-05-14T00:02:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The company raised about $310 million from the Nasdaq listing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Helene Braun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Flattening Rust’s learning curve]]></title>
        <id>https://corrode.dev/blog/flattening-rusts-learning-curve/</id>
        <link href="https://corrode.dev/blog/flattening-rusts-learning-curve/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-13T22:25:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Notion bets big on integrated LLMs, adds GPT-4.1 and Claude 3.7 to platform]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3007515</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/notion-bets-big-on-integrated-llms-adds-gpt-4-1-and-claude-3-7-to-platform/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-13T22:18:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Notion used OpenAI's GPT-4.1 and Anthropic's Claude 3.7 for its new AI features for enterprises, moving away from reasoning models.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Emilia David</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Type-constrained code generation with language models]]></title>
        <id>https://arxiv.org/abs/2504.09246</id>
        <link href="https://arxiv.org/abs/2504.09246"/>
        <updated>2025-05-13T22:15:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What your tools miss at 2:13 AM: How gen AI attack chains exploit telemetry lag – Part 2]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3005726</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/what-your-tools-miss-at-213-am-how-gen-ai-attack-chains-exploit-telemetry-lag-part-2/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-13T22:05:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Explore a strategic 2025 roadmap for cybersecurity leaders to tackle GenAI, insider risks, and team burnout with actionable guidance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Louis Columbus</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AI power rankings upended: OpenAI, Google rise as Anthropic falls, Poe report finds]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3007490</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/ai-power-rankings-upended-openai-google-rise-as-anthropic-falls-poe-report-finds/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-13T19:13:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New Poe data reveals major shifts in AI market share as OpenAI and Google gain ground while specialized reasoning models surge to 10% of usage in 2025.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Nuñez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SimilarWeb’s new AI usage report reveals 5 surprising findings, including explosive growth in coding tools]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3007475</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/similarwebs-new-ai-usage-report-reveals-5-surprising-findings-including-explosive-growth-in-coding-tools/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-13T17:22:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The signs point to early-stage AI disruption beginning to erode the utility of some legacy platforms. It also offers a hint to enterprises...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carl Franzen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Branch Privilege Injection: Exploiting branch predictor race conditions]]></title>
        <id>https://comsec.ethz.ch/research/microarch/branch-privilege-injection/</id>
        <link href="https://comsec.ethz.ch/research/microarch/branch-privilege-injection/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-13T16:44:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google is building its own DeX: First look at Android's Desktop Mode]]></title>
        <id>https://www.androidauthority.com/android-desktop-mode-leak-3550321/</id>
        <link href="https://www.androidauthority.com/android-desktop-mode-leak-3550321/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-13T14:30:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Top Ways Hackers Exploit Web Applications (and How to Prevent Them)]]></title>
        <id>682354c58b3805ff1d2335d0</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-hackers-exploit-web-applications-and-how-to-prevent-them/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-13T14:18:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Every website that takes user input is a potential target for an attacker. You might think your app is too small or too new to get noticed, but attackers use tools to scan the web for common security mistakes. If your site is online and has a login f...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Manish Shivanandhan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The interoperability breakthrough: How MCP is becoming enterprise AI’s universal language]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3007355</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/the-interoperability-breakthrough-how-mcp-is-becoming-enterprise-ais-universal-language/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-13T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Just a few months after it's release, MCP adoption is growing. VentureBeat spoke to some enterprises asking why MCP is winning the standards race.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Emilia David</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Guardian agents: New approach could reduce AI hallucinations to below 1%]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3007370</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/beyond-detection-why-automatically-correcting-hallucinations-could-transform-enterprise-ai-adoption/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-13T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There are lots of ways to detect AI hallucination, new guardian agent model promises to correct them.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sean Michael Kerner</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Download: CRISPR in court, and the police’s ban-skirting AI]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1116357</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/05/13/1116357/the-download-crispr-in-court-and-the-polices-ban-skirting-ai/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-13T12:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is today’s edition of The Download, our weekday newsletter that provides a daily dose of what’s going on in the world of technology. A US court just put ownership of CRISPR back in play The CRISPR patents are back in play. Yesterday, the US Court of Appeals for the Federal Circuit said scientists Jennifer Doudna and…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rhiannon Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Police tech can sidestep facial recognition bans now]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1116321</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/05/13/1116321/police-tech-can-sidestep-facial-recognition-bans-now/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-13T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Six months ago I attended the largest gathering of chiefs of police in the US to see how they’re using AI. I found some big developments, like officers getting AI to write their police reports. Today, I published a new story that shows just how far AI for police has developed since then.  It’s about…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>James O'Donnell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A US court just put ownership of CRISPR back in play]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1116344</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/05/13/1116344/a-us-court-just-put-ownership-of-crispr-back-in-play/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-13T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The CRISPR patents are back in play. On Monday, the US Court of Appeals for the Federal Circuit said scientists Jennifer Doudna and Emmanuelle Charpentier will get another chance to show they ought to own the key patents on what many consider the defining biotechnology invention of the 21st century. The pair shared a 2020…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Antonio Regalado</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sakana introduces new AI architecture, ‘Continuous Thought Machines’ to make models reason with less guidance — like human brains]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3007376</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/sakana-introduces-new-ai-architecture-continuous-thought-machines-to-make-models-reason-with-less-guidance-like-human-brains/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-12T23:08:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While the CTM shows strong promise, it is still primarily a research architecture and is not yet production-ready out of the box.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carl Franzen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OpenAI just fixed ChatGPT’s most annoying business problem: meet the PDF export that changes everything]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3007361</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/openai-just-fixed-chatgpts-most-annoying-business-problem-meet-the-pdf-export-that-changes-everything/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-12T20:43:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[OpenAI has added a powerful PDF export feature to its Deep Research tool, signaling a major push into enterprise AI and transforming how businesses generate and share insights.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Nuñez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New fully open source vision encoder OpenVision arrives to improve on OpenAI’s Clip, Google’s SigLIP]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3007349</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/new-fully-open-source-vision-encoder-openvision-arrives-to-improve-on-openais-clip-googles-siglip/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-12T18:19:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A vision encoder is a necessary component for allowing many leading LLMs to be able to work with images uploaded by users.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carl Franzen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Automate Compliance and Fraud Detection in Finance with MLOps]]></title>
        <id>68222009a8daed5c1fbf1692</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/automate-compliance-and-fraud-detection-in-finance-with-mlops/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-12T16:21:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[These days, businesses are under increasing pressure to comply with stringent regulations while also combating fraudulent activities. The high volume of data and the intricate requirements of real-time fraud detection and compliance reporting are fre...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Balajee Asish Brahmandam</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn Object-Oriented Programming in TypeScript]]></title>
        <id>682201c8ba77730da04e15a8</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-object-oriented-programming-in-typescript/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-12T14:12:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Object-Oriented Programming (OOP) is one of the most widely used programming paradigms in software development. But is also one of the most misunderstood. This article will help you gain a solid grasp of OOP in TypeScript by walking you through the l...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lucas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Become an Analytical Programmer – Solve the "Rock, Paper, Scissors" Game 5 Ways Using JavaScript & Mermaid.js]]></title>
        <id>6822006162f6347293451e07</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-become-an-analytical-programmer-compare-five-projects/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-12T14:06:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Over the past year, I’ve explored tools and practices that help developers build an analytical mindset. One recurring theme is how experienced programmers often describe understanding code as forming a mental picture – a conceptual map of the program...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>evaristo.c</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Glass Imaging raises $20M to use AI to improve digital image quality]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3007251</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/games/glass-imaging-raises-20m-to-use-ai-to-improve-digital-image-quality/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-12T13:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Glass Imaging, a company harnessing the power of artificial intelligence to revolutionize digital image quality, raised $20 million in funding. Global software investor insight Partners led the round. With the funding, Glass Imaging will continue to refine and implement their proprietary GlassAI technologies across a wide range of camera platforms – from smartphones to drones to wearables and […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dean Takahashi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Aarki launches Encore as privacy-first mobile growth platform]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3007252</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/games/aarki-launches-encore-as-privacy-first-mobile-growth-platform/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-12T12:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Aarki has launched Encore, a next-generation machine learning platform built to deliver full-funnel growth for mobile marketers in a privacy-first landscape. Designed for smarter user acquisition and stronger retention, Encore combines dynamic targeting, continuous model evolution, and SKAN 4-ready optimization.  Encore is the industry’s only unified platform with a privacy-first framework that supports both User […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dean Takahashi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Download: a new form of AI surveillance, and the US and China’s tariff deal]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1116307</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/05/12/1116307/the-download-a-new-form-of-ai-surveillance-and-the-us-and-chinas-tariff-deal/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-12T12:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is today’s edition of The Download, our weekday newsletter that provides a daily dose of what’s going on in the world of technology. How a new type of AI is helping police skirt facial recognition bans Police and federal agencies have found a controversial new way to skirt the growing patchwork of laws that curb how…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rhiannon Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How a new type of AI is helping police skirt facial recognition bans]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1116295</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/05/12/1116295/how-a-new-type-of-ai-is-helping-police-skirt-facial-recognition-bans/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-12T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Police and federal agencies have found a controversial new way to skirt the growing patchwork of laws that curb how they use facial recognition: an AI model that can track people using attributes like body size, gender, hair color and style, clothing, and accessories.  The tool, called Track and built by the video analytics company…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>James O'Donnell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sequencing for Value]]></title>
        <id>https://engineering.blueberrypediatrics.blog/sequencing-for-value</id>
        <link href="https://engineering.blueberrypediatrics.blog/sequencing-for-value"/>
        <updated>2025-05-11T17:13:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[From silicon to sentience: The legacy guiding AI’s next frontier and human cognitive migration]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3007219</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/from-silicon-to-sentience-the-legacy-guiding-ais-next-frontier-and-human-cognitive-migration/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-11T17:05:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As AI systems master tasks once uniquely human, we find ourselves on an accelerated journey to discover what truly lies beyond automation.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gary Grossman, Edelman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Breaking the Sound Barrier Part I: Fuzzing CoreAudio with Mach Messages]]></title>
        <id>https://googleprojectzero.blogspot.com/2025/05/breaking-sound-barrier-part-i-fuzzing.html</id>
        <link href="https://googleprojectzero.blogspot.com/2025/05/breaking-sound-barrier-part-i-fuzzing.html"/>
        <updated>2025-05-11T02:10:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MCP and the innovation paradox: Why open standards will save AI from itself]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3007210</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/mcp-and-the-innovation-paradox-why-open-standards-will-save-ai-from-itself/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-10T19:05:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Much like HTTP and REST standardized how web applications connect to services, MCP standardizes how AI models connect to tools.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Noah Schwartz, Postman API Network</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Interferometer Device Sees Text from a Mile Away]]></title>
        <id>https://physics.aps.org/articles/v18/99</id>
        <link href="https://physics.aps.org/articles/v18/99"/>
        <updated>2025-05-10T14:05:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ash Framework – Model your domain, derive the rest]]></title>
        <id>https://ash-hq.org/</id>
        <link href="https://ash-hq.org/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-10T13:32:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[RPG in a Box]]></title>
        <id>https://rpginabox.com/</id>
        <link href="https://rpginabox.com/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-10T08:52:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fine-tuning vs. in-context learning: New research guides better LLM customization for real-world tasks]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3007197</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/fine-tuning-vs-in-context-learning-new-research-guides-better-llm-customization-for-real-world-tasks/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-10T00:23:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By combining fine-tuning and in-context learning, you get LLMs that can learn tasks that would be too difficult or expensive for either method]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ben Dickson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Make IT Operations More Efficient with AIOps: Build Smarter, Faster Systems]]></title>
        <id>681e7192df44ab8496bca883</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/make-it-operations-more-efficient-with-aiops/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-09T21:20:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the rapidly evolving IT landscape, development teams have to operate at their best and manage complex systems while minimizing downtime. And having to do many routine tasks manually can really slow down operations and reduce efficiency. These days...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Balajee Asish Brahmandam</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What your tools miss at 2:13 AM: How gen AI attack chains exploit telemetry lag – Part 1]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3005673</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/security/what-your-tools-miss-at-213-am-how-gen-ai-attack-chains-exploit-telemetry-lag-part-1/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-09T20:56:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Explore a strategic 2025 roadmap for cybersecurity leaders to tackle gen AI, insider risks, and team burnout with actionable guidance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Louis Columbus</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OpenAI’s $3B Windsurf move: the real reason behind its enterprise AI code push]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3007170</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/openais-3b-windsurf-move-the-real-reason-behind-its-enterprise-ai-agent-code-push/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-09T17:00:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[OpenAI’s $3B Windsurf buy puts it on defense as Google & Anthropic surge in AI-powered coding—discover the stakes for agentic development and enterprise teams.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matt Marshall</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is Technical Debt and How Do You Manage it?]]></title>
        <id>681e31e668aa6f9f0c37bb12</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-technical-debt-and-how-do-you-manage-it/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-09T16:48:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You’ve probably heard someone say, “We’ll fix it later.” Maybe you’ve said it yourself. In the rush to launch a feature, meet a deadline, or impress a client, you take a shortcut. The code works – for now. The design passes – for now. But over time, ...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Manish Shivanandhan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Updated rate limits for unauthenticated requests]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/changelog/2025-05-08-updated-rate-limits-for-unauthenticated-requests/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/changelog/2025-05-08-updated-rate-limits-for-unauthenticated-requests/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-09T14:11:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Zencoder launches Zen Agents, ushering in a new era of team-based AI for software development]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3007152</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/zencoder-launches-zen-agents-ushering-in-a-new-era-of-team-based-ai-for-software-development/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-09T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Zencoder launches Zen Agents, the first AI platform enabling teams to create, share, and leverage custom development assistants organization-wide, plus an open-source marketplace for enterprise-grade AI tools.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Nuñez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Download: AI headphone translation, and the link between microbes and our behavior]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1116247</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/05/09/1116247/the-download-ai-headphone-translation-and-the-link-between-microbes-and-our-behavior/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-09T12:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is today’s edition of The Download, our weekday newsletter that provides a daily dose of what’s going on in the world of technology. A new AI translation system for headphones clones multiple voices simultaneously What’s new: Imagine going for dinner with a group of friends who switch in and out of different languages you don’t speak,…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rhiannon Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ditching a Microsoft Job to Enter Startup Purgatory with Lonewolf Engineer Sam Crombie [Podcast #171]]]></title>
        <id>681dc8d07dcd2a77c4bbe048</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/ditching-a-microsoft-job-to-enter-startup-hell-with-lonewolf-engineer-sam-crombie-podcast-171/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-09T09:20:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On this week's episode of the podcast, freeCodeCamp founder Quincy Larson interviews Sam Crombie. He's a software engineer and prolific open source contributor to freeCodeCamp. He abandon his job at Microsoft, got into Y Combinator, and is currently ...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OpenAI, Microsoft tell Senate ‘no one country can win AI’]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3007056</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/openai-microsoft-tell-senate-no-one-country-can-win-ai/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-09T01:02:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Executives like OpenAI's Sam Altman said US support for infrastructure would make it easier for AI companies to meet demand.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Emilia David</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[You can now fine-tune your enterprise’s own version of OpenAI’s o4-mini reasoning model with reinforcement learning]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3007091</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/you-can-now-fine-tune-your-enterprises-own-version-of-openais-o4-mini-reasoning-model-with-reinforcement-learning/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-09T00:07:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For organizations with clearly defined problems and verifiable answers, RFT offers a compelling way to align models.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carl Franzen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How The Ottawa Hospital uses AI ambient voice capture to reduce physician burnout by 70%, achieve 97% patient satisfaction]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3007069</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/how-the-ottawa-hospital-uses-ai-ambient-voice-capture-to-reduce-physician-burnout-by-70-achieve-97-patient-satisfaction/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-08T23:57:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[TOH is using Microsoft’s DAX Copilot to capture physician-patient conversations and generate draft clinical notes in real time.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Taryn Plumb</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[5 strategies that separate AI leaders from the 92% still stuck in pilot mode]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3007013</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/5-strategies-that-separate-ai-leaders-from-the-92-still-stuck-in-pilot-mode/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-08T23:09:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Accenture's new research reveals the critical strategies that separate the companies successfully scaling AI from the 92% stuck in perpetual pilot mode, providing enterprise leaders with actionable insights to accelerate their AI transformation journey.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sean Michael Kerner</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Prepare for your iOS interview]]></title>
        <id>681d1bbfb1018a470d0d8a02</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/prepare-for-your-ios-interview/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-08T21:01:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Preparing for an iOS developer interview can be a daunting task, especially when you're trying to master both conceptual questions and practical coding challenges. Whether you're just starting your iOS development journey or gearing up for your next ...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The walled garden cracks: Nadella bets Microsoft’s Copilots—and Azure’s next act—on A2A/MCP interoperability]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3006872</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/the-walled-garden-cracks-nadella-bets-microsofts-copilots-and-azures-next-act-on-a2a-mcp-interoperability/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-08T20:47:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft CEO Satya Nadella’s endorsement of Google DeepMind‘s A2A open protocol and Anthropic's MCP is huge sign the industry is moving to an open garden.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Louis Columbus</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Alibaba’s ‘ZeroSearch’ lets AI learn to google itself — slashing training costs by 88 percent]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3007024</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/alibabas-zerosearch-lets-ai-learn-to-google-itself-slashing-training-costs-by-88-percent/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-08T19:15:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Alibaba’s ZeroSearch trains large language models to beat Google Search and slash API costs by 88%, redefining how AI learns to retrieve information.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Nuñez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mem0’s scalable memory promises more reliable AI agents that remembers context across lengthy conversations]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3006826</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/mem0s-scalable-memory-promises-more-reliable-ai-agents-that-remembers-context-across-lengthy-conversations/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-08T19:13:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mem0's architecture is designed to LLM memory and enhance consistency for more reliable agent performance in long conversations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ben Dickson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use Arrow Functions in PHP 7.4+]]></title>
        <id>681cf9062cbe43bee0f4138f</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-arrow-functions-in-php/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-08T18:33:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Arrow functions were introduced in PHP 7.4 to allow devs to write short, anonymous functions. They offer a compact alternative to traditional closures, especially when the function body is small and focused. In this article, you will learn how to use...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Montasser Mossallem</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Free GenAI 65-Hour Bootcamp]]></title>
        <id>681cd4ea505e2f4aa02206d5</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/free-genai-65-hour-bootcamp/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-08T15:59:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Generative AI is revolutionizing how we create, learn, and interact with digital content. From intelligent chatbots and personalized language tutors to realistic image generation and interactive story engines, the applications are endless. We just pu...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OpenAI names Instacart leader Fidji Simo as new CEO of Applications]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3006978</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/openai-names-instacart-leader-fidji-simo-as-new-ceo-of-applications/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-08T15:25:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Simo’s appointment may also hint at a broader productization push within OpenAI. Her background at Facebook and Instacart underscores...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carl Franzen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Imagination unveils E-Series GPUs for graphics and AI at the edge]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3006922</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/games/imagination-unveils-e-series-gpus-for-graphics-and-ai-at-the-edge/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-08T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Imagination Technologies is unveiling its E-Series graphics processing units (GPUs) for graphics and AI processing at the edge.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dean Takahashi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nvidia welcomes Trump’s proposal to rescind global chip restrictions]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3006921</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/gaming-business/nvidia-welcomes-trumps-proposal-to-rescind-global-chip-restrictions/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-08T06:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Donald Trump's administration is expected to rescind Joe Biden's curbs on AI chip sales as part of a broader effort to revise semiconductor restrictions, Bloomberg reported.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dean Takahashi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Breathe lands $21M Series B to predict battery performance]]></title>
        <id>https://techcrunch.com/?p=3003769</id>
        <link href="https://techcrunch.com/2025/05/07/breathe-lands-21m-series-b-to-predict-battery-performance/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-07T12:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Breathe has developed a suite of tools that it says helps automakers and others get the most out of their batteries.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tim De Chant</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Join the 2025 Web3j Mentorships: Build the Future of Ethereum on the JVM]]></title>
        <id>6819c8dc41eeeb000183d37b</id>
        <link href="https://blog.web3labs.com/join-the-2025-web3j-mentorships-build-the-future-of-ethereum-on-the-jvm/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T08:32:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Linux Foundation’s Decentralized Trust (LFDT) mentorship program is back in 2025 with two exciting opportunities for developers passionate about Ethereum, Android, and the Java Virtual Machine (JVM). Whether you’re a seasoned blockchain developer or an Android enthusiast eager to dive into Web3, these mentorships offer]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>George Tebrean</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>