<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2025-04-30T23:41:49.468Z</id>
    <title>AngJianming RSS Feed</title>
    <updated>2025-04-30T23:41:49.468Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Exploring Corporate Sponsorship and Blockchain Innovation: A Deep Dive]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/laetitiaperraut/exploring-corporate-sponsorship-and-blockchain-innovation-a-deep-dive-7p8</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/laetitiaperraut/exploring-corporate-sponsorship-and-blockchain-innovation-a-deep-dive-7p8"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T23:27:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Abstract

In this post, we explore how corporate sponsorship is driving blockchain innovation through financial backing, strategic partnerships, technological support, and marketing endorsements. We delve into the background of blockchain, explain its transformative capabilities, present case studies like IBM’s role in Hyperledger and Microsoft’s Azure Blockchain, and discuss challenges and future outlooks. Additionally, we offer practical examples, a comprehensive table comparing sponsorship types, and bullet lists of key benefits and challenges, all optimized for both search engines and human readers.
Blockchain technology has evolved rapidly from an experimental concept to an indispensable tool powering various industries. Its secure, transparent, and efficient decentralized ledger enab…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Laetitia Perraut</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Creating A Basic Discord Bot]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/yourdailybrick_9a0f9810ae/creating-a-basic-discord-bot-3kha</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/yourdailybrick_9a0f9810ae/creating-a-basic-discord-bot-3kha"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T23:18:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hey everyone,
Here’s a simple tutorial for making a basic Discord bot using Python. This bot will automatically reply with "very cool" whenever anyone sends a message in any text channel on your server.
It’s a great starting point if:
1:You’re learning how Discord bots work
2:You want to test basic features
3:You plan to build something bigger later
Let’s jump in.
🧠 What the Bot Does
💻 The Code
import discord

# Hardcoded bot token — only for testing/learning
TOKEN = "YOUR_BOT_TOKEN_HERE"

# Enable reading messages
intents = discord.Intents.default()
intents.message_content = True

# Create the bot client
client = discord.Client(intents=intents)

# Called when the bot connects to Discord
@client.event
async def on_ready():
    print(f"Logged in as {client.user}")

# Called when any messa…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>YourDailyBrick</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AI-Driven Development: My Database Experiment]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/lukaszbudnik/ai-driven-development-my-database-experiment-14e4</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/lukaszbudnik/ai-driven-development-my-database-experiment-14e4"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T23:15:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There's plenty of debate about AI's role in coding. As an engineer, I've been working with Large Language Models and GenAI since their early days. I decided to skip the debate and put AI to a practical test: build a DynamoDB-like database service from scratch with AI assistance. Because who doesn't love a good database challenge?
The idea was to build a service with the following characteristics:
 DynamoDB-like API: Implementing the essentials from PutItem to TransactWriteItems.
 Robust Storage Layer: A RocksDB implementation with full transaction support.
 Modern Communication: High-performance gRPC service, Protocol Buffer serialization, and TLS 1.3 (including mutual authentication).
 Containerization: Multi-arch Docker support and Kubernetes deployment manifests.
 Agile Development Simu…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Łukasz Budnik</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bulut'un Gücü: Cloud Chronicles]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/yunus_emremert_1756b71d3/bulutun-gucu-cloud-chronicles-4hf9</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/yunus_emremert_1756b71d3/bulutun-gucu-cloud-chronicles-4hf9"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T23:12:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Yaz tatili birçok kişi için dinlenmek ve yeni yerler keşfetmek demek. Peki ya bulutlar hakkındaki maceralarımızı ve keşiflerimizi paylaşsak? Bulut teknolojileri, günümüzün hızlı hareket eden dijital dünyasında büyük önem taşıyor ve bu yazımda "Bulut'un Gücü"nü keşfetmek istiyorum.
Bulut bilişim, son yıllarda büyük bir evrim geçirdi ve işletmeler ile bireyler için güçlü bir araç haline geldi. Artık bulut, yalnızca bir veri depolama alanı değil, güçlü bir işlem gücü ve esneklik sunan bir platform. Bulut hizmetlerinin sunduğu avantajlar, geliştiricilerden işletme sahiplerine kadar herkesi etkilemekte ve yeni fırsatlar yaratmaktadır. Bu yazı, bulut bilişimin gücünü, esnekliğini ve günümüz web mimarileri ve uygulamaları üzerindeki etkilerini inceleyecek. Ayrıca, bulut hizmetlerinin popülerliğin…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yunus Emre Mert</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Exploring Cisco's Innovations: Open Source Networking and Blockchain Security]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/vitalisorenko/exploring-ciscos-innovations-open-source-networking-and-blockchain-security-5doi</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/vitalisorenko/exploring-ciscos-innovations-open-source-networking-and-blockchain-security-5doi"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T23:11:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Abstract:

Cisco is at the forefront of technology with its forward-thinking approach to open source networking and blockchain security. This post details Cisco’s major contributions, examines the core concepts and real-world applications, and discusses the challenges and future outlook in these inter-related fields. With a focus on transparency, collaboration, and security, Cisco’s initiatives are not only revolutionizing network infrastructures but are also redefining the digital security landscape for enterprises worldwide.
In today’s rapidly changing digital environment, traditional networking and centralized security approaches are being disrupted by innovations rooted in open source and blockchain technologies. Cisco—the global leader in networking solutions—is embracing these trends…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Vitali Sorenko</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Fun Kubernetes: A Beginner's Guide to the Container Playground]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/collinsushi/the-fun-kubernetes-a-beginners-guide-to-the-container-playground-5e5l</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/collinsushi/the-fun-kubernetes-a-beginners-guide-to-the-container-playground-5e5l"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T23:06:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you've been lurking around the tech world, you've probably heard the word Kubernetes being tossed around like it's some kind of secret code for elite engineers. It sounds complex, maybe even intimidating. But guess what? It doesn't have to be. If you've ever played with building blocks, you know how fun it is to stack, rearrange, and create structures. Now, imagine doing the same thing—but with software applications instead of blocks. That’s Kubernetes (K8s) in a nutshell!
Kubernetes (pronounced koo-ber-net-ees) is actually an exciting, powerful, and yes, fun tool once you understand what it does and how it fits into modern software development. This article aims to unpack Kubernetes for absolute beginners using simple language, analogies, and practical insights. By the end, you'll know…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Collins Ushi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Meeting-Centric Tools Fail at Async Work]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/rally_for_jira/why-meeting-centric-tools-fail-at-async-work-mic</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/rally_for_jira/why-meeting-centric-tools-fail-at-async-work-mic"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T23:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Async isn’t just in-sync work with a delay.
It’s a different rhythm entirely.
Trying to force meeting centric tools into async workflows doesn’t work because they rely on live participation, fast decisions, and one-time events.
But async work is continuous. Evolving.
It needs structure that’s flexible, not fixed.
The solution?
Tools built for async from day one, not retrofitted afterward.
Ahem Rally 😅]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rally for Jira</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Arte da Simplicidade no Desenvolvimento de Software: DRY, KISS, YAGNI e TDA]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/diegobrandao/a-arte-da-simplicidade-no-desenvolvimento-de-software-dry-kiss-yagni-e-tda-aak</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/diegobrandao/a-arte-da-simplicidade-no-desenvolvimento-de-software-dry-kiss-yagni-e-tda-aak"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T22:59:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA["A simplicidade é o último grau de sofisticação." - Leonardo da Vinci
Introdução
O que são Princípios de Desenvolvimento de Software?
Por que seguir Princípios de Desenvolvimento é importante?
DRY - Don't Repeat Yourself (Não Se Repita)
DRY e o Padrão Factory
KISS - Keep It Simple, Stupid (Mantenha Simples, Estúpido)
YAGNI - You Aren't Gonna Need It (Você Não Vai Precisar Disso)
TDA - Tell, Don't Ask (Diga, Não Pergunte)
TDA e a Lei de Demeter
Críticas e Limitações dos Princípios
Integrando os Princípios em seu Desenvolvimento
Conclusão
Referências Bibliográficas
No cenário atual do desenvolvimento de software, onde a complexidade dos sistemas cresce exponencialmente, a busca por clareza e simplicidade tornou-se uma necessidade fundamental. Desenvolvedores experientes reconhecem que código…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Diego de Sousa Brandão</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Revolutionizing Blockchain Innovation: The Synergy of Bounty Programs and Project Grants]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/bobcars/revolutionizing-blockchain-innovation-the-synergy-of-bounty-programs-and-project-grants-5bj5</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/bobcars/revolutionizing-blockchain-innovation-the-synergy-of-bounty-programs-and-project-grants-5bj5"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T22:55:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Abstract


This blog post explores how bounty programs and project grants are revolutionizing blockchain innovation. By blending immediate community-driven responses with long‑term financial and technical support, these funding models fuel rapid development, enhance security, and drive decentralized governance. In this detailed guide, we explain the history, core concepts, and technical aspects of these models. We also dive into practical use cases, list challenges, and predict future trends in blockchain innovation such as enhanced interoperability, NFT integration, and advances in zero‑knowledge proofs. With supporting tables, bullet lists, and embedded authoritative resources such as Arbitrum and Ethereum Interoperability and Arbitrum and Community Governance, this post is designed for …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bob Cars(on)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Understanding Core Architectural Components of Microsoft Azure]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/habeeb_hameed_0753445424a/understanding-core-architectural-components-of-microsoft-azure-2hjl</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/habeeb_hameed_0753445424a/understanding-core-architectural-components-of-microsoft-azure-2hjl"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T22:41:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[🌐 Introduction


Microsoft Azure is one of the top cloud platforms today, offering flexible, scalable services for developers, engineers, and businesses. This blog breaks down the core architectural components that power solutions in Azure — from regions to compute, identity, and monitoring.
Azure divides the globe into regions, which are collections of datacenters. Each region may have multiple availability zones, offering redundancy.
📍 Use Case: Deploying a mission-critical app? Use Availability Zones for high availability.

All Azure resources (VMs, databases, etc.) are organized in resource groups. Azure Resource Manager (ARM) lets you manage them as a unit using templates or code.
🧩 Benefits:
Easy grouping for billing
Unified access control
Infrastructure-as-Code (IaC) support
🖼️ …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Habeeb Hameed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blockchain vs. Traditional Databases: A Comprehensive Comparison]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/rachellovestowrite/blockchain-vs-traditional-databases-a-comprehensive-comparison-5h99</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/rachellovestowrite/blockchain-vs-traditional-databases-a-comprehensive-comparison-5h99"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T22:40:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Abstract


This post presents a holistic view and detailed analysis of blockchain technology compared to traditional databases. We discuss their history, key features, applications, challenges, and future outlook. With clear explanations and technical insights, this guide will assist decision makers and developers in understanding when to apply these data management technologies. Along the way, we include tables, bullet lists for quick reference, and several authoritative links, including our original article on Blockchain vs. Traditional Databases.
In today’s data-driven world, efficient data management is essential for businesses of all sizes. Traditional databases have long been the backbone of information storage, while blockchain technology is emerging as a disruptive force. Both appr…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rachel Duncan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘Huge Shift’ in crypto firms’ compliance mindset, says Elliptic co-founder]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/huge-shift-crypto-firms-compliance-mindset-elliptic</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/huge-shift-crypto-firms-compliance-mindset-elliptic?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T22:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The crypto industry has seen a significant shift toward regulatory compliance since its early days, according to James Smith, co-founder of Elliptic, a crypto compliance firm established in 2013.
“In the early days, only a few companies approached compliance in a serious way,” Smith told Cointelegraph at the Token2049 event. “Coinbase was our first customer — they knew from the start that they wanted to build their business that way. But for most others, it just wasn’t a major priority.”Elliptic co-founder James Smith at Token2049. Source: Cointelegraph
That began to shift as regulators, including those in New York State, took a more active interest in the crypto industry. The involvement of traditional financial institutions like Fidelity and DBS Bank also contributed, as they entered the…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Christopher Tepedino</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[&#039;To have freedom of money, you have to have freedom of speech&#039; — CZ]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/to-have-freedom-money-you-need-free-speech-cz</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/to-have-freedom-money-you-need-free-speech-cz?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T22:24:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Binance co-founder and former CEO Changpeng “CZ” Zhao took the stage at Token2049 in Dubai, United Arab Emirates (UAE), where he told the audience that his investment in social media platform X was aimed at protecting freedom of speech.
The former Binance executive joined a fireside panel with macroeconomic analyst Raoul Pal to discuss the rationale behind his 2022 investment in X and artificial intelligence. Zhao said:
"I think freedom of money is important, but to have freedom of money, you have to have freedom of speech. Freedom of speech is kind of the bottom line. If you don't have that, nothing — no other freedom — works."  
"So, when we invested in Twitter back then, it was based on that philosophy," Zhao continued.
The former Binance CEO also criticized Europe's crypto policies, ch…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Vince Quill</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blockchain's Role in Enhancing Open Source Transparency]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/zhangwei42/blockchains-role-in-enhancing-open-source-transparency-2m3b</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/zhangwei42/blockchains-role-in-enhancing-open-source-transparency-2m3b"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T22:24:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Abstract:

This post explores how blockchain technology is revolutionizing open source development by enhancing transparency, accountability, and governance. We discuss blockchain’s core features such as immutability, contribution verification, and decentralized governance, and examine practical use cases and challenges to integration. By comparing traditional open source models with blockchain‐enhanced systems, we offer insights into the future trends and innovations that may shape the open source ecosystem. Links to additional resources—such as blockchain audit trails and blockchain and authenticity—supplement our discussion and provide further reading for enthusiasts and developers.
Blockchain technology is best known for powering cryptocurrencies, but its impact extends far beyond digi…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Zhang Wei</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Espressif's ESP32-C5 Is Now in Mass Production]]></title>
        <id>https://www.espressif.com/en/news/ESP32-C5_Mass_Production</id>
        <link href="https://www.espressif.com/en/news/ESP32-C5_Mass_Production"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T22:15:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Home washing machines fail to remove important pathogens from textiles]]></title>
        <id>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-04-home-machines-important-pathogens-textiles.html</id>
        <link href="https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-04-home-machines-important-pathogens-textiles.html"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T22:04:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tether Finalizes Buying 70% of Adecoagro Stake, Securing Tokenization Ambition]]></title>
        <id>e67b36ce-430f-4d5e-ada9-f091dbc13e04</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/04/30/tether-finalizes-buying-70-of-adecoagro-stake-securing-tokenization-ambition"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T22:03:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The USDT issuer expands beyond crypto with a controlling stake in Adecoagro, a major Latin American producer.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tom Carreras</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Here’s what happened in crypto today]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/what-happened-in-crypto-today</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/what-happened-in-crypto-today?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T22:00:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today in crypto, Ripple reportedly made a $5 billion bid to acquire Circle, an elderly US citizen was targeted in a $330 million Bitcoin social engineering scam, and a court ruled that Tornado Cash cannot be sanctioned again.
Ripple $4B-$5B bid to purchase Circle rejected — Report
Blockchain payments firm Ripple has reportedly bid up to $5 billion in an effort to acquire stablecoin issuer Circle, but the offer was rejected.
According to an April 30 Bloomberg report, Ripple put in a bid of $4 billion to $5 billion as part of an attempted takeover of Circle, which was rejected as being too low. Ripple hasn’t considered whether to make another bid to purchase the stablecoin issuer.
The reported acquisition attempt came less than 30 days after Circle applied for an initial public offering (IPO…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Cointelegraph</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin rebounds from bearish US GDP data as dip buyers push BTC price back toward $95K]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-rebounds-from-bearish-us-gdp-data-as-dip-buyers-push-btc-price-back-toward-95-k</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-rebounds-from-bearish-us-gdp-data-as-dip-buyers-push-btc-price-back-toward-95-k?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T21:58:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Key takeaways: 

Bitcoin bulls are attacking the $95,000 level again after today’s brief US GDP-induced sell-off. 

Traders are semi-agnostic to negative US economic data as they expect the Federal Reserve to resume easing and rate cuts at some point in the future. 

Bitcoin (BTC) price knocks on the door of $95,000 after starting the NY trading session with a slight sell-off to $92,910 following alarm-raising US GDP data, which showed the economy shrank in Q1 2025. The move mirrors a similar recovery seen in the DOW and S&P 500, which bounced 0.35% and 0.15% respectively at the closing bell. 
The quick recovery in Bitcoin price highlights the strong bid by a variety of market participants, and it lines up with the view that the April 30 GDP data could be a one-off event resulting from bus…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Big Smokey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mercury, the first commercial-scale diffusion language model]]></title>
        <id>https://www.inceptionlabs.ai/introducing-mercury</id>
        <link href="https://www.inceptionlabs.ai/introducing-mercury"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T21:51:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bloomberg Intelligence boosts Solana ETF approval odds to 90%]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/bloomberg-boosts-solana-etf-approval-odds-90</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/bloomberg-boosts-solana-etf-approval-odds-90?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T21:47:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bloomberg Intelligence has boosted its estimated odds of US regulators approving a Solana exchange-traded fund (ETF) in 2025 to 90%, according to an April 30 post on the X platform. 
The company also set more favorable chances of approval for other altcoin ETFs, including proposed funds holding XRP (XRP) and Dogecoin (DOGE), Bloomberg analyst Eric Balchunas said in an X post. 
The estimates reflect an improved outlook from Bloomberg analysts. In a February analysis, Bloomberg pegged the odds of a Solana (SOL) ETF approval at only 70%. They ascribed a 65% and 75% chance of approval to funds holding XRP and DOGE, respectively. 
As of April 30, six asset managers — including Grayscale, VanEck and 21Shares — are awaiting clearance from the US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) to list ET…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Alex O’Donnell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase files brief with US Supreme Court in support of taxpayers&#039; privacy]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/coinbase-amicus-irs-user-data-privacy</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/coinbase-amicus-irs-user-data-privacy?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T21:31:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[US-based cryptocurrency exchange Coinbase has filed an amicus brief in the country’s Supreme Court in support of a taxpayer fighting the Internal Revenue Service (IRS) gaining access to his data from a digital asset platform.
In an April 30 filing in the Supreme Court of the United States (SCOTUS), lawyers for Coinbase argued that a First Circuit Court of Appeals decision set a “dangerous precedent” for crypto users, potentially allowing the government to “trace users’ every crypto transaction in the past and monitor every crypto transaction in the future.” The appeal to the Supreme Court stemmed from petitioner James Harper, a Coinbase user, who took legal action against the IRS after the crypto exchange was forced to turn over transaction data to the government using a sweeping “John Doe…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Turner Wright</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[UiPath’s new orchestrator guides AI agents to follow your enterprise’s rules]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3006059</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/uipaths-new-orchestrator-guides-ai-agents-to-follow-your-enterprises-rules/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T21:20:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[UiPath's agent orchestration layer Maestro moves prompts through three layers: the agent, a human and the robotic process automation system.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Emilia David</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Stablecoins on track for $2T market cap by 2028 — US Treasury]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/stablecoins-on-track-for-2-t-market-cap-by-2028-us-treasury</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/stablecoins-on-track-for-2-t-market-cap-by-2028-us-treasury?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T21:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[US Dollar-pegged stablecoins are on track to reach an aggregate market capitalization of approximately $2 trillion by 2028, according to the United States Department of the Treasury’s Q1 2025 report. 
Stablecoins’ cumulative market cap currently stands at roughly $230 billion, but “[e]volving market dynamics [have] the potential to accelerate stablecoins’ trajectory to reach ~$2tn in market cap by 2028,” the Treasury said in the April 30 report. 
A stablecoin is a cryptocurrency whose value is pegged to a traditional asset like the US dollar. According to the report, such tokens are already “ubiquitously utilized as ‘cash on-chain,’ effectively serving as a new payment mechanism.” 
Additionally, the emergence of “tokenized [money market funds] has recently created an alternative option to …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Alex O’Donnell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[3 Ethereum charts flash signal last seen in 2017 when ETH price rallied 25,000%]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/3-ethereum-charts-flash-signal-last-seen-in-2017-when-eth-price-rallied-25-000</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/3-ethereum-charts-flash-signal-last-seen-in-2017-when-eth-price-rallied-25-000?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Key takeaways:

Ether price printed a rare monthly Dragonfly doji candlestick, which is often seen before major ETH bull market cycles.

ETH is retesting its long-term parabolic support zone that preceded its historic 2017 rally.

The MVRV Z-Score has entered the accumulation zone, signaling undervaluation.

Ethereum’s native token, Ether (ETH), is flashing a combination of technical and onchain signals once seen in the early stages of its 2017 bull run, a cycle that produced over 25,000% gains.
Dragonfly doji hints ETH bulls are regaining control
Ether is flashing a rare Dragonfly Doji candlestick on its monthly chart, the same structure that preceded its historic 25,000% rally during the 2017 bull cycle.
This pattern is confirmed when the price prints a long lower wick, little to no uppe…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Yashu Gola</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CZ aims to teach 1 billion kids through Giggle Academy — Token2049]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/cz-wants-teach-1-billion-kids-giggle-academy-token2049</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/cz-wants-teach-1-billion-kids-giggle-academy-token2049?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T20:55:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Binance co-founder Changpeng “CZ” Zhao wants to provide free education for up to a billion children worldwide with his Giggle Academy venture, he told an audience at Token2049 in Dubai, United Arab Emirates (UAE).
"In a few years, I think, I want to teach 100 million or 1 billion kids for free,” Zhao told the audience. Giggle is a free online platform that provides elementary education through gamified lessons.
"With the technologies we have today, it's not that hard to make an app that will stick, that's educational, but also glues the kids to the device," the crypto entrepreneur said.
Raoul Pal pictured (left) and Binance co-founder Changpeng Zhao (right) at the Token2049 conference in Dubai. Source: Cointelegraph
Giggle's concept paper outlines the project's goal of providing K-12 educa…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Vince Quill</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The ‘era of experience’ will unleash self-learning AI agents across the web—here’s how to prepare]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3005579</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/the-era-of-experience-will-unleash-self-learning-ai-agents-across-the-web-heres-how-to-prepare/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T20:38:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AI visionaries predict an 'Era of Experience' where AI learns autonomously, and it will have important implications for application design.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ben Dickson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The best – but not good – way to limit string length]]></title>
        <id>https://adam-p.ca/blog/2025/04/string-length/</id>
        <link href="https://adam-p.ca/blog/2025/04/string-length/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T20:37:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Rebounds From Early Declines Alongside Reversal in U.S. Stocks]]></title>
        <id>24e88b28-a0a9-47ec-9bee-02d4987e2111</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/04/30/crypto-rebounds-from-early-declines-alongside-reversal-in-us-stocks"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T20:34:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The major U.S. stock market averages tumbled about 2% to begin Wednesday following underwhelming economic data.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tom Carreras</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Qwen swings for a double with 2.5-Omni-3B model that runs on consumer PCs, laptops]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3006114</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/qwen-swings-for-a-double-with-2-5-omni-3b-model-that-runs-on-consumer-pcs-laptops/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T20:31:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Qwen2.5-Omni-3B model is licensed for non-commercial use only under Alibaba Cloud’s Qwen Research License Agreement.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carl Franzen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Zhaoxin's KX-7000]]></title>
        <id>https://chipsandcheese.com/p/zhaoxins-kx-7000</id>
        <link href="https://chipsandcheese.com/p/zhaoxins-kx-7000"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T20:23:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin ‘aging’ chart projects sixfold BTC price rally above $350K]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-aging-chart-projects-sixfold-btc-price-rally-above-350-k</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-aging-chart-projects-sixfold-btc-price-rally-above-350-k?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T20:18:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Key takeaways:

Bitcoin’s price increased by sixfold each time its age increased by 40%.

If the pattern holds, Bitcoin could rally to $351,046 in 2025.

New data highlights a historical pattern that results in Bitcoin (BTC) price increasing by sixfold. Using a logarithmic chart to illustrate the trend from 2011, the model projects BTC price to hit $351,046 in 2025.
According to 21st Capital co-founder Sina, the study plots Bitcoin’s price on a log-log graph, showing a linear relationship that reflects predictable long-term growth driven by network dynamics, a behavior characteristic associated with BTC’s limited supply. 
Bitcoin 40% age increase-price rise comparison chart. Source: X.com
The math behind the price target relies on Bitcoin’s age in years and a 6x price multiplier per 40% ag…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Biraajmaan Tamuly</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Robinhood Tops Q1 Earnings Estimates, Boosts Buyback Authorization by $500M]]></title>
        <id>bef454ec-3e49-4c98-9470-ee0c16b33aa3</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/04/30/robinhood-tops-q1-earnings-estimates-boosts-buyback-authorization-by-usd500m"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T20:16:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The trading platform’s results could give an indication for Coinbase’s earnings on May 8.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Helene Braun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tether plans US stablecoin launch as soon as this year — Report]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/tether-plans-us-stablecoin-launch-as-soon-as-this-year-cnbc</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/tether-plans-us-stablecoin-launch-as-soon-as-this-year-cnbc?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T19:55:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tether plans to launch a stablecoin product in the United States as soon as this year, the stablecoin issuer’s CEO, Paul Ardoino, said in an April 30 CNBC interview. 
Tether’s flagship stablecoin, USDT (USDT), is already the US dollar’s top “exporter,” Ardoino told CNBC. It has a market capitalization of nearly $150 billion, according to data from CoinGecko. 
Now, Tether is preparing to expand into the US market “by the end of this year or early next year, at the fastest,” Ardoino said, adding that the timing depends on US lawmakers’ progress on stablecoin legislation. 
The stablecoin issuer is working to woo US regulators by proactively collaborating with law enforcement and highlighting USDT’s benefits for the US economy. 
"We are just exporters of what we believe to be the best product …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Alex O’Donnell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NYC home prices rise 10% in early 2025]]></title>
        <id>https://qns.com/2025/04/home-prices-rise-early-2025-malba-highest-queens/</id>
        <link href="https://qns.com/2025/04/home-prices-rise-early-2025-malba-highest-queens/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T19:43:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[VC Roundup: Funding surge targets confidentiality, tokenization and Web3 infrastructure]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/vc-roundup-funding-surge-targets-confidentiality-tokenization-web3-infrastructure</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/vc-roundup-funding-surge-targets-confidentiality-tokenization-web3-infrastructure?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T19:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After months of volatility and extreme fear, crypto markets turned a positive corner in the second half of April, highlighting the industry’s big sentiment shift. 
For venture capital, it was business as usual, with investors continuing to pour money into promising startups across layer-1 blockchains, infrastructure, real-world asset tokenization (RWA), and Web3 social media.
This edition of VC Roundup highlights six notable funding deals from April.
Unto Labs raises $14.4M for layer-1 blockchain
Blockchain R&D company Unto Labs raised $14.4 million to continue developing its scalable layer-1 network called Thru. The pre-seed and seed funding was led by venture firms Electric Capital and Framework, with support from angel investors in the Solana engineering community.
The company is led by…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Sam Bourgi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Visa and Baanx Launch USDC Stablecoin Payment Cards]]></title>
        <id>56a651a6-1534-40b8-8a7f-4a42e3dccc53</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2025/04/30/visa-and-baanx-launch-usdc-stablecoin-payment-cards"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T19:14:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Visa cards enable holders to spend USDC directly from their crypto wallets, using smart contracts to move a stablecoin balance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ian Allison</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google Play sees 47% decline in apps since start of last year]]></title>
        <id>https://techcrunch.com/2025/04/29/google-play-sees-47-decline-in-apps-since-start-of-last-year/</id>
        <link href="https://techcrunch.com/2025/04/29/google-play-sees-47-decline-in-apps-since-start-of-last-year/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T19:03:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Breaking the ‘intellectual bottleneck’: How AI is computing the previously uncomputable in healthcare]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3005667</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/breaking-the-intellectual-bottleneck-how-ai-is-computing-the-previously-uncomputible-in-healthcare/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T19:03:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How University of Texas Medical Branch is using AI to identify patients at high cardiovascular risk, flag for stroke and catch 'basic stuff.']]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Taryn Plumb</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Linux Kernel Exploitation: Attack of the Vsock]]></title>
        <id>https://hoefler.dev/articles/vsock.html</id>
        <link href="https://hoefler.dev/articles/vsock.html"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T19:03:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum Pectra upgrade goes live next week — Will ETH price rally?]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/ethereum-pectra-upgrade-goes-live-next-week-will-eth-price-rally</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/ethereum-pectra-upgrade-goes-live-next-week-will-eth-price-rally?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T19:01:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Key takeaways:

ETH price has underperformed its peers during the current bull market, but gas sponsorship could lure developers and traders back to the network.

Ethereum’s upcoming Pectra upgrade promises to improve staking efficiency, potentially increasing demand for ETH.

Data suggests ETH price bottomed. Will the Pectra narrative reignite bullish momentum?

Since 2024, ETH (ETH) has been more of a meme than a market mover. Unlike most of its rivals, ETH still hasn’t reclaimed its all-time high of $4,870 from November 2021, and it regularly underperforms even in the weak altcoin market. Currently, ETH trades at $1,813, down 56% from its local peak in December 2024.
Despite the dismal price action, dismissing Ethereum as a relic may be premature. The network continues to evolve, and th…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Marie Poteriaieva</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ripple $4B-$5B bid to purchase Circle rejected — Report]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/ripple-circle-bid-rejected-bloomberg</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/ripple-circle-bid-rejected-bloomberg?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T18:57:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Blockchain payments firm Ripple has reportedly bid up to $5 billion in an effort to acquire stablecoin issuer Circle, but the offer was rejected.
According to an April 30 Bloomberg report, Ripple put in a bid of $4 billion to $5 billion as part of an attempted takeover of Circle, which was rejected as being too low. Ripple hasn’t considered whether to make another bid to purchase the stablecoin issuer.
The reported acquisition attempt came less than 30 days after Circle applied for an initial public offering (IPO) in the US. Cointelegraph reached out to representatives of Circle and Ripple for comment, but had not received a response from either at the time of publication.

Related: Ripple acquisition of Hidden Road a ‘defining moment’ for XRPL — Ripple CTO
Ripple reportedly had an $11 bil…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Turner Wright</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Future of OSU Open Source Lab in Jeopardy]]></title>
        <id>https://osuosl.org/blog/osl-future/</id>
        <link href="https://osuosl.org/blog/osl-future/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T18:51:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Protocol: Inside Movement’s Token-Dump Scandal]]></title>
        <id>35eb5786-2a08-44cb-85ea-77d1ab587b4f</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/tech/2025/04/30/the-protocol-inside-movement-s-token-dump-scandal"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T18:38:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Also: ETH Gas Limit Ceiling Proposal, Bitcoin Data Limits Debate, and Base Becomes a Stage 1 Rollup]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Margaux Nijkerk</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ripple Offered $4B-$5B for Stablecoin Issuer Circle: Bloomberg]]></title>
        <id>a18b01c0-7344-4320-b36a-8ecc617443ec</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2025/04/30/ripple-offered-4b-5b-for-stablecoin-issuer-circle-bloomberg"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T18:38:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The offer was rejected as too low, according to the story.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephen Alpher</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Price predictions 4/30: BTC, ETH, XRP, BNB, SOL, DOGE, ADA, SUI, LINK, AVAX]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/price-predictions-4-30-btc-eth-xrp-bnb-sol-doge-ada-sui-link-avax</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/price-predictions-4-30-btc-eth-xrp-bnb-sol-doge-ada-sui-link-avax?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T18:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Key points:

Bitcoin’s 7-day volatility is the lowest in 563 days, signaling an impending range expansion.

Bitcoin’s breakout above $95,000 could swiftly take it to $100,000 and above.

Although the probability is low, traders should remain cautious about a pullback in the near term.

Bitcoin (BTC) has been trading in a tight consolidation near the $95,000 level for several days. K33 Research head of research Vetle Lunde said in a post on X that Bitcoin’s 7-day volatility has hit a 563-day low.
A range expansion usually follows a low-volatility period. Although it is difficult to predict the direction of the breakout, a tight consolidation just below a crucial resistance increases the likelihood of an upside rally. Several analysts are also optimistic that Bitcoin’s break will occur to th…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Rakesh Upadhyay</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Global demand grows for non-dollar stablecoins, says Fireblocks exec]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/global-demand-grows-non-dollar-stablecoins-fireblocks-exec</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/global-demand-grows-non-dollar-stablecoins-fireblocks-exec?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T18:29:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Governments outside the US, including Singapore, are increasingly interested in stablecoins not tied to the US dollar, despite their currently limited liquidity, Fireblocks director of policy Dea Markova told Cointelegraph at Token2049.
In an exclusive interview, Markova described the competition with dollar-pegged stablecoins as “all about sovereignty.” She compared the situation to earlier tensions between governments and US payment giants like Visa and Mastercard. “Now we’re seeing the same dynamic with stablecoins — on a smaller scale for now — but they’re definitely emerging as a new arena for sovereign concerns,” she said.
According to Markova, dollar-pegged stablecoins operating in the European Union are already "having a massive headache," particularly from central banks. "Even tho…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Christopher Tepedino</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin selling at $95K is ‘profit-taking pressure test’ but BTC whales are still buying]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-selling-at-95-k-is-profit-taking-pressure-test-but-btc-whales-are-still-buying</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-selling-at-95-k-is-profit-taking-pressure-test-but-btc-whales-are-still-buying?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T17:51:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Key Takeaways:

US GDP shrank -0.3% in Q1, far below +0.3% forecasts, sparking recession fears.

Bitcoin faces selling pressure with its spot volume delta dropping $300 million in 3 days.

Whales are accumulating BTC, but smaller holders are selling, hinting at profit-taking.

Bitcoin’s (BTC) price dropped under $93,000 on April 30, after the US Gross Domestic Product (GDP) data revealed a -0.3% contraction in Q1. While the GDP missed expectations of +0.3%, the GDP Price Index soared to 3.7%—the highest since August 2023. Polymarket odds of a recession in 2025 hit 67%, with consumer confidence at its lowest since May 2020.
Quarterly US GDP growth data. Source: X.com
Meanwhile, in March 2025, PCE (Personal Consumption Expenditures) inflation fell to 2.3% (above the expected 2.2%), and Core …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Biraajmaan Tamuly</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Local cosmetics sector can be launchpad to position Malaysia as innovation-led economy: Sirim chief tech officer]]></title>
        <id>f3d9620891e0882d2a66ea582395ca3a</id>
        <link href="https://thesun.my/business-news/local-cosmetics-sector-can-be-launchpad-to-position-malaysia-as-innovation-led-economy-sirim-chief-tech-officer-AH14020110"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T17:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SHAH ALAM: The Malaysian cosmetics sector can serve as a launchpad to position the nation as an innovation-led economy, said Sirim Bhd chief technolog...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hayatun Razak</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Reversible computing with mechanical links and pivots]]></title>
        <id>https://tennysontbardwell.com/blog/2025/04/30/mechanical-computing/index.html</id>
        <link href="https://tennysontbardwell.com/blog/2025/04/30/mechanical-computing/index.html"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T17:35:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NotebookLM Audio Overviews are now available in over 50 languages]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.google/technology/google-labs/notebooklm-audio-overviews-50-languages/</id>
        <link href="https://blog.google/technology/google-labs/notebooklm-audio-overviews-50-languages/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T17:28:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ex-Binance CEO chides Europe over crypto adoption]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/changpeng-zhao-europe-over-crypto-adoption</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/changpeng-zhao-europe-over-crypto-adoption?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T17:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Changpeng “CZ” Zhao, the former CEO of crypto exchange Binance, said most European countries were moving “nowhere” in terms of the adoption of digital currencies.
Speaking at the Token2049 conference in Dubai on April 30, Zhao said that areas of the United Arab Emirates were “extremely pro-business,” leading to crypto adoption in Dubai, while others like Bhutan were building national Bitcoin (BTC) and Ether (ETH) stockpiles. According to Zhao, the US was pressing other countries’ hands by exploring its own policies for a crypto reserve, but those in Europe didn’t seem to be reacting.
“I don’t see Europe in this discussion,” said Zhao, highlighting one exception. “Montenegro is actually quite pro-crypto. We had an active dialogue with [the] prime minister there, and he’s a very forward-thin…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Turner Wright</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Grayscale launches Bitcoin adopters exchange-traded fund]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/grayscale-launches-grayscale-bitcoin-adopters-etf</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/grayscale-launches-grayscale-bitcoin-adopters-etf?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T17:08:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Asset manager Grayscale launched the Grayscale Bitcoin Adopters exchange-traded fund (ETF), an investment vehicle that tracks companies employing a Bitcoin (BTC) treasury, or holding strategy.
According to the April 30 announcement, the ETF will provide exposure to companies across seven business sectors, including Bitcoin mining firms, automotive companies, and energy.
Some of the most notable firms in the ETF include Michael Saylor's Strategy, mining company MARA, automotive manufacturer Tesla, BTC treasury company Metaplanet, and aerospace energy firm KULR Technology Group.
Grayscale's Bitcoin Adopters ETF highlights the growing trend of Bitcoin acquisition companies using the scarce digital asset to drive up shareholder prices and to protect their corporate financial reserves against t…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Vince Quill</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin drops under $93K after US GDP data shows shrinking economy, raising recession alarms]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-drops-under-93-k-after-us-gdp-data-shows-shrinking-economy-raising-recession-alarm</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-drops-under-93-k-after-us-gdp-data-shows-shrinking-economy-raising-recession-alarm?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T17:01:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Key points: 

US GDP shrank in Q1, raising recession alarms while also prompting calls for Fed rate cuts.

Bitcoin dropped to $92,910 as GDP figures were released, but sustained buy-side demand could provide support. 

Today’s crypto derisking is likely transitory; market fundamentals remain strong.

Bitcoin (BTC) price took an abrupt tumble as data showed the US gross domestic product (GDP) retracting by 0.3% in Q1, raising alarms among analysts anticipating a recession. Following the news, BTC price dropped to an intra-day low of $92,910, while the DOW and S&P 500 fell by 1% and 1.3% respectively. 
While the GDP figures are shocking at face value, CNBC pointed out that the drop was primarily due to “a surge in imports ahead of President Donald Trump’s tariffs.” Imports are subtracted fro…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Big Smokey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Archil (YC F24) Is Hiring a Distributed Systems Engineer (In-Person, SF)]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=43848007</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=43848007"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T17:01:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DeepSeek-Prover-V2]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/deepseek-ai/DeepSeek-Prover-V2</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/deepseek-ai/DeepSeek-Prover-V2"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T16:23:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AI-Powered Court System Is Coming to Crypto With GenLayer]]></title>
        <id>df94e6f3-f82a-4505-8d89-de84c57517e8</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/tech/2025/04/30/ai-powered-court-system-is-coming-to-crypto-with-genlayer"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T16:04:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[YeagerAI is building a protocol that uses AI models as judges, with the goal of providing reliable, neutral, third-party arbitration in record time.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tom Carreras</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Show HN: Create your own finetuned AI model using Google Sheets]]></title>
        <id>https://promptrepo.com/finetune/</id>
        <link href="https://promptrepo.com/finetune/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T15:53:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How IPv4 Works – A Handbook for Developers]]></title>
        <id>68124752fa6fa6a9a91d9994</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-ipv4-works-a-handbook-for-developers/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T15:52:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Internet Protocol version 4 (IPv4) is one of the core protocols of standards-based internetworking methods in the Internet and other packet-switched networks. IPv4 is still the most widely deployed Internet protocol. Google’s IPv6 Statistics show...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Omer Rosenbaum</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Show HN: ART – a new open-source RL framework for training agents]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/OpenPipe/ART</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/OpenPipe/ART"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T15:35:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Get Your First SaaS Customers]]></title>
        <id>681242328ca367c7e5d58873</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-get-your-first-saas-customers/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T15:30:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Starting a SaaS (Software as a Service) business is exciting. You’ve put in the long hours building something you believe people will love. But now comes the big question: How do you get your first customers? Getting those first few users can feel li...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Udemezue John</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Alpha-Generating Digital Asset Strategies Will Reshape Alternative Investing]]></title>
        <id>17ae8139-dd24-4790-8dcd-6afeb437e729</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/coindesk-indices/2025/04/30/how-alpha-generating-digital-asset-strategies-will-reshape-alternative-investing"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T15:30:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Now that returns that simply mirror the broader crypto market are easily attainable, investors are looking for more ways to potentially exceed the market, says Lionsoul Global’s Gregory Mall.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gregory Mall</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AI Crypto Agents Are Ushering in a New Era of ‘DeFAI’]]></title>
        <id>f5a3afe9-ab7b-4133-8420-7a13ab9156ec</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/coindesk-indices/2025/04/30/ai-crypto-agents-are-ushering-in-a-new-era-of-defai"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T15:29:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The use of autonomous agents to analyze market trends, balance portfolios and even manage liquidity across decentralized exchanges is a revolution you can’t afford to ignore, says the HBAR Foundation’s Gregg Bell.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gregg Bell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Get User Model in Django – A Simple Guide With Examples]]></title>
        <id>68123f859249b83d2215937d</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-get-user-model-in-django/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T15:19:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When I’m working with Django, one of the first things I often need to do is work with users – like getting the logged-in user, creating a new one, or extending the default user model to add more information. Now, Django has a built-in User model, but...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Udemezue John</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Someone at YouTube needs glasses]]></title>
        <id>https://jayd.ml/2025/04/30/someone-at-youtube-needs-glasses.html</id>
        <link href="https://jayd.ml/2025/04/30/someone-at-youtube-needs-glasses.html"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T15:18:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Oracle ERP Test Automation Guide – Examples and Best Practices]]></title>
        <id>68123ef3b70ffa1e4ce467ae</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/oracle-erp-test-automation-guide/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T15:17:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Oracle Enterprise Resource Planning helps businesses manage finance and supply chains. It also supports human resources and brings different functions together. Many growing businesses rely on it to handle complex tasks, as system failures or errors ...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nazneen Ahmad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OpenAI rolls back ChatGPT’s sycophancy and explains what went wrong]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3006053</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/openai-rolls-back-chatgpts-sycophancy-and-explains-what-went-wrong/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T15:14:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Many organizations may also begin shifting toward open-source alternatives that they can host and tune themselves.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carl Franzen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase Leaps Into Supreme Court Case in Defense of User Data Going to IRS]]></title>
        <id>1fdbaa1e-a5e3-4332-a0a0-78b9de537e9a</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2025/04/30/coinbase-leaps-into-supreme-court-case-in-defense-of-user-data-going-to-irs"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The U.S. crypto exchange filed a brief in a longstanding privacy battle over records the tax agency sought on customers' crypto transactions.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jesse Hamilton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[EU digital product passports won’t solve food fraud, but blockchain can]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/blockchain-can-solve-food-fraud</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/blockchain-can-solve-food-fraud?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Opinion by: Fraser Edwards, co-founder and CEO, Cheqd
Brutal honesty has its place, especially when confronting discomfort, so here’s one that can’t be sweetened with honey: 96% of imported honey in the UK is fake! Tests found that 24 of 25 jars were suspicious or didn’t meet regulatory standards. 
Self-sovereign identity (SSI) can fix this. 
The UK Food Standards Agency and the European Commission both urge reform to tackle this concern by creating a robust traceability database within supply chain networks to ensure consumer transparency and trust. Data, however, is not the problem. The issue is people tampering with it. 
This is not the first time products have been revealed to be inauthentic, with the Honey Authenticity Network highlighting that one-third of all honey products were fak…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Fraser Edwards</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Joining Sun Microsystems – 40 years ago (2022)]]></title>
        <id>https://akapugs.blog/2022/05/03/674/</id>
        <link href="https://akapugs.blog/2022/05/03/674/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T14:57:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Three Omani innovators selected for ITEX 2025 in Malaysia]]></title>
        <id>57ab645df98f4874d208689be5dc65c4</id>
        <link href="https://www.muscatdaily.com/2025/04/30/three-omani-innovators-selected-fpr-itex-2025-in-malaysia/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T14:55:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Three Omani innovators selected to compete at ITEX 2025 in Malaysia. Projects include innovations in water filtration, dental materials, and remote control technology]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nisha Joshi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin price recovers, Ethereum RWA value up 20%: April in charts]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-price-recovers-ethereum-rwa-value-up-april-2025</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-price-recovers-ethereum-rwa-value-up-april-2025?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T14:37:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[April 2025 witnessed crypto markets rocked by more tariffs at the direction of US President Donald Trump — controversial policies that could have influenced the outcome of Canada’s elections on April 28. 
On April 2, Trump levied “discounted reciprocal tariffs” on 185 countries and territories. The Dow Jones Industrial Average dropped 2,200 points on April 4, while the S&P 500 dropped nearly 6%, its largest decline since March 2020. Bitcoin (BTC) went along for the ride but broke from stocks as it recovered toward the end of the month. 
Blockchain adoption metrics for Ethereum are looking good, as the network now boasts 60% real-world asset (RWA) tokenization value. Major firms like BlackRock are sure the blockchain will be the standard for RWAs, but other observers believe that scaling is…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Aaron Wood</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Banks Must Adopt Crypto or 'Be Extinct in 10 Years,' Eric Trump Says]]></title>
        <id>3ac4b718-389d-4e22-8aad-98a97adbf2bd</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2025/04/30/banks-must-adopt-crypto-or-be-extinct-in-10-years-eric-trump-says"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T14:32:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The son of U.S. President Donald Trump said the current financial system is broken and blockchain technology is the fix.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Helene Braun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Coalition Tells SEC Staking Is 'Essential Good,' Not a Security]]></title>
        <id>a61ece06-5e37-4cc3-9eee-c83a72a4a8eb</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2025/04/28/crypto-coalition-tells-sec-staking-is-essential-good-not-a-security"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Industry entities led by the Crypto Council for Innovation argued in a letter to the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission that it shouldn't regulate staking.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jesse Hamilton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[China’s DeepSeek launches new open-source AI after R1 took on OpenAI]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/china-s-deep-seek-launches-new-open-source-ai-after-its-r1-took-on-open-ai</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/china-s-deep-seek-launches-new-open-source-ai-after-its-r1-took-on-open-ai?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T13:47:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Chinese artificial intelligence development company DeepSeek has released a new open-weight large language model (LLM).
DeepSeek uploaded its newest model, Prover V2, to the hosting service Hugging Face on April 30. The latest model, released under the permissive open-source MIT license, aims to tackle math proof verification.
 DeepSeek-Prover-V2 HuggingFace repository. Source: HuggingFace
Prover V2 has 671 billion parameters, making it significantly larger than its predecessors, Prover V1 and Prover V1.5, which were released in August 2024. The paper accompanying the first version explained that the model was trained to translate math competition problems into formal logic using the Lean 4 programming language — a tool widely used for proving theorems.  
The developers say Prover V2 compr…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Adrian Zmudzinski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vitalik Buterin outlines vision as Ethereum ecosystem addresses hit new high]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/vitalik-shares-ethereum-vision-as-addresses-hit-record-high</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/vitalik-shares-ethereum-vision-as-addresses-hit-record-high?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T13:34:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum co-founder Vitalik Buterin released another update on what he believes the future of the network should entail.
In an April 30 post on blockchain-based social media platform Farcaster, Buterin outlined his personal areas of focus for Ethereum development this year. These include investigating changes to the network infrastructure to achieve single-slot finality, updates to smart contract execution and enhancements to privacy.
The post comes as the Ethereum network hits a new milestone. GrowThePie data shows that the weekly number of unique addresses interacting with the Ethereum ecosystem reached a new high of over 15.4 million, with nearly 13.45 million on layer-2 protocols.
Weekly chart of unique active addresses in the Ethereum ecosystem. Source: GrowThePie
Buterin recently arg…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Adrian Zmudzinski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Stagflationary Data Puts Pressure on Bitcoin, Stocks]]></title>
        <id>3c744e3b-2623-4d12-9ee3-371eda918810</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/04/30/stagflationary-data-puts-pressure-on-bitcoin-stocks-early-in-u-s-day"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T13:34:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[U.S. GDP turned negative in the first quarter, while prices rose more than forecast; ADP jobs data was the weakest in nearly one year.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephen Alpher</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trump's Crypto Sherpa Bo Hines Says Crypto Legislation on Target for Quick Completion]]></title>
        <id>4faa7f7a-b9c4-4d0c-9168-a7dd151d1185</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/consensus-toronto-2025-coverage/2025/04/30/trumps-crypto-sherpa-bo-hines-says-crypto-legislation-on-target-for-quick-completion"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T13:28:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The head of the Presidential Council of Advisers for Digital Assets says new laws could be set by August, and Trump's own crypto interests aren't a factor.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jesse Hamilton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[$330M Bitcoin social engineering theft victim is elderly US citizen]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/elderly-us-victim-loses-330m-bitcoin-in-social-engineering-theft</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/elderly-us-victim-loses-330m-bitcoin-in-social-engineering-theft?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T13:18:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An elderly US individual is reportedly the victim of a devastating $330 million Bitcoin heist, now ranked as the fifth-largest crypto hack in history.
The attacker used advanced social engineering tactics to gain access to the victim’s wallet, onchain investigator ZachXBT said in an April 30 update on X.
The hack took place on April 28, 2025, when ZachXBT flagged a suspicious transfer involving 3,520 Bitcoin (BTC), valued at $330.7 million.
Following the transfer, the stolen stash was quickly laundered through over six instant exchanges and swapped into privacy-focused cryptocurrency Monero (XMR).
Onchain data shows that the victim had held over 3,000 BTC since 2017, with no prior history of large-scale transactions.
ZachXBT confirming the victim of the hack. Source: ZachXBT
Once stolen, t…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Amin Haqshanas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CoinDesk 20 Performance Update: Index Declines 2% as Nearly All Assets Trade Lower]]></title>
        <id>c1cd9dad-e07b-4abe-9187-978f1d043b24</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/coindesk-indices/2025/04/30/coindesk-20-performance-update-index-declines-2-as-nearly-all-assets-trade-lower"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T13:12:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Aave (AAVE) fell 4.7% and Ripple (XRP) dropped 4%, leading the index lower from Tuesday.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CoinDesk Indices</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Port of Los Angeles says shipping volume will plummet 35% next week]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cnbc.com/2025/04/29/port-of-los-angeles-sees-shipping-volume-down-35percent-next-week-as-tariffs-bite.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.cnbc.com/2025/04/29/port-of-los-angeles-sees-shipping-volume-down-35percent-next-week-as-tariffs-bite.html"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T13:07:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Show HN: Kexa.io – Open-Source IT Security and Compliance Verification]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=43844665</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=43844665"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T13:04:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The open source debate: Is crypto losing its soul?]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/open-source-debate-crypto-losing-soul</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/open-source-debate-crypto-losing-soul?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T13:03:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto was born from an open-source ethos, where code was shared publicly, accessible for review and shaped by community contributions. Transparency and verifiability are foundational principles that enable trust in Bitcoin.
But as the space matured, some disadvantages of open source surfaced. Innovative smart contract platforms and decentralized finance (DeFi) applications were forked to create direct competitors — from the wave of Uniswap clones to Ethereum forks — which prioritized speed and lower fees over decentralization.
As a result, some projects opted for closed-source development to protect proprietary designs and reduce the risk of exploits, hoping to delay or deter malicious actors by making the code harder to analyze. This approach is often criticized as “security through obsc…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Yohan Yun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto hackers hit DeFi for $92M in April as attacks double from March]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/crypto-hackers-steal-92-m-april-hacked-funds-1-7-b-2025</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/crypto-hackers-steal-92-m-april-hacked-funds-1-7-b-2025?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T13:00:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency hackers stole more than $90 million in April, dealing another blow to the industry’s mainstream reputation despite ongoing efforts to improve cybersecurity.
Hackers made off with $92 million of digital assets across 15 incidents in April, according to an April 30 research report by blockchain cybersecurity firm Immunefi.
The total marks a 124% month-over-month increase from March, when hackers stole $41 million.
Crypto stole in April 2025. Source: Immunefi
The month’s largest hack on open-source platform UPCX accounted for most of the damage in April, with over $70 million in losses, while KiloEx lost $7.5 million as April’s second-largest hack.
The KiloEx exploiter returned the stolen funds just days after the attack occurred.
All of April’s reported attacks targeted decent…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Zoltan Vardai</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Structify raises $4.1M seed to turn unstructured web data into enterprise-ready datasets]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3006010</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/structify-raises-4-1m-seed-to-turn-unstructured-web-data-into-enterprise-ready-datasets/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Brooklyn-based Structify emerges from stealth with $4.1 million in seed funding to transform how businesses prepare data for AI, promising to save data scientists from the task that consumes 80% of their time.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Nuñez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mantra links OM token crash to risky crypto exchange policies]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/mantra-om-token-crash-exchange-risk-policies</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/mantra-om-token-crash-exchange-risk-policies?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T12:34:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Update (April 30, 4:10 pm UTC): This article has been updated to add a comment from Mantra CEO John Mullin.
Decentralized finance (DeFi) platform Mantra has called for industry-wide cooperation to reduce investor risks in the aftermath of its OM token crash.
On April 30, Mantra published its latest update since the sudden collapse of its OM token, claiming that the incident was “bigger than Mantra.”
“Liquidation cascades could happen to any project in the crypto industry,” Mantra CEO John Mullin warned in the post, pointing to the role of “aggressive leverage positions” on exchanges as a broader threat to investor safety.
Mantra’s industry-wide call to action is the biggest section in the latest OM crash update. Source: Mantra
“We’re cooperating with major exchanges to improve market stabi…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Helen Partz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OCaml's Wings for Machine Learning]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/raven-ml/raven</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/raven-ml/raven"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T12:31:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tokenized Apollo Credit Fund Makes DeFi Debut With Levered-Yield Strategy by Securitize, Gauntlet]]></title>
        <id>677307ee-e3e4-4cc2-bf42-97ffd9c4e6fd</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/04/30/tokenized-apollo-credit-fund-makes-defi-debut-with-levered-yield-strategy-by-securitize-gauntlet"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T12:17:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The offering aims to make real-world asset tokens competitive with stablecoins for DeFi yield strategies, Securitize's Reid Simon said.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Krisztian Sandor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin macro indicator that predicted 2022 bottom flashes &#039;buy signal&#039;]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-macro-indicator-predicted-2022-bottom-flashes-buy</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-macro-indicator-predicted-2022-bottom-flashes-buy?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T12:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Key takeaways:

Macro Chain Index issues first buy signal since 2022, hinting at a new Bitcoin bull run.

RSI crossover on the MCI aligns with past cycle bottoms that preceded 500%+ BTC rallies.

Bitcoin price recovers from $74K to $95K amid rising open interest and positive funding rates.

A key Bitcoin (BTC) indicator that accurately signaled the 2022 market bottom has just flashed another buy signal, suggesting the cryptocurrency may be entering a new bull phase.
Bitcoin metric hints at “absolute bottom”
Dubbed the Macro Chain Index (MCI), the indicator is a composite of several long-term on-chain and macroeconomic metrics. 
It analyzes factors such as accumulation behavior, network activity, and supply trends, helping identify whether Bitcoin is undervalued or overvalued relative to it…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Yashu Gola</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FIFA shifts NFT platform to new Ethereum-compatible blockchain]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/fifa-collect-nfts-move-to-evm-blockchain</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/fifa-collect-nfts-move-to-evm-blockchain?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T12:12:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Federation Internationale de Football Association (FIFA) plans to launch a new blockchain network to support its non-fungible token (NFT) collectibles, the organization announced on April 30.
FIFA will launch its “FIFA Blockchain,” with Ethereum Virtual Machine (EVM) compatibility and aims to provide “better performance, future features, and improved scalability.”
As part of the move, FIFA Collect — its official NFT collection — will migrate from the Algorand blockchain to the new FIFA Blockchain. The migration is scheduled to begin no earlier than May 20, FIFA said.  
FIFA announces new blockchain for FIFA collection migration. Source: collect.fifa.com

“At this stage, no immediate action is required. When the migration process begins, we will provide clear, step-by-step instructions …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Zoltan Vardai</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Download: stereotypes in AI models, and the new age of coding]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1115952</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/04/30/1115952/the-download-stereotypes-in-ai-models-and-the-new-age-of-coding/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T12:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is today’s edition of The Download, our weekday newsletter that provides a daily dose of what’s going on in the world of technology. This data set helps researchers spot harmful stereotypes in LLMs What’s new? AI models are riddled with culturally specific biases. A new data set, called SHADES, is designed to help developers combat the…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rhiannon Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mastercard Introduces Agent Pay, A New System For AI-Led Commerce]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=350185</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/350185/mastercard-introduces-agent-pay/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T12:04:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mastercard has introduced a new technology called “Agent Pay”, aimed at powering secure and intelligent payments in a world increasingly shaped by artificial intelligence. Developed with companies including Microsoft and other leading AI platforms, the system is designed to allow AI agents – such as virtual assistants, chatbots, or autonomous shopping tools – to initiate […]
The post Mastercard Introduces Agent Pay, A New System For AI-Led Commerce appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Heirul Kamel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Retailers will soon have only about 7 weeks of full inventories left]]></title>
        <id>https://fortune.com/article/retailers-weeks-of-inventory-left-trump-china-trade-war/</id>
        <link href="https://fortune.com/article/retailers-weeks-of-inventory-left-trump-china-trade-war/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T11:42:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Daybook Americas: Robinhood Earnings to Preview Trump's 'Damage']]></title>
        <id>0b8f55d6-8763-4cc6-9352-6bfcb3db8bab</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/daybook-us/2025/04/30/crypto-daybook-americas-biggest-tokens-show-restraint-for-now-but-damage-has-already-been-done"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T11:17:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Your day-ahead look for April 30, 2025]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Francisco Rodrigues</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nasdaq Seeks SEC Approval to List 21Shares Dogecoin ETF]]></title>
        <id>11f6cfaa-74d7-43a5-b5cd-081a49c73d92</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/04/30/nasdaq-seeks-sec-approval-to-list-21shares-dogecoin-etf"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T11:06:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase Custody Trust will hold the fund’s tokens and serve as the official custodian for the ETF.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shaurya Malwa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Inside Movement’s Token-Dump Scandal: Secret Contracts, Shadow Advisers and Hidden Middlemen]]></title>
        <id>ca25f2fb-f887-4098-86ec-a0104210e64e</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/tech/2025/04/30/inside-movement-s-token-dump-scandal-secret-contracts-shadow-advisors-and-hidden-middlemen"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Movement, backed by Trump's World Liberty Financial, says it was duped into an agreement that experts say incentivized price manipulation.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sam Kessler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Week In Gaming: EA Cancels Titanfall Game, Borderlands 4 Gets New Release Date, And More]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=350162</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/350162/this-week-in-gaming/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T10:53:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’re halfway through the week, and in the world of gaming, some things have happened but not in such a major fashion that it would make waves. That being said, their occurrence is still important enough to warrant a report and as such, here’s a quick list of them. EA Lays Off Hundreds Of Staff, […]
The post This Week In Gaming: EA Cancels Titanfall Game, Borderlands 4 Gets New Release Date, And More appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John Law</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[KuCoin Commits $2B to 'Trust Project' Focusing on Crypto Security, Transparency]]></title>
        <id>2a3c88da-cd66-4d75-8f07-1dbedc9e3cc9</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2025/04/30/kucoin-commits-usd2-billion-to-trust-project-focusing-on-crypto-security-and-transparency"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T10:08:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[KuCoin’s native token, KCS, will play a more pivotal role in the ecosystem.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Omkar Godbole</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Samsung One UI 8 Might Bring AI Video Summarisation]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=350177</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/350177/samsung-one-ui-8-might-bring-ai-video-summarisation/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T09:50:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Samsung will reportedly bring an AI video summarisation tool in its One UI 8 based on Android 16. As reported by SammyGuru, the tool will be able to analyse a video, based on speech, visuals, and captions. A multi-modal AI model will then summarise the main points of the video. The feature will apparently be […]
The post Samsung One UI 8 Might Bring AI Video Summarisation appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Newsdesk</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This data set helps researchers spot harmful stereotypes in LLMs]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1115946</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/04/30/1115946/this-data-set-helps-researchers-spot-harmful-stereotypes-in-llms/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T09:41:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AI models are riddled with culturally specific biases. A new data set, called SHADES, is designed to help developers combat the problem by spotting harmful stereotypes and other kinds of discrimination that emerge in AI chatbot responses across a wide range of languages. Margaret Mitchell, chief ethics scientist at AI startup Hugging Face, led the…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rhiannon Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chery Tiggo Cross HEV To Get Malaysian Appearance In May]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=350155</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/350155/chery-tiggo-cross-hev-to-get-malaysian-appearance-in-may/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T09:04:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This year’s edition of the Malaysia Auto Show is scheduled to happen in May as it usually does, but it looks like Chery may have a hybrid car to showcase during the event. This may come in the form of the Tiggo Cross, which may be known instead as the Tiggo 4 elsewhere. Paul Tan […]
The post Chery Tiggo Cross HEV To Get Malaysian Appearance In May appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ian Chee</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Xiaomi Debuts Its Own AI Model]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=350157</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/350157/xiaomi-debuts-its-own-ai-model/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T08:57:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Xiaomi has recently unveiled MiMo, its in-house open source AI model with reasoning capabilities. With the release of the large language model, the company has joined the ranks of China’s tech firms, hoping to gain a foothold in the AI industry. According to Xiaomi, MiMo was developed by Core, a specialised AI task force. The […]
The post Xiaomi Debuts Its Own AI Model appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nurul Kamil</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Xiaomi MiMo Reasoning Model]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/XiaomiMiMo/MiMo</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/XiaomiMiMo/MiMo"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T08:48:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Debate on Looser Data Limits Brings to Mind the Divisive Ordinals Controversy]]></title>
        <id>6feae542-2b1a-4681-be27-d67fdf8e8d0f</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/tech/2025/04/30/bitcoin-debate-on-looser-data-limits-brings-to-mind-the-divisive-ordinals-controversy"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T08:44:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Removing the blockchain's OP_RETURN size controls would allow more data to be embedded in transactions. Critics say this will only be used for spam.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sam Reynolds</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin May Evolve Into Low-Beta Equity Play Reflexively, BlackRock's Mitchnik Says]]></title>
        <id>74f0300a-3daa-4fd9-a866-5e9ec9ac6149</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2025/04/30/bitcoin-may-evolve-into-low-beta-equity-play-blackrocks-mitchnik-says"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T08:39:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA["It makes no fundamental sense, and yet when it's repeated enough, it can actually become a little self-fulfilling,” Mitchnik said.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Omkar Godbole</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trump Administration Could Alter Biden-Era AI Chip Rule]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=350146</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/350146/trump-administration-could-alter-biden-era-ai-chip-rule/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T08:24:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[US President Trump and his administration could be looking to bring back a Biden-era rule regarding the export of AI chips to other countries. Supposedly, it’s planning on making a few tweaks to the rule and, in conjunction, do away with its current way of segregating recipient countries into three tiers. According to sources close […]
The post Trump Administration Could Alter Biden-Era AI Chip Rule appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John Law</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Apple Watch SE 3 Display Leaked, May Come In Two Sizes]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=350132</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/350132/apple-watch-se-3-display-leaked-two-sizes/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T08:13:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There is a chance that Apple might be releasing its Watch SE 3 soon, possibly this year, as reported by 9to5Mac. The original model of the watch was released back in 2020, with the 2nd generation being launched two years later in 2022. Like the two preceding models, the third generation may also come in […]
The post Apple Watch SE 3 Display Leaked, May Come In Two Sizes appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ian Chee</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Leaderboard Illusion]]></title>
        <id>https://arxiv.org/abs/2504.20879</id>
        <link href="https://arxiv.org/abs/2504.20879"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T07:58:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[realme 14T Set To Land In Malaysia On 16 May]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=350149</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/350149/realme-14t-16-may/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T07:51:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hot on the heels of its recent launch of the 14 series, realme has revealed that it will be launching the 14T next month. The upcoming device has been listed on the brand’s official Shopee page with an arrival date of 16 May 2025. Aside from the first sale date, the listing also reveals that […]
The post realme 14T Set To Land In Malaysia On 16 May appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ikmal Rozlan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[I created Perfect Wiki and reached $250k in annual revenue without investors]]></title>
        <id>https://habr.com/en/articles/905812/</id>
        <link href="https://habr.com/en/articles/905812/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T07:45:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BlackRock Looking to Tokenize Shares of Its $150B Treasury Trust Fund, SEC Filing Shows]]></title>
        <id>c3e9da3d-b1ba-4d10-99bf-07ac25dd1351</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/04/30/sec-filing-shows-blackrock-preparing-150-billion-tokenized-treasury-trust-offering"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T06:15:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BlackRock will work with BNY Mellon in creating a new class of Distributed Ledger Technology shares for the fund.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sam Reynolds</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Samsung To Add Direct Access To Gemini For Galaxy A Series]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=350134</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/350134/samsung-adds-direct-access-gemini-for-galaxy-a-series/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T06:10:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Samsung has announced that it is adding a feature to select Galaxy A series devices that allows users to directly access Gemini using the side button. With this feature, which is already available on the company’s Galaxy S series, users can simply press and hold the side button to activate the AI assistant. The upcoming […]
The post Samsung To Add Direct Access To Gemini For Galaxy A Series appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nurul Kamil</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Telegram’s TON Takes On Real World Assets With Libre’s $500M Tokenized Bond Fund]]></title>
        <id>ebe6875e-7c61-4b31-9f2e-03a0d9648aa6</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2025/04/30/telegram-s-ton-takes-on-real-world-assets-with-libre-s-usd500m-tokenized-bond-fund"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T06:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Libre’s Telegram Bond Fund ($TBF) will offer accredited investors institutional-grade yield products that will also be available as collateral for on-chain borrowing and product development on TON,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ian Allison</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google’s “Audio Overviews” Feature For NotebookLM Now Supports Bahasa Malaysia]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=350138</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/350138/google-audio-overviews-now-supports-bahasa-malaysia/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T05:59:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google has updated its AI-powered learning tool, NotebookLM, by introducing support for more than 50 languages in its Audio Overviews feature. With this update, users can now generate podcast-style summaries of their submitted content in languages beyond English — including Bahasa Malaysia. According to a recent blog post, Google says the expansion is part of […]
The post Google’s “Audio Overviews” Feature For NotebookLM Now Supports Bahasa Malaysia appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Heirul Kamel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SEC Delays Dogecoin and XRP ETF Decisions]]></title>
        <id>6bb80abf-8034-42d9-991c-6a51ab9ce9a3</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/04/30/sec-delays-dogecoin-and-xrp-etf-decisions"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T05:25:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The delays are expected as most ETF filings have final deadlines in October or beyond, one analyst pointed out.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shaurya Malwa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sycophancy in GPT-4o]]></title>
        <id>https://openai.com/index/sycophancy-in-gpt-4o/</id>
        <link href="https://openai.com/index/sycophancy-in-gpt-4o/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T03:06:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Malaysia attracts US$3.7 billion in digital investments, solidifying]]></title>
        <id>b95e1bfb983c9cc102bc4266d362a8c2</id>
        <link href="https://www.digitalnewsasia.com/digital-economy/malaysia-attracts-us37-billion-digital-investments-solidifying-position-aseans-tech"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T02:31:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Malaysia’s digital economy continues to go from strength to strength, emerging as a strategic engine of growth that creates jobs, opens new opportunities, and fosters local innovation for businesses]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>@DigitalNewsAsia</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MDV powers Malaysia's tech innovation with over RM13bil financing]]></title>
        <id>d3f5fdc4ea236d719dc3a9d352d4620c</id>
        <link href="https://www.nst.com.my/business/corporate/2025/04/1209375/mdv-powers-malaysias-tech-innovation-over-rm13bil-financing"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T01:56:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[KUALA LUMPUR: Malaysia Debt Ventures Bhd (MDV) has emerged as a key enabler of the nation’s innovation and digital transformation agenda, with more than RM13 billion channelled into over 1,000 high-impact, technology-driven projects.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bernama</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[You Wouldn't Download a Hacker News]]></title>
        <id>https://www.jasonthorsness.com/25</id>
        <link href="https://www.jasonthorsness.com/25"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T01:26:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[No more window switching: Mastercard’s Agent Pay transforms how enterprises use AI search]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3005997</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/no-more-window-switching-mastercards-agent-pay-transforms-how-enterprises-use-ai-search/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T22:24:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mastercard is working with AI companies and banks to allow AI platforms and agents to facilitate transactions.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Emilia David</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meta unleashes Llama API running 18x faster than OpenAI: Cerebras partnership delivers 2,600 tokens per second]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3005976</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/meta-unleashes-llama-api-running-18x-faster-than-openai-cerebras-partnership-delivers-2600-tokens-per-second/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T20:02:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Meta partners with Cerebras to launch its new Llama API, offering developers AI inference speeds up to 18 times faster than traditional GPU solutions, challenging OpenAI and Google in the fast-growing AI services market.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Nuñez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meta’s first dedicated AI app is here with Llama 4 — but it’s more consumer than productivity or business oriented]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3005961</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/metas-first-dedicated-ai-app-is-here-with-llama-4-but-its-more-consumer-than-productivity-or-business-oriented/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T18:19:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This mainstream exposure will likely accelerate a shift in what people expect not just from consumer apps, but from workplaces...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carl Franzen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Create Accessible and User-Friendly Forms in React]]></title>
        <id>6810f59e8deee87383c1bc46</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-create-accessible-and-user-friendly-forms-in-react/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T15:51:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When designing web applications, you’ll often be asked the age old question “How accessible is your website” and “Does it offer the best user experience?”. These are both very valid questions, but they are often overlooked in favour of rich or fancy ...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Grant Riordan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn College Calculus and Implement with Python]]></title>
        <id>6810eebd43aa3d16a14700eb</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-college-calculus-and-implement-with-python/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T15:22:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Calculus is one of the cornerstones of higher mathematics and a powerful tool for understanding change, motion, and growth across countless disciplines. But for many students, Calculus can seem intimidating or abstract. What if you could learn it ste...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Register Models in Django Admin]]></title>
        <id>6810e5a2dc9845a2ab207f06</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-register-models-in-django-admin/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T14:43:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When you're building a website or an app with Django, one of the most exciting moments is when your database models finally come to life. But to manage your data easily – adding, editing, or deleting entries – you need Django’s Admin panel. Now, here...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Udemezue John</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Jepsen: Amazon RDS for PostgreSQL 17.4]]></title>
        <id>https://jepsen.io/analyses/amazon-rds-for-postgresql-17.4</id>
        <link href="https://jepsen.io/analyses/amazon-rds-for-postgresql-17.4"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T14:30:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tripp launches Kōkua AI as mental wellness coach across multiple platforms]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3005798</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/games/tripp-launches-kokua-ai-as-mental-wellness-coach-across-multiple-platforms/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T13:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tripp launched Kōkua AI, a mental wellness guide designed to deliver real-time, personalized emotional support across multiple platforms.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dean Takahashi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[xMEMS extends micro cooling fan-on-a-chip tech to AI data centers]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3005879</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/game-development/xmems-extends-micro-cooling-fan-on-a-chip-tech-to-ai-data-centers/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[xMEMS Labs, a pioneer of MEMS-based chips, announced that its innovative µCooling fan-on-a-chip tech will be expanded to AI data centers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dean Takahashi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New atomic fountain clock joins group that keeps the world on time]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nist.gov/news-events/news/2025/04/new-atomic-fountain-clock-joins-elite-group-keeps-world-time</id>
        <link href="https://www.nist.gov/news-events/news/2025/04/new-atomic-fountain-clock-joins-elite-group-keeps-world-time"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T12:39:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Is "Induced Atmospheric Vibration"?]]></title>
        <id>https://physics.stackexchange.com/questions/848666/what-is-induced-atmospheric-vibration</id>
        <link href="https://physics.stackexchange.com/questions/848666/what-is-induced-atmospheric-vibration"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T12:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Download: the AI Hype Index, and “normal” AI]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1115932</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/04/29/1115932/the-download-the-ai-hype-index-and-normal-ai/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T12:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is today’s edition of The Download, our weekday newsletter that provides a daily dose of what’s going on in the world of technology. The AI Hype Index: AI agent cyberattacks, racing robots, and musical models Separating AI reality from hyped-up fiction isn’t always easy. That’s why we’ve created the AI Hype Index—a simple, at-a-glance summary of…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rhiannon Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The AI Hype Index: AI agent cyberattacks, racing robots, and musical models]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1115918</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/04/29/1115918/the-ai-hype-index-ai-agent-cyberattacks-racing-robots-and-musical-models/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Separating AI reality from hyped-up fiction isn’t always easy. That’s why we’ve created the AI Hype Index—a simple, at-a-glance summary of everything you need to know about the state of the industry. AI agents are the AI industry’s hypiest new product—intelligent assistants capable of completing tasks without human supervision. But while they can be theoretically…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Editors</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Web3j Six Month Project Update]]></title>
        <id>68109495670a1300013504c2</id>
        <link href="https://blog.web3labs.com/web3j-six-month-project-update/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T09:10:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[November 2024 - April 2025
This report summarizes the activities and accomplishments of Web3j, an LF Decentralized Trust project, from November 2024 to April 2025. During this period, the project made significant strides in improving the framework’s functionality, enhancing user engagement, and bolstering overall community interaction. 
Key]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>George Tebrean</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[We need to start thinking of AI as “normal”]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1115928</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/04/29/1115928/is-ai-normal/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Right now, despite its ubiquity, AI is seen as anything but a normal technology. There is talk of AI systems that will soon merit the term “superintelligence,” and the former CEO of Google recently suggested we control AI models the way we control uranium and other nuclear weapons materials. Anthropic is dedicating time and money…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>James O'Donnell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Alibaba launches open source Qwen3 model that surpasses OpenAI o1 and DeepSeek R1]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3005880</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/alibaba-launches-open-source-qwen3-model-that-surpasses-openai-o1-and-deepseek-r1/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-28T23:56:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Qwen3’s open-weight release under an accessible license marks an important milestone, lowering barriers for developers and organizations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carl Franzen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ex-OpenAI CEO and power users sound alarm over AI sycophancy and flattery of users]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3005850</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/ex-openai-ceo-and-power-users-sound-alarm-over-ai-sycophancy-and-flattery-of-users/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-28T21:49:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crucially, the turbulence also nudges many organizations to explore open-source models they can host, monitor, and fine-tune themselves.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carl Franzen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Beyond A2A and MCP: How LOKA’s Universal Agent Identity Layer changes the game]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3005824</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/beyond-a2a-and-mcp-how-lokas-universal-agent-identity-layer-changes-the-game/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-28T20:35:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The LOKA protocol, a proposed standard for AI agents from Carnegie Mellon University researchers, will give identities and intentions to agents.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Emilia David</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build a Production-Ready DevOps Pipeline with Free Tools]]></title>
        <id>680fe1e69418a1165cb184a2</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-build-a-production-ready-devops-pipeline-with-free-tools/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-28T20:15:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A few months ago, I dove into DevOps, expecting it to be an expensive journey requiring costly tools and infrastructure. But I discovered you can build professional-grade pipelines using entirely free resources. If DevOps feels out of reach because y...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Opaluwa Emidowojo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[30 seconds vs. 3: The d1 reasoning framework that’s slashing AI response times]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3005393</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/30-seconds-vs-3-the-d1-reasoning-framework-thats-slashing-ai-response-times/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-28T19:31:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[d1 framework changes boosts diffusion LLMs with novel reinforcement learning, unlocking efficient, problem-solving AI possibilities.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ben Dickson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build a Website from Scratch – Start to Finish Walkthrough]]></title>
        <id>680fd51ef631538076304a73</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-build-a-website-from-scratch-start-to-finish-walkthrough/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-28T19:21:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, fellow developers! Building a website can feel overwhelming at first – especially when you're staring at a blank HTML file, wondering how it ever turns into a real website on the internet. If you're new to web development, you've probably asked y...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kunal Nalawade</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Writer releases Palmyra X5, delivers near GPT-4.1 performance at 75% lower cost]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3005734</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/writer-releases-palmyra-x5-delivers-near-gpt-4-performance-at-75-lower-cost/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-28T17:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Writer unveils Palmyra X5: The enterprise AI model that processes 1,500 pages at once, costs 75% less than GPT-4, and enables affordable autonomous agents for businesses seeking automation ROI.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Nuñez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[QuickNode: Building the Infrastructure for the Next Generation of Blockchain]]></title>
        <id>6807d5787fb8500001c39b99</id>
        <link href="https://blog.quicknode.com/quicknode-building-the-infrastructure-for-the-next-generation-of-blockchain/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-28T16:02:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Join QuickNode co-founder Dmitry Shklovsky as he discusses blockchain infrastructure, building decentralized applications, and the future of Web3 development on TheCube's Crypto Trailblazer Series.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>QuickNode</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Enable CORS in Django]]></title>
        <id>680fa40e9096ceb5eeedd90e</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-enable-cors-in-django/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-28T15:51:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you've ever tried to connect your frontend app to your Django backend and suddenly hit an error that looks something like "has been blocked by CORS policy", you're not alone. It’s frustrating, especially when your code seems fine. So what’s going ...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Udemezue John</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Download: China’s manufacturers’ viral moment, and how AI is changing creativity]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1115909</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/04/28/1115909/the-download-chinas-manufacturers-viral-moment-and-how-ai-is-changing-creativity/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-28T12:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is today’s edition of The Download, our weekday newsletter that provides a daily dose of what’s going on in the world of technology. Why Chinese manufacturers are going viral on TikTok Since the video was posted earlier this month, millions of TikTok users have watched as a young Chinese man in a blue T-shirt sits beside…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rhiannon Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Does RAG make LLMs less safe?  Bloomberg research reveals hidden dangers]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3005592</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/does-rag-make-llms-less-safe-bloomberg-research-reveals-hidden-dangers/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-28T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[RAG is supposed to make enterprise AI more accurate, but it could potentially also make it less safe according to new research.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sean Michael Kerner</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Chinese manufacturers are going viral on TikTok]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1115876</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/04/28/1115876/why-chinese-manufacturers-are-going-viral-on-tiktok/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-28T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Since the video was posted earlier this month, millions of TikTok users have watched as a young Chinese man in a blue T-shirt sits beside a traditional tea set and speaks directly to the camera in accented English: “Let’s expose luxury’s biggest secret.”  He stands and lifts what looks like an Hermès Birkin bag, one…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Caiwei Chen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[UPDATED] Malaysia and Maldives explore new ties in solar, defence, and digital tech [WATCH]]]></title>
        <id>2ff00997f9c35cff9b55bf1c234d9fd9</id>
        <link href="https://www.nst.com.my/news/nation/2025/04/1208426/updated-malaysia-and-maldives-explore-new-ties-solar-defence-and-digital"/>
        <updated>2025-04-28T04:17:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[PUTRAJAYA: Malaysia is eager to explore new avenues of cooperation with the Maldives, including floating solar energy, defence, and digital technology, says Datuk Seri Anwar Ibrahim.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hakim Mahari</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Retail & E-Commerce Innovation Marketing & Tech Summit: Malaysia 2025]]></title>
        <id>cd2a0d19be53d9723fc0475f09d0da2d</id>
        <link href="https://marketech-apac.com/conference/retail-e-commerce-innovation-marketing-tech-summit-malaysia-2025/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-28T01:58:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Retail & E-Commerce Innovation Marketing & Tech Summit: Malaysia 2025]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Zyra Kate Capilastique</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Is your AI product actually working? How to develop the right metric system]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3005642</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/is-your-ai-product-actually-working-how-to-develop-the-right-metric-system/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-27T19:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Metrics are critical for determining AI product performance. But where to begin? Here's a framework to apply across various use cases.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sharanya Rao, Intuit</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bits + Bytes: A Miscellany Of Technology]]></title>
        <id>92c9e6ae0de9449f2a2cd9808d52c95a</id>
        <link href="https://theedgemalaysia.com/node/752832"/>
        <updated>2025-04-27T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[NEWS

Malaysia sees tech salary surge in 2025, led by system engineers

Tech salaries in Malaysia have risen significantly this year, with system engineers recording the highest increase at 8%, according to NodeFlair’s Tech Salary Report 2...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Edge Malaysia</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FORKLIFTACTION, B2B news service and business platform about forklifts and materials handling]]></title>
        <id>20065c212264065b824a3328d06be4fc</id>
        <link href="https://www.forkliftaction.com/pagenotfound.aspx"/>
        <updated>2025-04-27T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[FORKLIFTACTION, B2B news service and business platform about forklifts and materials handling]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Forkliftaction</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DeepSeek’s success shows why motivation is key to AI innovation]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3005636</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/deepseeks-success-shows-why-motivation-is-key-to-ai-innovation/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-26T19:55:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How did DeepSeek attain such cost-savings while American companies could not? Let's dive into the technical details.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Debasish Ray Chawdhuri, Talentica Software</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The True Size Of]]></title>
        <id>https://thetruesize.com/</id>
        <link href="https://thetruesize.com/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-26T15:41:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Malaysia remains 9th largest global exporter of high-tech products]]></title>
        <id>ec83e12fc9489689eba3a736f7c0fd4e</id>
        <link href="https://e.vnexpress.net/news/tech/tech-news/malaysia-remains-9th-largest-global-exporter-of-high-tech-products-4878750.html"/>
        <updated>2025-04-26T02:41:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Malaysia successfully maintained its position as the ninth-largest exporter of high-tech goods out of 143 economies in 2023, the highest recognition it has achieved in the past decade, Bernama has reported.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>VnExpress</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Liquid AI is revolutionizing LLMs to work on edge devices like smartphones with new ‘Hyena Edge’ model]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3005611</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/liquid-ai-is-revolutionizing-llms-to-work-on-edge-devices-like-smartphones-with-new-hyena-edge-model/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-25T22:02:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hyena Edge’s success positions Liquid AI as one of the emerging players to watch in the evolving AI model landscape.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carl Franzen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The new AI calculus: Google’s 80% cost edge vs. OpenAI’s ecosystem]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3005571</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/the-new-ai-calculus-googles-80-cost-edge-vs-openais-ecosystem/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-25T20:26:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Explore the Google vs OpenAI AI ecosystem battle post-o3. Deep dive into Google's huge cost advantage (TPU vs GPU), agent strategies & model risks for enterprise]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matt Marshall</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Malaysia remains 9th largest global exporter of high-tech products]]></title>
        <id>e1054193ac5220fd5f3cf3fb0ac3fcbd</id>
        <link href="https://en.vietnamplus.vn/malaysia-remains-9th-largest-global-exporter-of-high-tech-products-post318075.vnp"/>
        <updated>2025-04-25T18:11:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Malaysia’s high-tech exports increased by 2 billion USD to reach 127 billion USD in 2023. He said high-tech exports comprised 58.69% of total manufacturing exports in 2023, up from 52.48% recorded in 2022.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Vietnam+ (VietnamPlus)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[UK agrees to assist Malaysia in technology, new energy]]></title>
        <id>9bba1ab03b6cc59e6474a313d3bc9d9c</id>
        <link href="https://theedgemalaysia.com/node/753068"/>
        <updated>2025-04-25T15:31:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The UK has agreed to collaborate with Malaysia in various fields, including technology and new energy management, said Deputy Prime Minister Datuk Seri Fadillah Yusof.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Edge Malaysia</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Download: how Trump’s tariffs will affect US manufacturing, and AI architecture]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1115868</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/04/25/1115868/the-download-how-trumps-tariffs-will-affect-us-manufacturing-and-ai-architecture/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-25T12:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is today’s edition of The Download, our weekday newsletter that provides a daily dose of what’s going on in the world of technology. Sweeping tariffs could threaten the US manufacturing rebound Despite the geopolitical chaos and market collapses triggered by President Trump’s announcement of broad tariffs on international goods, some supporters still hope the strategy will…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rhiannon Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Need to embrace technological advancements, sustainable practices discussed at country's premier real estate event]]></title>
        <id>13ba8e804fd9567fa951b4f7cc51bead</id>
        <link href="https://theedgemalaysia.com/node/753073"/>
        <updated>2025-04-25T12:00:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Industry leaders, policymakers, investors and experts explored the future of Malaysia's real estate landscape at the National Real Estate Convention (NREC) 2025 held here recently.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Edge Malaysia</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sweeping tariffs could threaten the US manufacturing rebound]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1115827</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/04/25/1115827/sweeping-tariffs-could-threaten-the-us-manufacturing-rebound/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-25T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Despite the geopolitical chaos and market collapses triggered by President Trump’s announcement of broad tariffs on international goods, some supporters still hope the strategy will produce a “golden age” of American industry. Trump himself insists, “Jobs and factories will come roaring back into our country.” While it’s possible that very targeted tariffs could help protect…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Rotman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Is that really your boss calling? Jericho Security raises $15M to stop deepfake fraud that’s cost businesses $200M in 2025 alone]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3005473</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/is-that-really-your-boss-calling-jericho-security-raises-15m-to-stop-deepfake-fraud-thats-cost-businesses-200m-in-2025-alone/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-24T22:18:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Pentagon-backed Jericho Security raises $15 million to combat deepfake fraud that has already cost North American businesses $200 million in 2025, using AI to detect increasingly convincing voice and video impersonations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Nuñez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Intel’s new CEO signals streamlining efforts but does not spell out exact layoff numbers]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3005456</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/games/intels-new-ceo-signals-streamlining-efforts-but-does-not-spell-out-exact-layoff-numbers/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-24T21:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Lip-Bu Tan, the new CEO of Intel, sent out a blunt message to employees saying the company has to reorganize to be more efficient.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dean Takahashi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Zencoder buys Machinet to challenge GitHub Copilot as AI coding assistant consolidation accelerates]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3005445</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/zencoder-buys-machinet-to-challenge-github-copilot-as-ai-coding-assistant-consolidation-accelerates/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-24T20:36:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Zencoder acquires Machinet to strengthen its position in the rapidly consolidating AI coding assistant market, expanding its JetBrains ecosystem integration while outperforming competitors like GitHub Copilot with innovative features such as Repo Grokking and Coffee Mode.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Nuñez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethically trained AI startup Pleias releases new small reasoning models optimized for RAG with built-in citations]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3005435</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/ethically-trained-ai-startup-pleias-releases-new-small-reasoning-models-optimized-for-rag-with-built-in-citations/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-24T17:03:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Pleias emphasizes the models’ suitability for integration into search-augmented assistants, educational tools, and user support systems.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carl Franzen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Evil Geniuses and Theta Labs launch AI chatbot based on esports mascot Meesh]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3005327</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/games/evil-geniuses-and-theta-labs-launch-ai-chatbot-based-on-esports-mascot-meesh/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-24T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Evil Geniuses, the well-known esports organization and brand, has launched its Meesh AI chatbot in a partnership with Theta Labs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dean Takahashi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Driving business value by optimizing the cloud]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1115716</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/04/24/1115716/driving-business-value-by-optimizing-the-cloud/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-24T13:56:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Organizations are deepening their cloud investments at an unprecedented pace, recognizing its fundamental role in driving business agility and innovation. Synergy Research Group reports that companies spent $84 billion worldwide on cloud infrastructure services in the third quarter of 2024, a 23% rise over the third quarter of 2023 and the fourth consecutive quarter in…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>MIT Technology Review Insights</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google adds more AI tools to its Workspace productivity apps]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3005313</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/google-adds-more-ai-tools-to-its-workspace-productivity-apps/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-23T22:43:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google expanded Gemini's features, adding the popular podcast-style feature Audio Overviews to the platform.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Emilia David</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Former DeepSeeker and collaborators release new method for training reliable AI agents: RAGEN]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3005302</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/former-deepseeker-and-collaborators-release-new-method-for-training-reliable-ai-agents-ragen/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-23T20:04:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[RAGEN stands out not just as a technical contribution but as a conceptual step toward more autonomous, reasoning-capable AI agents.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carl Franzen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon’s SWE-PolyBench just exposed the dirty secret about your AI coding assistant]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3005166</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/amazon-swe-polybench-just-exposed-the-dirty-secret-about-your-ai-coding-assistant/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-23T19:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon launches SWE-PolyBench, a groundbreaking multi-language benchmark that exposes critical limitations in AI coding assistants across Python, JavaScript, TypeScript, and Java while introducing new metrics beyond simple pass rates for real-world development tasks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Nuñez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cooperations with China continue to drive Malaysia's tech ambitions: experts]]></title>
        <id>7cf31983f27357e33a7e7403d769042c</id>
        <link href="https://english.news.cn/20250423/23952d602d384abe9a3be2f40797fa2d/c.html"/>
        <updated>2025-04-23T09:33:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cooperations with China continue to drive Malaysia's tech ambitions: experts-]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>english.news.cn</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[IBM Tech Innovation Summit]]></title>
        <id>eb7b875c351e513c2d4750bb29a0ab40</id>
        <link href="https://www.malaysiakini.com/news/741130"/>
        <updated>2025-04-23T02:44:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Seats are limited. Register now!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Malaysiakini Team</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Alabama’s Pursell Agri-Tech teams with Wastech on fertilizer venture in Malaysia]]></title>
        <id>af0a46cec4f3cf8c521e3bd5a58cb6d6</id>
        <link href="https://www.madeinalabama.com/2025/04/alabamas-pursell-agri-tech-teams-with-wastech-on-fertilizer-venture-in-malaysia/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-21T18:21:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Pursell and Wastech Group are establishing a state-of-the-art facility in Malaysia to producte advanced controlled release fertilizers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jerry Underwood</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>