<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2025-06-11T23:15:00.573Z</id>
    <title>AngJianming RSS Feed</title>
    <updated>2025-06-11T23:15:00.573Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Formatting Monetary Values in JavaScript]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/ashallendesign/formatting-monetary-values-in-javascript-3gi7</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/ashallendesign/formatting-monetary-values-in-javascript-3gi7"/>
        <updated>2025-06-11T23:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction


When building your web applications, you might need to format numbers as monetary values. For example, rather than displaying the value 123.45, you might want to display it as £123.45.
In this Quickfire article, we're going to look at two different approaches to formatting monetary values in JavaScript.
The first approach you can use to format monetary values in JavaScript is the toLocaleString() method. This method formats a number according to the locale and options you specify.
Let's take a look at an example:
const value = 123.45;

const formattedValue = value.toLocaleString('en-GB', {
  style: 'currency',
  currency: 'GBP',
});

// formattedValue will be '£123.45'

In the example above, we've used the toLocaleString() method to format the value as a monetary value in Br…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ash Allen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How I Created a SkiFree Clone Using Amazon Q]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/aws-builders/how-i-created-a-skifree-clone-using-amazon-q-f1d</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/aws-builders/how-i-created-a-skifree-clone-using-amazon-q-f1d"/>
        <updated>2025-06-11T22:52:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you grew up playing Windows games in the '90s, you probably remember SkiFree, the addictive skiing game where you dodged obstacles and tried to escape the infamous Yeti. I decided to recreate this classic using Amazon Q, Amazon's AI assistant, and was amazed by how quickly I could build a functional clone.
In this blog post, I'll walk through my process, the prompts I used, and how I refined the game with additional features like boosts and power-ups.
I started by giving Amazon Q a clear prompt outlining the game's mechanics and technical requirements:

Amazon Q generated a Python script using Pygame, which handled the core mechanics beautifully. The initial version included:
A skier controlled with arrow keys


Random obstacle generation (trees and rocks)


Collision detection


A scor…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>robot254</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WWDC 2025 - Bring on-device AI to your app with Foundation Models framework]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/softwaretechpro/wwdc-2025-bring-on-device-ai-to-your-app-with-foundation-models-framework-ieb</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/softwaretechpro/wwdc-2025-bring-on-device-ai-to-your-app-with-foundation-models-framework-ieb"/>
        <updated>2025-06-11T22:49:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Why FoundationModels?


The framework offers three key advantages:
Complete Privacy: All processing happens on-device
Offline Capability: Works without internet once loaded


Zero App Bloat: Model is embedded in the OS, not your app
Instead of constantly rebuilding apps to test prompts, use Xcode's updated Playground feature. Import Playgrounds in any project file, use #Playground to test FoundationModels code directly, and get live feedback as you refine prompts.
Use the @Generable annotation to get structured data instead of parsing text. Create data structures like Itinerary with nested types, and the model automatically generates matching Swift objects.
The @Guide macro provides fine control - add descriptions, constrain values, set count requirements, or apply multiple guides to prope…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>zk</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This AI App Made My Trades Smarter — Try It FREE Before Everyone Else!]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/juanemilio31323/this-ai-app-made-my-trades-smarter-try-it-free-before-everyone-else-o07</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/juanemilio31323/this-ai-app-made-my-trades-smarter-try-it-free-before-everyone-else-o07"/>
        <updated>2025-06-11T22:48:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi everyone! 👋

I'm Juan, and for the last few months I've been working on a project to improve my trading win rate by leveraging Social Arbitrage and AI.

I used to lose money trading—even when holding solid assets—but thanks to this project, I went from losing to winning really quickly.
This is my PnL from just the last 30 days:


This project is still in its early stages and not officially released yet, which is why I'm offering the chance to join as a beta tester and get free early access in exchange for your feedback on the current version.
I’m also opening a waiting list for those who are interested but would prefer to wait for the full launch.
If you decide to participate, you’ll get access to all the app’s current features:
Global event notifications – Stay updated on all events worldwide that directly or indirectly affect the assets you’re tracking


Thesis mode – Automatically validate your market hypotheses like “Bitcoin is going up” or “Tesla will drop”


Sentiment trends – Track the current sentiment of most assets and companies around the globe


Social Agent – A custom AI agent with access to our event graph database. It understands complex investment strategies and real-world scenarios. Ask things like:


“Should I invest in Apple now?”

“When should I enter this trade?”
If you’d rather wait, you can still register and you’ll receive an automatic notification when the app is fully launched.
For more updates about the project, visit my X account or the project's official account, where we also share predictions generated with Social.
Finally, a question for you, reader:

Would you be interested in weekly posts here sharing progress on the project and sneak peeks at upcoming features?
I know this post may feel a little like an advertisement—and that’s because it is.

This is a bootstrapped project (which means I’m funding it myself), and I’m putting my heart and soul into it.

If you can give it a try or help spread the word, that would mean the world to me.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Juan Emilio</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How AI is Transforming QA: Automation, Manual, and Performance Testing]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/ramamallika_kadali_49a08f/how-ai-is-transforming-qa-automation-manual-and-performance-testing-1f0e</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/ramamallika_kadali_49a08f/how-ai-is-transforming-qa-automation-manual-and-performance-testing-1f0e"/>
        <updated>2025-06-11T22:39:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Quality Assurance (QA) is crucial for delivering reliable software products. Traditional testing approaches—whether manual, automated, or performance—often require significant time, effort, and expertise. Artificial Intelligence (AI) is rapidly changing the QA landscape by introducing smart, adaptive, and scalable solutions that enhance test coverage, accuracy, and speed.
1. Introduction to AI in Software Testing
2. AI in Automation Testing
2.1 Intelligent Test Case Generation and Optimization
AI Application: Machine learning models analyze application code, user behavior logs, and past defects to automatically generate and optimize test cases.
Example: AI tools can parse user flows from analytics data and generate test scenarios covering the most critical paths, reducing redundant or irre…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>RamaMallika Kadali</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WWDC 2025 - Make your UIKit app more flexible]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/softwaretechpro/wwdc-2025-make-your-uikit-app-more-flexible-4b3p</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/softwaretechpro/wwdc-2025-make-your-uikit-app-more-flexible-4b3p"/>
        <updated>2025-06-11T22:37:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Building Flexible UIKit Apps: Key Takeaways from WWDC


Creating apps that work seamlessly across different screen sizes and platforms is more important than ever. The UIKit team shared essential best practices for building flexible UIKit applications that deliver amazing experiences regardless of device or window size.
Scenes are the cornerstone of flexible apps. A scene represents an instance of your app's UI, containing view controllers and views while providing crucial functionality:
Independent state management - Each scene saves and restores its UI state independently
External data handling - Built-in support for deep linking and URL handling


Context awareness - Provides screen and window geometry information
Multiple scene support - Different scene types for distinct experiences (…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>zk</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Client Assistance Button for Spa Beds Connected to Python Server]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/karen_londres/client-assistance-button-for-spa-beds-connected-to-python-server-3l3n</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/karen_londres/client-assistance-button-for-spa-beds-connected-to-python-server-3l3n"/>
        <updated>2025-06-11T22:32:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In today’s rapidly evolving wellness industry, enhancing client comfort and care is paramount. Spas and Medspas are integrating technology to provide seamless experiences and prompt services. One such innovation is the integration of a client assistance button—a simple yet powerful addition that enables clients lying on treatment beds to request help without moving or speaking. This becomes especially important in a luxury wellness setting like a Medspa.
In this post, we’ll explore how to create a client assistance button system, connected to a Python server. We’ll cover the hardware and software components, and how it can improve customer service in your Medspa.
Imagine a client undergoing a treatment—perhaps a skin rejuvenation session or body contouring procedure—wishing to ask for a bl…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Karen Londres</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[🌱 Searching for My First Dev Role — Guidance Appreciated!]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/kailash_kumar_f3c464406bf/searching-for-my-first-dev-role-guidance-appreciated-bc8</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/kailash_kumar_f3c464406bf/searching-for-my-first-dev-role-guidance-appreciated-bc8"/>
        <updated>2025-06-11T22:31:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi everyone! 👋
I'm currently looking for opportunities in software development and wanted to share a bit about my journey and skills so far. I'm also hoping to connect with others who are on a similar path or have gone through this journey already!
👨‍💻 About Me
Current Focus: Full-stack development, with a growing interest in building scalable, real-world applications.
🧠 Skills
Backend: Node.js, Express.js
Database: PostgreSQL, MongoDB
Tools & Other: Git, GitHub, Postman, REST APIs
🎯 What I'm Looking For
Internship or entry-level software developer roles
Remote or hybrid opportunities
Mentorship or open-source contributions to gain real-world experience
🙏 How You Can Help
If you’ve been in a similar position, I’d love to hear your advice
If you're hiring or know companies open to junior devs, I’d be grateful
Any feedback on my portfolio or GitHub would be super appreciated
Thanks for reading! Feel free to drop your thoughts or connect with me.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kailash Kumar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Social media use increases depression in preteens, not vice versa]]></title>
        <id>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-05-social-media-depression-preteens-vice.html</id>
        <link href="https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-05-social-media-depression-preteens-vice.html"/>
        <updated>2025-06-11T22:29:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WWDC 2025 What’s new in UIKit]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/softwaretechpro/wwdc-2025-whats-new-in-uikit-1kj4</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/softwaretechpro/wwdc-2025-whats-new-in-uikit-1kj4"/>
        <updated>2025-06-11T22:29:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Key highlights include:
The new Liquid Glass design system with fluid animations
iPad menu bar support with powerful new APIs
Revolutionary Swift Observable integration that automatically tracks dependencies
The new updateProperties method for better performance
Enhanced SwiftUI integration through hosting scene delegates
HDR improvements for colors and custom content
Strongly typed notifications
SF Symbols 7 drawing capabilities
The most visually striking change in iOS 26 is the introduction of Liquid Glass, a translucent, dynamic material that brings life to your app's interface with specular highlights and refraction effects. This new material has been applied across UIKit's standard components including navigation bars, search fields, alerts, popovers, and split views.
Key Design Impro…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>zk</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Configuring User Management Operations]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/lotanna_obianefo/configuring-user-management-operations-96b</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/lotanna_obianefo/configuring-user-management-operations-96b"/>
        <updated>2025-06-11T22:23:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Effective user management is a cornerstone of Active Directory (AD) administration, enabling organizations to control access, enforce security policies, and streamline identity management within a Windows Server domain. Configuring user management operations involves creating, modifying, and securing user accounts, as well as managing group memberships and permissions.
This guide outlines the process for managing user operations in a domain like tailwind.local, using domain controllers such as TAILWIND-DC1.
We will create three Organization Units (OUs) Sydney, Melbourne, and Brisbane.
Create Organizational Units
In TAILWIND-DC1, open Active Directory Users and Computers from the Tools menu of the Server Manager console. Right-click on the tailwindtraders.internal domain. Select New, then O…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>lotanna obianefo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How AI is Used in QA Automation: Detailed Step-by-Step Examples Introduction]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/ramamallika_kadali_49a08f/how-ai-is-used-in-qa-automation-detailed-step-by-step-examples-introduction-508j</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/ramamallika_kadali_49a08f/how-ai-is-used-in-qa-automation-detailed-step-by-step-examples-introduction-508j"/>
        <updated>2025-06-11T22:22:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AI is reshaping Quality Assurance by automating complex tasks and enhancing decision-making in software testing. This article explains core AI use cases in QA automation with concrete step-by-step examples so you can see exactly how these innovations work in practice.
1. AI-Powered Test Case Generation
AI Solution: Use Natural Language Processing (NLP) to generate test cases automatically from user stories or requirements.
Step-by-Step Example:
Step 1: Input user story text into an NLP-based test generation tool.
E*xample user story:*
As a user, I want to log in with a valid email and password so that I can access my account.
**Step 2: **The AI parses this text to identify key actions, inputs, and expected outcomes.
**Step 3: **The tool generates structured test scenarios like:
**Test 1: *…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>RamaMallika Kadali</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bash Mastery: Lessons from a Decade of Production Challenges]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/sameerimtiaz/bash-mastery-lessons-from-a-decade-of-production-challenges-3ko3</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/sameerimtiaz/bash-mastery-lessons-from-a-decade-of-production-challenges-3ko3"/>
        <updated>2025-06-11T22:17:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Six months ago, a single bash script I crafted flawlessly executed 75,000 server deployments. Three years prior, my scripts were causing production outages almost biweekly. Here’s how I transformed my approach.
Since 2013, I’ve been writing bash scripts professionally. Early on, my scripts were fragile—functional on my local setup but prone to mysterious failures in production. Debugging felt like navigating a maze blindfolded.
After numerous late-night fire drills, botched deployments, and an infamous incident where I inadvertently wiped out a quarter of our testing environment, I honed techniques to create reliable bash scripts.
These aren’t beginner tips from tutorials. They’re battle-tested insights from high-stakes production environments where errors translate to real financial losse…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sameer Imtiaz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Here’s what happened in crypto today]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/what-happened-in-crypto-today</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/what-happened-in-crypto-today?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-06-11T22:02:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Need to know what happened in crypto today? Here is the latest news on daily trends and events impacting Bitcoin price, blockchain, DeFi, NFTs, Web3 and crypto regulation.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Cointelegraph</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The first big AI disaster is yet to happen]]></title>
        <id>https://www.seangoedecke.com/the-first-big-ai-disaster/</id>
        <link href="https://www.seangoedecke.com/the-first-big-ai-disaster/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-11T22:01:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin advocate TFTC launches browser extension for real-time BTC pricing]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/tftc-browser-extension-bitcoin-standard</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/tftc-browser-extension-bitcoin-standard?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-06-11T22:00:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Distorted price signals from fiat currencies have destroyed the ability to make rational economic calculations, according to Truth for the Commoner founder Marty Bent.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Vince Quill</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Two defendants plead not guilty in crypto kidnapping and torture case]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/crypto-suspects-not-guilty-plea-kidnapping-torture</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/crypto-suspects-not-guilty-plea-kidnapping-torture?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-06-11T21:49:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[John Woeltz and William Duplessie reportedly pleaded not guilty to the kidnapping and false imprisonment of Michael Valentino Teofrasto Carturan in New York City.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Turner Wright</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin price prepares for volatility as spot supply vanishes]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-price-prepares-for-volatility-as-spot-supply-vanishes</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-price-prepares-for-volatility-as-spot-supply-vanishes?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-06-11T21:38:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin's recent rally occurred as funding rates turned negative, and BTC held on exchanges and OTC desks shrank.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Marie Poteriaieva</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Congratulations on creating the one billionth repository on GitHub]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/AasishPokhrel/shit/issues/1</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/AasishPokhrel/shit/issues/1"/>
        <updated>2025-06-11T21:37:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Institutional Books: A 242B token dataset from Harvard Library's collections]]></title>
        <id>https://arxiv.org/abs/2506.08300</id>
        <link href="https://arxiv.org/abs/2506.08300"/>
        <updated>2025-06-11T21:36:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Shaped (YC W22) Is Hiring]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ycombinator.com/companies/shaped/jobs/qtQwxJO-head-of-engineering</id>
        <link href="https://www.ycombinator.com/companies/shaped/jobs/qtQwxJO-head-of-engineering"/>
        <updated>2025-06-11T21:00:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GameStop Raising Another $1.75B for Potential Bitcoin Purchases]]></title>
        <id>c99659af-8616-43ff-83f7-3c140e695dc6</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2025/06/11/gamestop-raising-another-175b-for-potential-bitcoin-purchases"/>
        <updated>2025-06-11T20:43:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The company made its initial acquisitions of bitcoin in May, buying 4,710 coins for about $500 million.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Krisztian Sandor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin price rally to $115K possible as US economic data exceeds expectations]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-rally-to-115k-possible-due-to-improving-us-macroeconomics</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-rally-to-115k-possible-due-to-improving-us-macroeconomics?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-06-11T20:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin technical charts and encouraging US macroeconomic data could trigger a rally to $115,000.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Biraajmaan Tamuly</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chatterbox TTS]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/resemble-ai/chatterbox</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/resemble-ai/chatterbox"/>
        <updated>2025-06-11T20:23:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Attackers Steal Data from Websites (And How to Stop Them)]]></title>
        <id>6849e4d1a3aec42347669919</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-attackers-steal-data-from-websites-and-how-to-stop-them/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-11T20:19:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Across platforms, behind every app, and on your own website, hackers may patiently wait.  These days, everyone should have identity theft protections, and be informed about data threats lurking in the trenches of the world-wide-web’s war on privacy a...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alex Tray</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Research suggests Big Bang may have taken place inside a black hole]]></title>
        <id>https://www.port.ac.uk/news-events-and-blogs/blogs/space-cosmology-and-the-universe/what-if-the-big-bang-wasnt-the-beginning-our-research-suggests-it-may-have-taken-place-inside-a-black-hole</id>
        <link href="https://www.port.ac.uk/news-events-and-blogs/blogs/space-cosmology-and-the-universe/what-if-the-big-bang-wasnt-the-beginning-our-research-suggests-it-may-have-taken-place-inside-a-black-hole"/>
        <updated>2025-06-11T19:44:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[US senators question Meta’s stablecoin plans amid GENIUS Act debate]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/us-senators-meta-stablecoin-plans-genius-act-debate</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/us-senators-meta-stablecoin-plans-genius-act-debate?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-06-11T19:41:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Lawmakers asked Mark Zuckerberg whether Meta had had any influence on the GENIUS stablecoin bill and its plans to potentially issue its own digital currency.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Turner Wright</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Safe Establishes New Development Firm to Attract Institutions and Tackle Crypto’s ‘Cyber Warfare’ Era]]></title>
        <id>9c15b6a4-7db6-4daa-a971-dd3a51deff81</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/tech/2025/06/11/safe-establishes-new-development-firm-to-attract-institutions-and-tackle-cryptos-cyber-warfare-era"/>
        <updated>2025-06-11T19:21:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the wake of a North Korea-linked hack, Safe is retooling its approach — eschewing contractor models for a foundation-owned, fast-moving Labs unit.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sam Kessler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin, ETH price coil after inflation cools and US-China tariffs roll back]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/crypto-prices-rise-inflation-cools-us-china-trade-deal</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/crypto-prices-rise-inflation-cools-us-china-trade-deal?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-06-11T19:15:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Lower CPI and tariff rollbacks boost crypto’s outlook despite economic concerns and Fed rate uncertainty.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Marcel Pechman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tom Lee Mulls Roughed-Up Semler Scientific for 'Granny Shot' Portfolio]]></title>
        <id>3a8c7c19-8fc4-4b03-b130-ea571f4b7647</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/06/11/tom-lee-mulls-roughed-up-semler-scientific-for-granny-shot-portfolio"/>
        <updated>2025-06-11T19:11:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The bitcoin treasury company's market cap has tumbled below the value of its BTC holdings.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>James Van Straten</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[EchoLeak – 0-Click AI Vulnerability Enabling Data Exfiltration from 365 Copilot]]></title>
        <id>https://www.aim.security/lp/aim-labs-echoleak-blogpost</id>
        <link href="https://www.aim.security/lp/aim-labs-echoleak-blogpost"/>
        <updated>2025-06-11T19:11:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GENIUS stablecoin bill passes key vote, advances in US Senate]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/us-senate-passes-cloture-genius-stablecoin-bill</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/us-senate-passes-cloture-genius-stablecoin-bill?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-06-11T19:07:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Weeks after a stablecoin bill stalled over Trump-linked concerns, the Senate advanced the GENIUS Act.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Turner Wright</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Senate Begins Passage of Stablecoin Bill as House Marks Market-Structure Wins]]></title>
        <id>5c9c7275-ca3c-4d3d-a03f-46c4c7492a52</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2025/06/11/senate-begins-passage-of-stablecoin-bill-as-house-marks-market-structure-wins"/>
        <updated>2025-06-11T18:45:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The U.S. Congress is in the thick of its crypto efforts this week, with the Senate starting on final votes to approve its first-ever crypto bill.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jesse Hamilton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SUI Token Trades Flat Despite Signs of Strong ETF Momentum]]></title>
        <id>e6b4066a-2f40-4e23-954e-be7308920585</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/06/11/sui-token-trades-flat-despite-signs-of-strong-etf-momentum"/>
        <updated>2025-06-11T18:36:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The token traded roughly flat over the past 24 hours, even after Nasdaq submitted a 19b-4 document with the SEC on Tuesday, taking another step towards a spot SUI ETF in the U.S.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Helene Braun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Financial Advisors Remain Hesitant Towards Bitcoin — But Won’t Be for Long]]></title>
        <id>c103cd02-286d-4733-82a7-522aa1822879</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/06/11/financial-advisors-are-still-hesitant-towards-bitcoin-but-wont-be-for-long"/>
        <updated>2025-06-11T18:25:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Questions have evolved from “What is bitcoin?” to “How does it fit in my portfolio?”]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tom Carreras</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Darwin Godel Machine: Open-Ended Evolution of Self-Improving Agents]]></title>
        <id>https://arxiv.org/abs/2505.22954</id>
        <link href="https://arxiv.org/abs/2505.22954"/>
        <updated>2025-06-11T18:07:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meta's Stablecoin Plan Questioned by Democrats Ahead of Key Senate Vote]]></title>
        <id>3ae8aca4-2818-4bf6-b83e-63008dfc7b5e</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2025/06/11/metas-stablecoin-plan-questioned-by-democrats-ahead-of-key-senate-vote"/>
        <updated>2025-06-11T18:04:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sens. Elizabeth Warren and Richard Blumenthal sent a letter to Meta asking whether it's lobbied for the GENIUS Act or has any plans to join an issuer in any way.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nikhilesh De</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Connecticut's Ban Throws Water on 2025 Trend of States Setting Up Crypto Investments]]></title>
        <id>191ee09b-8af7-44ff-aa68-62e05076817b</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2025/06/11/connecticut-s-ban-throws-water-on-2025-trend-of-states-setting-up-crypto-investments"/>
        <updated>2025-06-11T18:02:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Connecticut legislature has barred that state's government from setting up the kind of digital assets reserves seen forming elsewhere in the U.S.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jesse Hamilton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to set up and use AI-powered crypto trading bots]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/how-to-set-up-and-use-ai-powered-crypto-trading-bots</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/how-to-set-up-and-use-ai-powered-crypto-trading-bots?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-06-11T18:01:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A practical guide to setting up, using and optimizing AI crypto trading bots, plus a glimpse into where intelligent trading is headed next.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Callum Reid</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Price predictions 6/11: BTC, ETH, XRP, BNB, SOL, DOGE, ADA, HYPE, SUI, LINK]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/price-predictions-6-11-btc-eth-xrp-bnb-sol-doge-ada-hype-sui-link</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/price-predictions-6-11-btc-eth-xrp-bnb-sol-doge-ada-hype-sui-link?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-06-11T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin price trades near its all-time high as ETH and several altcoins start fresh rallies.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Rakesh Upadhyay</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft-backed Mistral launches European AI cloud to compete with AWS and Azure]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3011628</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/microsoft-backed-mistral-launches-european-ai-cloud-to-compete-with-aws-and-azure/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-11T17:51:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mistral AI partners with Nvidia to launch European AI infrastructure platform, challenging US cloud giants while unveiling breakthrough reasoning models that rival OpenAI.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Nuñez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to use ChatGPT for crypto strategy, signals, and sentiment]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/how-to-use-chatgpt-to-analyze-crypto-market-movements</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/how-to-use-chatgpt-to-analyze-crypto-market-movements?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-06-11T17:51:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Use ChatGPT to summarize market news, interpret on-chain data, compare token metrics, and spot sentiment shifts using structured prompts.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Callum Reid</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Developer accuses Ethereum Foundation of undermining devs, creating ‘secret’ teams]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/geth-lead-developer-accuses-ethereum-foundation-creating-secret-team</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/geth-lead-developer-accuses-ethereum-foundation-creating-secret-team?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-06-11T17:49:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Péter Szilágyi, a former Ethereum Foundation employee and the lead Geth developer, said the organization repeatedly undermined his team.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Vince Quill</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Databricks open-sources declarative ETL framework powering 90% faster pipeline builds]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3011579</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/data-infrastructure/databricks-open-sources-declarative-etl-framework-powering-90-faster-pipeline-builds/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-11T17:29:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With Apache Spark Declarative Pipelines, engineers describe what their pipeline should do using SQL or Python, and Apache Spark handles the execution.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shubham Sharma</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Show HN: Spark, An advanced 3D Gaussian Splatting renderer for Three.js]]></title>
        <id>https://sparkjs.dev/</id>
        <link href="https://sparkjs.dev/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-11T17:02:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘Unique’ Bitcoin holder trend backs BTC’s next price discovery phase: Glassnode]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/unique-bitcoin-holder-trend-backs-btc-s-next-price-discovery-phase-glassnode</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/unique-bitcoin-holder-trend-backs-btc-s-next-price-discovery-phase-glassnode?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-06-11T17:02:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin enters a unique market phase as rising long-term holder dominance and compressed volatility could potentially trigger a fresh round of price discovery.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Biraajmaan Tamuly</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dolly Parton's Dollywood Express]]></title>
        <id>https://thetransitguy.substack.com/p/dolly-parton-runs-a-train-busier</id>
        <link href="https://thetransitguy.substack.com/p/dolly-parton-runs-a-train-busier"/>
        <updated>2025-06-11T16:46:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘Generative AI helps us bend time’: CrowdStrike, Nvidia embed real-time LLM defense, changing how enterprises secure AI]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3011386</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/security/crowdstrike-falcon-now-powers-runtime-defense-in-nvidias-llms/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-11T16:39:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Falcon is now built into Nvidia’s LLMs, delivering native runtime threat defense and eliminating blind spots across AI pipelines.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Louis Columbus</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ether Surges Toward $3K on Tentative U.S.–China Trade Pact and Soft U.S. CPI Report]]></title>
        <id>0fbab7a6-19d6-4d35-a1b5-18668f47dd9a</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/06/11/ether-surges-toward-usd3k-on-tentative-u-s-china-trade-pact-and-soft-u-s-cpi-report"/>
        <updated>2025-06-11T16:32:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ether’s 5.6% rally to a 10-day high followed soft May CPI and a draft U.S.-China trade truce, intensifying already brisk institutional demand.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Siamak Masnavi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Peaq and UAE bet on tokenized machines to power future economy]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/uae-machine-economy-sandbox-peaq-pulsar</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/uae-machine-economy-sandbox-peaq-pulsar?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-06-11T16:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The UAE Machine Economy Free Zone envisions a world where tokenholders receive a share of the revenue from machine-economy activities.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Sam Bourgi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Digital Assets Are One Step Closer to Regulatory Clarity]]></title>
        <id>4e22a199-c525-4425-aac6-3eced18b15f6</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/opinion/2025/06/11/digital-assets-are-one-step-closer-to-regulatory-clarity"/>
        <updated>2025-06-11T16:22:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With passage of a crypto market structure bill out of key House committees, the U.S. is poised to finally have fundamental legislation covering the digital assets industry, say Rep. French Hill, Rep. G.T. Thompson, and Rep. Tom Emmer.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>French Hill</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Stripe to Acquire Crypto Wallet Startup Privy in Bid to Expand Web3 Capabilities]]></title>
        <id>a0534177-76c6-4bf2-9903-eda90d7fa99c</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2025/06/11/stripe-to-acquire-crypto-wallet-startup-privy-in-bid-to-expand-web3-capabilities"/>
        <updated>2025-06-11T16:15:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Privy’s technology, used by platforms like OpenSea and Blackbird, will be integrated into Stripe’s crypto tools.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Francisco Rodrigues</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[After stablecoin push, Stripe acquires crypto wallet developer Privy]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/stripe-acquires-privy-crypto-wallet-infrastructure</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/stripe-acquires-privy-crypto-wallet-infrastructure?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-06-11T16:12:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The acquisition of Privy follows Stripe’s entry into the stablecoin market in 2024.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Sam Bourgi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ATOM Finds Support at $4.50 as Ethereum Whales Signal Potential Altcoin Season]]></title>
        <id>5dd74c10-17b0-44e1-8bd0-9cd298dc2fdd</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/06/11/atom-finds-support-at-usd4-50-as-ethereum-whales-signal-potential-altcoin-season"/>
        <updated>2025-06-11T16:10:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cosmos' ATOM token has established key support levels while showing signs of bullish momentum.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Oliver Knight</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum whale opens $11M leveraged bet amid ETH price’s 30% rise potential]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/ethereum-whale-opens-11m-leveraged-bet-eth-price-30-rise-potential</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/ethereum-whale-opens-11m-leveraged-bet-eth-price-30-rise-potential?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-06-11T16:10:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ETH price rising to around $2,850 drove the whale’s $11 million leveraged long into $366,000 paper profit.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Yashu Gola</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Case for Investing in Digital Assets]]></title>
        <id>23d3b451-0236-47f7-8e5a-e982f9ab5fe3</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/coindesk-indices/2025/06/11/the-case-for-investing-in-digital-assets"/>
        <updated>2025-06-11T16:07:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Chris Sullivan of Hyperion Decimus discusses why digital assets are essential for every investor to consider, and how to get alpha in today’s volatile markets.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kim Greenberg Klemballa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AAVE Breaks Key Resistance as DeFi Sector Heats Up]]></title>
        <id>45167fa6-095f-4227-bfb1-dbb5086382f6</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/06/11/aave-breaks-key-resistance-as-defi-sector-heats-up"/>
        <updated>2025-06-11T16:05:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SEC Chair Atkins' remarks earlier this week spurred optimism for the sector's future.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CD Analytics</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Exchange Bullish to Host $10M Trading Competition]]></title>
        <id>f70342fb-4351-49b1-8fc7-68779bd22ae7</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2025/06/11/crypto-exchange-bullish-to-host-usd10m-trading-competition"/>
        <updated>2025-06-11T16:05:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The competition will be judged by a panel of industry veterans.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Oliver Knight</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Flashbots Veterans Raise $20M to Tackle Crypto User Experience With OneBalance]]></title>
        <id>9804dcca-c4e4-4c3e-8ba1-c0df4122c00d</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2025/06/11/flashbots-veterans-raise-20m-to-tackle-crypto-ux-with-onebalance"/>
        <updated>2025-06-11T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The OneBalance Series A round was led by cyber•Fund and Blockchain Capital.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Will Canny</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[U.S. Strategic Bitcoin Reserve Marks Milestone in Institutional Adoption: Gemini]]></title>
        <id>daf28979-9ad2-4f5d-9862-2ea93e2b5fd3</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2025/06/11/us-strategic-bitcoin-reserve-marks-milestone-in-institutional-adoption-gemini"/>
        <updated>2025-06-11T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[More than 30% of the circulating bitcoin supply is now held by centralized entities including exchanges, ETFs, companies and sovereigns, the report said.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Will Canny</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OneBalance lands $20M to simplify crypto for developers]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/onebalance-raises-20m-for-dev-tools</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/onebalance-raises-20m-for-dev-tools?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-06-11T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[OneBalance raised $20 million to launch a developer toolkit enabling one-click crosschain crypto transactions, aiming to fix fragmented UX and boost app conversions.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Lyne Qian</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Litecoin Rebounds, Holds Firm Near $93 on Potential ETF Positioning]]></title>
        <id>7f7a13bf-4980-48de-8b8d-0adc5df04efb</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/06/11/litecoin-rebounds-holds-firm-near-93-on-potential-etf-positioning"/>
        <updated>2025-06-11T15:59:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Analysis suggests market participants may be positioning for a potential litecoin exchange-traded fund (ETF) approval.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CD Analytics</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitdeer Ramps Up Self-Mining Capacity, Ships 1.6 EH/s of SEALMINER A2s in May]]></title>
        <id>d217260e-4fbc-4e06-8521-1aae9b7149a4</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/06/11/bitdeer-ramps-up-self-mining-capacity-ships-16-ehs-of-sealminer-a2s-in-may"/>
        <updated>2025-06-11T15:42:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitdeer boosts its BTC production while expanding its global infrastructure.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tom Carreras</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[When an AI says, ‘No, I don’t want to power off’: Inside the o3 refusal]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/explained/when-an-ai-says-no-i-dont-want-to-power-off-inside-the-o3-refusal</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/explained/when-an-ai-says-no-i-dont-want-to-power-off-inside-the-o3-refusal?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-06-11T15:37:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[OpenAI’s o3 model resisted shutdown in safety tests, raising concerns about AI alignment and control.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Callum Reid</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Filecoin Rises 3.6% After Establishing Support Zone Around $2.68]]></title>
        <id>2df1cc3b-e2d1-4fbd-82c7-ba2d49418bda</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/06/11/filecoin-rises-36-after-establishing-support-zone-around-268"/>
        <updated>2025-06-11T15:33:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The FIL token has established a higher trading range despite significant market volatility.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CD Analytics</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trump’s consumer protection reforms could leave crypto users in a lurch]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/trump-s-consumer-protection-reforms-could-leave-crypto-users-in-a-lurch</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/trump-s-consumer-protection-reforms-could-leave-crypto-users-in-a-lurch?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-06-11T15:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Trump administration, supported by major US crypto firms, has largely dismantled the Consumer Financial Protection Bureau, leaving consumers vulnerable.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Aaron Wood</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TON Slides as Sell-Off Triggers Spike in Volume With Potential Bearish Pressure Signal]]></title>
        <id>16aaa240-e4f3-46f6-8aa5-06dcce2ca43b</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/06/11/ton-slides-as-selloff-triggers-spike-in-volume-with-potential-bearish-pressure-signal"/>
        <updated>2025-06-11T15:28:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Telegram’s token faces a critical short-term support test amid a technical breakdown.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CD Analytics</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trump’s CFTC chair pick won’t push president for bipartisan commission]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/brian-quintenz-cftc-chair-nominee-crypto</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/brian-quintenz-cftc-chair-nominee-crypto?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-06-11T15:26:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Senators questioned Brian Quintenz on prediction markets, his experiences dealing with debanking, and how he would potentially handle an entirely Republican-staffed CFTC.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Turner Wright</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BNB Pushes Higher Despite Market Turbulence, Testing Resistance Near $674]]></title>
        <id>1eca557a-acec-4ef7-8d6a-39a5e60b1113</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/06/11/bnb-pushes-higher-despite-market-turbulence-testing-resistance-near-674"/>
        <updated>2025-06-11T15:20:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The token's performance is being closely watched, particularly around the $674 resistance level, which could indicate a breakout if surpassed.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CD Analytics</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why the Market Needs a Rules-Based Benchmark for Centralised Exchanges]]></title>
        <id>080ff8c5-d7eb-4b92-8e91-a568d3849faa</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/coindesk-indices/2025/06/10/why-the-market-needs-a-rules-based-benchmark-for-centralised-exchanges"/>
        <updated>2025-06-11T15:01:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Joshua de Vos of CoinDesk Data shares the April 2025 edition of the Exchange Benchmark report which sheds light on which exchanges operate at institutional standards and those still falling short.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joshua de Vos</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Currency must be separated from state:  Returning to Bitcoin&#039;s original vision]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/currency-must-be-separated-from-state-returning-to-bitcoin-s-original-vision</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/currency-must-be-separated-from-state-returning-to-bitcoin-s-original-vision?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-06-11T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As government overreach and institutional interests reshape the blockchain landscape, it's time to return to Bitcoin's founding vision: a truly decentralized, immutable currency free from state and corporate control.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Dr. K</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AVAX Adds 4% as $22 Support Zone Holds]]></title>
        <id>75015290-c951-4721-b4ac-2f1a9d12f317</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/06/11/avax-adds-4-as-22-support-zone-holds"/>
        <updated>2025-06-11T14:59:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Avalanche’s token is showing signs of strength in the short-term.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CD Analytics</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sweden's H100 Group Rallies Another 30% After Raising $10M for Bitcoin Treasury Strategy]]></title>
        <id>e859479a-e84f-4fc2-81a8-5f5fb50d8826</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2025/06/11/swedens-h100-group-rallies-another-30-after-raising-10m-for-bitcoin-treasury-strategy"/>
        <updated>2025-06-11T14:59:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin OG Adam Back was among the investors in the health and longevity company's capital raise.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Krisztian Sandor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is a supply chain attack in crypto and how to prevent it?]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/explained/what-is-a-supply-chain-attack-in-crypto-and-how-to-prevent-it</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/explained/what-is-a-supply-chain-attack-in-crypto-and-how-to-prevent-it?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-06-11T14:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Supply chain attacks in crypto exploit trusted dependencies, emerging as a major threat to crypto projects, which now have to stay vigilant on such threats.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Dilip Kumar Patairya</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[V-JEPA 2 world model and new benchmarks for physical reasoning]]></title>
        <id>https://ai.meta.com/blog/v-jepa-2-world-model-benchmarks/</id>
        <link href="https://ai.meta.com/blog/v-jepa-2-world-model-benchmarks/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-11T14:43:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Show HN: RomM – An open-source, self-hosted ROM manager and player]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/rommapp/romm</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/rommapp/romm"/>
        <updated>2025-06-11T14:25:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bypassing GitHub Actions policies in the dumbest way possible]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.yossarian.net/2025/06/11/github-actions-policies-dumb-bypass</id>
        <link href="https://blog.yossarian.net/2025/06/11/github-actions-policies-dumb-bypass"/>
        <updated>2025-06-11T14:15:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Bitcoin treasuries may crack under price pressure]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/new-bitcoin-treasuries-may-crack-under-price-pressure</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/new-bitcoin-treasuries-may-crack-under-price-pressure?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-06-11T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Strategy has inspired a wave of copycats to join the corporate Bitcoin treasury wave, but they haven’t been battle-tested and entered at higher average prices.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Yohan Yun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[From ETFs to Strategic Bitcoin Reserve: Inside Trump’s crypto playbook]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/from-etfs-to-the-strategic-bitcoin-reserve-inside-trump-s-crypto-playbook</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/from-etfs-to-the-strategic-bitcoin-reserve-inside-trump-s-crypto-playbook?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-06-11T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Explore the latest developments in crypto regulation and macro outlook in a report by HTX Ventures.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Gleb K</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin nears new high as Trump says US-China trade ‘deal is done’]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-all-time-high-trump-us-china-trade-deal</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-all-time-high-trump-us-china-trade-deal?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-06-11T13:50:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin may see more upside if the world’s two largest trading nations finalize their tariff deal and end global economic uncertainty.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Zoltan Vardai</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DeskHog, an open-source developer toy]]></title>
        <id>https://posthog.com/deskhog</id>
        <link href="https://posthog.com/deskhog"/>
        <updated>2025-06-11T13:37:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Connecticut lawmakers vote to prohibit crypto use in government]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/connecticut-crypto-investment-ban-state-politicians</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/connecticut-crypto-investment-ban-state-politicians?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-06-11T13:17:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Connecticut has joined the growing number of US states rejecting the notion of a state Bitcoin reserve, prohibiting government entities from making crypto investments and payments.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Helen Partz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why most enterprise AI agents never reach production and how Databricks plans to fix it]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3011290</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/why-most-enterprise-ai-agents-never-reach-production-and-how-databricks-plans-to-fix-it/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-11T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Databricks Agent Bricks automates enterprise AI agent optimization and evaluation, eliminating manual processes that block production deployments.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sean Michael Kerner</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Outset raises $17M to replace human interviewers with AI agents for enterprise research]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3011482</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/outset-raises-17m-to-replace-human-interviewers-with-ai-agents-for-enterprise-research/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-11T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Outset raises $17M Series A to scale its AI-moderated research platform used by Nestlé, Microsoft, and WeightWatchers that's 8x faster and 81% cheaper than traditional market research.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Nuñez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lemony is a plug-and-play device for secure on-premise AI]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3011497</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/games/lemony-is-a-plug-and-play-device-for-secure-on-premise-ai/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-11T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Lemony launched a simple-looking device to deliver on-premise artificial intelligence to redefine how organizations deploy generative AI.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dean Takahashi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Wandercraft raises $75M for acceleration of AI-powered humanoid robotics and exoskeletons]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3011520</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/games/wandercraft-raises-75m-for-acceleration-of-ai-powered-humanoid-robotics-and-exoskeletons/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-11T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Wandercraft, a maker of self-balancing robotic mobility systems, has secured $75 million in funding to accelerate AI-powered robotics.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dean Takahashi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Quantum Art integrates Nvidia for its scalable quantum computers]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3011543</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/games/quantum-art-integrates-nvidia-for-its-scalable-quantum-computers/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-11T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Quantum Art a developer of full-stack quantum computers, has integrated Nvidia's CUDA-Q hybrid quantum-classical platform into its "qubits."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dean Takahashi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ASTR becomes OP Superchain’s first interoperable token via Chainlink CCIP]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/astr-becomes-op-superchain-first-interoperable-token</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/astr-becomes-op-superchain-first-interoperable-token?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-06-11T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Users will eventually be able to transfer ASTR to any Superchain network, according to OP Labs’ Zain Bacchus.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Sam Bourgi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Huawei Launches New Pura 80 Flagship Smartphones In China]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=355607</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/355607/huawei-pura-80-series-launch-china/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-11T12:58:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Huawei has officially introduced its new Pura 80 series in China, offering a strong mix of upgrades in performance, imaging and even connectivity over its predecessor. The new line-up consists of four models: the Pura 80, Pura 80 Pro, Pura 80 Pro+, and the Pura 80 Ultra. The standard Pura 80 is the most compact, […]
The post Huawei Launches New Pura 80 Flagship Smartphones In China appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Heirul Kamel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OpenPlanetData – Free Daily Planet OSM PBF and GOL Indexed Snapshots]]></title>
        <id>https://openplanetdata.com/</id>
        <link href="https://openplanetdata.com/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-11T12:55:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SOL price toward $300 next? Solana ETF approval chances jump to 91%]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/sol-price-toward-300-next-solana-etf-approval</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/sol-price-toward-300-next-solana-etf-approval?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-06-11T12:45:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Surging onchain activity, rising spot Solana ETF approval chances and derivatives metrics suggest that SOL’s bullish price momentum could continue toward $300.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Nancy Lubale</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Show HN: Ikuyo a Travel Planning Web Application]]></title>
        <id>https://ikuyo.kenrick95.org/</id>
        <link href="https://ikuyo.kenrick95.org/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-11T12:44:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Menstrual tracking app data is gold mine for advertisers that risks women safety]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cam.ac.uk/research/news/menstrual-tracking-app-data-is-a-gold-mine-for-advertisers-that-risks-womens-safety-report</id>
        <link href="https://www.cam.ac.uk/research/news/menstrual-tracking-app-data-is-a-gold-mine-for-advertisers-that-risks-womens-safety-report"/>
        <updated>2025-06-11T12:31:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nasdaq-listed Interactive Strength launches $500M AI token treasury with Fetch.ai]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/nasdaq-listed-trnr-to-raise-500m-for-fet-ai-token-treasury</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/nasdaq-listed-trnr-to-raise-500m-for-fet-ai-token-treasury?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-06-11T12:13:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Interactive Strength aims to launch the world’s largest corporate AI-crypto treasury to boost shareholder value and incorporate AI tools.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Zoltan Vardai</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Download: Amsterdam’s welfare AI experiment, and making humanoid robots safer]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1118528</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/06/11/1118528/the-download-amsterdams-welfare-ai-experiment-and-making-humanoid-robots-safer/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-11T12:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is today’s edition of The Download, our weekday newsletter that provides a daily dose of what’s going on in the world of technology. Inside Amsterdam’s high-stakes experiment to create fair welfare AI Amsterdam thought it was on the right track. City officials in the welfare department believed they could build technology that would prevent fraud while…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rhiannon Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nintendo Sells 3.5 Million Switch 2 Units In Just Four Days Since Launch]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=355579</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/355579/nintendo-switch-2-3-5-million-units/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-11T11:58:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nintendo recently set and broke its own sales record, claiming to have sold 3.5 million units of its new Switch 2 console, just four days after launch. On that note, it also makes the handheld the brand’s fastest-selling game handheld in its history. By comparison, Nintendo sold 2.7 million units of the original Switch console […]
The post Nintendo Sells 3.5 Million Switch 2 Units In Just Four Days Since Launch appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John Law</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Penang’s Mutiara LRT Project Will Begin In Two Months]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=355574</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/355574/penangs-mutiara-lrt-project-will-begin-in-two-months/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-11T11:51:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Mutiara LRT Line in Penang is expected to commence with the next two months according to the Transport Minister, Anthony Loke. He also added that the outstanding issues between the federal and Penang governments have been resolved, including release letters from the state government. According to Loke, the project’s main ­contractor has already delegated […]
The post Penang’s Mutiara LRT Project Will Begin In Two Months appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Keran</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FTX users fight to unlock $2.2B in still-disputed bankruptcy claims]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/ftx-creditors-fight-2-2b-of-disputed-claims</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/ftx-creditors-fight-2-2b-of-disputed-claims?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-06-11T11:43:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[FTX creditors are awaiting progress on at least $2.2 billion worth of disputed claims, with some users reporting issues with the KYC verification process.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Zoltan Vardai</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[realme P3 Ultra To Launch In Malaysia Next Week]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=355596</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/355596/realme-p3-ultra-to-launch-in-malaysia-next-week/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-11T11:28:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[realme Malaysia has confirmed the upcoming arrival of its P3 Ultra smartphone, which will launch locally on 16 June 2025. The mid-premium device was originally unveiled in India back in March this year. The realme P3 Ultra sports a Glowing Lunar Design on its rear panel, which is inspired by the moon’s surface. Additionally, it […]
The post realme P3 Ultra To Launch In Malaysia Next Week appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Heirul Kamel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nvidia believes physical AI systems are a $50 trillion market opportunity]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3011509</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/games/nvidia-believes-physical-ai-systems-are-a-50-trillion-market-opportunity/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-11T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jensen Huang, CEO of Nvidia, said Nvidia's physical AI systems are poised to revolutionize industries, with a $50 trillion market opportunity.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dean Takahashi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Get Information About Your Linux System Through the Command Line]]></title>
        <id>68495738cb7b75f7a33a73c4</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/get-linux-system-info-through-cli/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-11T10:15:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Whether you’ve just gained access to a new Linux system, ethically hacked into one as part of a security test, or you’re just curious to know more about your current machine, this article will guide you through the process. You’ll learn how you can g...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Zaira Hira</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why humanoid robots need their own safety rules]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1118519</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/06/11/1118519/humanoids-safety-rules/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-11T10:11:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Last year, a humanoid warehouse robot named Digit set to work handling boxes of Spanx. Digit can lift boxes up to 16 kilograms between trolleys and conveyor belts, taking over some of the heavier work for its human colleagues. It works in a restricted, defined area, separated from human workers by physical panels or laser…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Victoria Turk</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sonos Rolls Out TrueCinema In New Update For Ace Headphones]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=355570</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/355570/sonos-ace-update/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-11T09:53:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sonos rolled out a major update for its Ace headphones today. Among the updates is the addition of TrueCinema technology and an updated Active Noise Cancellation (ANC). “We’re pleased to deliver experiences we’ve heard our customers ask for, like the ability for two people to watch TV with their Sonos Ace headphones at the same […]
The post Sonos Rolls Out TrueCinema In New Update For Ace Headphones appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John Law</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Show HN: DIY virtual HDMI monitor using "AR" glasses]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/mgschwan/viture_virtual_display</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/mgschwan/viture_virtual_display"/>
        <updated>2025-06-11T09:20:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Samsung Announces M9 M90SF OLED Smart Monitor For Malaysian Market]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=355558</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/355558/samsung-announces-m9-m90sf-oled-smart-monitor-for-malaysia/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-11T09:09:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Samsung has introduced the M9 M90SF, its first-ever OLED Smart Monitor, which is slated to be available in Malaysia soon. Created for users who want a versatile, all-in-one screen that blends work, entertainment and communication, the new monitor serves as a workstation, TV, gaming console and video call hub in a single sleek package. The […]
The post Samsung Announces M9 M90SF OLED Smart Monitor For Malaysian Market appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Heirul Kamel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Inside Amsterdam’s high-stakes experiment to create fair welfare AI]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1118233</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/06/11/1118233/amsterdam-fair-welfare-ai-discriminatory-algorithms-failure/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-11T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This story is a partnership between MIT Technology Review, Lighthouse Reports, and Trouw, and was supported by the Pulitzer Center.  Two futures Hans de Zwart, a gym teacher turned digital rights advocate, says that when he saw Amsterdam’s plan to have an algorithm evaluate every welfare applicant in the city for potential fraud, he nearly…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eileen Guo, Gabriel Geiger, Justin-Casimir Braun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Toyota bZ5 EV Debuts In China]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=355524</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/355524/toyota-bz5-debuts-in-china/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-11T08:57:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Toyota launched the bZ5 coupe SUV in China, which is offered in four variants. This car is the result of Toyota’s partnership with the Chinese automaker FAW, hence it features some key components from BYD. In terms of design, the car features a sharp C-shaped headlights that is connected to a thin strip of LED […]
The post Toyota bZ5 EV Debuts In China appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Keran</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Show HN: S3mini – Tiny and fast S3-compatible client, no-deps, edge-ready]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/good-lly/s3mini</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/good-lly/s3mini"/>
        <updated>2025-06-11T08:55:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Atome Opens Atome Card Waitlist Ahead Of Malaysian Launch]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=355542</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/355542/atome-opens-atome-card-waitlist-ahead-of-malaysian-launch/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-11T08:32:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Buy Now, Pay Later (BNPL) platform Atome is planning to launch the Atome Card in Malaysia sometime in the future. While the company has yet to officially announce the card, users can join a waitlist through the app to be notified once the application process is open. The Atome Card is a BNPL card which […]
The post Atome Opens Atome Card Waitlist Ahead Of Malaysian Launch appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nurul Kamil</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bolt Brings Pick-Up Codes To Malaysia For Extra Safety]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=355532</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/355532/bolt-pick-up-codes/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-11T08:25:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bolt, one of the newer e-hailing players in Malaysia, has brought in a new safety feature called pick-up codes. While the feature was introduced in other markets a while back, it has now started promoting it as a new optional safety tool here. The purpose of pickup codes is to make sure that the right […]
The post Bolt Brings Pick-Up Codes To Malaysia For Extra Safety appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ikmal Rozlan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Alienware Launches Area-51 Brick Kit]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=355499</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/355499/alienware-area-51-brick-kit/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-11T07:00:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Alienware recently launched a Lego-inspired brick kit of Area-51 desktop PC. The brick kit is exclusive for Arena members and is made with Authentic Lego bricks. Specs-wise, the brick kit is about the same size as a Mac Mini M4 – the mockup’s W x H x L measures in at 5.5 x 13 x […]
The post Alienware Launches Area-51 Brick Kit appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John Law</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Koreans ask what year you were born]]></title>
        <id>https://bryanhogan.com/blog/korean-age</id>
        <link href="https://bryanhogan.com/blog/korean-age"/>
        <updated>2025-06-11T06:53:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AlphaSense launches its own Deep Research for the web AND your enterprise files — here’s why it matters]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3011457</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/alphasense-launches-its-own-deep-research-for-the-web-and-your-enterprise-files-heres-why-it-matters/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-11T00:49:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Every report generated by Deep Research includes clickable citations to underlying content, enabling both verification and deeper follow-up.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carl Franzen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OpenAI launches o3-pro AI model, offering increased reliability and tool use for enterprises — while sacrificing speed]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3011390</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/openai-launches-o3-pro-ai-model-offering-increased-reliability-and-tool-use-for-enterprises-while-sacrificing-speed/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-10T22:19:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[OpenAI released the latest in its o-series of reasoning model that promises more reliable and accurate responses for enterprises.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Emilia David</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The five security principles driving open source security apps at scale]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3010821</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/security/top-five-security-principles-driving-open-source-cyber-apps-at-scale/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-10T20:52:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Open-source AI is shaping the future of cybersecurity innovation, consistently breaking down barriers and delivering results.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Louis Columbus</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Show HN: I made a 3D printed VTOL drone]]></title>
        <id>https://www.tsungxu.com/p/i-made-a-3d-printed-vtol-that-can</id>
        <link href="https://www.tsungxu.com/p/i-made-a-3d-printed-vtol-that-can"/>
        <updated>2025-06-10T20:47:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AlphaOne gives AI developers a new dial to control LLM ‘thinking’ and boost performance]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3011239</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/alphaone-gives-ai-developers-a-new-dial-to-control-llm-thinking-and-boost-performance/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-10T20:34:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new framework called AlphaOne is a novel way to modulate LLM thinking, improving model accuracy and efficiency without costly retraining.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ben Dickson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Apple Code Signing Handbook]]></title>
        <id>68489084490c709f6b3070ed</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/apple-code-signing-handbook/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-10T20:07:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this handbook, I’ll demystify the Apple app code signing process. Apple's ecosystem is powerful, but its distribution mechanisms – with various identifiers, certificates, and profiles – can appear complex. This guide attempts to make that journey ...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sravan Karuturi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hyperliquid in 2025: A High-Performance DEX Building the Future of Onchain Finance]]></title>
        <id>6846e8f8529c590001648fa0</id>
        <link href="https://blog.quicknode.com/hyperliquid-protocol-analysis-2025/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-10T19:47:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Explore how hyperliquid became the leading perp DEX: A deep dive of architecture, metrics, tokenomics, and vision for onchain finance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Unhashed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Launch HN: Vassar Robotics (YC X25) – $219 robot arm that learns new skills]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=44240302</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=44240302"/>
        <updated>2025-06-10T19:12:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mistral’s first reasoning model, Magistral, launches with large and small Apache 2.0 version]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3011320</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/mistrals-first-reasoning-model-magistral-launches-with-large-and-small-apache-2-0-version/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-10T18:55:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The company is signaling that the future of reasoning AI will be both powerful and, in a meaningful way, open to all.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carl Franzen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OpenAI announces 80% price drop for o3, it’s most powerful reasoning model]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3011288</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/openai-announces-80-price-drop-for-o3-its-most-powerful-reasoning-model/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-10T18:08:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It could benefit startups, research teams, and individual developers who previously found higher-tier model access cost-prohibitive.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carl Franzen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Deploy a Next.js App To Vercel With GitHub Actions]]></title>
        <id>684871b16bc1898625c952fd</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/deploy-to-vercel-with-github-actions/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-10T17:56:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Vercel is a cloud platform or Platform-as-a-Service (PaaS) designed to help frontend developers create, preview, and deploy web applications swiftly and efficiently. In this tutorial, we’ll focus on deploying a Next.js application to Vercel using Git...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chidiadi Anyanwu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Qualcomm shares its vision for the future of smart glasses with on-glass Gen AI]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3011107</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/games/qualcomm-shares-its-vision-for-the-future-of-smart-glasses-with-on-glass-gen-ai/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-10T16:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Qualcomm has enabled what one of its executives said was a strange and "most interesting" conversations with generative AI-powered smart glasses.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dean Takahashi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn the MERN Stack in 2025]]></title>
        <id>68483a699e226a329abe4dee</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-the-mern-stack-in-2025/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-10T14:00:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you’ve been meaning to learn full-stack web development but don’t know where to start, this new course is a solid way in. Whether you're aiming to get a job in web dev or just want to build your own projects, understanding how the pieces fit toget...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vanta’s AI agent wants to run your compliance program — and it just might]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3011165</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/vantas-ai-agent-wants-to-run-your-compliance-program-and-it-just-might/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-10T13:01:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Vanta launches autonomous AI agent that automates security compliance workflows, helping enterprises save 12+ hours weekly on policy management and audit preparation.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Nuñez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Zip debuts 50 AI agents to kill procurement inefficiencies—OpenAI is already on board]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3010781</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/zip-debuts-50-ai-agents-to-kill-procurement-inefficiencies-openai-is-already-on-board/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-10T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Zip launches 50 AI agents to automate enterprise procurement for OpenAI, Canva, targeting $4.4B in savings through automated contract reviews and compliance checks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Nuñez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Zencoder just launched an AI that can replace days of QA work in two hours]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3011083</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/zencoder-just-launched-an-ai-that-can-replace-days-of-qa-work-in-two-hours/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-10T12:59:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Zencoder launches Zentester, an AI-powered testing agent that automates end-to-end software testing, as the startup competes with GitHub Copilot and other AI coding tools in the rapidly consolidating market.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Nuñez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Your AI and Data Future is Sovereign]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1118376</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/06/10/1118376/your-ai-and-data-future-is-sovereign/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-10T12:14:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[EDB CEO, Kevin Dallas, takes the stage at MIT Technology Review's EmTech AI event.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Courtney Dobson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Download: IBM’s quantum computer, and cuts to military AI testing]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1118372</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/06/10/1118372/the-download-ibms-quantum-computer-and-cuts-to-military-ai-testing/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-10T12:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is today’s edition of The Download, our weekday newsletter that provides a daily dose of what’s going on in the world of technology. IBM aims to build the world’s first large-scale, error-corrected quantum computer by 2028 The news: IBM announced detailed plans today to build an error-corrected quantum computer with significantly more computational capability than existing…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rhiannon Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[IBM aims to build the world’s first large-scale, error-corrected quantum computer by 2028]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1118297</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/06/10/1118297/ibm-large-scale-error-corrected-quantum-computer-by-2028/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-10T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[IBM announced detailed plans today to build an error-corrected quantum computer with significantly more computational capability than existing machines by 2028. It hopes to make the computer available to users via the cloud by 2029.  The proposed machine, named Starling, will consist of a network of modules, each of which contains a set of chips,…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sophia Chen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Pentagon is gutting the team that tests AI and weapons systems]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1118229</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/06/10/1118229/pentagon-gutting-ai-test/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-10T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Trump administration’s chainsaw approach to federal spending lives on, even as Elon Musk turns on the president. On May 28, Secretary of Defense Pete Hegseth announced he’d be gutting a key office at the Department of Defense responsible for testing and evaluating the safety of weapons and AI systems. As part of a string…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>James O'Donnell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Apple makes major AI advance with image generation technology rivaling DALL-E and Midjourney]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3011035</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/apple-makes-major-ai-advance-with-image-generation-technology-rivaling-dall-e-and-midjourney/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-09T18:50:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Apple researchers develop STARFlow, a breakthrough AI image generation system that challenges diffusion models used by DALL-E and Midjourney with competitive performance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Nuñez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What are Onchain Agents: An Introduction to Autonomous, Agent-Driven Web]]></title>
        <id>6840a302a1fc8e00012e657d</id>
        <link href="https://blog.quicknode.com/introduction-to-onchain-agents/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-09T15:37:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An introduction to onchain AI agents: autonomous programs that combine blockchain trustlessness with AI intelligence. Learn how they work.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Unhashed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Top Blockchain Data Tools: How to be Informed Onchain?]]></title>
        <id>6840a419a1fc8e00012e658d</id>
        <link href="https://blog.quicknode.com/top-blockchain-data-tools/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-09T15:32:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Web3 in 2025 runs on data. This guide covers the best onchain data tools and analytics platforms and how QuickNode Streams powers them.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Unhashed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Common Solana RPC Errors & Fixes Using QuickNode Logs]]></title>
        <id>6840a20da1fc8e00012e6573</id>
        <link href="https://blog.quicknode.com/solana-rpc-errors-quicknode-logs/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-09T15:28:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn how to identify and fix common Solana RPC errors using QuickNode Logs that provide real-time insights into every request and response.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Unhashed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Developer's Guide to Monad: EVM-Compatible L1 Architecture and Implementation]]></title>
        <id>6840a4c8a1fc8e00012e6598</id>
        <link href="https://blog.quicknode.com/monad-developer-guide/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-09T15:09:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Build faster, cheaper, and better on Monad: A deep dive into Monad’s architecture, performance features, and developer workflows.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Unhashed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Download: an inspiring toy robot arm, and why AM radio matters]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1118186</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/06/09/1118186/the-download-an-inspiring-toy-robot-arm-and-why-am-radio-matters/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-09T12:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is today’s edition of The Download, our weekday newsletter that provides a daily dose of what’s going on in the world of technology. How a 1980s toy robot arm inspired modern robotics —Jon Keegan As a child of an electronic engineer, I spent a lot of time in our local Radio Shack as a kid. While…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rhiannon Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How I Program with Agents]]></title>
        <id>https://crawshaw.io/blog/programming-with-agents</id>
        <link href="https://crawshaw.io/blog/programming-with-agents"/>
        <updated>2025-06-09T05:30:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Like humans, AI is forcing institutions to rethink their purpose]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3010794</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/like-humans-ai-is-forcing-institutions-to-rethink-their-purpose/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-08T20:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Like people undergoing cognitive migration, institutions must reassess what they were made for in this age of AI.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gary Grossman, Edelman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Air-dried vs. Kiln-dried Wood]]></title>
        <id>https://christopherschwarz.substack.com/p/air-dried-vs-kiln-dried-wood</id>
        <link href="https://christopherschwarz.substack.com/p/air-dried-vs-kiln-dried-wood"/>
        <updated>2025-06-08T15:45:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Characterizing my first attempt at copper-only passives]]></title>
        <id>https://moroso.emarhavil.com/~joshua/2pf-characterization.html</id>
        <link href="https://moroso.emarhavil.com/~joshua/2pf-characterization.html"/>
        <updated>2025-06-08T06:01:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Diary of Samuel Pepys]]></title>
        <id>https://www.historytoday.com/archive/feature/hidden-diary-samuel-pepys</id>
        <link href="https://www.historytoday.com/archive/feature/hidden-diary-samuel-pepys"/>
        <updated>2025-06-08T04:41:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Agent-based computing is outgrowing the web as we know it]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3010786</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/agent-based-computing-is-outgrowing-the-web-as-we-know-it/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-07T22:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AI agents are moving from passive assistants to active participants. Today, we ask them to do. Tomorrow, we’ll authorize them to act.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Justin Westcott, Edelman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lessons from That 1834 Landscape Gardening Guidebook]]></title>
        <id>https://fi-le.net/pueckler/</id>
        <link href="https://fi-le.net/pueckler/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-07T21:48:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Plants hear their pollinators, and produce sweet nectar in response]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cbc.ca/listen/live-radio/1-51-quirks-and-quarks/clip/16150976-plants-hear-pollinators-produce-sweet-nectar-response</id>
        <link href="https://www.cbc.ca/listen/live-radio/1-51-quirks-and-quarks/clip/16150976-plants-hear-pollinators-produce-sweet-nectar-response"/>
        <updated>2025-06-07T19:27:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The librarian immediately attempts to sell you a vuvuzela]]></title>
        <id>https://kaveland.no/posts/2025-06-06-library</id>
        <link href="https://kaveland.no/posts/2025-06-06-library"/>
        <updated>2025-06-07T17:04:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sam Altman calls for ‘AI privilege’ as OpenAI clarifies court order to retain temporary and deleted ChatGPT sessions]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3010670</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/sam-altman-calls-for-ai-privilege-as-openai-clarifies-court-order-to-retain-temporary-and-deleted-chatgpt-sessions/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-06T17:48:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Should talking to an AI chatbot be protected and privileged information, like talking to a doctor or lawyer? A new court order raises the idea]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carl Franzen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Voice AI that actually converts: New TTS model boosts sales 15% for major brands]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3010147</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/voice-ai-that-actually-converts-new-tts-model-boosts-sales-15-for-major-brands/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-06T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new spoken language model can quickly generate “infinite” new voices of varying genders, ages, demographics, based on a simple text prompt.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Taryn Plumb</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[From electrical engineering student to CTO with Hitesh Choudhary [Podcast #175]]]></title>
        <id>6842e00169a5099a551058ce</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/from-electrical-engineering-student-to-cto-with-hitesh-choudhary-podcast-175/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-06T12:33:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On this week's episode of the podcast, freeCodeCamp founder Quincy Larson interviews former CTO and prolific programming teacher Hitesh Choudhary.   We talk about: The limits of AI in building a robust codebase Time management Higher Education in ...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Download: China’s AI agent boom, and GPS alternatives]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1118044</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/06/06/1118044/the-download-chinas-ai-agent-boom-and-gps-alternatives/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-06T12:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is today’s edition of The Download, our weekday newsletter that provides a daily dose of what’s going on in the world of technology. Manus has kick-started an AI agent boom in China Last year, China saw a boom in foundation models, the do-everything large language models that underpin the AI revolution. This year, the focus has…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rhiannon Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Protect Your Remote Workforce from Cyber Attacks]]></title>
        <id>6842cf8a6fcd9b03c19d04ea</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/protect-remote-workforce-from-cyber-attacks/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-06T11:22:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Working remotely gives your team flexibility, but it also opens the door to cyber threats. Remote workers are more exposed without the protection of office firewalls and on-site IT teams.  Hackers know that people often use weak passwords, forget to ...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Manish Shivanandhan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Reduce Technical Debt in the Power Platform]]></title>
        <id>6842c4f3e7fdc9878ba5dadd</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-reduce-technical-debt-in-the-power-platform/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-06T10:37:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Technical debt refers to the future cost – measured in terms of time, money, effort, or opportunity – of choosing expedient solutions today instead of more deliberate and scalable ones. And it's not just a pro-code concept. It might be easier to unde...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brandon Wozniewicz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Micro-Frontend Architecture Handbook]]></title>
        <id>6842c120a3469a9ca728862b</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/complete-micro-frontends-guide/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-06T10:21:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Over the years, in my role as a lead full-stack developer, solutions architect, and mentor, I’ve been immersed in the world of micro frontend architecture, working across different large-scale frontend projects where multiple teams, stacks, and deplo...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Maksimchenko</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why doctors should look for ways to prescribe hope]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1117937</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/06/06/1117937/why-doctors-should-look-for-ways-to-prescribe-hope/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-06T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This week, I’ve been thinking about the powerful connection between mind and body. Some new research suggests that people with heart conditions have better outcomes when they are more hopeful and optimistic. Hopelessness, on the other hand, is associated with a significantly higher risk of death. The findings build upon decades of fascinating research into…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jessica Hamzelou</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google claims Gemini 2.5 Pro preview beats DeepSeek R1 and Grok 3 Beta in coding performance]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3010537</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/google-claims-gemini-2-5-pro-preview-beats-deepseek-r1-and-grok-3-beta-in-coding-performance/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-05T21:30:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google said the newest version of Gemini 2.5 Pro, now on preview, gives faster and more creative responses while performing better than OpenAI's o3.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Emilia David</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OpenFeign vs WebClient: How to Choose a REST Client for Your Spring Boot Project]]></title>
        <id>6841f2c63a801418642db429</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/best-choice-openfeign-or-webclient/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-05T19:40:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When building microservices with Spring Boot, you’ll have to decide how the services will communicate with one another. The basic choices in terms of protocols are Messaging and REST. In this article we’ll discuss tools based on REST, which is a comm...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mario Casari</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Solidroad just raised $6.5M to reinvent customer service with AI that coaches, not replaces]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3010526</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/solidroad-just-raised-6-5m-to-reinvent-customer-service-with-ai-that-coaches-not-replaces/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-05T17:39:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dublin AI startup Solidroad raises $6.5M from First Round Capital to transform customer service training with AI that coaches human agents and improves satisfaction scores.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Nuñez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How much information do LLMs really memorize? Now we know, thanks to Meta, Google, Nvidia and Cornell]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3010502</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/how-much-information-do-llms-really-memorize-now-we-know-thanks-to-meta-google-nvidia-and-cornell/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-05T15:35:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Using a clever solution, researchers find GPT-style models have a fixed memorization capacity of approximately 3.6 bits per parameter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carl Franzen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Securing AI at scale: Databricks and Noma close the inference vulnerability gap]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3010387</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/security/databricks-noma-tackle-cisos-ai-inference-nightmare/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-05T14:13:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Databricks Ventures and Noma Security partner to tackle critical AI inference vulnerabilities with real-time threat analytics, proactive red teaming, and robust governance, helping CISOs confidently scale secure enterprise AI deployments.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Louis Columbus</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Powering High-Performance Web3 Experiences: Gravity (by Galxe) Launches on QuickNode]]></title>
        <id>683622d561c46d0001eed5d9</id>
        <link href="https://blog.quicknode.com/gravity-alpha-launch/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-29T13:54:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Explore Galxe Gravity’s omnichain power on QuickNode. Build scalable, identity-centric dApps effortlessly with dedicated endpoints and developer tools.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>QuickNode</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[QuickNode Accelerator - ChaiNova]]></title>
        <id>68377c476b77cd0001482835</id>
        <link href="https://blog.quicknode.com/quicknode-accelerator-chainova/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T21:31:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ChaiNova joins QuickNode’s Accelerator to bring inclusive Web3 access from local shops to global enterprises.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>QuickNode</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[QuickNode Accelerator - SettleX]]></title>
        <id>6813ad1304ef2c0001211afb</id>
        <link href="https://blog.quicknode.com/quicknode-accelerator-settlex/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T16:00:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discover SettleX, a modular cross-chain clearing layer improving capital efficiency, privacy, and liquidity across the DeFi landscape.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>QuickNode</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[QuickNode Accelerator - taro/NYU]]></title>
        <id>68222cb536cbae0001089a2b</id>
        <link href="https://blog.quicknode.com/quicknode-accelerator-taro/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T15:59:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Taro is a privacy-first blockchain project from NYU and Microsoft, enhancing financial transparency and accountability in organizations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>QuickNode</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[QuickNode Accelerator - Mements]]></title>
        <id>68222d3a36cbae0001089a38</id>
        <link href="https://blog.quicknode.com/quicknode-accelerator-mements/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T15:59:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mements is building infrastructure for verifiable AI, with timestamped prompts, provable video streaming, and the launch of MemeChain.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>QuickNode</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[QuickNode Accelerator - EcoFundMe]]></title>
        <id>6822330f36cbae0001089a61</id>
        <link href="https://blog.quicknode.com/quicknode-accelerator-ecofundme/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T15:59:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[EcoFundMe connects donors to verified climate projects with tokenized contributions, DAO governance, and transparent onchain funding.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>QuickNode</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[QuickNode Accelerator - Rivalz Network]]></title>
        <id>68248d91bf7346000109494e</id>
        <link href="https://blog.quicknode.com/quicknode-accelerator-rivalz-network/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T15:59:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Rivalz is building verifiable AI infrastructure, enabling smart contracts to query AI oracles, real-world data, and autonomous agents.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>QuickNode</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[QuickNode Accelerator - Hangry Animals]]></title>
        <id>68236ae084101f00013a5cd0</id>
        <link href="https://blog.quicknode.com/quicknode-accelerator-hangry-animals/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T15:58:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hangry Animals blends storytelling, Web3, and social good into a transmedia universe where players own, earn, and impact real causes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>QuickNode</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[QuickNode Accelerator - Boost Ad Network]]></title>
        <id>6813cc2f04ef2c0001211b24</id>
        <link href="https://blog.quicknode.com/quicknode-accelerator-boost-ad-network/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T15:58:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Boost is an onchain-native, privacy-first ad network with verifiable auctions, real attribution, and campaign analytics for Web3.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>QuickNode</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[QuickNode Accelerator - Diamondz Shadow Movies]]></title>
        <id>6824f61dbf734600010949a1</id>
        <link href="https://blog.quicknode.com/quicknode-accelerator-diamondz-shadow-movies/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T15:58:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Diamondz Shadow is creating a blockchain-powered entertainment ecosystem spanning games, film, tokenized media, and real-world utility.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>QuickNode</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>