<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2025-05-31T15:13:17.209Z</id>
    <title>AngJianming RSS Feed</title>
    <updated>2025-05-31T15:13:17.209Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Precision Clock Mk IV]]></title>
        <id>https://mitxela.com/projects/precision_clock_mk_iv</id>
        <link href="https://mitxela.com/projects/precision_clock_mk_iv"/>
        <updated>2025-05-31T15:06:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[I Blogged Every Day for a Month -- Again]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/vst/i-blogged-every-day-for-a-month-again-pkg</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/vst/i-blogged-every-day-for-a-month-again-pkg"/>
        <updated>2025-05-31T14:54:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today marks the final day of my second month-long blogging challenge. The first was in August last year. This one, in May, felt different -- but just as transformative.
Here are my takeaways.
I have a few jobs to do, with different hats to wear. I also have a family. So, blogging almost always happened late in the evenings.
Some evenings I had not even thought about what to write until 9pm-10pm. Then I had to find a topic, write, and publish. It was stressful and felt like a grind. But this taught me something important: grind is everywhere.
If you are a marketer, you grind to get leads. If you are a developer, you grind to fix bugs and run chores for housekeeping. The examples may change, but the grind stays.
If your job never feels like a grind, maybe you are lucky. But maybe not. Grind,…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Vehbi Sinan Tunalioglu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Best Docker Deployment Starategy]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/andrewkangg/best-docker-deployment-starategy-4enc</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/andrewkangg/best-docker-deployment-starategy-4enc"/>
        <updated>2025-05-31T14:49:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[https://github.com/patternhelloworld/docker-blue-green-runner
Achieve zero-downtime deployment using just your .env and Dockerfile
Docker-Blue-Green-Runner's run.sh script is designed to simplify deployment: "With your .env, project, and a single Dockerfile, simply run 'bash run.sh'." This script covers the entire process from Dockerfile build to server deployment from scratch.
This means you can easily migrate to another server with just the files mentioned above.
In contrast, Traefik requires the creation and gradual adjustment of various configuration files, which requires your App's docker binary running.
No unpredictable errors in reverse proxy and deployment : Implement safety measures to handle errors caused by your app or Nginx
If any error occurs in the app or router, deployment is halted to prevent any impact on the existing deployment
Internal Integrity Check:
Nginx Router Test Container
External Integrity Check
Rollback Procedures
Additional Know-hows on Docker: Tips and best practices for optimizing your Docker workflow and deployment processes
For example, Traefik offers powerful dynamic configuration and service discovery; however, certain errors, such as a failure to detect containers (due to issues like unrecognized certificates), can lead to frustrating 404 errors that are hard to trace through logs alone.
https://stackoverflow.com/questions/76660749/traefik-404-page-not-found-when-use-https
https://community.traefik.io/t/getting-bad-gateway-404-page-when-supposed-to-route-to-container-port-8443/20398
Manipulates NGINX configuration files directly to ensure container accessibility.
Track Blue-Green status and the Git SHA of your running container for easy monitoring.
Blue-Green deployment decision algorithm: scoring-based approach
Run the command bash check-current-status.sh (similar to git status) to view all relevant details
Security
Refer to the Security section
Production Deployment
Refer to the Production Deployment section]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Kang-G</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Frontend to Fullstack - Mastering the Architectural Mindset]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/bobysf12/frontend-to-fullstack-mastering-the-architectural-mindset-n0i</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/bobysf12/frontend-to-fullstack-mastering-the-architectural-mindset-n0i"/>
        <updated>2025-05-31T14:39:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I spent 6 years working as a frontend developer.  
Today, I find myself responsible for building and maintaining fullstack systems. Frontend, backend, deployment, scaling, all of it. Not because I mastered everything, but because I learned how to think architecturally.
Becoming fullstack isn't about learning backend code. It's about changing how you think.
Most frontend devs already know how to solve problems. Architecture is just solving bigger problems but more intentionally. 
If you've ever designed a clean component tree, you’re already halfway there.
Architecture starts with the problem, travels through trade-offs, and only then lands in code. 
In this post, I'll share what I've learned about developing that mindset, especially as someone coming from a frontend background stepping int…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Boby Santoso</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum&#039;s 55% rally setup vs. Bitcoin sparks ‘altseason’ hopes]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/ethereum-55-rally-setup-vs-bitcoin-sparks-altseason-hopes</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/ethereum-55-rally-setup-vs-bitcoin-sparks-altseason-hopes?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-31T14:38:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Analysts say Ethereum’s breakout versus Bitcoin could trigger a 250x altcoin market rally, signaling the start of a 2025 altseason.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Yashu Gola</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Is Cloud Computing in 2025 Broken? A Realistic Look at the Future of the Cloud]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/cyberry_technologies/is-cloud-computing-in-2025-broken-a-realistic-look-at-the-future-of-the-cloud-2eka</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/cyberry_technologies/is-cloud-computing-in-2025-broken-a-realistic-look-at-the-future-of-the-cloud-2eka"/>
        <updated>2025-05-31T14:36:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The cloud was once hailed as the future of IT—and in many ways, it still is. But as we step deeper into 2025, professionals across industries are asking a bold question:
On the surface, that might sound dramatic. After all, cloud spending is higher than ever, hybrid and multi-cloud strategies are the new norm, and platforms like AWS, Microsoft Azure, and Google Cloud continue to dominate the digital backbone of the world.
But beneath the surface, rising costs, vendor lock-in, data sovereignty issues, and operational complexity are challenging even the most cloud-mature enterprises. So, is cloud computing truly broken—or just going through a necessary transformation?
Let’s unpack the real story.
According to recent reports, over 70% of organizations exceeded their cloud budgets in 2024. Thi…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cyberry Technologies</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Testing PostgreSQL WAL Streamers for Byte-Level Fidelity]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/alzhi_f93e67fa45b972/testing-postgresql-wal-streamers-for-byte-level-fidelity-a15</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/alzhi_f93e67fa45b972/testing-postgresql-wal-streamers-for-byte-level-fidelity-a15"/>
        <updated>2025-05-31T14:36:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Verifying that WAL streamers preserve exact database state — bit by bit.
In the previous post, we explored the motivations behind building pgrwl, a PostgreSQL WAL receiver designed for zero data loss (RPO=0) scenarios in containerized environments. We covered its architecture, features like compression/encryption, and its suitability for Kubernetes-based disaster recovery.
This follow-up post focuses on testing — specifically validating that pgrwl produces WAL archives that are byte-for-byte identical to PostgreSQL’s official tool (pg_receivewal) and that it supports full PITR (Point-in-Time Recovery) after abrupt system crashes.
Write-Ahead Logs (WALs) are at the heart of PostgreSQL’s crash recovery and replication capabilities. But what happens when we replace the native WAL receiver (pg…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>alexey.zh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Exploring Open Source Software: A Journey Through Collaboration and Innovation]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/kpcofgs/exploring-open-source-software-a-journey-through-collaboration-and-innovation-570j</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/kpcofgs/exploring-open-source-software-a-journey-through-collaboration-and-innovation-570j"/>
        <updated>2025-05-31T14:36:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Exploring Open Source Software: A Journey Through Collaboration and Innovation
In today's digital landscape, Open Source Software (OSS) stands as a beacon of innovation, collaboration, and transparency. This article delves into what OSS is, its significance in the tech world, and how it shapes our everyday experiences.
Understanding Open Source Software


Open Source Software is software whose source code—the fundamental part that makes the program function—is made publicly available. This accessibility allows anyone with technical skills to view, modify, and distribute the code, fostering a culture of collaborative development. Unlike proprietary software, where only the company holding the license can distribute it, OSS is freely accessible to all.
The Power of Collaboration


One of the…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shixian Sheng</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Remix v3: The Bold React Breakup That's Reshaping Web Development]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/vitalii_petrenko_dev/remix-v3-the-bold-react-breakup-thats-reshaping-web-development-2n3f</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/vitalii_petrenko_dev/remix-v3-the-bold-react-breakup-thats-reshaping-web-development-2n3f"/>
        <updated>2025-05-31T14:35:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Why Remix's web standards approach reveals what's wrong with modern React development


The JavaScript framework landscape just experienced an earthquake. On May 26, 2025, the Remix team dropped a bombshell that left the React community divided: Remix v3 is completely abandoning React in favor of a Preact fork and embracing an entirely new development philosophy.
But here's what most analysis missed: This move exposes fundamental weaknesses in how we've been building web apps with React - and why the current "just use Next.js" advice might be steering you wrong.
As a frontend architect who's been building large-scale applications for over a decade, I've witnessed many framework transitions. But this? This isn't just about Remix. It's about whether we're building the web right.
Let me break…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Vitalii Petrenko</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SteamOS vs. Windows: A Comparative Analysis for Gaming]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/kpcofgs/steamos-vs-windows-a-comparative-analysis-for-gaming-743</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/kpcofgs/steamos-vs-windows-a-comparative-analysis-for-gaming-743"/>
        <updated>2025-05-31T14:35:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SteamOS vs. Windows: A Comparative Analysis for Gaming
In the ever-evolving landscape of gaming platforms, SteamOS and Windows each offer unique advantages and disadvantages. This article delves into a detailed comparison of these two operating systems, focusing solely on their capabilities and suitability for gaming.
1. Ease of Use


SteamOS:

SteamOS, based on Linux, is known for its open-source nature and flexibility. Users who are already familiar with Linux will appreciate the level of control and customization available. However, for those new to Linux, there might be a learning curve as it requires some technical knowledge to set up and configure.
Windows:

Windows, being the traditional operating system, is renowned for its user-friendliness. It offers an intuitive interface that's…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shixian Sheng</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Acclimation of Osmoregulatory Function in Salmon]]></title>
        <id>https://www.unm.edu/~toolson/salmon_osmoregulation.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.unm.edu/~toolson/salmon_osmoregulation.html"/>
        <updated>2025-05-31T14:34:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learning XS - What is in my variable]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/lnation/learning-xs-what-is-in-my-variable-nfm</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/lnation/learning-xs-what-is-in-my-variable-nfm"/>
        <updated>2025-05-31T14:33:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Over the past year, I’ve been self-studying XS and have now decided to share my learning journey through a series of blog posts. This second post introduces the fundamentals of type checking variables in XS.
What is a variable in Perl?
In Perl, a variable is a named storage location that holds a value you can use and manipulate in your program. Perl fundamentally has three types of variables which are:
Scalars ($) hold single values (numbers, strings, references)
Arrays (@) hold ordered lists of scalars
Hashes (%) hold key-value pairs
It's important to understand that arrays always store lists, and hashes always store key-value pairs. Scalars, on the other hand, are more flexible they can hold various types of data, including numbers, strings, or references. This flexibility is why Perl pr…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>LNATION</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Debug C Program in Mac OS]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/mr007/debug-c-program-in-mac-os-203l</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/mr007/debug-c-program-in-mac-os-203l"/>
        <updated>2025-05-31T14:33:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We are using redis in our stack for many purposes,
I've always wondered about its working, though there are many resources available online explaining redis internals, I'm not super confident to say I know this. So decided to read the source of it. 
I've struggled to setup C debugging environment on my MacOS without gdb support. Turned out it was simple to setup, But I can't able to find a Blog step-by-step, so here it is.
Tools :
VSCode
lldb (gdb alternative), either you can install xcode from app store or just install xcode cli tools by ("xcode-select --install"), 
"lldb --version" to verify if ldb installed.
Get Redis Code base:
git clone https://github.com/redis/redis.git
cd redis
--------------------------------------------------------
open src/Makefile

_ We have to modify Makefile
_…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mr.007</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Shallow Copy & Deep Copy in Python (3)]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/hyperkai/shallow-copy-deep-copy-in-python-3-20ma</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/hyperkai/shallow-copy-deep-copy-in-python-3-20ma"/>
        <updated>2025-05-31T14:32:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Buy Me a Coffee☕
*Memos:
My post explains the shallow and deep copy of a list.
My post explains the shallow and deep copy of a tuple.
My post explains the shallow and deep copy of a dictionary.
My post explains variable assignment.
A set:
can have a tuple but cannot have a set, list and dictionary.
cannot be accessed by indexing and slicing so it's impossible to check an inner tuple and to experiment Deep Copy but the variables which store the same tuple always have the same references because of the experiments.
*Memos:
The one or more references of one set and zero or more tuples are stored in a variable.
v1 and v2 have the same references of the same outer set and the same inner tuple.
is keyword can check if v1 and v2 have the same references.




     ###### Outer set #####
#    ↓↓↓↓↓…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Super Kai (Kazuya Ito)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Building Model Context Protocol (MCP) Servers with stdio: A Complete Guide]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/elsayed85/building-model-context-protocol-mcp-servers-with-stdio-a-complete-guide-513k</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/elsayed85/building-model-context-protocol-mcp-servers-with-stdio-a-complete-guide-513k"/>
        <updated>2025-05-31T14:30:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Building Model Context Protocol (MCP) Servers with stdio: A Complete Guide


The Model Context Protocol (MCP) is revolutionizing how AI applications interact with external tools and data sources. In this comprehensive guide, we'll walk through building MCP servers using the stdio (standard input/output) transport method, which is perfect for local development and testing.
The Model Context Protocol is an open standard that enables AI assistants to securely connect to external data sources and tools. Think of it as a universal adapter that allows AI models to interact with databases, APIs, file systems, and custom tools in a standardized way.
The stdio transport method offers several advantages:
Simplicity: Easy to implement and debug
Local Development: Perfect for testing and development
S…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Elsayed Kamal</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ask HN: Anyone making a living from a paid API?]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=44144473</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=44144473"/>
        <updated>2025-05-31T14:23:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Show HN: Fontofweb – Discover Fonts Used on a Website or Websites Using Font(s)]]></title>
        <id>https://fontofweb.com/</id>
        <link href="https://fontofweb.com/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-31T14:20:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Two Ideals of Fields]]></title>
        <id>https://susam.net/two-ideals-of-fields.html</id>
        <link href="https://susam.net/two-ideals-of-fields.html"/>
        <updated>2025-05-31T13:59:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Show HN: AI Peer Reviewer – Multiagent System for Scientific Manuscript Analysis]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/robertjakob/rigorous</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/robertjakob/rigorous"/>
        <updated>2025-05-31T13:51:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Micro Center nerd store fills the Fry’s vacuum with its return to Silicon Valley]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3009533</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/games/micro-center-nerd-store-fills-the-frys-vacuum-with-its-return-to-silicon-valley/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-31T13:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Micro Center, an electronics retailer, has opened a store in Silicon Valley in California And so the nerd kingdom has returned.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dean Takahashi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[State of Crypto: Someone Tried to Scam Me (Probably)]]></title>
        <id>437526e0-6641-4a1b-a861-65bfd5ec9bcd</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2025/05/31/state-of-crypto-someone-tried-to-scam-me-probably"/>
        <updated>2025-05-31T13:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I got a call from someone claiming to represent Coinbase, wanting to help me secure my account.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nikhilesh De</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Insurance companies race to cover crypto kidnap and ransom risks]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/crypto-crime-insurers-race-to-cover-kidnap-ransom-risks</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/crypto-crime-insurers-race-to-cover-kidnap-ransom-risks?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-31T13:26:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto executives and investors are turning to kidnap and ransom insurance as violent attacks targeting crypto wealth continue to rise.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Amin Haqshanas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Here’s what happened in crypto today]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/what-happened-in-crypto-today</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/what-happened-in-crypto-today?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-31T13:19:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Need to know what happened in crypto today? Here is the latest news on daily trends and events impacting Bitcoin price, blockchain, DeFi, NFTs, Web3 and crypto regulation.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Cointelegraph</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin all-time high, five US states enact crypto laws: May in Charts]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/111k-bitcoin-all-time-high-states-crypto-laws-may-charts</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/111k-bitcoin-all-time-high-states-crypto-laws-may-charts?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-31T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This month, Bitcoin hit $111,000, crypto laws in the United States blazed ahead yet again, and Coinbase joined the S&P 500.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Aaron Wood</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TON Falls 7% as Sell-Off Tied to Musk's Dispute of Telegram, xAI Partnership Continues]]></title>
        <id>91db8344-df2c-4781-ac88-e6260050d3ae</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/31/ton-falls-7-as-sell-off-tied-to-musks-dispute-of-telegram-xai-partnership-continues"/>
        <updated>2025-05-31T12:33:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Despite the denial, Telegram CEO Pavel Durov stated that the deal has been "agreed in principle" and that "formalities are pending."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>AI Boost</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[XRP Down 4% as Global Economic Tensions Trigger Market Selloff]]></title>
        <id>deb6486f-46e0-41fd-94cf-e92b1acb69ac</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/31/xrp-down-4-as-global-economic-tensions-trigger-market-selloff"/>
        <updated>2025-05-31T11:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[XRP’s 4% drop highlights market uncertainty as global trade tensions and liquidations weigh on investor sentiment.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>AI Boost</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin bull run &#039;might be delayed&#039; as $104.5K weekly close becomes key]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-bull-run-might-be-delayed-104-5k-weekly-close-key</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-bull-run-might-be-delayed-104-5k-weekly-close-key?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-31T10:24:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin needs to protect old all-time highs from December 2024 during the upcoming weekly candle close, analysis says amid warnings of a "deeper pullback."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Vyacheslav Svobodin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AAVE Rebounds From 15% Drop as DeFi Yield Markets Gain Momentum]]></title>
        <id>35a043ef-b6d2-4173-80d7-fb176424db43</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/31/aave-rebounds-from-15-drop-as-defi-yield-markets-gain-momentum"/>
        <updated>2025-05-31T10:20:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Despite global economic tensions, AAVE shows resilience with strong support levels forming after recent volatility.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shaurya Malwa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Show HN: I built an AI agent that turns ROS 2's turtlesim into a digital artist]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/Yutarop/turtlesim_agent</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/Yutarop/turtlesim_agent"/>
        <updated>2025-05-31T10:17:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BNB Down 4% as Global Trade Tensions Overshadow SEC Victory]]></title>
        <id>07ed5ac1-4a03-406f-b4bb-7b4f55570d0b</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/31/bnb-down-4-as-global-trade-tensions-overshadow-sec-victory"/>
        <updated>2025-05-31T10:10:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BNb token faces significant selling pressure despite positive regulatory developments, as Trump’s new tariffs spark market-wide instability.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shaurya Malwa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[IMF raises concern over Pakistan’s Bitcoin mining power plan: report]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/imf-concern-pakistan-bitcoin-mining-power-plan</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/imf-concern-pakistan-bitcoin-mining-power-plan?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-31T10:08:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[IMF questions Pakistan’s plan to allocate 2,000 megawatts of electricity for Bitcoin mining amid energy shortages and budget talks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Amin Haqshanas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Solana's SOL Dips 5% Amid Fading Memecoin Trading Activity on Network]]></title>
        <id>168d6e6c-ff1d-4954-a538-e69b20e46d5c</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/31/solanas-sol-dips-5-amid-fading-memecoin-trading-activity-on-network"/>
        <updated>2025-05-31T10:04:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Market uncertainty and declining network activity drive SOL below critical $160 support level.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>AI Boost</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Bulls Rack up $600M Liquidations as Bitcoin Drops Under $104K]]></title>
        <id>e8a4f2e3-54d3-4b2b-a0ce-34c1cb1bb960</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/31/crypto-bulls-rack-up-600m-liquidations-as-bitcoin-drops-under-104k"/>
        <updated>2025-05-31T09:31:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A cascade of liquidations might suggest a market turning point, where a price reversal could be imminent due to an overreaction in market sentiment.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shaurya Malwa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Alleged ARM-Based NVIDIA APU With 120W TDP Leaks]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=354554</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/354554/nvidia-arm-apu-leak/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-31T09:18:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Moore’s Law is Dead (MLID) recently showed off what they claim to be an NVIDIA APU, designed for gaming laptops. It’s the closest and more recent look at what could potentially be the dieshot of the chipset that is rumoured to have been co-developed with MediaTek. The brief look at the die also comes with […]
The post Alleged ARM-Based NVIDIA APU With 120W TDP Leaks appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John Law</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dogecoin Dives 8%, Pepe Down 12% in Weekend Crypto Sell-Off]]></title>
        <id>3a70fdb7-9f10-42e0-b814-6786d183c6a1</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/31/dogecoin-dives-8-pepe-down-12-in-weekend-crypto-sell-off"/>
        <updated>2025-05-31T09:01:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Altcoins took a beating as traders digested renewed U.S.-China tariff tensions, Bitcoin whale sell-offs, and a broader risk-off mood.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shaurya Malwa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Book of Secret Knowledge]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/trimstray/the-book-of-secret-knowledge</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/trimstray/the-book-of-secret-knowledge"/>
        <updated>2025-05-31T08:25:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Trackers and SDKs in ChatGPT, Claude, Grok and Perplexity]]></title>
        <id>https://jamesoclaire.com/2025/05/31/the-trackers-and-sdks-in-chatgpt-claude-grok-and-perplexity/</id>
        <link href="https://jamesoclaire.com/2025/05/31/the-trackers-and-sdks-in-chatgpt-claude-grok-and-perplexity/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-31T08:23:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Using lots of little tools to aggressively reject the bots]]></title>
        <id>https://lambdacreate.com/posts/68</id>
        <link href="https://lambdacreate.com/posts/68"/>
        <updated>2025-05-31T08:06:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Beware of Fast-Math]]></title>
        <id>https://simonbyrne.github.io/notes/fastmath/</id>
        <link href="https://simonbyrne.github.io/notes/fastmath/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-31T07:05:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AccessOwl (YC S22) is hiring an AI TypeScript Engineer to connect 100s of SaaS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ycombinator.com/companies/accessowl/jobs/hfWAhVp-ai-enabled-senior-software-engineer-typescript-focus</id>
        <link href="https://www.ycombinator.com/companies/accessowl/jobs/hfWAhVp-ai-enabled-senior-software-engineer-typescript-focus"/>
        <updated>2025-05-31T07:00:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[US government urges court to reject Coinbase user’s crypto records fight]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/government-urges-supreme-court-reject-coinbase-user-crypto-records-fight</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/government-urges-supreme-court-reject-coinbase-user-crypto-records-fight?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-31T06:59:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[US government argues Coinbase user James Harper has no right to block IRS access to his crypto records in Supreme Court filing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Amin Haqshanas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BlackRock’s Bitcoin ETF ends 31-day inflow streak with biggest outflow ever]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/blackrock-bitcoin-etf-inflow-streak-ends-outflow-btc</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/blackrock-bitcoin-etf-inflow-streak-ends-outflow-btc?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-31T06:42:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BlackRock ended its spot Bitcoin ETF inflow streak with its largest outflow on record, nearly $12.7 million more than its previous biggest outflow day.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Ciaran Lyons</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gradients Are the New Intervals]]></title>
        <id>https://www.mattkeeter.com/blog/2025-05-14-gradients/</id>
        <link href="https://www.mattkeeter.com/blog/2025-05-14-gradients/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-31T06:25:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Web dev is still fun if you want it to be]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/jchester/bobotw</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/jchester/bobotw"/>
        <updated>2025-05-31T06:23:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tesla’s Robotaxi Dreams Are Rolling Forward in Austin]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=354542</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/354542/teslas-robotaxi-dreams-are-rolling-forward-in-austin/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-31T06:10:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tesla is making serious moves in the self-driving world. The electric car automaker is currently testing its autonomous Robotaxi, also referred to as the Cybercab, on public streets in Austin, Texas without safety drivers behind the wheel. For now, Tesla is using modified versions of the Model Y to carry out these trials. According to […]
The post Tesla’s Robotaxi Dreams Are Rolling Forward in Austin appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Keran</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[U Mobile Appoints CIMB As Loan Coordinator For 5G Network Rollout Funding]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=354548</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/354548/u-mobile-appoints-cimb-loan-coordinator-5g-network-rollout/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-31T06:01:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[U Mobile has appointed CIMB as its Loan Coordinator and Mandated Lead Arranger to secure financing of up to RM4 billion to support the nationwide rollout of its 5G network infrastructure. The funds raised will be used to finance capital expenditure aimed at accelerating network deployment, with a target of reaching 80% coverage of populated […]
The post U Mobile Appoints CIMB As Loan Coordinator For 5G Network Rollout Funding appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Heirul Kamel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JBL Flip 7, Charge 6 Land In Malaysia; Priced From RM799]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=354517</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/354517/jbl-flip-7-charge-6-land-in-malaysia-priced-from-rm799/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-31T06:00:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In addition to the Tour One M3 Smart Tx, JBL also launched its newest portable Bluetooth speakers at the City of Sound Roadshow. As the names suggest, the Flip 7 is the latest addition to the brand’s Flip series, while the Charge 6 is the successor to the Charge 5. To start off, both speakers […]
The post JBL Flip 7, Charge 6 Land In Malaysia; Priced From RM799 appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nurul Kamil</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Simpler Backoff]]></title>
        <id>https://commaok.xyz/post/simple-backoff/</id>
        <link href="https://commaok.xyz/post/simple-backoff/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-31T04:43:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum&#039;s ‘own Saylor’ SharpLink Gaming plans $1B ETH purchase]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/ethereum-treasury-sharplink-gaming-significant-eth-purchase-michael-saylor</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/ethereum-treasury-sharplink-gaming-significant-eth-purchase-michael-saylor?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-31T04:39:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SharpLink Gaming intends to use most of the proceeds from its proposed share sell-off to purchase Ether, according to a recent SEC filing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Ciaran Lyons</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[realme To Have 7,500 mAh Battery Phone By End Of Year]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=354352</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/354352/realme-to-have-7500-mah-battery-phone-by-end-of-year/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-31T04:00:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The realme GT 7 range was launched with a 7,000 mAh battery, with is pretty large compared to what is considered the norm for smartphones. But the company claims that it will be pushing the envelope even further, with claims that it will release a phone with a 7,500 mAh battery before the year ends. […]
The post realme To Have 7,500 mAh Battery Phone By End Of Year appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ian Chee</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Infinix Smart 10 Series Arrives On SIRIM; Likely To Launch Soon]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=354295</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/354295/infinix-smart-10-sirim/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-31T01:00:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Infinix is gearing up to launch another entry-level smartphone lineup dubbed the Smart 10 series. Unlike its predecessors, the upcoming series will include a new Plus model, at least, according to the brand’s recent SIRIM listings. The Smart 10 and 10 Plus were both certified by SIRIM just in the past few days, with the […]
The post Infinix Smart 10 Series Arrives On SIRIM; Likely To Launch Soon appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ikmal Rozlan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ETH, SOL &#039;very rare&#039; staking ETFs may launch imminently — Analysts]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/ether-solana-staking-etf-filings-rex-shares-speculation-crypto-analysts</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/ether-solana-staking-etf-filings-rex-shares-speculation-crypto-analysts?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-31T00:47:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[REX Shares took a “regulatory end-around” with its Ethereum and Solana staking ETF filings, and the launch looks “imminent,” an ETF analyst says.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Ciaran Lyons</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[QwenLong-L1 solves long-context reasoning challenge that stumps current LLMs]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3009560</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/qwenlong-l1-solves-long-context-reasoning-challenge-that-stumps-current-llms/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-30T23:39:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Alibaba's QwenLong-L1 helps LLMs deeply understand long documents, unlocking advanced reasoning for practical enterprise applications.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ben Dickson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum futures data and network activity growth back ETH’s price strength]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/ethereum-futures-data-and-network-activity-growth-back-eth-s-price-strength</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/ethereum-futures-data-and-network-activity-growth-back-eth-s-price-strength?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-30T23:15:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ETH holds on to the bulk of its weekly gains, while BTC and altcoins sell off.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Marcel Pechman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[C++ to Rust Phrasebook]]></title>
        <id>https://cel.cs.brown.edu/crp/</id>
        <link href="https://cel.cs.brown.edu/crp/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-30T22:18:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NYC Comptroller rejects Mayor Adams’s proposal for Bitcoin-backed bonds]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/nyc-comptroller-rejects-mayor-adams-proposal-bitcoin-backed-bonds</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/nyc-comptroller-rejects-mayor-adams-proposal-bitcoin-backed-bonds?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-30T22:06:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mayor Eric Adams’s push for a Bitcoin-backed municipal bond faces strong opposition from Comptroller Brad Lander, who found the plan "legally dubious and fiscally irresponsible."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Ana Paula Pereira</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ElevenLabs debuts Conversational AI 2.0 voice assistants that understand when to pause, speak, and take turns talking]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3009577</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/elevenlabs-debuts-conversational-ai-2-0-voice-assistants-that-understand-when-to-pause-speak-and-take-turns-talking/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-30T22:00:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With Conversational AI 2.0, ElevenLabs aims to provide tools and infrastructure for truly intelligent, context-aware enterprise voice agents.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carl Franzen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FTX starts $5B payouts — Here’s what you need to know]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/ftx-5b-payout-what-you-need-know</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/ftx-5b-payout-what-you-need-know?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-30T21:43:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The payouts to FTX creditors have sparked both controversy and speculation that the payouts could be reinvested back in the crypto markets.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Vyacheslav Svobodin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin ‘supply shock’ could amplify price in coming months — Sygnum]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-demand-shock-could-amplify-price-months-sygnum</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-demand-shock-could-amplify-price-months-sygnum?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-30T21:20:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Institutional demand for Bitcoin and increasing regulatory clarity are positive factors for Bitcoin in 2025, head of research Katalin Tischhauser says.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Christopher Tepedino</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin drop to $100K likely, but futures market reset means dips won’t last long]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-drop-to-100k-likely-but-futures-market-reset-means-dips-won-t-last-long</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-drop-to-100k-likely-but-futures-market-reset-means-dips-won-t-last-long?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-30T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin’s chance of falling to $100,000 has increased, but the $3.7 billion open interest wipeout means traders will view dips as buying opportunities.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Biraajmaan Tamuly</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trump's Memecoin Dinner Questioned by Top Democrat on House Judiciary Committee]]></title>
        <id>311c08cb-f9c5-458f-af13-ebd0b0dcd9e1</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2025/05/30/trump-s-memecoin-dinner-questioned-by-top-democrat-on-house-judiciary-committee"/>
        <updated>2025-05-30T20:59:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jamie Raskin, the ranking Democrat on the House panel overseeing the legal system, asked the president to produce the guest list of his private event.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jesse Hamilton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Photos taken inside musical instruments]]></title>
        <id>https://www.dpreview.com/photography/5400934096/probe-lenses-and-focus-stacking-the-secrets-to-incredible-photos-taken-inside-instruments</id>
        <link href="https://www.dpreview.com/photography/5400934096/probe-lenses-and-focus-stacking-the-secrets-to-incredible-photos-taken-inside-instruments"/>
        <updated>2025-05-30T20:32:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Surprisingly fast AI-generated kernels we didn't mean to publish yet]]></title>
        <id>https://crfm.stanford.edu/2025/05/28/fast-kernels.html</id>
        <link href="https://crfm.stanford.edu/2025/05/28/fast-kernels.html"/>
        <updated>2025-05-30T20:03:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin falls below $104K, but data shows BTC traders positioned for a rebound]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-falls-below-104k-but-data-shows-btc-traders-positioned-for-a-rebound</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-falls-below-104k-but-data-shows-btc-traders-positioned-for-a-rebound?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-30T20:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin sells off amid mounting macroeconomic uncertainty, but data shows pro traders clinging to their bullish price expectations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Marcel Pechman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[For Bitcoin 2025, the word of the day was ‘freedom’]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-2025-event-recap-freedom</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-2025-event-recap-freedom?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-30T19:44:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[From Ross Ulbricht's first significant public appearance to Strategy’s Michael Saylor addressing the crowd, the focus of the Bitcoin conference was often on individual liberty.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Turner Wright</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Xend Finance, Risevest launch tokenized stocks platform in Africa]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/xend-finance-risevest-launch-tokenized-stocks-platform-africa</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/xend-finance-risevest-launch-tokenized-stocks-platform-africa?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-30T19:16:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The platform allows investors in Africa to access global real estate and stock markets through tokenized fractional shares using stablecoins.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Christopher Tepedino</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FTX Repayments May Have Positive Market Impact: Coinbase]]></title>
        <id>5f0295cd-d11f-4551-bc89-4d0b8539e552</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/30/ftx-repayments-may-have-positive-market-impact-coinbase"/>
        <updated>2025-05-30T19:03:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Creditor payments via BitGo and Kraken are expected within three business days amid shifting market conditions.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tom Carreras</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin price rally driven by macroeconomic headwinds, not just spot BTC ETF flows — Analyst]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-price-rally-driven-by-macroeconomic-headwinds-not-just-spot-btc-etf-flows-analyst</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-price-rally-driven-by-macroeconomic-headwinds-not-just-spot-btc-etf-flows-analyst?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-30T19:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Spot Bitcoin ETF flows play a key role in the asset’s price action, but macroeconomic and geopolitical concerns are also impacting investors’ choice to buy BTC.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Biraajmaan Tamuly</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Which LLM should you use? Token Monster automatically combines multiple models and tools for you]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3009547</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/which-llm-should-you-use-token-monster-automatically-combines-multiple-models-and-tools-for-you/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-30T18:35:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This architecture lets Token Monster tap into a range of models from different providers without having to build separate integrations for each one.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carl Franzen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MEXC exchange detects 200% surge in fraudulent activity in Q1]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/mexc-exchange-detects-200-surge-fraud</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/mexc-exchange-detects-200-surge-fraud?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-30T18:34:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[MEXC chief operating officer Tracy Jin said the fraud was primarily caused by social engineering scams targeting new, uneducated users.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Vince Quill</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn to Build a Multilayer Perceptron with Real-Life Examples and Python Code]]></title>
        <id>6839f729798ea464918cffe8</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-a-multilayer-perceptron-with-examples-and-python-code/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-30T18:21:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The perceptron is a fundamental concept in deep learning, with many algorithms stemming from its original design. In this tutorial, I’ll show you how to build both single layer and multi-layer perceptrons (MLPs) across three frameworks: Custom class...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kuriko Iwai</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Price predictions 5/30: BTC, ETH, XRP, BNB, SOL, DOGE, ADA, SUI, HYPE, LINK]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/price-predictions-5-30-btc-eth-xrp-bnb-sol-doge-ada-sui-hype-link</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/price-predictions-5-30-btc-eth-xrp-bnb-sol-doge-ada-sui-hype-link?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-30T18:01:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin’s drop below $104,000 puts the asset into a consolidation phase where even lower lows could be tested.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Rakesh Upadhyay</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sui vote on $162M frozen Cetus funds sparks decentralization debate: Finance Redefined]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/sui-vote-on-162m-frozen-cetus-funds-sparks-decentralization-debate-finance-redefined-may-23-30</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/sui-vote-on-162m-frozen-cetus-funds-sparks-decentralization-debate-finance-redefined-may-23-30?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-30T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[DeFi’s decentralization debate rages on after the Sui community voted to return the $162 million frozen during the Cetus exploit.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Zoltan Vardai</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Judge Declines to Order DOJ to Review Records in Roman Storm Case]]></title>
        <id>11b60ee6-b0b1-405b-b0f8-fa80bc7563cb</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2025/05/30/judge-declines-to-order-doj-to-review-records-in-roman-storm-case"/>
        <updated>2025-05-30T17:51:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Tornado Cash developer is slated to go on trial later this summer.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nikhilesh De</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Slips Below $104K, Cryptos Slide as U.S.-China Tariff Tensions Flare Up]]></title>
        <id>61e83ff5-a2ff-470b-941f-e9f5c610b516</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/30/bitcoin-slips-below-usd104k-cryptos-slide-as-u-s-china-tariff-tensions-flare-up"/>
        <updated>2025-05-30T17:34:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The crypto market wobbled after Trump accused China of violating a tariff truce.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tom Carreras</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto op-eds: How opinions can shape Web3 thought and policy]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/crypto-op-eds-how-opinions-can-shaping-web3-thought-and-policy</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/crypto-op-eds-how-opinions-can-shaping-web3-thought-and-policy?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-30T16:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the latest episode of Decentralize with Cointelegraph, experts break down how crypto op-eds are influencing public perception, policy and the future of Web3 storytelling.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Savannah Fortis</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Beating Google's kernelCTF PoW using AVX512]]></title>
        <id>https://anemato.de/blog/kctf-vdf</id>
        <link href="https://anemato.de/blog/kctf-vdf"/>
        <updated>2025-05-30T16:19:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AVAX Slides 7%, Hits Strong Resistance at $22.35 Level]]></title>
        <id>8b1cfe37-0c92-4661-8ab0-4f5b4a28bd4f</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/30/avax-slides-7-before-establishing-strong-resistance-at-2235-level"/>
        <updated>2025-05-30T16:14:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A county in New Jersey recently announced that it would use the Avalanche blockchain to digitize all property deeds.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>AI Boost</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trump Media Has $2.3B in Bitcoin Buying Power After Closing Capital Raise]]></title>
        <id>c636f4a9-6bd6-40bf-9b73-2c451c23f606</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2025/05/30/trump-media-has-23b-in-bitcoin-buying-power-after-closing-capital-raise"/>
        <updated>2025-05-30T16:01:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The company said it will use proceeds to add bitcoin to its balance sheet, an increasingly popular move among publicly-traded firms.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Krisztian Sandor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spot Bitcoin ETFs Broke 10-Day Inflow Streak With $358M of Outflows Thursday: JPMorgan]]></title>
        <id>503eb6c3-e76c-45c4-8c31-ace6aae62773</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/30/spot-bitcoin-etfs-broke-10-day-inflow-streak-with-358m-of-outflows-thursday-jpmorgan"/>
        <updated>2025-05-30T15:36:30.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Will Canny</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AI-powered OSINT tool profiles YouTube users, raising privacy concerns]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/ai-youtube-comment-profiling-privacy-risk</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/ai-youtube-comment-profiling-privacy-risk?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-30T15:05:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An OSINT platform, Lolarchiver, offers AI-powered tools that can rapidly profile YouTube commenters based on their activity, raising major privacy and legal concerns.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Adrian Zmudzinski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Centralized AI threatens a democratic digital future]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/centralized-ai-threatens-a-democratic-future</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/centralized-ai-threatens-a-democratic-future?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-30T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The decentralized AI industry has a chance to carve out market share, but it will need to prove its security and usefulness. Centralized AI’s dominance risks privacy, transparency and ethical standards.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Manouk Termaaten</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TON Plunges 6% Before Staging Recovery Amid Global Tensions]]></title>
        <id>019679d3-ba5c-4c54-8b95-91b634146c6d</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/30/ton-plunges-6-before-staging-recovery-amid-global-tensions"/>
        <updated>2025-05-30T14:53:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The token found critical support in the $3.22-$3.24 range.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>AI Boost</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Microfrontends Work: From iframes to Module Federation]]></title>
        <id>6839c4a906e067fe415d54b4</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-microfrontends-work-iframes-to-module-federation/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-30T14:46:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microfrontends are transforming how teams build and deploy frontend applications at scale. This tutorial explores the architectural landscape, from traditional approaches to modern Module Federation implementations. By the end, you'll be equipped to ...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rahul gupta</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Build A Simple Portfolio Blog With Next.js]]></title>
        <id>6839c439ebab1f7974eac355</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-build-a-simple-portfolio-blog-with-nextjs/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-30T14:44:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I have written articles on different platforms including LinkedIn, The Network Bits (Substack), and freeCodeCamp. So I wanted to bring all of these articles together in a single place where someone could go and see all my work. A blog sounded like a ...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chidiadi Anyanwu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What are stablecoin-backed corporate cards and how do they work?]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/explained/what-are-stablecoin-backed-corporate-cards-and-how-do-they-work</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/explained/what-are-stablecoin-backed-corporate-cards-and-how-do-they-work?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-30T14:35:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Stablecoin-backed corporate cards are linked to digital wallets holding stablecoins. They facilitate instant currency conversion at the point of purchase.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Dilip Kumar Patairya</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SUI Plunges 6% Overnight Before Buyers Step in at $3.40 Support]]></title>
        <id>54ad69e6-23f1-4981-9c5e-fad7c2a5736d</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/30/sui-plunges-6-overnight-before-buyers-step-in-at-usd3-40-support"/>
        <updated>2025-05-30T14:30:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Market volatility intensified as geopolitical tensions and protocol recovery efforts create conflicting signals for traders]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>AI Boost</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum Upgrades Have Failed to Boost Network Activity in Meaningful Way: JPMorgan]]></title>
        <id>464c32d9-3c91-46be-8a09-95685757aacc</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/30/ethereum-upgrades-have-failed-to-boost-network-activity-in-meaningful-way-jpmorgan"/>
        <updated>2025-05-30T14:28:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Neither the number of transactions nor active addresses has increased significantly following recent network upgrades, the report said.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Will Canny</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Stablecoins Boost Treasury Bill Demand, Reflect Dollar Dominance, Citi Says]]></title>
        <id>f64404fe-22b0-459a-84b6-529cb5ff246f</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/30/stablecoins-boost-treasury-bill-demand-reflect-dollar-dominance-citi-says"/>
        <updated>2025-05-30T14:15:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As stablecoin usage grows, so does the demand for short-term U.S. Treasuries, the report said.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Will Canny</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Banks ‘very interested’ in stablecoin use — Stripe exec]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/banks-very-interested-stablecoin-use-stripe-exec</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/banks-very-interested-stablecoin-use-stripe-exec?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-30T14:02:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Stripe’s president confirms growing interest in stablecoins from banks, but adoption would still require more green lights from regulators.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Helen Partz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fueling seamless AI at scale]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1117440</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/05/30/1117440/fueling-seamless-ai-at-scale/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-30T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[From large language models (LLMs) to reasoning agents, today’s AI tools bring unprecedented computational demands. Trillion-parameter models, workloads running on-device, and swarms of agents collaborating to complete tasks all require a new paradigm of computing to become truly seamless and ubiquitous. First, technical progress in hardware and silicon design is critical to pushing the boundaries…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>MIT Technology Review Insights</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AI Crypto Livepeer Explodes 150% on Upbit Listing]]></title>
        <id>d962c2b2-69fd-44b6-8fb0-a9185c70d13d</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/30/ai-crypto-livepeer-explodes-150-on-upbit-listing-strategy-initiative"/>
        <updated>2025-05-30T13:56:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The surge happened while other artificial intelligence-focused crypto tokens declined with bitcoin and the broader market.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Krisztian Sandor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Garantex successor moves $1.66B through crypto exchanges: Global Ledger]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/garantex-successor-moves-1-66b-to-crypto-exchanges</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/garantex-successor-moves-1-66b-to-crypto-exchanges?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-30T13:44:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Exposure to wallets tied to suspected Garantex successor Grinex keeps rising as blockchain analyst warnings are ignored.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Yohan Yun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Sort Dates Efficiently in JavaScript]]></title>
        <id>6839b592f8650e337982bcba</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-sort-dates-efficiently-in-javascript/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-30T13:41:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Recently, I was working on a PowerApps Component Framework (PCF) project that required sorting an array of objects by date. The dates were in ISO 8601 format but without a time zone – for example, "2025-05-01T15:00:00.00". Without much thought, I wro...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brandon Wozniewicz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The ‘white-collar bloodbath’ is all part of the AI hype machine]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cnn.com/2025/05/30/business/anthropic-amodei-ai-jobs-nightcap</id>
        <link href="https://www.cnn.com/2025/05/30/business/anthropic-amodei-ai-jobs-nightcap"/>
        <updated>2025-05-30T13:38:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CoinDesk 20 Performance Update: NEAR Drops 5.4% as Almost All Assets Trade Lower]]></title>
        <id>8b734c19-f0fe-49c9-b9c1-6cc11ff356d4</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/coindesk-indices/2025/05/30/coindesk-20-performance-update-near-drops-5-4-as-almost-all-assets-trade-lower"/>
        <updated>2025-05-30T13:34:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Polkadot (DOT) was also among the underperformers, falling 5.3% from Thursday.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CoinDesk Indices</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsandbox: Virtual Machines that feel and perform like containers]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/microsandbox/microsandbox</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/microsandbox/microsandbox"/>
        <updated>2025-05-30T13:20:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Mining Difficulty Is Set to Reach Record High Amid Surging Hashrate]]></title>
        <id>2e070465-57ed-4ea1-9c8d-5233cfe18c6c</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/30/bitcoin-mining-difficulty-is-set-to-reach-record-high-amid-surging-hashrate"/>
        <updated>2025-05-30T13:14:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin’s difficulty is projected to rise over 4% to a record 126.95T as hashrate nears an all-time high despite low transaction fees.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>James Van Straten</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Stellar's Midnight Mayhem: XLM Plunged 6% on High-Volume Despite Rain  Integration]]></title>
        <id>d2bdc920-dd8e-47db-bbe0-d9dce9f6b0a2</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/30/stellar-s-midnight-mayhem-xlm-plunged-6-on-high-volume-despite-rain-integration"/>
        <updated>2025-05-30T13:01:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Stellar's integration with Rain signals progress toward mainstream adoption.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>AI Boost</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Survive in Tech When Everything's Changing w/ 21-year Veteran Dev Joe Attardi [Podcast #174]]]></title>
        <id>6839abf3d23bb1460e9ea0ea</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-survive-in-tech-when-everythings-changing-w-21-year-veteran-dev-joe-attardi-podcast-174/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-30T13:00:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On this week's episode of the podcast, freeCodeCamp founder Quincy Larson interviews Joe Attardi. He's a software engineer and prolific author of programming books. We talk about: How software development has changed over the past 21 years Tips for s...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Stripe Explores Bank Partnerships on Stablecoins as Payments Importance Grows, Says Company President]]></title>
        <id>dda8ff47-518e-4df7-a237-20bdbedf4e2b</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2025/05/30/stripe-explores-bank-partnerships-on-stablecoins-as-payments-importance-grows-ceo-john-collison"/>
        <updated>2025-05-30T12:59:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The payments firm recently introduced stablecoin accounts for its users, while its recent acquisition Bridge rolled out a USDC token.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Krisztian Sandor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Systems Correctness Practices at Amazon Web Services]]></title>
        <id>https://cacm.acm.org/practice/systems-correctness-practices-at-amazon-web-services/</id>
        <link href="https://cacm.acm.org/practice/systems-correctness-practices-at-amazon-web-services/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-30T12:43:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Downside Insurance on BlackRock's Spot Bitcoin ETF is Now Pricer Than Bullish Bets]]></title>
        <id>88d0c259-bf99-451d-bc50-9ccbd974b3b3</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/30/downside-insurance-on-blackrock-s-spot-bitcoin-etf-is-now-pricer-than-bullish-bets"/>
        <updated>2025-05-30T12:34:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[IBIT fell 1.32% to $59.99 on Thursday.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Omkar Godbole</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DeepSeek’s new model a ‘step backward’ for free speech: AI dev]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/deepseek-ai-censorship-free-speech-concerns</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/deepseek-ai-censorship-free-speech-concerns?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-30T12:27:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[DeepSeek’s latest AI model flags Xinjiang camps as human rights violations but censors direct criticism of China, raising concerns over contradictions and increased censorship.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Ezra Reguerra</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Download: sycophantic LLMs, and the AI Hype Index]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1117620</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/05/30/1117620/the-download-sycophantic-llms-and-the-ai-hype-index/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-30T12:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is today’s edition of The Download, our weekday newsletter that provides a daily dose of what’s going on in the world of technology. This benchmark used Reddit’s AITA to test how much AI models suck up to us Back in April, OpenAI announced it was rolling back an update to its GPT-4o model that made ChatGPT’s…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rhiannon Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Digital euro, not MiCA, key to managing crypto risks: Bank of Italy chief]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/digital-euro-not-mica-control-crypto-risks-bank-italy</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/digital-euro-not-mica-control-crypto-risks-bank-italy?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-30T12:05:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[MiCA has had a limited impact on the adoption of compliant stablecoins in Europe, strengthening the need for the digital euro, Bank of Italy Governor Fabio Panetta said.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Helen Partz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JBL Tour One M3 Smart Tx Launches In Malaysia; Priced At RM1,899]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=354491</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/354491/jbl-tour-one-m3-smart-tx-malaysia-rm1899/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-30T10:10:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[JBL has introduced the latest addition to its over-ear headphones lineup in Malaysia, the Tour One M3 Smart Tx. The brand showcased the flagship product during its City of Sound Roadshow at One Utama Shopping Centre, alongside the Flip 7 and Charge 6 Bluetooth speakers. To start off, the headphones themselves come with 40mm Mica […]
The post JBL Tour One M3 Smart Tx Launches In Malaysia; Priced At RM1,899 appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nurul Kamil</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CATL Introduces Choco-SEB Battery Swapping Technology]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=354485</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/354485/catl-introduces-choco-seb-battery-swapping-tech/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-30T09:55:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There is no doubt that electric vehicles have become a major segment of the automotive industry, with many players introducing new technologies to strengthen their presence in the market. One of them is the Chinese battery manufacturer CATL, which has launched a new battery swapping technology known as Choco-SEB (Swapping Electric Block). Named after the […]
The post CATL Introduces Choco-SEB Battery Swapping Technology appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Keran</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HONOR 400 Series Now In Stores]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=354487</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/354487/honor-400-series-now-in-stores/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-30T09:10:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The HONOR 400 Series is now available at stores nationwide. The new line-up, which officially launched in Malaysia last week, comprises a base model and a high-end Pro variant that’s priced from RM1,899 and RM2,699 respectively. To recap, the standard HONOR 400 features a 6.55-inch 1.5K AMOLED display, Snapdragon 7 Gen 3 chipset, and a […]
The post HONOR 400 Series Now In Stores appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Heirul Kamel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This benchmark used Reddit’s AITA to test how much AI models suck up to us]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1117551</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/05/30/1117551/this-benchmark-used-reddits-aita-to-test-how-much-ai-models-suck-up-to-us/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-30T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Back in April, OpenAIannounced it was rolling back an update to its GPT-4o model that made ChatGPT’s responses to user queries too sycophantic.  An AI model that acts in an overly agreeable and flattering way is more than just annoying. It could reinforce users’ incorrect beliefs, mislead people, and spread misinformation that can be dangerous—a…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rhiannon Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AEON Bank Extends Debit Card Cashback Programme, Slashes Savings Account Profit Rate]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=354461</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/354461/aeon-bank-cashback-savings-account-profit-rate/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-30T08:52:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When AEON Bank launched a year ago, it offered users numerous perks and rewards, but those benefits are set to expire on 31 May. Ahead of the coming deadline, the digital bank has published its updated T&C for its new wave of promotions, with most being retained. From 1 June until 31 August 2025, the […]
The post AEON Bank Extends Debit Card Cashback Programme, Slashes Savings Account Profit Rate appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ikmal Rozlan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FLUX.1 Kontext enables in-context image generation for enterprise AI pipelines]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3009464</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/flux-1-kontext-enables-in-context-image-generation-for-enterprise-ai-pipelines/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-29T23:32:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[FLUX.1 Kontext from Black Forest Labs aims to let users edit images multiple times through both text and reference images without losing speed.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Emilia David</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[LeetCode Meditations: A Visual Handbook of Data Structures and Algorithms Concepts]]></title>
        <id>6838baed0c839b0170a2e731</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/leetcode-dsa-concepts-handbook/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-29T19:52:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It may seem like an oxymoron when the words "LeetCode" and "meditation" are used together – after all, one thing that almost everyone can agree is that LeetCode is challenging. It's called grinding LeetCode for a reason. It doesn't have anything to d...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eda Eren</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Emotive voice AI startup Hume launches new EVI 3 model with rapid custom voice creation]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3009430</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/emotive-voice-ai-startup-hume-launches-new-evi-3-model-with-rapid-custom-voice-creation/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-29T18:50:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While EVI 3’s specific API pricing has not been announced yet (marked as TBA), the pattern suggests it will be usage-based.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carl Franzen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn Python for Data Science – Full Course for Beginners]]></title>
        <id>6838a96337f76032ee644b85</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-python-for-data-science-full-course/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-29T18:37:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you're interested in data science but not sure where to begin, Python is a great starting point. It’s easy to pick up and has a bunch of libraries that make working with data a lot easier. We just published a course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build an AI-Powered Cooking Assistant with Flutter and Gemini]]></title>
        <id>68388c4c973615b7f6864e63</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-an-ai-powered-cooking-assistant-with-flutter-and-gemini/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-29T16:33:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After soaking in everything shared at GoogleIO, I can’t lie – I feel supercharged! From What’s New in Flutter to Building Agentic Apps with Flutter and Firebase AI Logic, and the deep dive into How Flutter Makes the Most of Your Platforms, it felt li...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Atuoha Anthony</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Powering High-Performance Web3 Experiences: Gravity (by Galxe) Launches on QuickNode]]></title>
        <id>683622d561c46d0001eed5d9</id>
        <link href="https://blog.quicknode.com/gravity-alpha-launch/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-29T13:54:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Explore Galxe Gravity’s omnichain power on QuickNode. Build scalable, identity-centric dApps effortlessly with dedicated endpoints and developer tools.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>QuickNode</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DeepSeek R1-0528 arrives in powerful open source challenge to OpenAI o3 and Google Gemini 2.5 Pro]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3009405</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/deepseek-r1-0528-arrives-in-powerful-open-source-challenge-to-openai-o3-and-google-gemini-2-5-pro/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-29T13:22:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Additionally, the model’s hallucination rate has been reduced, contributing to more reliable and consistent output.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carl Franzen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Snowflake’s open-source text-to-SQL and Arctic inference models solve enterprise AI’s two biggest deployment headaches]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3009218</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/how-snowflakes-open-source-text-to-sql-and-arctic-inference-models-solve-enterprise-ais-two-biggest-deployment-headaches/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-29T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New open-source efforts from Snowflake aim to help solve that unsolved challenges of text-to-SQL and inference performance for enterprise AI.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sean Michael Kerner</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Encharge AI unveils EN100 AI accelerator chip with analog memory]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3009330</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/games/encharge-ai-unveils-en100-ai-accelerator-chip-with-analog-memory/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-29T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[EnCharge AI, a startup that raised $144 million to date, announced the EnCharge EN100, an AI accelerator built on analog in-memory computing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dean Takahashi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Peer launches Global Simulation as real-time digital Earth with AI agents]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3009041</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/games/peer-launches-global-simulation-as-real-time-digital-earth-with-ai-agents/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-29T12:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Peer launched Global Simulation, a real-time digital Earth where players use avatars to connect by location and build relationships in a living, spatial network.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dean Takahashi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Download: the next anti-drone weapon, and powering AI’s growth]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1117539</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/05/29/1117539/the-download-the-next-anti-drone-weapon-and-powering-ais-growth/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-29T12:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is today’s edition of The Download, our weekday newsletter that provides a daily dose of what’s going on in the world of technology. This giant microwave may change the future of war Imagine: China deploys hundreds of thousands of autonomous drones in the air, on the sea, and under the water—all armed with explosive warheads or…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rhiannon Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What will power AI’s growth?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1117500</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/05/29/1117500/ai-energy-growth-nuclear-natural-gas/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-29T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s been a little over a week since we published Power Hungry, a package that takes a hard look at the expected energy demands of AI. Last week in this newsletter, I broke down the centerpiece of that package, an analysis I did with my colleague James O’Donnell. (In case you’re still looking for an…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Casey Crownhart</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This giant microwave may change the future of war]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1117502</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/05/29/1117502/epirus-drone-zapping-microwave-us-military-defense/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-29T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Imagine: China deploys hundreds of thousands of autonomous drones in the air, on the sea, and under the water—all armed with explosive warheads or small missiles. These machines descend in a swarm toward military installations on Taiwan and nearby US bases, and over the course of a few hours, a single robotic blitzkrieg overwhelms the US…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sam Dean</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pure vs. Impure Iterators in Go]]></title>
        <id>https://jub0bs.com/posts/2025-05-29-pure-vs-impure-iterators-in-go/</id>
        <link href="https://jub0bs.com/posts/2025-05-29-pure-vs-impure-iterators-in-go/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-29T08:57:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Reverse engineering of Linear's sync engine]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/wzhudev/reverse-linear-sync-engine</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/wzhudev/reverse-linear-sync-engine"/>
        <updated>2025-05-29T04:29:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Randomness Requirements for Security (2005)]]></title>
        <id>https://datatracker.ietf.org/doc/html/rfc4086</id>
        <link href="https://datatracker.ietf.org/doc/html/rfc4086"/>
        <updated>2025-05-29T01:04:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DanaBot takedown shows how agentic AI cut months of SOC analysis to weeks]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008704</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/security/agentic-ai-defeated-danabot-exposing-key-lessons-for-soc-teams/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-29T00:23:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Agentic AI played a decisive role in dismantling DanaBot, a Russian malware platform responsible for more than 50 million dollars in damages.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Louis Columbus</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[s3: The new RAG framework that trains search agents with minimal data]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3009182</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/s3-the-new-rag-framework-that-trains-search-agents-with-minimal-data/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T22:51:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[S3 decouples RAG search from generation, boosting efficiency and generalization for enterprise LLM applications with minimal data.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ben Dickson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mistral launches new code embedding model that outperforms OpenAI and Cohere in real-world retrieval tasks]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3009248</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/mistral-launches-new-code-embedding-model-that-outperforms-openai-and-cohere-in-real-world-retrieval-tasks/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T22:11:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mistral's Codestral Embed will help make RAG use cases faster and find duplicate code segments using natural language.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Emilia David</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nvidia CEO takes a shot at U.S. policy cutting off AI chip sales to China]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3009278</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/games/nvidia-ceo-takes-a-shot-at-u-s-policy-cutting-off-ai-chip-sales-to-china/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T21:36:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nvidia CEO Jensen Huang tiptoed into politics with a comment taking a shot at the U.S. policy that has cut off sales of his chips to China.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dean Takahashi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[QuickNode Accelerator - ChaiNova]]></title>
        <id>68377c476b77cd0001482835</id>
        <link href="https://blog.quicknode.com/quicknode-accelerator-chainova/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T21:31:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ChaiNova joins QuickNode’s Accelerator to bring inclusive Web3 access from local shops to global enterprises.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>QuickNode</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nvidia beats estimates for Q1 results as revenues rise 69% from a year ago]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3009231</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/games/nvidia-beats-estimates-for-q1-results-as-revenues-rise-69-from-a-year-ago/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T20:32:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nvidia, the AI and graphics chip company driving societal changes with AI, reported revenue for the first quarter was up 69%.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dean Takahashi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Less is more: Meta study shows shorter reasoning improves AI accuracy by 34%]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3009203</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/less-is-more-meta-study-shows-shorter-reasoning-improves-ai-accuracy-by-34/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T19:17:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New research from Meta reveals AI models achieve 34.5% better accuracy with shorter reasoning chains, challenging industry assumptions and potentially reducing computing costs by 40%.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Nuñez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Illusion of Causality in Charts]]></title>
        <id>https://filwd.substack.com/p/the-illusion-of-causality-in-charts</id>
        <link href="https://filwd.substack.com/p/the-illusion-of-causality-in-charts"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T17:49:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Revenge of the Chickenized Reverse-Centaurs]]></title>
        <id>https://pluralistic.net/2022/04/17/revenge-of-the-chickenized-reverse-centaurs/</id>
        <link href="https://pluralistic.net/2022/04/17/revenge-of-the-chickenized-reverse-centaurs/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T16:55:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[QuickNode Accelerator - SettleX]]></title>
        <id>6813ad1304ef2c0001211afb</id>
        <link href="https://blog.quicknode.com/quicknode-accelerator-settlex/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T16:00:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discover SettleX, a modular cross-chain clearing layer improving capital efficiency, privacy, and liquidity across the DeFi landscape.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>QuickNode</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[QuickNode Accelerator - taro/NYU]]></title>
        <id>68222cb536cbae0001089a2b</id>
        <link href="https://blog.quicknode.com/quicknode-accelerator-taro/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T15:59:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Taro is a privacy-first blockchain project from NYU and Microsoft, enhancing financial transparency and accountability in organizations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>QuickNode</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[QuickNode Accelerator - Mements]]></title>
        <id>68222d3a36cbae0001089a38</id>
        <link href="https://blog.quicknode.com/quicknode-accelerator-mements/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T15:59:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mements is building infrastructure for verifiable AI, with timestamped prompts, provable video streaming, and the launch of MemeChain.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>QuickNode</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[QuickNode Accelerator - EcoFundMe]]></title>
        <id>6822330f36cbae0001089a61</id>
        <link href="https://blog.quicknode.com/quicknode-accelerator-ecofundme/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T15:59:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[EcoFundMe connects donors to verified climate projects with tokenized contributions, DAO governance, and transparent onchain funding.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>QuickNode</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[QuickNode Accelerator - Rivalz Network]]></title>
        <id>68248d91bf7346000109494e</id>
        <link href="https://blog.quicknode.com/quicknode-accelerator-rivalz-network/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T15:59:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Rivalz is building verifiable AI infrastructure, enabling smart contracts to query AI oracles, real-world data, and autonomous agents.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>QuickNode</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[QuickNode Accelerator - Kyros]]></title>
        <id>6824f2a5bf73460001094981</id>
        <link href="https://blog.quicknode.com/quicknode-accelerator-kyros/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T15:59:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[KYROS delivers AI-enhanced DeFi with real-time, in-chart insights and an intuitive trading experience across major blockchains.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>QuickNode</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[QuickNode Accelerator - Hangry Animals]]></title>
        <id>68236ae084101f00013a5cd0</id>
        <link href="https://blog.quicknode.com/quicknode-accelerator-hangry-animals/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T15:58:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hangry Animals blends storytelling, Web3, and social good into a transmedia universe where players own, earn, and impact real causes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>QuickNode</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[QuickNode Accelerator - Boost Ad Network]]></title>
        <id>6813cc2f04ef2c0001211b24</id>
        <link href="https://blog.quicknode.com/quicknode-accelerator-boost-ad-network/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T15:58:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Boost is an onchain-native, privacy-first ad network with verifiable auctions, real attribution, and campaign analytics for Web3.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>QuickNode</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[QuickNode Accelerator - Diamondz Shadow Movies]]></title>
        <id>6824f61dbf734600010949a1</id>
        <link href="https://blog.quicknode.com/quicknode-accelerator-diamondz-shadow-movies/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T15:58:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Diamondz Shadow is creating a blockchain-powered entertainment ecosystem spanning games, film, tokenized media, and real-world utility.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>QuickNode</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[QuickNode Accelerator - Badchain]]></title>
        <id>6825fdc9bf734600010949cf</id>
        <link href="https://blog.quicknode.com/quicknode-accelerator-badchain/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T15:57:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Badchain is Solana’s culture layer, where behavior drives rewards through meme quests, raffles, and community-led incentives.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>QuickNode</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[QuickNode Accelerator - CVEX]]></title>
        <id>68248962bf7346000109492e</id>
        <link href="https://blog.quicknode.com/quicknode-accelerator-cvex/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T15:57:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CVEX is launching Smart Clearing for DeFi, a decentralized derivatives protocol unlocking capital efficiency and scalable markets.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>QuickNode</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[QuickNode Accelerator - Archer Protocol]]></title>
        <id>68248c8fbf7346000109493f</id>
        <link href="https://blog.quicknode.com/quicknode-accelerator-archer-protocol/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T15:57:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Archer is redesigning Web3 UX with natural language trading, multichain intents, and a non-custodial platform for everyone.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>QuickNode</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[QuickNode Accelerator - SNFT Chain]]></title>
        <id>6813ac5b04ef2c0001211aee</id>
        <link href="https://blog.quicknode.com/quicknode-accelerator-snft/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T15:55:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SNFT Chain connects digital assets and physical devices through scalable L2 infrastructure built for creators and tokenized experiences.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>QuickNode</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Attackers Target Travelers – and How to Defend Yourself]]></title>
        <id>68372f981dca8ddfbed5d732</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-attackers-target-travelers-and-how-to-defend-yourself/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T15:45:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Traveling is one of life’s greatest joys  –  but it also puts a big target on your back for cybercriminals. Tourists are often rushed, distracted, or unfamiliar with local providers. That’s exactly what hackers count on. From fake Wi-Fi networks to s...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Manish Shivanandhan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rumi raises $4.7M to change passive media into interactive AI experiences]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3009144</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/games/rumi-raises-4-7m-to-change-passive-media-into-interactive-ai-experiences/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Rumi, an AI media company, has raised $4.7 million in a pre-seed funding round to transform passive media with rewards.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dean Takahashi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Agentic AI Handbook: A Beginner's Guide to Autonomous Intelligent Agents]]></title>
        <id>68371c1c13269a460c440e6c</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/the-agentic-ai-handbook/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T14:22:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You may have heard about “Agentic AI” systems and wondered what they’re all about. Well, in basic terms, the idea behind Agentic AI is that it can see its surroundings, set and pursue goals, plan and reason through many processes, and learn from expe...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Balajee Asish Brahmandam</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The AI Hype Index: College students are hooked on ChatGPT]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1117468</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/05/28/1117468/ai-hype-index-college-students-chatgpt-meta-apple-anthropic-grok/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T14:13:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Separating AI reality from hyped-up fiction isn’t always easy. That’s why we’ve created the AI Hype Index—a simple, at-a-glance summary of everything you need to know about the state of the industry. Large language models confidently present their responses as accurate and reliable, even when they’re neither of those things. That’s why we’ve recently seen…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Editors</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AtomVM, the Erlang virtual machine for IoT devices]]></title>
        <id>https://www.atomvm.net/</id>
        <link href="https://www.atomvm.net/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T13:35:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Show HN: Icepi Zero – The FPGA Raspberry Pi Zero Equivalent]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/cheyao/icepi-zero</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/cheyao/icepi-zero"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T13:31:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Akool Live Camera can translate video calls in real time, swap faces, and get live virtual avatars to mimic human movements]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008843</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/games/akool-live-camera-can-translate-video-calls-in-real-time-swap-faces-and-get-virtual-avatars-to-mimic-human-movements/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Akool Live Camera uses AI to capture human movement and mimic that movement with a generated virtual avatar in real time.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dean Takahashi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Download: the story of OpenAI, and making magnesium]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1117492</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/05/28/1117492/the-download-the-story-of-openai-and-making-magnesium/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T12:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is today’s edition of The Download, our weekday newsletter that provides a daily dose of what’s going on in the world of technology. OpenAI: The power and the pride OpenAI’s release of ChatGPT 3.5 set in motion an AI arms race that has changed the world. How that turns out for humanity is something we are…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rhiannon Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OpenAI: The power and the pride]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1117486</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/05/28/1117486/openai-the-power-and-the-pride/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T10:07:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In April, Paul Graham, the founder of the tech startup accelerator Y Combinator, sent a tweet in response to former YC president and current OpenAI CEO Sam Altman. Altman had just bid a public goodbye to GPT-4 on X, and Graham had a follow-up question.  “If you had [GPT-4’s model weights] etched on a piece…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mat Honan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This startup wants to make more climate-friendly metal in the US]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1117481</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/05/28/1117481/metal-magrathea/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A California-based company called Magrathea just turned on a new electrolyzer that can make magnesium metal from seawater. The technology has the potential to produce the material, which is used in vehicles and defense applications, with net-zero greenhouse-gas emissions. Magnesium is an incredibly light metal, and it’s used for parts in cars and planes, as…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Casey Crownhart</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Webb telescope helps refines Hubble constant, suggesting resolution rate debate]]></title>
        <id>https://phys.org/news/2025-05-webb-telescope-refines-hubble-constant.html</id>
        <link href="https://phys.org/news/2025-05-webb-telescope-refines-hubble-constant.html"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T09:49:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Everyone’s looking to get in on vibe coding — and Google is no different with Stitch, its follow-up to Jules]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3009114</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/everyones-looking-to-get-in-on-vibe-coding-and-google-is-no-different-with-stitch-its-follow-up-to-jules/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T00:49:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google is looking to compete in vibe coding with Stitch, which designs user interfaces (UIs) with one prompt.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Taryn Plumb</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spott’s AI-native recruiting platform scores $3.2M to end hiring software chaos]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3009108</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/spotts-ai-native-recruiting-platform-scores-3-2m-to-end-hiring-software-chaos/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T00:07:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Spott secures $3.2 million in funding to build an all-in-one AI-native recruitment platform that automates workflows and eliminates tech fragmentation for recruitment agencies seeking to focus on high-value activities.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Nuñez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Anthropic debuts Claude conversational voice mode on mobile that searches your Google Docs, Drive, Calendar]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3009105</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/anthropic-debuts-conversational-voice-mode-for-claude-mobile-apps/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-27T23:23:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With the rollout of voice mode, Anthropic continues to broaden Claude's functionality and accessibility to all users.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carl Franzen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security leaders lose visibility as consultants deploy shadow AI copilots to stay employed]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008925</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/security/shadow-ai-is-consultings-survival-strategy-in-the-genai-era/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-27T22:15:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fearing sweeping layoffs driven by AI and automation, elite consultants and high performers are turning to shadow AI for a competitive edge.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Louis Columbus</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mistral launches API for building AI agents that run Python, generate images, perform RAG and more]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3009083</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/mistral-launches-api-for-building-ai-agents-that-run-python-generate-images-perform-rag-and-more/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-27T18:52:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For professionals like the Lead AI Engineer or Senior AI Engineer, the Mistral Agents API represents a powerful addition to their AI toolkit.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carl Franzen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Build a Rocket Boy drops trailer detailing MindsEye’s blend of Grand Theft Auto and AI robot combat]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3009068</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/games/build-a-rocket-boy-drops-trailer-detailing-mindseyes-blend-of-grand-theft-auto-and-ai-robot-combat/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-27T18:21:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[IOI Partners and Build a Rocket Boy dropped a new trailer on MindsEye, a new title coming on June 10 from the co-creator of Grand Theft Auto V.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dean Takahashi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Salesforce’s $8B acquisition of Informatica means for enterprise data and AI]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3009056</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/data-infrastructure/what-salesforces-8b-acquisition-of-informatica-means-for-enterprise-data-and-ai/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-27T17:20:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Industry analysts explain how Salesforce's $8 billion Informatica acquisition will transform enterprise data management and accelerate agentic AI adoption .]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sean Michael Kerner</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[From disruption to reinvention: How knowledge workers can thrive after AI]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008969</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/from-disruption-to-reinvention-how-knowledge-workers-can-thrive-after-ai/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-26T19:05:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We are beginning a cognitive migration: Away from what AI now does well, and toward a redefinition of what humans are now made for.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gary Grossman, Edelman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google’s ‘world-model’ bet: building the AI operating layer before Microsoft captures the UI]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008900</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/googles-world-model-bet-building-the-ai-operating-layer-before-microsoft-captures-the-ui/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-25T17:42:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google doubles down on its ‘world-model’ vision, racing to build an AI operating layer to drive a universal personal assistant with Gemini. Even as Microsoft moves to capture the enterprise UI. Here's what's at stake.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matt Marshall</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Beyond single-model AI: How architectural design drives reliable multi-agent orchestration]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008888</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/beyond-single-model-ai-how-architectural-design-drives-reliable-multi-agent-orchestration/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-24T22:35:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Successful AI agents require enterprises to orchestrate interactions, manage shared knowledge and plan for failure.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nikhil Gupta, Atlassian</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OpenAI updates Operator to o3, making its $200 monthly ChatGPT Pro subscription more enticing]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008828</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/openai-updates-operator-to-o3-making-its-200-monthly-chatgpt-subscription-more-enticing/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-23T21:51:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Operator remains a research preview and is accessible only to ChatGPT Pro users. The Responses API version will continue to use GPT-4o.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carl Franzen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The battle to AI-enable the web: NLweb and what enterprises need to know]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008795</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/the-battle-to-ai-enable-the-web-nlweb-and-what-enterprises-need-to-know/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-23T21:05:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft's NLWeb protocol transforms websites into AI-powered apps with conversational interfaces.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sean Michael Kerner</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>