<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2025-04-29T18:19:20.460Z</id>
    <title>AngJianming RSS Feed</title>
    <updated>2025-04-29T18:19:20.460Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Future Trends and the Role of .NET 9 in the Evolution of Software Development]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/leandroveiga/future-trends-and-the-role-of-net-9-in-the-evolution-of-software-development-i8k</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/leandroveiga/future-trends-and-the-role-of-net-9-in-the-evolution-of-software-development-i8k"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, we’ll analyze how the innovations introduced in .NET 9 align with emerging software development trends, show practical code examples, discuss real-world use cases and best practices, and peek at what’s next in future .NET releases.
Introduction
Key Innovations in .NET 9
Emerging Software Development Trends
Alignment of .NET 9 with Future Trends
Use Cases & Adoption Scenarios
Looking Ahead: What to Expect in .NET 10+
Conclusion
The .NET ecosystem continues to evolve at a brisk pace. With each major release, Microsoft introduces features to improve performance, developer productivity, and cross-platform consistency. .NET 9 arrives at a time when cloud-native architectures, AI/ML integration, edge computing, and low-code trends are reshaping how we build software. Let’s see h…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Leandro Veiga</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dev Diary #1 — Google Agent Development Kit: Lessons I Learned]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/protsenko/dev-diary-1-google-agent-development-kit-lessons-i-learned-332g</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/protsenko/dev-diary-1-google-agent-development-kit-lessons-i-learned-332g"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T17:59:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This diary-tutorial hybrid tracks my first months with Google’s Agent Development Kit (ADK) — pure experience, insight sharing, and nothing else. The ADK is Google’s open-source framework for designing, chaining, and shipping autonomous AI agents. If you are unfamiliar with this framework, read my beginner guide to build AI agents quickly.
You don’t need many AI agents, one for each task. An agent can call as many tools as it needs. AI independently decides what tool it should use and when. Write a precise prompt and correctly declare what tools AI can access and when it should be used.
You should care what you save in the session state. AI agents could save the output to the session state, and different agents in your AI pipeline could access it. While developing, you should navigate to t…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dmitry Protsenko</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The `final` Keyword in Java]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/sudhakar_v_c404997aeec839/the-final-keyword-in-java-2505</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/sudhakar_v_c404997aeec839/the-final-keyword-in-java-2505"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T17:58:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The final keyword in Java is used to restrict certain modifications in your code. It can be applied to variables, methods, and classes, with different effects in each case.
When applied to a variable, final means the variable cannot be reassigned after initialization.
Final local variables: Cannot be modified after initialization
Final instance variables: Must be initialized either at declaration or in constructor
Final static variables (constants): Typically declared with static final and named in ALL_CAPS




final int MAX_VALUE = 100;  // Final local variable
// MAX_VALUE = 200;  // Compile error - cannot reassign

class Example {
    final int instanceVar;  // Final instance variable

    Example() {
        instanceVar = 42;  // Must be initialized in constructor
    }

    static fin…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sudhakar V</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nasdaq files to list 21Shares Dogecoin ETF]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/nasdaq-files-list-21-shares-dogecoin-etf</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/nasdaq-files-list-21-shares-dogecoin-etf?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T17:57:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The United States exchange Nasdaq has asked regulators for permission to list a 21Shares exchange-traded fund (ETF) holding the popular memcoin Dogecoin, regulatory filings show. 
The move follows 21Shares’ April 10 filing of its initial proposal to launch its Dogecoin ETF, shortly after similar applications from rivals Bitwise and Grayscale. The asset manager has also sought regulators’ permission to list ETFs holding other cryptocurrencies, including Solana (SOL), XRP (XRP), and Polkadot (DOT). 
Nasdaq must gain approval from the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) before it can list and trade the fund. The request amounts to a regulatory review process that could determine whether Dogecoin becomes accessible to a broader range of investors through an ETF structure.
Crypto ETFs sche…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Alex O’Donnell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Object literals with satisfies operator for UI field mapping]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/angelapy/object-literals-with-satisfies-operator-for-ui-field-mapping-2ggp</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/angelapy/object-literals-with-satisfies-operator-for-ui-field-mapping-2ggp"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T17:56:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Our Frontend is responsible for converting fields into labels that make more sense to users.
So far I have seen the use of Enums to solve that purpose but we can also use Objects literals  with satisfies and I believe its more developer friendly, flexible and when compiled, it resembles JS.
Object literals: Meant to be used for key-value pairs.
Object literals with satisfies: Preserves the exact literal types.
Let’s say we have an Artist songs page  that can be sorted by either title, album name, duration , and # of plays. Our sorting mechanism, in this case a REST API, allows sorting by any of the fields. 
First, I would create a declarative sort dropdown component where the keys match the API fields and the values offer user-friendly labels
const artistSongSortOptions = {
  title: 'Title…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Angela Pat.</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Interface In Java]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/sudhakar_v_c404997aeec839/interface-in-java-c7k</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/sudhakar_v_c404997aeec839/interface-in-java-c7k"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T17:55:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Interfaces in Java


An interface in Java is a reference type that contains only abstract methods (until Java 8), default methods, static methods, and constant declarations. It's a way to achieve abstraction and multiple inheritance in Java.
All methods are abstract by default (before Java 8)
Cannot be instantiated directly
No constructors
All fields are public, static, and final by default
A class can implement multiple interfaces
public interface Vehicle {
    // Constant (implicitly public, static, final)
    int MAX_SPEED = 120;

    // Abstract method (implicitly public and abstract)
    void start();
    void stop();

    // Default method (Java 8+)
    default void honk() {
        System.out.println("Honking the horn");
    }

    // Static method (Java 8+)
    static int getMaxSpe…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sudhakar V</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Translate Entire Google Sheets (All Cells)]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/colinreed/how-to-translate-entire-google-sheets-all-cells-57mi</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/colinreed/how-to-translate-entire-google-sheets-all-cells-57mi"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T17:55:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Translating Google Sheets cells one-by-one for your organization isn’t the most productive activity in your workday, is it? As it turns out, the best way to translate an entire Google Sheets spreadsheet to another language in 2024 isn’t with Google Sheets itself. Nor is it by using free third-party Google Sheets translator tools online.
Here you will learn why you can’t translate a whole Google Sheets spreadsheet (all cells) efficiently with your current method. We also tell you how to translate an entire Google Sheets document most efficiently with the best Google Sheets document translator online. As a result, you will translate Google Sheets faster, smarter and easier.
1. Google Sheets itself can’t translate entire Google Sheets at once (unless you run a script)
You cannot translate ent…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Colin Reed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Eslint rules for dealing with Enums peculiarities]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/angelapy/eslint-rules-for-dealing-with-enums-peculiarities-3p4h</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/angelapy/eslint-rules-for-dealing-with-enums-peculiarities-3p4h"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T17:53:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As of now Enum have their peculiarities in Typescript; they can behave hmm... How should I put it? Inconsistenly. If you still love Enums then, let me suggest some EsLint rules for writing better Enum
Enums peculiarities
Helpful ESLint Rules for Enums!
EsLint: New to ESLint? It helps you write better JavaScript and TypeScript. https://typescript-eslint.io/




  
  
  Enums peculiarities 


I am going to walk you through a few peculiarities I’ve come across while building components using declarative rendering.
Let me show you with examples
Enums behave different when its created with string values versus numbers.
 enum TransferStatus {
  Pending = 'pending',
  Completed = 'completed',
  Failed = 'failed',
}

console.log(Object.keys(TransferStatus)) 
// Output : ["Pending", "Completed", "F…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Angela Pat.</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ElasticFourierTransformer: Probabilistic Token Mapping via Learned Centroids]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/ryo_suwito/elasticfouriertransformer-probabilistic-token-mapping-via-learned-centroids-107p</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/ryo_suwito/elasticfouriertransformer-probabilistic-token-mapping-via-learned-centroids-107p"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T17:44:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Abstract


We present ElasticFourierTransformer, a novel neural architecture that learns to embed tokens in a semantic space where natural language concepts are represented as centroids in a continuous embedding space. Unlike traditional language models that map directly from context to token probabilities, our approach separates these tasks: it first maps context to "concept centroids" in embedding space, then maps these centroids to probabilistic token distributions. This separation enables more flexible, interpretable language modeling that captures semantic relationships between tokens while maintaining high precision. We demonstrate that our model discovers meaningful linguistic patterns beyond its explicit training objective, exhibiting properties of emergent semantic organization wi…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryo Suwito</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Partitioning in Distributed Data Systems: Explained with Real-World Examples]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/dhanush___b/partitioning-in-distributed-data-systems-explained-with-real-world-examples-356e</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/dhanush___b/partitioning-in-distributed-data-systems-explained-with-real-world-examples-356e"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T17:43:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When systems grow beyond a single machine's capabilities, partitioning (also called sharding) becomes essential. Chapter 6 of "Designing Data-Intensive Applications" by Martin Kleppmann dives deep into how partitioning works and the challenges it introduces. Let's break it down into an easy-to-understand tech blog, complete with practical examples!
Partitioning distributes data across multiple nodes to:
Scale storage beyond a single machine.
Improve query throughput and reduce latency.
Increase system fault tolerance.
Without partitioning, a database might hit bottlenecks in CPU, RAM, disk, or network.
Real-World Example:
Twitter stores billions of tweets. A single server can't handle this load, so tweets are partitioned based on user IDs across many servers.
Data is partitioned based on a…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dhanush B</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dash with PropelAuth: Add Authentication to Your Data Apps with Just a Few Lines of Code]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/propelauth/dash-with-propelauth-add-authentication-to-your-data-apps-with-just-a-few-lines-of-code-3nm1</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/propelauth/dash-with-propelauth-add-authentication-to-your-data-apps-with-just-a-few-lines-of-code-3nm1"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T17:43:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Original author: Paul Vatterott
We’re excited to announce our new integration with Dash, the powerful Python framework from Plotly that enables data scientists and analysts to build interactive web applications with beautiful dashboard and reactive data visualizations.
Let’s say you’ve built a powerful and interactive data dashboard with Dash. It’s insightful, dynamic, and looks great. But as your application grows and handles sensitive data, the critical question becomes: how do you ensure the right people see the right data? That’s where PropelAuth comes in.
Here at PropelAuth we’re huge fans of the NBA. With the NBA playoffs in full swing we wanted to show how you can use PropelAuth and Dash to display stats for each member of a team. Just as NBA teams need the right combination of tale…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Victoria</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The YAGNI Principle]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/ahadalireach/the-yagni-principle-2a6d</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/ahadalireach/the-yagni-principle-2a6d"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T17:42:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Before moving into the DRY principle, let's understand the goals of a good programmer:
Solving Problems
Writing Amazing Code


Maintainsability
Simplicity
Cleanliness
Optimization
You're writing for humans. 
Whether it's for a team.
When you revisit your code 6 months later, it must be understandable by you.
Yes! Here are some principles:
DRY
KISS
YAGNI
SOLID
We often want our code to handle every imaginable situation or future feature.
However, this mindset leads to bloated code, wasted time, and unnecessary complexity.  
This is where YAGNI comes to the rescue.
Let's Deep Dive...
In this article, we will cover:
What is YAGNI?
Common Pitfalls of Ignoring it
Why is it Important?
How to Apply it?
When Not to Use it?
Disadvantages of YAGNI
Only build something when you really need it - not j…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ahad Ali</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[2.2.2 Decentralized Architectures (Distributed Systems)]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/dima853/222-decentralized-architectures-distributed-systems-1kff</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/dima853/222-decentralized-architectures-distributed-systems-1kff"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T17:41:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Before we begin, notice:
Multitiered client-server architectures are a direct consequence of dividing applications into a user-interface, processing components, and a data level.
obviously, but...
The different tiers correspond directly with the logical organization of applications. In many business environments, distributed processing is equivalent to organizing a client-server application as a multitiered architecture. We refer to this type of distribution as vertical distribution. The characteristic feature of vertical distribution is that it is achieved by placing logically different components on different
.


but
The term is related to the concept of vertical fragmentation as used in
don't forget, that


Decentralized architectures are not the exclusive prerogative of big business. A…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>dima853</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bamba: An open-source LLM that crosses a transformer with an SSM]]></title>
        <id>https://research.ibm.com/blog/bamba-ssm-transformer-model</id>
        <link href="https://research.ibm.com/blog/bamba-ssm-transformer-model"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T17:24:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[I made my AI think harder by making it argue with itself. It works stupidly well]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/PhialsBasement/Chain-of-Recursive-Thoughts</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/PhialsBasement/Chain-of-Recursive-Thoughts"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T17:19:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Everything we announced at our first-ever LlamaCon]]></title>
        <id>https://ai.meta.com/blog/llamacon-llama-news/?_fb_noscript=1</id>
        <link href="https://ai.meta.com/blog/llamacon-llama-news/?_fb_noscript=1"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T17:17:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hestus, Inc. (YC S24) Is Hiring an ML Engineer to Revolutionize CAD]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ycombinator.com/companies/hestus-inc/jobs/WQVdwX8-machine-learning-engineer</id>
        <link href="https://www.ycombinator.com/companies/hestus-inc/jobs/WQVdwX8-machine-learning-engineer"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T17:01:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[O3 beats a master-level GeoGuessr player, even with fake EXIF data]]></title>
        <id>https://sampatt.com/blog/2025-04-28-can-o3-beat-a-geoguessr-master</id>
        <link href="https://sampatt.com/blog/2025-04-28-can-o3-beat-a-geoguessr-master"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T16:48:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Samourai Wallet Prosecutors Are Considering Dropping Charges Under New DOJ Crypto Enforcement Priorities: Filing]]></title>
        <id>9b36b910-d4ee-462e-9886-3535208b8bf1</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2025/04/29/samourai-wallet-prosecutors-are-considering-dropping-charges-under-new-doj-crypto-enforcement-priorities-filing"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T16:46:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The co-founders are each facing up to 25 years in prison for alleged money laundering and unlicensed money transmitting.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cheyenne Ligon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Indian court orders blocking of Proton Mail]]></title>
        <id>https://techcrunch.com/2025/04/29/indian-court-orders-blocking-of-proton-mail/</id>
        <link href="https://techcrunch.com/2025/04/29/indian-court-orders-blocking-of-proton-mail/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T16:41:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WonderFi’s Dean Skurka on Bringing Users Onchain and Canada's Crypto Evolution]]></title>
        <id>a385b7d2-bf6b-439c-ac1f-788c4e93eea3</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/consensus-toronto-2025-coverage/2025/04/29/wonderfis-dean-skurka-on-bringing-users-onchain-and-canadas-crypto-evolution"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T16:26:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[WonderFi's CEO, a speaker at Consensus 2025, outlines the firm’s Layer-2 ambitions, Australia expansion, regulatory hopes for Canada, and how volatility impacts the industry.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Aoyon Ashraf</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Will Arizona Become the First State to Join Feds in Planning a Bitcoin Reserve?]]></title>
        <id>d9063668-1142-442c-8cc1-b523c9bc1b60</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2025/04/29/will-arizona-become-the-first-state-to-join-feds-in-planning-a-bitcoin-reserve"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T16:11:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new approval from Arizona lawmakers to form a digital assets stockpile must still survive a veto potential from the Democratic governor.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jesse Hamilton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase’s Base Network Achieves ‘Stage 1’ Status, Reducing Centralization Risk]]></title>
        <id>7d072d24-3f60-421a-a920-8e95c984d5c0</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/tech/2025/04/29/coinbases-base-network-achieves-stage-1-status-reducing-centralization-risk"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T16:00:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The move means that Base will now have a security council which will  help approve certain network upgrades if needed.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Margaux Nijkerk</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Firefox tab groups are here]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.mozilla.org/en/firefox/tab-groups-community/</id>
        <link href="https://blog.mozilla.org/en/firefox/tab-groups-community/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T15:37:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn College Calculus and Implement with Python]]></title>
        <id>6810eebd43aa3d16a14700eb</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-college-calculus-and-implement-with-python/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T15:22:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Calculus is one of the cornerstones of higher mathematics and a powerful tool for understanding change, motion, and growth across countless disciplines. But for many students, Calculus can seem intimidating or abstract. What if you could learn it ste...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meta AI App built with Llama 4]]></title>
        <id>https://about.fb.com/news/2025/04/introducing-meta-ai-app-new-way-access-ai-assistant/</id>
        <link href="https://about.fb.com/news/2025/04/introducing-meta-ai-app-new-way-access-ai-assistant/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T15:13:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Robinhood Crypto Revenue Expected to Fall in Q1 After Record Late 2024 Gain: JPMorgan]]></title>
        <id>566c9f9c-b936-42b1-a04e-184afe5d0f85</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/04/29/robinhood-crypto-revenue-expected-to-fall-in-q1-after-record-late-2024-gain-jpmorgan"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T15:12:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After a 700% surge in Q4 crypto revenue, analysts now expect a pullback in Q1 as trading activity slows.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Helene Braun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[UK gov&#039;t proposes crypto rules in response to scams]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/uk-government-crypto-rules-consumer-protection</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/uk-government-crypto-rules-consumer-protection?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T15:08:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The United Kingdom’s Treasury and Chancellor of the Exchequer, Rachel Reeves, have proposed new crypto rules aimed at “support[ing] innovation while cracking down on fraudsters.”
In an April 29 notice, the UK government announced draft rules for cryptocurrencies, including Bitcoin (BTC) and Ether (ETH), that would bring “crypto exchanges, dealers and agents” in line with regulations, as many residents were “exposed to risky firms and scams.” It cited discussions with US government officials, including a proposed US-UK cross-border sandbox from the Securities and Exchange Commission’s Hester Peirce.
“Today’s announcement sends a clear signal: Britain is open for business — but closed to fraud, abuse, and instability,” said the notice. “The government will bring forward final cryptoasset leg…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Turner Wright</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AI has a trust problem — Decentralized privacy-preserving tech can fix it]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/ai-has-a-trust-problem</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/ai-has-a-trust-problem?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Opinion by: Felix Xu, co-founder of ARPA Network and Bella Protocol
AI has been a dominant narrative since 2024, but users and companies still cannot completely trust it. Whether it’s finances, personal data or healthcare decisions, hesitation around AI’s reliability and integrity remains high.
This growing AI trust deficit is now one of the most significant barriers to widespread adoption. Decentralized, privacy-preserving technologies are quickly being recognized as viable solutions that offer verifiability, transparency and stronger data protection without compromising AI’s growth.
The pervasive AI trust deficit 
AI was the second most popular category occupying crypto mindshare in 2024, with over 16% investor interest. Startups and multinational companies have allocated considerable re…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Felix Xu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin &#039;hot supply&#039; nears $40B as new investors flood in at $95K]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-hot-supply-nears-40b-new-investors-flood-in-at-95k</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-hot-supply-nears-40b-new-investors-flood-in-at-95k?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T14:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Key points:

Bitcoin’s most recently-moved supply segment is increasing as higher prices see an influx of “speculative capital.”

“Hot supply” has doubled in just five weeks versus local lows in March.

Active address numbers have yet to mimic a classic bull market comeback.

Bitcoin (BTC) short-term holders (STHs) are back in the game as a “speculative capital” enters the market.
In an X thread on April 29, onchain analytics firm Glassnode reported a surge in Bitcoin’s so-called “hot capital.”
Bitcoin sees “surge in capital turnover”
New investors are entering the market as BTC price action circles its highest levels in several months.
Glassnode reveals that the sum of coins which last moved up to a week ago has reached its largest figure since early February.
“This metric captures short-…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by William Suberg</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Register Models in Django Admin]]></title>
        <id>6810e5a2dc9845a2ab207f06</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-register-models-in-django-admin/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T14:43:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When you're building a website or an app with Django, one of the most exciting moments is when your database models finally come to life. But to manage your data easily – adding, editing, or deleting entries – you need Django’s Admin panel. Now, here...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Udemezue John</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ArkFlow: High-performance Rust stream processing engine]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/arkflow-rs/arkflow</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/arkflow-rs/arkflow"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T14:38:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[$649B stablecoin transfers linked to illicit activity in 2024: Report]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/stablecoin-risk-crypto-transactions-bitrace-2024-report</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/stablecoin-risk-crypto-transactions-bitrace-2024-report?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T14:28:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency compliance firm Bitrace found that $649 billion worth of stablecoins flowed through addresses classified as high-risk in 2024, according to an April 29 report.
Bitrace defines high-risk blockchain addresses as those used by illegal entities to receive, transfer or store stablecoins.
Crypto compliance firms typically score crypto wallet addresses based on their likelihood of involvement in illicit activities. The higher the risk, the higher the likelihood of foul play, and the less likely compliant crypto businesses are to accept the assets.
Per the report, the amount accounted for roughly 5.14% of all stablecoin transaction volume in 2024. This is down 0.8% from 5.94% the previous year, but significantly higher than the 2.8% reported in 2022 and 1.63% in 2021.
Proportion of …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Adrian Zmudzinski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[One-sixth of the planet's cropland has toxic levels of one or more metals]]></title>
        <id>https://english.elpais.com/science-tech/2025-04-17/one-sixth-of-the-planets-cropland-has-toxic-levels-of-one-or-more-metals.html</id>
        <link href="https://english.elpais.com/science-tech/2025-04-17/one-sixth-of-the-planets-cropland-has-toxic-levels-of-one-or-more-metals.html"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T14:00:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[UK Government Targets Exchanges and Stablecoins With New Draft Crypto Rules]]></title>
        <id>fcb85fd8-4f27-4591-b2f0-903dd0f5a661</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2025/04/29/uk-government-releases-draft-crypto-rules"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T14:00:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The statutory instruments will see the creation of new regulated activities such as operating a cryptoasset trading exchange and stablecoin issuance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Camomile Shumba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Is XRP price going to crash again?]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/is-xrp-price-going-to-crash-again</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/is-xrp-price-going-to-crash-again?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T13:56:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Key takeaways:

XRP trades over 120% above its realized price, flashing heightened correction risk.

A rising wedge breakdown on the 4H chart could send XRP toward $1.89 by mid-May.

Weekly falling wedge pattern and 50-week EMA support suggest a possible 25% recovery to $2.92 by June.

XRP (XRP) price has rebounded by over 40% in the last three weeks to reach over $2.28 on April 29, but it’s still trading over 30% below its local high of $3.39.
XRP/USD daily price chart. Source: TradingView
Will XRP’s price sustain the recovery or drop further in the coming days?
XRP’s rising wedge flashes selloff risks
XRP is showing signs of a potential breakdown as a rising wedge pattern forms on its 4-hour chart, raising the risk of a sharp short-term correction.
As of April 29, XRP trades around $2.29…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Yashu Gola</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How $330M BTC Hacker May Have Doubled Down on Monero Derivatives]]></title>
        <id>c860b182-cbd2-4443-a40e-0c334598597a</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2025/04/29/did-the-usd330m-btc-hacker-deliberatley-pump-monero-to-make-even-more-money"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T13:56:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Monero rose by 45% after a flurry of spot buys, but open interest increased by 107%.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Oliver Knight</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum price has several reasons to break $2,000 next]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/ethereum-price-has-several-reasons-break-2000-next</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/ethereum-price-has-several-reasons-break-2000-next?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T13:33:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Key takeaways:

Strong Ethereum ETF inflows signal high institutional demand.

Ethereum’s $51.8B TVL and 30% DEX weekly volume rise show robust network strength.

A bull flag pattern on the ETH’s four-hour chart targets $2,100.

Ether’s (ETH) price rose to a new range high at $1,860 on April 28, its highest value since April 2.
Several analysts argue that the ETH price needs to hold above $1,800 to increase the chances of rising higher.
“Once ETH confirms this 4H close above resistance [$1,800], Ether and altcoins will finally get their time to shine,” trader Kiran Gadakh said in an April 29 post on X.  
“I can feel it in my bones, $2,000 ETH coming fast.” 
ETH/USD 12-hour chart. Source: Kiran Gadak
Popular analyst Nebraskangooner opined that if ETH faces high volume rejection from the $1,…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Nancy Lubale</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tripp launches Kōkua AI as mental wellness coach across multiple platforms]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3005798</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/games/tripp-launches-kokua-ai-as-mental-wellness-coach-across-multiple-platforms/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T13:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tripp launched Kōkua AI, a mental wellness guide designed to deliver real-time, personalized emotional support across multiple platforms.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dean Takahashi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Here’s what happened in crypto today]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/what-happened-in-crypto-today</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/what-happened-in-crypto-today?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T13:29:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today in crypto, the US Department of Justice has requested a 20-year prison sentence for Alex Mashinsky, the co-founder and former CEO of defunct crypto lender Celsius, a crypto group petitioned the White House to drop charges against crypto devs, including Tornado Cash’s Roman Storm, and Arizona’s House passed two crypto reserve bills.
US DOJ requests 20-year sentence for Celsius founder Alex Mashinsky
Alex Mashinsky, the founder and former CEO of the now-defunct cryptocurrency lending platform Celsius, faces a 20-year prison sentence as the US Department of Justice (DOJ) seeks a severe penalty for his role in a multibillion-dollar fraud.
The DOJ on April 28 filed the government’s sentencing memorandum against Mashinsky, recommending a 20-year prison sentence for his fraudulent actions, …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Cointelegraph</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CBDCs ‘costly fiat copy’, not fintech success so far: Ex-Binance exec]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/cbdc-costly-fiat-copy-not-fintech-success-ex-binance-exec</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/cbdc-costly-fiat-copy-not-fintech-success-ex-binance-exec?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T13:18:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The United States’ rejection of a central bank digital currency has not halted the progress of CBDCs globally, but their success has been questionable so far, according to a former Binance executive.
Global CBDC projects have not failed, but they have also not become what they were anticipated to be, according to Olga Goncharova, CEO at the consulting firm Rizz Go and former director of government relations in the Commonwealth of Independent States at Binance.
“CBDCs were conceived as a technological breakthrough, but so far they look like expensive imitations of existing traditional fiat currencies that citizens and businesses already use through online banking and payment apps,” Goncharova told Cointelegraph at the Blockchain Forum in Moscow.
Olga Goncharova during a panel on Web3 geopol…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Helen Partz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CoinDesk 20 Performance Update: Bitcoin Cash (BCH) Gains 6.3% as Index Trades Higher]]></title>
        <id>80eb4f67-7086-4331-82c2-98a06bfb7f69</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/coindesk-indices/2025/04/29/coindesk-20-performance-update-bitcoin-cash-bch-gains-6-3-as-index-trades-higher"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T13:14:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum (ETH) joined Bitcoin Cash (BCH) as a top performer, rising 1.8% from Monday.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CoinDesk Indices</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Vanishing $212M Bitcoin Order Caused Chaos for Traders. Is Spoofing Back in Crypto?]]></title>
        <id>9adbeb31-30dc-42b0-b1c9-0d9fb663c71e</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2025/04/29/a-vanishing-usd212m-bitcoin-order-caused-chaos-for-traders-is-spoofing-back-in-crypto"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T13:06:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Despite increased scrutiny, spoofing remains a challenge in crypto, highlighting the need for better surveillance and stricter regulations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Oliver Knight</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Beijing to invest in blockchain, integrate into infrastructure]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/beijing-to-invest-in-blockchain-integrate-into-infrastructure-and-host-nodes</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/beijing-to-invest-in-blockchain-integrate-into-infrastructure-and-host-nodes?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T13:03:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Beijing city administration has announced a plan for local blockchain development and implementation over the next two years.
According to an April 29 announcement, the plan was jointly developed by the Beijing Municipal Science and Technology Commission, the Zhongguancun Administrative Committee, the Cyberspace Administration Office, the Bureau of Government Services and Data, the Bureau of Economy and Information Technology and the Bureau of Commerce. The implementation is expected to start this year and continue until 2027.
The announcement. Source: Beijing government
The Beijing Blockchain Innovation and Application Development Action Plan recognizes blockchain as a “critical foundational technology for industrial digitalization and vital digital infrastructure.” 
Notably, the obje…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Adrian Zmudzinski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[xMEMS extends micro cooling fan-on-a-chip tech to AI data centers]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3005879</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/game-development/xmems-extends-micro-cooling-fan-on-a-chip-tech-to-ai-data-centers/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[xMEMS Labs, a pioneer of MEMS-based chips, announced that its innovative µCooling fan-on-a-chip tech will be expanded to AI data centers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dean Takahashi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BONK Bets Gain Favor as New Token Issuance Platform Nets $800K in 3 Days]]></title>
        <id>a0f905dc-a43b-4370-839c-8fffa965effe</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/04/29/bonk-bets-gain-favor-as-new-token-issuance-platform-nets-800k-in-3-days"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T12:53:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“I expect the platform's success to surprise many,” well-followed X user @theunipcs “Bonk Guy” told CoinDesk in a Telegram message.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shaurya Malwa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Is "Induced Atmospheric Vibration"?]]></title>
        <id>https://physics.stackexchange.com/questions/848666/what-is-induced-atmospheric-vibration</id>
        <link href="https://physics.stackexchange.com/questions/848666/what-is-induced-atmospheric-vibration"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T12:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Performance optimization is hard because it's fundamentally a brute-force task]]></title>
        <id>https://purplesyringa.moe/blog/why-performance-optimization-is-hard-work/</id>
        <link href="https://purplesyringa.moe/blog/why-performance-optimization-is-hard-work/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T12:29:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Polygon Spin-Off Miden Secures $25M to Bring Speed, Privacy to Institutional Giants]]></title>
        <id>f84107fc-007e-4dfa-88d9-3fb439e5e114</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/tech/2025/04/29/polygon-spin-off-miden-secures-25m-to-bring-speed-privacy-to-institutional-giants"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T12:27:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The funding round was led by a16z crypto, 1kx and Hack VC.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Margaux Nijkerk</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Programming languages should have a tree traversal primitive]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.tylerglaiel.com/p/programming-languages-should-have</id>
        <link href="https://blog.tylerglaiel.com/p/programming-languages-should-have"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T12:23:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A16z leads $25M funding for Miden blockchain project]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/miden-raises-25m-to-scale-zk-blockchain-after-polygon-spinout</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/miden-raises-25m-to-scale-zk-blockchain-after-polygon-spinout?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T12:20:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A16z Crypto led a $25 million investment round into Miden, an independent blockchain project spun out of Polygon Labs.
Miden closed its $25 million seed rounds led by a16z Crypto, 1kx, and Hack VC, with participation from Finality Capital Partners, Symbolic Capital, P2 Ventures, Delta Fund, MH Ventures, as well as from angel investors, including MakerDAO’s Rune Christensen and EigenLayer’s Sreeram Kannan.
Miden is a zero-knowledge (ZK) proof-powered blockchain focused on high scalability through its hybrid consensus mode, which moves transaction execution from the mainnet on “edge devices,” referring to users’ devices.
Designed for institutions that value confidentiality, Miden enables applications to execute both public and private transactions with full privacy, according to an April 29 …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Zoltan Vardai</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[After 53 years, a failed Soviet Venus spacecraft is crashing back to Earth]]></title>
        <id>https://gizmodo.com/after-53-years-a-failed-soviet-venus-spacecraft-is-crashing-back-to-earth-2000595234</id>
        <link href="https://gizmodo.com/after-53-years-a-failed-soviet-venus-spacecraft-is-crashing-back-to-earth-2000595234"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T12:20:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pyrefly - A faster Python type checker written in Rust]]></title>
        <id>https://pyrefly.org/</id>
        <link href="https://pyrefly.org/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T12:13:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Download: the AI Hype Index, and “normal” AI]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1115932</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/04/29/1115932/the-download-the-ai-hype-index-and-normal-ai/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T12:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is today’s edition of The Download, our weekday newsletter that provides a daily dose of what’s going on in the world of technology. The AI Hype Index: AI agent cyberattacks, racing robots, and musical models Separating AI reality from hyped-up fiction isn’t always easy. That’s why we’ve created the AI Hype Index—a simple, at-a-glance summary of…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rhiannon Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trump’s first 100 days ‘worst in history’ despite crypto promises]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/trump-first-100-days-worst-in-history-despite-crypto-promises</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/trump-first-100-days-worst-in-history-despite-crypto-promises?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T11:58:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The first 100 days of the administration of US President Donald Trump have deeply impacted the crypto industry, starting with his own memecoin and culminating in a Bitcoin reserve and a spate of blockchain policymaking. 
Trump’s trade war with the entire world has had the largest short-term impact on crypto markets, as crypto prices have wavered amid macroeconomic worry and uncertainty. Higher prices on electronics mean Bitcoin (BTC) miners are finding it harder to break even, and de-dollarization concerns abound. 
Still, crypto markets have shown some resilience and cause for optimism in the administration’s crypto-friendly policies. A number of pro-crypto leaders have been appointed to key government agencies, including the Securities and Exchange Commission and the Commodity Futures Tra…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Aaron Wood</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gaussian Splatting Meets ROS2]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/shadygm/ROSplat</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/shadygm/ROSplat"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T11:57:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[$2B Bitcoin-Staking Protocol Solv Unveils First Shariah-Compliant BTC Yield Offering in the Middle East]]></title>
        <id>3d6f8d08-b349-4fff-8cfe-4784429221ee</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/04/29/2b-bitcoin-staking-protocol-solv-unveils-first-shariah-compliant-btc-yield-offering-in-the-middle-east"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T11:56:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The product allows BTC holders to earn yields while adhering to Islamic finance principles, expanding opportunities for investors in the Middle East.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Omkar Godbole</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Show HN: A Chrome extension that will auto-reject non-essential cookies]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.bymitch.com/posts/reject-cookies/</id>
        <link href="https://blog.bymitch.com/posts/reject-cookies/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T11:49:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Circle gets Abu Dhabi regulatory nod to expand in Middle East]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/circle-abu-dhabi-adgm-approval-middle-east-expansion</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/circle-abu-dhabi-adgm-approval-middle-east-expansion?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T11:47:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[USDC stablecoin issuer Circle has received in-principle approval (IPA) from the Financial Services Regulatory Authority (FSRA) of the Abu Dhabi Global Market (ADGM), the company announced on April 29.
The approval moves Circle closer to obtaining a full Financial Services Permission (FSP) license, allowing it to operate as a regulated money services provider in the United Arab Emirates, the firm said in an official press release.
Jeremy Allaire, Circle’s Co-Founder and CEO, said the approval “advances our strategy to establish deep roots in markets embracing the onchain economy.” He added:
“It also underscores Circle’s enduring commitment to global stablecoin oversight—strengthening trust, compliance, and adoption worldwide, while laying a resilient foundation for the internet financial sy…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Amin Haqshanas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Acer Malaysia Launches Multiple Predator Products]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=350037</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/350037/acer-malaysia-launches-multiple-predator-products/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T11:44:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Acer Malaysia today officially launched a large lineup of products. That list includes two gaming laptops, a new OLED monitor, a graphics card, a desktop rig, and a foldable controller for mobile devices. We’ll start with the Orion 7000 desktop PC. Now available via Acer eStore and the brand’s Shopee and Lazada digital store for […]
The post Acer Malaysia Launches Multiple Predator Products appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John Law</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Heart disease deaths worldwide linked to chemical widely used in plastics]]></title>
        <id>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-04-heart-disease-deaths-worldwide-linked.html</id>
        <link href="https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-04-heart-disease-deaths-worldwide-linked.html"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T11:35:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin miner Phoenix Group adds 52 MW of mining capacity in Ethiopia]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-miner-phoenix-group-adds-52-megawatts-of-mining-capacity-in-ethiopia</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-miner-phoenix-group-adds-52-megawatts-of-mining-capacity-in-ethiopia?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T11:30:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin mining firm Phoenix Group announced the addition of 52 megawatts (MW) worth of mining capacity to its capabilities in Ethiopia.
According to an April 29 announcement, with this latest addition, Phoenix’s Bitcoin mining capacity in Ethiopia reaches 132 MW. The firm’s global capacity now reportedly exceeds 500 MW.
Phoenix’s co-founder and CEO, Munaf Ali, said the firm’s strategy relies on “securing prime locations with abundant, low-cost energy.”
“Initiatives like our latest expansion in Ethiopia are pivotal steps, not only creating significant value today but also solidifying our position,” he said.
Related: Arkansas city rejects crypto mining proposal after community pushback
Building on previous agreements
The news follows Phoenix Group signing an agreement that secures the right …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Adrian Zmudzinski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Your digital identity got stolen — Now what?]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/explained/your-digital-identity-got-stolen-now-what</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/explained/your-digital-identity-got-stolen-now-what?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T11:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What is digital identity?            
            
                
Your digital identity is the fingerprint you leave across the internet, a living map of who you are.
Your digital identity is more than just your name or email; it stretches from your social media profiles and crypto wallet addresses to your device fingerprints and even the rhythms of your daily browsing habits. In the fast-moving world of cryptocurrency, where identity and financial access often overlap, digital identity theft isn’t just a nuisance; it’s an open door to your assets. 

Without strong protection, even small pieces of stolen information can be stitched into a full profile, giving cybercriminals everything they need to impersonate you, seize your funds or lock you out of your accounts.
What many don’t realize…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Sasha Shilina</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Daybook Americas: Bitcoin Bulls Underpin Price After Pro-BTC Candidate Loses in Canada]]></title>
        <id>524ba9ab-b354-4610-9816-1f6f7ce92adc</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/daybook-us/2025/04/29/crypto-daybook-americas-bitcoin-bulls-underpin-price-after-pro-btc-candidate-loses-in-canada"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T11:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Your day-ahead look for April 29, 2025]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>James Van Straten</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Will Trump’s 100-day speech end Bitcoin’s &#039;compressing&#039; range?]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/will-trump-100-day-speech-end-bitcoin-compressing-range</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/will-trump-100-day-speech-end-bitcoin-compressing-range?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T10:27:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Key takeaways:

Bitcoin’s price consolidates as the market awaits President Trump’s 100-day speech.

Over $4.7 billion in BTC has been withdrawn from exchanges since April 22, reducing supply and boosting price sensitivity to demand.

Trump’s crypto policy clarity could spark a BTC surge, but tariffs may cap gains.

Traders say Bitcoin price must clear key hurdles above $95,000 before continuing the uptrend to $100,000 and beyond.


Bitcoin’s (BTC) price is consolidating in a tight range between $91,700 and $95,850, ahead of Trump’s 100-day commemorative rally.
BTC/USD daily chart. Source: Cointelegraph/TradingView 
Market awaits Trump’s 100-day speech
Bitcoin investors have adopted a wait-and-see approach ahead of US President Donald Trump’s speech to commemorate his 100th day in the Whit…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Nancy Lubale</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[iCAUR Teases First EV For Malaysia]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=350040</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/350040/icaur-teases-first-ev-for-malaysia/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T10:22:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We previously reported that Chery’s sub-brand iCAUR (or iCAR in China) will be entering the Malaysia during the Malaysia Auto Show 2025 (MAS). The brand has since confirmed the news through a teaser poster shared on their social media channels, which also features a silhouette of the vehicle it plans to introduce to the local […]
The post iCAUR Teases First EV For Malaysia appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Keran</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Generative AI is not replacing jobs or hurting wages at all, say economists]]></title>
        <id>https://www.theregister.com/2025/04/29/generative_ai_no_effect_jobs_wages/</id>
        <link href="https://www.theregister.com/2025/04/29/generative_ai_no_effect_jobs_wages/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T10:08:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AirAsia MOVE Introduces “Easy Cancel” Feature]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=350021</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/350021/airasia-move-introduces-easy-cancel-feature/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T10:06:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AirAsia MOVE has introduced “Easy Cancel“, a new feature that allows users to receive a full refund when cancelling their trip bookings. Through this, customers can cancel their flights up to 48 hours before the departure time for any reason and receive their money through the original payment method. The refund covers not only the […]
The post AirAsia MOVE Introduces “Easy Cancel” Feature appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nurul Kamil</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SIGN Rises 60% on Upbit Listing Despite Slow Start on Binance]]></title>
        <id>01b9f3b6-e0c9-4be0-b80b-c264e4069cfd</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2025/04/29/sign-rises-60-on-upbit-listing-despite-slow-start-on-binance"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T10:04:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SIGN's rise is similar to FIL which also rose on an Upbit listing this month.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Oliver Knight</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DJI Ending Support For Phantom 4, Phantom 4 Pro On 1 June 2025]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=350047</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/350047/dji-ending-support-for-phantom-4-phantom-4-pro-on-1-june-2025/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T10:01:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[DJI has announced the ending of its support for two of its products: the Phantom 4 and Phantom 4 Pro drones. Through its official website, the company has stated that the service and support of the devices will be suspended starting 1 June 2025.  The Phantom 4 was released in Malaysia all the way back […]
The post DJI Ending Support For Phantom 4, Phantom 4 Pro On 1 June 2025 appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Newsdesk</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The AI Hype Index: AI agent cyberattacks, racing robots, and musical models]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1115918</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/04/29/1115918/the-ai-hype-index-ai-agent-cyberattacks-racing-robots-and-musical-models/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Separating AI reality from hyped-up fiction isn’t always easy. That’s why we’ve created the AI Hype Index—a simple, at-a-glance summary of everything you need to know about the state of the industry. AI agents are the AI industry’s hypiest new product—intelligent assistants capable of completing tasks without human supervision. But while they can be theoretically…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Editors</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to build Intrinsic Motivation: a review of the science]]></title>
        <id>https://erringtowardsanswers.substack.com/p/intrinsic-motivation</id>
        <link href="https://erringtowardsanswers.substack.com/p/intrinsic-motivation"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T09:59:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BlackRock’s IBIT Sees Second-Largest Bitcoin Inflow Since Launch, Nearing $1 Billion]]></title>
        <id>d67edf66-110d-4528-8b46-e1a46fea781d</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/04/29/blackrocks-ibit-sees-second-largest-bitcoin-inflow-since-launch-nearing-1-billion"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T09:49:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CME Bitcoin Futures open interest falls for four straight days, according to CME data.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>James Van Straten</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BlackRock Bitcoin ETF buys $970M in BTC as inflows surge, boost market]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/blackrock-ibit-etf-second-largest-inflow-970-m</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/blackrock-ibit-etf-second-largest-inflow-970-m?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T09:41:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BlackRock’s exchange-traded fund (ETF) bought nearly $1 billion worth of Bitcoin on behalf of its clients on April 28, with continued inflows providing “structural support” for Bitcoin’s price appreciation, according to market analysts.
BlackRock’s iShares Bitcoin Trust (IBIT) ETF bought $970 million worth of Bitcoin (BTC) on April 28, its second-largest day of inflows on record after scooping up $1.12 billion of BTC on Nov. 7, 2024, Sosovalue data shows.
IBIT ETF Inflows, all-time chart. Source: Sosovalue 
IBIT’s near $1 billion investment brought total net inflows to US spot BTC ETFs to just above $590 million, with all other ETFs realizing net negative outflows or remaining flat. ARK Invest’s ARKB ETF recorded the highest outflows of $226 million.
Related: Bitcoin treasury firms driving…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Zoltan Vardai</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin targets $115K as BTC supply metric nears &#039;historic euphoria&#039; zone]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-price-targets-115k-btc-supply-euphoric-zone</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-price-targets-115k-btc-supply-euphoric-zone?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T09:36:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Key takeaways:

Bitcoin supply in profit has climbed back above 85%, nearing the classic euphoric area.

Onchain data shows strong accumulation from new and momentum buyers with minimal profit-taking.

Bitcoin could rally toward $110,000–$115,000 helped by a “max buying” zone.

Bitcoin (BTC) is charging toward a potential new all-time high near $115,000, as a surge in profitable supply signals growing bullish momentum and a classic setup for market euphoria.
Nearly 87% of Bitcoin supply in profit
As of April 28, approximately 86.9% of all Bitcoin coins were in profit, according to on-chain data resource CryptoQuant. 
Historically, the metric’s climb into the 85–90% range has signaled a transition from healthy optimism to speculative euphoria among traders.
Between October and December 2024…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Yashu Gola</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Alleged OnePlus Ace 5 Racing Edition Specifications Appear Online]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=350027</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/350027/oneplus-ace-5-racing-edition-specs-appear-online/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T09:16:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[OnePlus launched its Ace 5 series late last year, and is now apparently gearing up to release a new variant within the series. Through a post on Weibo, known leakster Digital Chat Station is claiming that the phone may be called the Racing Edition, while also sharing details surrounding its specifications – including its chipset […]
The post Alleged OnePlus Ace 5 Racing Edition Specifications Appear Online appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Newsdesk</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Web3j Six Month Project Update]]></title>
        <id>68109495670a1300013504c2</id>
        <link href="https://blog.web3labs.com/web3j-six-month-project-update/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T09:10:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[November 2024 - April 2025
This report summarizes the activities and accomplishments of Web3j, an LF Decentralized Trust project, from November 2024 to April 2025. During this period, the project made significant strides in improving the framework’s functionality, enhancing user engagement, and bolstering overall community interaction. 
Key]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>George Tebrean</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Loopscale recovers $2.8M after weekend DeFi hack and bounty talks]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/loopscale-recovers-funds-after-defi-exploit-hacker-negotiations</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/loopscale-recovers-funds-after-defi-exploit-hacker-negotiations?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T09:05:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[DeFi protocol Loopscale has recovered nearly half of the funds stolen during a major exploit over the weekend, as white hat negotiations with the attacker show signs of progress.
In an April 29 update posted to X, Loopscale confirmed that approximately 19,463 Wrapped SOL (WSOL) (worth roughly $2.88 million) have been returned to its wallets since April 28.
The first two returns included 10,000 WSOL (~$1.48 million) and 4,463 WSOL (~$660,000), following an earlier recovery of 5,000 WSOL (~$740,000).
“Our pursuit of an amicable resolution regarding Saturday’s incident continues to make progress,” the team wrote.
Loopscale updating community on negotiations progress. Source: Loopscale
Related: DeFi platform KiloEx to compensate users impacted by $7.5M hack
Loopscale offers 10% bounty for retu…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Amin Haqshanas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Show HN: Flowcode – Turing-complete visual programming platform]]></title>
        <id>https://app.getflowcode.io/playground/example1</id>
        <link href="https://app.getflowcode.io/playground/example1"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T09:04:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Viant Technology Could Benefit From Buying Bitcoin, Eric Semler Says]]></title>
        <id>488f3a4a-64e8-4818-9be4-468979446862</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/04/29/viant-technology-could-benefit-from-buying-bitcoin-eric-semler-says"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T09:01:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Semler Scientific chairman flagged the ad tech firm as ripe for a bitcoin treasury strategy amid stock struggles and cash stockpile.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>James Van Straten</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Here’s why we need to start thinking of AI as “normal”]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1115928</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/04/29/1115928/is-ai-normal/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Right now, despite its ubiquity, AI is seen as anything but a normal technology. There is talk of AI systems that will soon merit the term “superintelligence,” and the former CEO of Google recently suggested we control AI models the way we control uranium and other nuclear weapons materials. Anthropic is dedicating time and money…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>James O'Donnell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Circle Wins Regulatory Nod From Abu Dhabi Watchdog as USDC Hits $62B]]></title>
        <id>46e567b1-6ccf-433b-88d7-c5d5b78c9a8f</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2025/04/29/circle-wins-regulatory-nod-from-abu-dhabi-watchdog-as-usdc-hits-usd62b"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T08:55:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The stablecoin issuer received in-principle approval from ADGM's Financial Services Regulatory Authority to operate as a money services provider.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Krisztian Sandor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[US DOJ requests 20-year sentence for Celsius founder Alex Mashinsky]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/celsius-alex-mashinsky-20-year-sentence-doj</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/celsius-alex-mashinsky-20-year-sentence-doj?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T08:50:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Alex Mashinsky, the founder and former CEO of the now-defunct cryptocurrency lending platform Celsius, faces a 20-year prison sentence as the US Department of Justice (DOJ) seeks a severe penalty for his role in a multibillion-dollar fraud.
The DOJ on April 28 filed the government’s sentencing memorandum against Mashinsky, recommending a 20-year prison sentence for his fraudulent actions, which led to billions of dollars in losses for Celsius customers.
The 97-page memo mentioned that Celsius users were unable to access approximately $4.7 billion in crypto assets after the platform halted withdrawals on June 12, 2022.
“The Court should sentence Alexander Mashinsky to twenty years’ imprisonment as just punishment for his years-long campaign of lies and self-dealing that left in its wake bil…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Helen Partz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Xiaomi’s Upcoming YU7 Electric SUV May Get Second Variant]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=349993</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/349993/xiaomi-yu7-electric-suv-may-get-second-variant/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T08:49:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Following the success of the SU7, Xiaomi is preparing to launch its second EV model, the YU7 SUV, in China between June or July this year. Now, a recent report by Car News China alleges that the upcoming vehicle will debut another variant alongside the original 820km trim, with a range of 835km. This detail […]
The post Xiaomi’s Upcoming YU7 Electric SUV May Get Second Variant appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Keran</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin in &#039;critical zone&#039; as triple breakout meets $93.5K support battle]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-in-critical-zone-triple-breakout-93-5-k-support-battle</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-in-critical-zone-triple-breakout-93-5-k-support-battle?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T08:34:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Key points:

Bitcoin has beaten out three key resistance levels in a single weekly candle.

The weekly close defended the 2025 yearly open, but a subsequent dip below it is making analysis question the strength of the BTC price breakout.

BTC/USD remains in a “critical zone” pending fresh support confirmations.

Bitcoin (BTC) has broken through three key resistance levels in a week, but its biggest reclaim battle continues.
Analysis from sources including popular trader and analyst Rekt Capital underscores BTC price acting in a critical area for bulls.
Bitcoin breaks through “triple resistance”
Bitcoin’s latest weekly candle saw a reclaim of a full three resistance lines, Rekt Capital reveals.
In addition to horizontal weekly resistance, BTC/USD broke beyond a multimonth downtrend previous…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by William Suberg</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Is the Paws Telegram mini app legit? What you need to know]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/explained/is-the-paws-telegram-mini-app-legit-what-you-need-to-know</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/explained/is-the-paws-telegram-mini-app-legit-what-you-need-to-know?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T08:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What is the Paws Telegram Mini App?            
            
                
Paws is a Telegram-based Mini App created by the same team behind other projects, such as Notcoin and Dogs. 
If you’ve been cruising around Telegram lately, chances are you’ve stumbled upon Paws, the viral crypto Mini App that’s got everyone tapping, clicking and inviting their friends like it’s 2010 FarmVille all over again. 
Originally launched in October 2024 on The Open Network (TON) blockchain, Paws exploded in popularity with its ultra-simple tap-to-earn concept. Think of it as a gamified rewards engine embedded directly in Telegram, where users rack up points by completing tasks, referring others and interacting with mini-game elements. 
Within just eight days of going live, Paws pulled in over 20 million …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Shailey Singh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[vivo V50 Lite Now Official In Malaysia From RM1,299]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=349962</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/349962/vivo-v50-lite-now-official-in-malaysia-from-rm1299/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T08:06:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[vivo previously promised to launch the V50 Lite in the local market, though at the time the company did not provide an exact date as to when it’s happening. But it has finally happened, with the launch event happening moments ago. The launch also confirms what we mostly knew beforehand, which includes the 6.77-inch AMOLED […]
The post vivo V50 Lite Now Official In Malaysia From RM1,299 appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ian Chee</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DOJ Seeks 20-Year Sentence for Celsius Founder Alex Mashinsky]]></title>
        <id>17f84d8f-dbf5-41c0-997c-3f0832a0247d</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2025/04/29/doj-seeks-20-year-sentence-for-celsius-founder-alex-mashinsky"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T07:43:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Federal prosecutors called Mashinsky the architect of a "years-long campaign of lies and self-dealing" that left customers with billions in losses.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sam Reynolds</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[1inch launches on Solana with crosschain swaps in the pipeline]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/1inch-launches-on-solana-plans-cross-chain-swaps</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/1inch-launches-on-solana-plans-cross-chain-swaps?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T07:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decentralized exchange (DEX) aggregator 1inch has launched on Solana, marking a significant step toward its vision of a “unified multichain” decentralized finance (DeFi) ecosystem.
According to a press release shared with Cointelegraph, the integration enables users to trade over 1 million Solana-based tokens directly through the 1inch decentralized application (DApp), benefiting from maximal extractable value-protected swaps, optimized rates and open-source smart contract infrastructure.
The move brings 1inch’s Fusion protocol to Solana for the first time. Fusion enables users to define their ideal swap parameters, which are then executed by competing professional market makers, or “resolvers,” using Dutch auction mechanics.
Combined with Solana’s ultra-fast block times, the setup promise…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Amin Haqshanas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin, XRP, ETH Steady as BTC ETFs Attract $590M Inflows]]></title>
        <id>2af14240-b29b-4cf3-ad13-9873edfdf11e</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/04/29/bitcoin-xrp-eth-steady-as-btc-etfs-attract-590m-inflows"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T07:23:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“We are bullish on BTC in the medium term due to expectations of monetary and fiscal easing in response to tariff-driven slowdowns,” one trader said.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shaurya Malwa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Try Switching to Kagi]]></title>
        <id>https://daringfireball.net/2025/04/try_switching_to_kagi</id>
        <link href="https://daringfireball.net/2025/04/try_switching_to_kagi"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T07:08:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Russian ruble stablecoin: Exec lists 7 ‘Tether replica’ features]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/russian-ruble-stablecoin-exec-names-7-usdt-replica-features</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/russian-ruble-stablecoin-exec-names-7-usdt-replica-features?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T06:53:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The concept of a Russian ruble stablecoin received special attention at a major local crypto event, the Blockchain Forum in Moscow, with key industry executives reflecting on some of the core features a ruble-backed stablecoin might require.
Sergey Mendeleev, founder of the digital settlement exchange Exved and inactive founder of the sanctioned Garantex exchange, put forward seven key criteria for a potential “replica of Tether” in a keynote at the Blockchain Forum on April 23.
Mendeleev said a potential ruble stablecoin must have untraceable transactions and allow transfers without Know Your Customer (KYC) checks.
However, because one of the criteria also requires the stablecoin to comply with Russian regulations, he expressed skepticism that such a product could emerge soon.
The DAI mod…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Helen Partz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Garmin Announces Instinct 3 Tactical Edition; Starts From RM2,479]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=349986</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/349986/garmin-instinct-3-tactical-edition/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T06:49:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Garmin has announced the arrival of the Tactical Edition of its Instinct 3 rugged smartwatch. Similar to the regular version, it comes in 45mm and 50mm options, but with the addition of a metal-reinforced bezel for enhanced durability. Customers can choose between an AMOLED display or a solar charging model, but the former is limited […]
The post Garmin Announces Instinct 3 Tactical Edition; Starts From RM2,479 appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ikmal Rozlan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Maxis Expands Its Home Solar Subscription Across Peninsular Malaysia]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=349969</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/349969/maxis-expands-its-home-solar-subscription-across-peninsular-malaysia/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T06:16:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Maxis today has announced plans to extend its Home Solar subscription service across Peninsular Malaysia starting May 2025, following its initial rollout to Klang Valley customers in late 2024. The telco is also planning to open the service to non-customers by the end of the year. The Maxis Home Solar offering now includes six subscription […]
The post Maxis Expands Its Home Solar Subscription Across Peninsular Malaysia appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Heirul Kamel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Abu Dhabi institutional giants team up for dirham stablecoin]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/trio-of-abu-dhabi-institutional-giants-team-up-for-new-bank-backed-stablecoin</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/trio-of-abu-dhabi-institutional-giants-team-up-for-new-bank-backed-stablecoin?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T06:13:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A trio of major Abu Dhabi institutions, including the Emirate’s sovereign wealth fund, have teamed up to launch a new dirham-pegged stablecoin.
Abu Dhabi’s sovereign wealth fund ADQ, the United Arab Emirates’ largest bank, First Abu Dhabi Bank (FAB), and the massive conglomerate the International Holding Company, have partnered to launch the stablecoin, pending regulatory approval, the three companies said on April 28.
The trio said the stablecoin would be regulated by the UAE’s central bank and backed by the country’s currency, the dirham. It will also support use cases such as machine-to-machine and artificial intelligence.
Source: IHC
The goal is to place the UAE at the “forefront of global blockchain innovation,” while also strengthening the digital infrastructure, according to ADQ.
If…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Stephen Katte</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NVIDIA GeForce RTX 5080 Super Could Feature 24GB GDDR7, RTX 5070 With 18GB]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=349956</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/349956/nvidia-geforce-rtx-5080-super-could-feature-24gb-gddr7-rtx-5070-with-18gb/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T06:04:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There is a rumour going around that NVIDIA’s Super variant of the GeForce RTX 5080 and RTX 5070 will both be getting a bump up in the amount of graphics memory. Specifically, the RTX 5080 Super could ship out with 24GB GDDR7, and the RTX 5070 Super with 18GB. The rumour comes from a post […]
The post NVIDIA GeForce RTX 5080 Super Could Feature 24GB GDDR7, RTX 5070 With 18GB appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John Law</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[LibreLingo – FOSS Alternative to Duolingo]]></title>
        <id>https://librelingo.app/</id>
        <link href="https://librelingo.app/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T05:45:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A single line of code cost $8000]]></title>
        <id>https://pietrasiak.com/one-line-of-code-that-did-cost-dollar8000</id>
        <link href="https://pietrasiak.com/one-line-of-code-that-did-cost-dollar8000"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T05:40:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bankera founders used ICO funds on global property buys: Report]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/bankera-founders-use-ico-funds-property-buys-occrp</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/bankera-founders-use-ico-funds-property-buys-occrp?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T05:24:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The founders of the crypto fintech firm Bankera used funds from the project’s 2018 initial coin offering to purchase luxury properties worldwide, according to a report by the Organized Crime and Corruption Reporting Project.
The OCCRP reported on April 28, citing leaked company records and bank statements, that nearly half of the funds from Bankera’s 100 million euro ($114 million) ICO were transferred to a bank in the Pacific Island country of Vanuatu that was purchased by the project’s founders, Vytautas Karalevičius, Justas Dobiliauskas and Mantas Mockevičius.
Soon after, the Vanuatu bank reportedly began issuing millions of euros in loans to companies owned by the trio to build a luxury real estate portfolio — including a villa in the French Riviera and high-end property in Lithuania, …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Brayden Lindrea</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Zurich Uni’s secret AI experiment manipulated Redditors’ opinions]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/zurich-uni-secret-ai-experiment-manipulated-redditor-opinions</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/zurich-uni-secret-ai-experiment-manipulated-redditor-opinions?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T05:13:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Researchers at the University of Zurich have been accused of undertaking an unauthorized four-month-long experiment on a Reddit board using artificial intelligence-generated comments to test whether AI could alter people’s opinions. 
As part of the experiment, AI-powered accounts faked a variety of personas, including a rape victim, a person opposed to specific social movements and a trauma counselor specializing in abuse, moderators of the r/changemyview subreddit said in an April 26 post.
“Our sub is a decidedly human space that rejects undisclosed AI as a core value,” the moderators said. “People do not come here to discuss their views with AI or to be experimented upon.” 
The researchers used AI to generate responses but attempted to personalize the replies based on information from th…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Stephen Katte</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Samourai Wallet, feds ask for time to mull dropping crypto mixer case]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/samourai-wallet-feds-ask-for-time-consider-dropping-crypto-mixer-case</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/samourai-wallet-feds-ask-for-time-consider-dropping-crypto-mixer-case?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T04:39:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[US federal prosecutors and the co-founders of the crypto mixer Samourai Wallet have asked a court for more time to consider potentially dismissing the case after the Justice Department rolled back its crypto enforcement.
Lawyers for Samourai Wallet CEO Keonne Rodriguez and chief technology officer William Hill said in an April 28 letter to Manhattan federal judge Richard Berman that they jointly requested with the government “for a continuance of the pretrial motions schedule by 16 days.”
The Samourai executives' lawyers said on April 10 that they wrote to Acting Manhattan US Attorney Jay Clayton to request the dismissal of the case after an April 7 memo from Deputy Attorney General Todd Blanche shuttered the Justice Department’s crypto team.
“On April 24, 2025, defense counsel met with th…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Martin Young</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin-Friendly Poilievre Loses Seat as Carney's Liberals Win 2025 Election]]></title>
        <id>b5cccd42-3fe4-44ce-b5af-ac176e8229b3</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2025/04/29/bitcoin-friendly-poilievre-loses-seat-as-carneys-liberals-win-2025-election"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T04:26:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Canada's 45th election turned out to be a close one as polls narrowed in the days leading up to the end of the campaign.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sam Reynolds</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[US dollar facing growing competition for stablecoin dominance: Tether co-founder]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/tether-reeve-collins-stablecoin-backing-gold-tokenized-assets</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/tether-reeve-collins-stablecoin-backing-gold-tokenized-assets?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T03:58:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While United States dollar-denominated stablecoins dominate the stablecoin and real-world asset (RWA) tokenization game, other competitors are coming into play, according to Tether co-founder Reeve Collins. 
Speaking to Cointelegraph in Dubai, Collins said that while dollar-backed stablecoins may be dominant, other currencies and assets may compete to back stablecoins.
“The stablecoin definitely helps preserve the dollar dominance, especially in the crypto space,” Collins said. “The dollar is kind of the reserve currency of crypto. But now there are other currencies coming into play. But more importantly, it’s not currencies. It’s other types of backing,” he added.
Collins said that other assets used to back stablecoins may compete with US dollars by bringing a higher yield to users. 
Inte…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Ezra Reguerra</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ray Dalio says global monetary order ‘on the brink’ of breakdown]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/ray-dalio-global-monetary-order-on-brink-breakdown</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/ray-dalio-global-monetary-order-on-brink-breakdown?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T03:15:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Legendary investor Ray Dalio has said the world is “on the brink” of the global monetary order breaking down, which is being accelerated by the Trump administration’s tariff disruptions.
The trade tensions are fracturing the monetary, political and international world orders by fueling deglobalization and unsustainable trade imbalances, Dalio, the former CEO of hedge fund Bridgewater Associates, said in an April 28 X post.
Dalio added that this is leading to irreversible damage, and an increasing number of importers and exporters, particularly between the US and China, are drastically reducing interdependencies and “making alternative plans.”
“[They’re] recognizing that whatever happens with tariffs, these problems won't go away, and that radically reduced interdependencies with the US is …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Brayden Lindrea</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Alibaba launches open source Qwen3 model that surpasses OpenAI o1 and DeepSeek R1]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3005880</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/alibaba-launches-open-source-qwen3-model-that-surpasses-openai-o1-and-deepseek-r1/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-28T23:56:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Qwen3’s open-weight release under an accessible license marks an important milestone, lowering barriers for developers and organizations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carl Franzen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why did Windows 7 log on slower for months if you had a solid color background?]]></title>
        <id>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20250428-00/?p=111121</id>
        <link href="https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20250428-00/?p=111121"/>
        <updated>2025-04-28T23:27:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The One-Person Framework in Practice]]></title>
        <id>https://link.mail.beehiiv.com/ss/c/u001.5SRwDQ9qxPQW8vmD5Do73b3R4eTCi2vXqPyztEk6wMFC9_fqEAcDVx6xEJ96T4BSMXrPS7z5exEBSTF4pF48z8SqJkJnkAwMUW9LtYdd8lWmvkDinT92nsk5HmXOHdWgLsysm9FMGrqmu7dnG57cXpga8ZOe8X0IV8pyeC3AswdRMaitfT307y7naP-_6W5CiolKhXCKrEndMGCW2PftFUu9ieYOxpVJ_fhu82gAh-4/4g1/wA_MG-I5SVCyR3KY66oEaQ/h30/h001.kLDFZMgisudi21zmTPbd_O8U7X98d4UxYqZjQTb_D7o</id>
        <link href="https://link.mail.beehiiv.com/ss/c/u001.5SRwDQ9qxPQW8vmD5Do73b3R4eTCi2vXqPyztEk6wMFC9_fqEAcDVx6xEJ96T4BSMXrPS7z5exEBSTF4pF48z8SqJkJnkAwMUW9LtYdd8lWmvkDinT92nsk5HmXOHdWgLsysm9FMGrqmu7dnG57cXpga8ZOe8X0IV8pyeC3AswdRMaitfT307y7naP-_6W5CiolKhXCKrEndMGCW2PftFUu9ieYOxpVJ_fhu82gAh-4/4g1/wA_MG-I5SVCyR3KY66oEaQ/h30/h001.kLDFZMgisudi21zmTPbd_O8U7X98d4UxYqZjQTb_D7o"/>
        <updated>2025-04-28T21:58:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ex-OpenAI CEO and power users sound alarm over AI sycophancy and flattery of users]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3005850</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/ex-openai-ceo-and-power-users-sound-alarm-over-ai-sycophancy-and-flattery-of-users/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-28T21:49:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crucially, the turbulence also nudges many organizations to explore open-source models they can host, monitor, and fine-tune themselves.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carl Franzen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Qwen3: Think deeper, act faster]]></title>
        <id>https://qwenlm.github.io/blog/qwen3/</id>
        <link href="https://qwenlm.github.io/blog/qwen3/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-28T20:44:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Beyond A2A and MCP: How LOKA’s Universal Agent Identity Layer changes the game]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3005824</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/beyond-a2a-and-mcp-how-lokas-universal-agent-identity-layer-changes-the-game/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-28T20:35:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The LOKA protocol, a proposed standard for AI agents from Carnegie Mellon University researchers, will give identities and intentions to agents.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Emilia David</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build a Production-Ready DevOps Pipeline with Free Tools]]></title>
        <id>680fe1e69418a1165cb184a2</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-build-a-production-ready-devops-pipeline-with-free-tools/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-28T20:15:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A few months ago, I dove into DevOps, expecting it to be an expensive journey requiring costly tools and infrastructure. But I discovered you can build professional-grade pipelines using entirely free resources. If DevOps feels out of reach because y...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Opaluwa Emidowojo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Holds Tight Despite Dismal Economic Data, Rising India/Pakistan Tensions]]></title>
        <id>6beb19db-7343-4b91-b63f-8d937bdb9a84</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/04/28/bitcoin-holds-tight-despite-dismal-economic-data-rising-indiapakistan-tensions"/>
        <updated>2025-04-28T19:57:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Dallas Fed Manufacturing Index plunged to its lowest level since the COVID pandemic closed the economy.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tom Carreras</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[One Million Chessboards]]></title>
        <id>https://onemillionchessboards.com/#199,276</id>
        <link href="https://onemillionchessboards.com/#199,276"/>
        <updated>2025-04-28T19:52:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[30 seconds vs. 3: The d1 reasoning framework that’s slashing AI response times]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3005393</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/30-seconds-vs-3-the-d1-reasoning-framework-thats-slashing-ai-response-times/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-28T19:31:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[d1 framework changes boosts diffusion LLMs with novel reinforcement learning, unlocking efficient, problem-solving AI possibilities.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ben Dickson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build a Website from Scratch – Start to Finish Walkthrough]]></title>
        <id>680fd51ef631538076304a73</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-build-a-website-from-scratch-start-to-finish-walkthrough/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-28T19:21:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, fellow developers! Building a website can feel overwhelming at first – especially when you're staring at a blank HTML file, wondering how it ever turns into a real website on the internet. If you're new to web development, you've probably asked y...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kunal Nalawade</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Writer releases Palmyra X5, delivers near GPT-4.1 performance at 75% lower cost]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3005734</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/writer-releases-palmyra-x5-delivers-near-gpt-4-performance-at-75-lower-cost/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-28T17:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Writer unveils Palmyra X5: The enterprise AI model that processes 1,500 pages at once, costs 75% less than GPT-4, and enables affordable autonomous agents for businesses seeking automation ROI.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Nuñez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kraken’s Former Legal Chief Marco Santori Joins Pantera Capital]]></title>
        <id>35f4337b-1102-4f3c-933c-270dbe2c4109</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2025/04/28/kraken-s-former-legal-chief-marco-santori-joins-pantera-capital"/>
        <updated>2025-04-28T17:07:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“The timing couldn’t be better, and Pantera couldn’t be better positioned to capitalize on it,” Santori said about his new role.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ian Allison</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tether's $770M XAUT Backed by 7.7 Tons of Gold in Swiss Vault, Says Company]]></title>
        <id>8e46f450-9662-4ebf-b187-0a5812198006</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/04/28/tethers-770m-xaut-backed-by-77-tons-of-gold-in-swiss-vault-says-company"/>
        <updated>2025-04-28T16:33:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tether reported the first attestation report for its Tether Gold product under new El Salvador regulations as gold demand surges globally]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tom Carreras</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Miner 1Q Results May Disappoint as Hashprice Fell, Tariffs Hit: CoinShares]]></title>
        <id>eab53f70-70b1-434e-9e03-79064efb9f59</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/04/28/bitcoin-miner-1q-results-may-disappoint-as-hashprice-fell-tariffs-hit-coinshares"/>
        <updated>2025-04-28T16:15:20.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Will Canny</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[QuickNode: Building the Infrastructure for the Next Generation of Blockchain]]></title>
        <id>6807d5787fb8500001c39b99</id>
        <link href="https://blog.quicknode.com/quicknode-building-the-infrastructure-for-the-next-generation-of-blockchain/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-28T16:02:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Join QuickNode co-founder Dmitry Shklovsky as he discusses blockchain infrastructure, building decentralized applications, and the future of Web3 development on TheCube's Crypto Trailblazer Series.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>QuickNode</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mastercard Unveils End-to-End Stablecoin Capabilities, Will Launch Card With OKX]]></title>
        <id>985a9f61-dd7e-4c1a-8343-6f9e13a58d76</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2025/04/28/mastercard-unveils-end-to-end-stablecoin-capabilities-will-launch-card-with-okx"/>
        <updated>2025-04-28T16:00:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mastercard's new global system aims to make stablecoin transactions as seamless as traditional payments.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Helene Braun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Enable CORS in Django]]></title>
        <id>680fa40e9096ceb5eeedd90e</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-enable-cors-in-django/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-28T15:51:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you've ever tried to connect your frontend app to your Django backend and suddenly hit an error that looks something like "has been blocked by CORS policy", you're not alone. It’s frustrating, especially when your code seems fine. So what’s going ...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Udemezue John</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Turn Ubuntu 24.04 into a KVM Hypervisor – Quick Setup with Web Management]]></title>
        <id>680fa285102a9fb019d4fa34</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/turn-ubuntu-2404-into-a-kvm-hypervisor/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-28T15:45:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Virtualization lets you run multiple operating systems on one machine. It’s perfect for testing apps, hosting servers, or learning DevOps. A hypervisor is the software that lets you run multiple virtual machines on a single physical machine, and the ...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shamsuddoha Ranju</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Automate Mobile Testing: Strategies for Reliable, Scalable Tests]]></title>
        <id>680fa2440e43e5b002c3c7f4</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-automate-mobile-testing-strategies/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-28T15:44:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mobile test automation uses tools and frameworks to test mobile applications automatically. It replicates user interactions to evaluate the app's functions and detect possible issues early on. This automated approach is helpful since it accelerates t...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nazneen Ahmad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Download: China’s manufacturers’ viral moment, and how AI is changing creativity]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1115909</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/04/28/1115909/the-download-chinas-manufacturers-viral-moment-and-how-ai-is-changing-creativity/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-28T12:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is today’s edition of The Download, our weekday newsletter that provides a daily dose of what’s going on in the world of technology. Why Chinese manufacturers are going viral on TikTok Since the video was posted earlier this month, millions of TikTok users have watched as a young Chinese man in a blue T-shirt sits beside…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rhiannon Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Does RAG make LLMs less safe?  Bloomberg research reveals hidden dangers]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3005592</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/does-rag-make-llms-less-safe-bloomberg-research-reveals-hidden-dangers/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-28T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[RAG is supposed to make enterprise AI more accurate, but it could potentially also make it less safe according to new research.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sean Michael Kerner</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Chinese manufacturers are going viral on TikTok]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1115876</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/04/28/1115876/why-chinese-manufacturers-are-going-viral-on-tiktok/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-28T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Since the video was posted earlier this month, millions of TikTok users have watched as a young Chinese man in a blue T-shirt sits beside a traditional tea set and speaks directly to the camera in accented English: “Let’s expose luxury’s biggest secret.”  He stands and lifts what looks like an Hermès Birkin bag, one…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Caiwei Chen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[UPDATED] Malaysia and Maldives explore new ties in solar, defence, and digital tech [WATCH]]]></title>
        <id>2ff00997f9c35cff9b55bf1c234d9fd9</id>
        <link href="https://www.nst.com.my/news/nation/2025/04/1208426/updated-malaysia-and-maldives-explore-new-ties-solar-defence-and-digital"/>
        <updated>2025-04-28T04:17:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[PUTRAJAYA: Malaysia is eager to explore new avenues of cooperation with the Maldives, including floating solar energy, defence, and digital technology, says Datuk Seri Anwar Ibrahim.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hakim Mahari</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ask HN: What are you working on? (April 2025)]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=43815523</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=43815523"/>
        <updated>2025-04-27T22:08:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Is your AI product actually working? How to develop the right metric system]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3005642</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/is-your-ai-product-actually-working-how-to-develop-the-right-metric-system/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-27T19:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Metrics are critical for determining AI product performance. But where to begin? Here's a framework to apply across various use cases.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sharanya Rao, Intuit</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bits + Bytes: A Miscellany Of Technology]]></title>
        <id>92c9e6ae0de9449f2a2cd9808d52c95a</id>
        <link href="https://theedgemalaysia.com/node/752832"/>
        <updated>2025-04-27T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[NEWS

Malaysia sees tech salary surge in 2025, led by system engineers

Tech salaries in Malaysia have risen significantly this year, with system engineers recording the highest increase at 8%, according to NodeFlair’s Tech Salary Report 2...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Edge Malaysia</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FORKLIFTACTION, B2B news service and business platform about forklifts and materials handling]]></title>
        <id>20065c212264065b824a3328d06be4fc</id>
        <link href="https://www.forkliftaction.com/pagenotfound.aspx"/>
        <updated>2025-04-27T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[FORKLIFTACTION, B2B news service and business platform about forklifts and materials handling]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Forkliftaction</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Running Clojure in WASM with GraalVM]]></title>
        <id>https://romanliutikov.com/blog/running-clojure-in-wasm</id>
        <link href="https://romanliutikov.com/blog/running-clojure-in-wasm"/>
        <updated>2025-04-27T07:50:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DeepSeek’s success shows why motivation is key to AI innovation]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3005636</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/deepseeks-success-shows-why-motivation-is-key-to-ai-innovation/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-26T19:55:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How did DeepSeek attain such cost-savings while American companies could not? Let's dive into the technical details.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Debasish Ray Chawdhuri, Talentica Software</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Malaysia remains 9th largest global exporter of high-tech products]]></title>
        <id>ec83e12fc9489689eba3a736f7c0fd4e</id>
        <link href="https://e.vnexpress.net/news/tech/tech-news/malaysia-remains-9th-largest-global-exporter-of-high-tech-products-4878750.html"/>
        <updated>2025-04-26T02:41:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Malaysia successfully maintained its position as the ninth-largest exporter of high-tech goods out of 143 economies in 2023, the highest recognition it has achieved in the past decade, Bernama has reported.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>VnExpress</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Liquid AI is revolutionizing LLMs to work on edge devices like smartphones with new ‘Hyena Edge’ model]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3005611</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/liquid-ai-is-revolutionizing-llms-to-work-on-edge-devices-like-smartphones-with-new-hyena-edge-model/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-25T22:02:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hyena Edge’s success positions Liquid AI as one of the emerging players to watch in the evolving AI model landscape.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carl Franzen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The new AI calculus: Google’s 80% cost edge vs. OpenAI’s ecosystem]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3005571</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/the-new-ai-calculus-googles-80-cost-edge-vs-openais-ecosystem/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-25T20:26:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Explore the Google vs OpenAI AI ecosystem battle post-o3. Deep dive into Google's huge cost advantage (TPU vs GPU), agent strategies & model risks for enterprise]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matt Marshall</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Create Models in Your Django Project]]></title>
        <id>680be6e3dfe4e9c64b6b0997</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-create-models-in-your-django-project/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-25T19:47:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you're building something with Django, there's one thing you can't skip: creating models. Models are the heart of any Django app. They define how your data is structured, how it's stored in the database, and how Django can interact with it. Now, i...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Udemezue John</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Harden Your Node.js APIs – Security Best Practices]]></title>
        <id>680bb2b3917896a550779bcb</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-harden-your-nodejs-apis-security-best-practices/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-25T16:05:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you’ve built an API with Node.js, chances are you’ve thought about security – at least a little. Maybe you’ve heard about SQL injection, brute force attacks, or data leaks. But here’s the thing: it’s not just about big hacks. Even small gaps in yo...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Manish Shivanandhan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[UK agrees to assist Malaysia in technology, new energy]]></title>
        <id>9bba1ab03b6cc59e6474a313d3bc9d9c</id>
        <link href="https://theedgemalaysia.com/node/753068"/>
        <updated>2025-04-25T15:31:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The UK has agreed to collaborate with Malaysia in various fields, including technology and new energy management, said Deputy Prime Minister Datuk Seri Fadillah Yusof.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Edge Malaysia</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Change Your Django Secret Key (Without Breaking Your App)]]></title>
        <id>680b9ed80564f7c150cbf95b</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-change-your-django-secret-key-without-breaking-your-app/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-25T14:40:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you're working on a Django project, you've probably come across the SECRET_KEY in your settings file. It might seem like just another line of code, but it's one of the most important pieces of your project. SECRET_KEY keeps your app secure by sign...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Udemezue John</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Download: how Trump’s tariffs will affect US manufacturing, and AI architecture]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1115868</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/04/25/1115868/the-download-how-trumps-tariffs-will-affect-us-manufacturing-and-ai-architecture/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-25T12:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is today’s edition of The Download, our weekday newsletter that provides a daily dose of what’s going on in the world of technology. Sweeping tariffs could threaten the US manufacturing rebound Despite the geopolitical chaos and market collapses triggered by President Trump’s announcement of broad tariffs on international goods, some supporters still hope the strategy will…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rhiannon Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Need to embrace technological advancements, sustainable practices discussed at country's premier real estate event]]></title>
        <id>13ba8e804fd9567fa951b4f7cc51bead</id>
        <link href="https://theedgemalaysia.com/node/753073"/>
        <updated>2025-04-25T12:00:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Industry leaders, policymakers, investors and experts explored the future of Malaysia's real estate landscape at the National Real Estate Convention (NREC) 2025 held here recently.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Edge Malaysia</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sweeping tariffs could threaten the US manufacturing rebound]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1115827</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/04/25/1115827/sweeping-tariffs-could-threaten-the-us-manufacturing-rebound/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-25T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Despite the geopolitical chaos and market collapses triggered by President Trump’s announcement of broad tariffs on international goods, some supporters still hope the strategy will produce a “golden age” of American industry. Trump himself insists, “Jobs and factories will come roaring back into our country.” While it’s possible that very targeted tariffs could help protect…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Rotman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Is that really your boss calling? Jericho Security raises $15M to stop deepfake fraud that’s cost businesses $200M in 2025 alone]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3005473</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/is-that-really-your-boss-calling-jericho-security-raises-15m-to-stop-deepfake-fraud-thats-cost-businesses-200m-in-2025-alone/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-24T22:18:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Pentagon-backed Jericho Security raises $15 million to combat deepfake fraud that has already cost North American businesses $200 million in 2025, using AI to detect increasingly convincing voice and video impersonations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Nuñez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Intel’s new CEO signals streamlining efforts but does not spell out exact layoff numbers]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3005456</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/games/intels-new-ceo-signals-streamlining-efforts-but-does-not-spell-out-exact-layoff-numbers/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-24T21:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Lip-Bu Tan, the new CEO of Intel, sent out a blunt message to employees saying the company has to reorganize to be more efficient.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dean Takahashi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Zencoder buys Machinet to challenge GitHub Copilot as AI coding assistant consolidation accelerates]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3005445</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/zencoder-buys-machinet-to-challenge-github-copilot-as-ai-coding-assistant-consolidation-accelerates/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-24T20:36:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Zencoder acquires Machinet to strengthen its position in the rapidly consolidating AI coding assistant market, expanding its JetBrains ecosystem integration while outperforming competitors like GitHub Copilot with innovative features such as Repo Grokking and Coffee Mode.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Nuñez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethically trained AI startup Pleias releases new small reasoning models optimized for RAG with built-in citations]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3005435</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/ethically-trained-ai-startup-pleias-releases-new-small-reasoning-models-optimized-for-rag-with-built-in-citations/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-24T17:03:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Pleias emphasizes the models’ suitability for integration into search-augmented assistants, educational tools, and user support systems.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carl Franzen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Evil Geniuses and Theta Labs launch AI chatbot based on esports mascot Meesh]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3005327</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/games/evil-geniuses-and-theta-labs-launch-ai-chatbot-based-on-esports-mascot-meesh/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-24T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Evil Geniuses, the well-known esports organization and brand, has launched its Meesh AI chatbot in a partnership with Theta Labs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dean Takahashi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Driving business value by optimizing the cloud]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1115716</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/04/24/1115716/driving-business-value-by-optimizing-the-cloud/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-24T13:56:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Organizations are deepening their cloud investments at an unprecedented pace, recognizing its fundamental role in driving business agility and innovation. Synergy Research Group reports that companies spent $84 billion worldwide on cloud infrastructure services in the third quarter of 2024, a 23% rise over the third quarter of 2023 and the fourth consecutive quarter in…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>MIT Technology Review Insights</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Download: Apple’s eucalyptus carbon bet, and climate tech’s bad vibes]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1115809</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/04/24/1115809/the-download-apples-eucalyptus-carbon-bet-and-climate-techs-bad-vibes/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-24T12:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is today’s edition of The Download, our weekday newsletter that provides a daily dose of what’s going on in the world of technology. Inside the controversial tree farms powering Apple’s carbon neutral goal “We were losing the light, and still about 20 kilometers from the main road, when the car shuddered and died at the edge…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rhiannon Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The vibes are shifting for US climate tech]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1115718</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/04/24/1115718/climate-tech-investments-trump/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-24T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The past few years have been an almost nonstop parade of good news for climate tech in the US. Headlines about billion-dollar grants from the government, massive private funding rounds, and labs churning out advance after advance have been routine. Now, though, things are starting to shift.   About $8 billion worth of US climate tech…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Casey Crownhart</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google adds more AI tools to its Workspace productivity apps]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3005313</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/google-adds-more-ai-tools-to-its-workspace-productivity-apps/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-23T22:43:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google expanded Gemini's features, adding the popular podcast-style feature Audio Overviews to the platform.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Emilia David</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Former DeepSeeker and collaborators release new method for training reliable AI agents: RAGEN]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3005302</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/former-deepseeker-and-collaborators-release-new-method-for-training-reliable-ai-agents-ragen/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-23T20:04:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[RAGEN stands out not just as a technical contribution but as a conceptual step toward more autonomous, reasoning-capable AI agents.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carl Franzen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon’s SWE-PolyBench just exposed the dirty secret about your AI coding assistant]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3005166</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/amazon-swe-polybench-just-exposed-the-dirty-secret-about-your-ai-coding-assistant/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-23T19:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon launches SWE-PolyBench, a groundbreaking multi-language benchmark that exposes critical limitations in AI coding assistants across Python, JavaScript, TypeScript, and Java while introducing new metrics beyond simple pass rates for real-world development tasks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Nuñez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OpenAI makes ChatGPT’s image generation available as API]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3005253</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/openai-makes-chatgpts-image-generation-available-as-api/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-23T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Enterprises can now make Studio Ghibli-inspired images through OpenAI's API.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Emilia David</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[From friction to flow: Why Swissport scrapped its VPN maze for Cato’s SASE platform]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3004830</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/security/from-friction-to-flow-why-swissport-scrapped-its-vpn-maze-for-catos-sase-platform/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-23T16:53:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Swissport ditches legacy tech, deploying a global SASE architecture with Cato Networks securing 26,000 users, unlocking real-time control.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Louis Columbus</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft just launched powerful AI ‘agents’ that could completely transform your workday — and challenge Google’s workplace dominance]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3005118</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/microsoft-just-launched-powerful-ai-agents-that-could-completely-transform-your-workday-and-challenge-googles-workplace-dominance/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-23T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft unveils new AI reasoning agents and Copilot features to transform workplace productivity, with Chief Product Officer Aparna Chennapragada sharing exclusive insights on the company's vision for human-agent collaboration.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Nuñez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cooperations with China continue to drive Malaysia's tech ambitions: experts]]></title>
        <id>7cf31983f27357e33a7e7403d769042c</id>
        <link href="https://english.news.cn/20250423/23952d602d384abe9a3be2f40797fa2d/c.html"/>
        <updated>2025-04-23T09:33:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cooperations with China continue to drive Malaysia's tech ambitions: experts-]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>english.news.cn</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[IBM Tech Innovation Summit]]></title>
        <id>eb7b875c351e513c2d4750bb29a0ab40</id>
        <link href="https://www.malaysiakini.com/news/741130"/>
        <updated>2025-04-23T02:44:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Seats are limited. Register now!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Malaysiakini Team</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[$42.1 million poured into startup offering energy-efficient solutions for costly and unwieldy operational data and AI workloads]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3005163</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/data-infrastructure/42-1-million-poured-into-startup-offering-energy-efficient-solutions-for-costly-and-unwieldy-operational-data-and-ai-workloads/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-23T02:28:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The funding infusion sharpens a mission to make hyperscale analytics radically cheaper and greener at the very moment enterprises fear ballooning data‑center power bills.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ujas Patel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[More accurate coding: Researchers adapt Sequential Monte Carlo for AI-generated code]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3005146</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/more-accurate-coding-researchers-adapt-sequential-monte-carlo-for-ai-generated-code/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-23T00:09:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Researchers from MIT, Yale, McGill University and others found that adapting the Sequential Monte Carlo algorithm can make AI-generated code better.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Emilia David</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SWiRL: The business case for AI that thinks like your best problem-solvers]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3004781</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/swirl-the-business-case-for-ai-that-thinks-like-your-best-problem-solvers/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-22T23:53:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Training LLMs on trajectories of reasoning and tool use makes them superior at multi-step reasoning tasks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ben Dickson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Batch data processing is too slow for real-time AI: How open-source Apache Airflow 3.0 solves the challenge with event-driven data orchestration]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3004953</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/data-infrastructure/open-source-airflow-3-0-set-to-accelerate-data-orchestration-for-enterprise-ai-inference/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-22T20:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Open-source data orchestration gets a major rewrite to help support inference and enterprise AI]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sean Michael Kerner</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A new, open source text-to-speech model called Dia has arrived to challenge ElevenLabs, OpenAI and more]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3005094</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/a-new-open-source-text-to-speech-model-called-dia-has-arrived-to-challenge-elevenlabs-openai-and-more/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-22T17:48:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With a focus on expressive quality, reproducibility, and open access, Dia adds a distinctive new voice to the landscape of text-to-speech.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carl Franzen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Relyance AI builds ‘x-ray vision’ for company data: Cuts AI compliance time by 80% while solving trust crisis]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3004971</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/relyance-ai-builds-x-ray-vision-for-company-data-cuts-ai-compliance-time-by-80-while-solving-trust-crisis/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-22T13:01:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Relyance AI's new Data Journeys platform gives enterprises unprecedented visibility into data flows, reducing AI compliance time by 80% while helping organizations build trustworthy artificial intelligence systems in an increasingly regulated landscape.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Nuñez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[eSelf will bring private AI tutors to students worldwide]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3004917</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/games/eself-will-bring-private-ai-tutors-to-students-worldwide/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-22T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[eSelf, a startup that focuses on conversational AI agents, is partnering an educational group to bring private AI tutors to students.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dean Takahashi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Retail & E-Commerce Innovation Marketing & Tech Summit: Malaysia 2025]]></title>
        <id>cd2a0d19be53d9723fc0475f09d0da2d</id>
        <link href="https://marketech-apac.com/conference/retail-e-commerce-innovation-marketing-tech-summit-malaysia-2025/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-22T07:49:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Retail & E-Commerce Innovation Marketing & Tech Summit: Malaysia 2025]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Zyra Kate Capilastique</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use QuickNode Yellowstone and Carbon to Decode and Process Solana Updates]]></title>
        <id>67fd580d307774000181b292</id>
        <link href="https://blog.quicknode.com/how-to-use-quicknode-yellowstone-and-carbon-to-decode-and-process-solana-updates/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-15T14:17:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn how to integrate QuickNode’s Yellowstone gRPC Geyser Add-on with Carbon to enhance Solana blockchain data indexing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Laurence Vandeyar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>