<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2025-05-15T15:44:02.212Z</id>
    <title>AngJianming RSS Feed</title>
    <updated>2025-05-15T15:44:02.212Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Day 22/ 30 Days of Linux Mastery: 'gzip' Command]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/amandaigwe/day-22-30-days-of-linux-mastery-gzip-command-1ji6</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/amandaigwe/day-22-30-days-of-linux-mastery-gzip-command-1ji6"/>
        <updated>2025-05-15T15:33:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Table of Contents



Introduction
What is the gzip Command?
Core gzip Commands
Real-World Scenario: gzip Command
Conclusion
Let's Connect

Welcome back to Day 22 of this practical Linux challenge! Today, we are diving into one of the most useful Linux commands: gzip.
When you think of compressing any file, think of gzip

gzip Command?


gzip stands for GNU zip, a tool used to compress files, making them smaller and easier to store or transfer.

gzip Commands


More commonly used gzip command options are listed in the table below.




gzip Command
Description




gzip filename
Compress the file (creates filename.gz)


gunzip filename.gz
Decompress .gz file back to original


gzip -k filename
Compress file and keep original



gzip -r folder/
Recursively compress all files in a folder


gzip -d filename.gz
Same as gunzip, decompress file


gzip -v filename
Verbose mode – shows compression info



Worthy to note that this command works only for files, not folders.

gzip Command



Select a file you wish to compress. Compress using the gzip command. It ends with .gz




gzip demologs.txt

ls -lh   # to confirm it compressed


Now you have seen how it works, let's decompress that .gz file back to the original format.




gunzip demologs.txt.gz 


If you notice when we compressed, it did not keep the original file. Now, let's keep the original file and the compressed file.




gzip -k demologs.txt

ls -lh   # to confirm both the original and compressed file are there



Learning gzip might seem simple, but it is a crucial skill in Linux.
Mastering it helps you maintain lean storage and improve transfer speeds.
If this is helpful to you, feel free to bookmark, comment, like and follow me for Day 23!

If you want to connect or share your journey, feel free to reach out on LinkedIn. 
#30DaysLinuxChallenge #Redhat#RHCSA #RHCE #CloudWhistler #Linux #Rhel #Ansible #Vim #CloudComputing #DevOps #LinuxAutomation #IaC #SysAdmin#CloudEngineer]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amanda Igwe</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[React Native 0.79+ New Architecture: Bridging with Android Native Modules]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/amitkumar13/react-native-079-new-architecture-bridging-with-android-native-modules-11ih</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/amitkumar13/react-native-079-new-architecture-bridging-with-android-native-modules-11ih"/>
        <updated>2025-05-15T15:33:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[React Native is a powerful framework that enables developers to build mobile apps using JavaScript and React. But what happens when you need to interact with platform-specific code, like accessing native Android features? That’s where Native Modules come into play.
In this blog post, we’ll walk through a simple yet effective example of creating a native module in Android and bridging it with React Native. We’ll:
Call a native method from React Native to get a message
Send data from React Native to the Android side
Create a Kotlin class called HelloWorldModule.kt inside android/app/src/main/java/com/nativebridging/HelloWorldModule.kt:
package com.nativebridging

import android.util.Log
import com.facebook.react.bridge.ReactApplicationContext
import com.facebook.react.bridge.ReactContextBase…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amit Kumar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Indie Stack: Building Client Systems That Scale Without People]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/codanyks/the-indie-stack-building-client-systems-that-scale-without-people-cf5</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/codanyks/the-indie-stack-building-client-systems-that-scale-without-people-cf5"/>
        <updated>2025-05-15T15:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA["The most powerful tools are the ones that disappear into your flow".
Most solo founders don't burn out from work.
operational chaos.
Endless back-and-forths. Missed follow-ups. Payment delays. Confused clients.
their business runs on memory instead of systems.
This article is not about tools.
processes you can shape to make your solo business feel like it runs itself.
Tools are just clay. What matters is the mold.
Every solo creator needs to flip their mental model:
What tool do I use for X?" ask "What needs to happen every time a client comes in?"



Trigger
Outcome




A lead fills out your inquiry
You know whether they’re a fit


A client says yes
They get an onboarding package automatically


A payment is confirmed
You're notified and the project is queued


A project is delivered
A f…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Codanyks</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Forecasting the Dollar rate with Python]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/josethz00/-2mej</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/josethz00/-2mej"/>
        <updated>2025-05-15T15:29:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Why is it so hard to forecast the Dollar rate? An attempt with Python
José Thomaz ・ May 15
#datascience
        #economics
        #math
        #python]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>José Thomaz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Free Open Dataset MultiScene360: Unlocking Next-Gen Character Generation]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/rita_ho_d399c28be9d8a25a3/unlocking-next-gen-character-generation-with-multiscene360-the-game-changing-multi-camera-dataset-18ed</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/rita_ho_d399c28be9d8a25a3/unlocking-next-gen-character-generation-with-multiscene360-the-game-changing-multi-camera-dataset-18ed"/>
        <updated>2025-05-15T15:29:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Why Multi-Camera Datasets Matter for AI-Generated Characters


The quest for hyper-realistic AI-generated movie characters just took a quantum leap forward with our newly released MultiScene360 Dataset - a groundbreaking multi-camera video dataset specifically designed for generative vision AI.
Unlike conventional single-view datasets, this real-world synchronized multi-view footage provides the spatial and temporal consistency essential for:
Persistent 3D character generation across different angles
Consistent facial expressions and movements during viewpoint transitions
Realistic occlusion handling in dynamic scenes
Natural lighting consistency across multiple viewpoints
As highlighted in this seminal paper on reconstruction from multi-camera arrays, synchronized multi-view capture provi…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rita Ho</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[🤖 Google Dorking for Job Hunting: Automate the Hunt & Real-World Results (Part 3)]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/nish2005karsh/google-dorking-for-job-hunting-automate-the-hunt-real-world-results-part-3-2nbh</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/nish2005karsh/google-dorking-for-job-hunting-automate-the-hunt-real-world-results-part-3-2nbh"/>
        <updated>2025-05-15T15:27:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[💡 You’ve learned how to craft powerful dorks. Now it’s time to automate the grind and start collecting real job leads like a pro.
⚡ What This Post Covers
🔎 Real-World Dorking: Success Stories
site:angel.co intitle:"we are hiring" filetype:pdf

→ Revealed a hidden remote developer PDF job description.
🏛️ Example 2: Internship Sheet on University Site
site:.edu intitle:"internship opportunities" filetype:xls

→ Found an Excel sheet listing 50+ internship roles.
📬 Automate With Google Alerts
Google Alerts
site:github.com intitle:"hiring" filetype:pdf

Set how often you want updates (daily/weekly).
🐍 Automate Dorking with Python (Public URLs Only)
⚠️ This script scrapes public Google Search results. Avoid scraping Google aggressively — always respect rate limits and terms.
import requests…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nishkarsh Pandey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Wavelet Trees: An Introduction (2011)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.alexbowe.com/wavelet-trees/</id>
        <link href="https://www.alexbowe.com/wavelet-trees/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-15T15:27:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Axios vs Fetch: A Practical Guide to Error Handling, Interceptors & Retry Strategies]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/crit3cal/axios-vs-fetch-a-practical-guide-to-error-handling-interceptors-retry-strategies-2f1i</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/crit3cal/axios-vs-fetch-a-practical-guide-to-error-handling-interceptors-retry-strategies-2f1i"/>
        <updated>2025-05-15T15:26:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Summary:
Both fetch and axios are used to make HTTP requests in JavaScript. While fetch is native and minimal, axios comes loaded with features. But when building production-grade applications, especially SPAs or SSR frameworks like Next.js, these differences matter — a lot.
✅ Fetch
fetch('/api/data')
  .then(response => {
    if (!response.ok) {
      throw new Error(`HTTP error! status: ${response.status}`);
    }
    return response.json();
  })
  .then(data => console.log(data))
  .catch(error => console.error('Fetch error:', error));


Fetch does not throw on HTTP errors (like 404 or 500).
You must manually check response.ok or status codes.
✅ Axios
axios.get('/api/data')
  .then(response => console.log(response.data))
  .catch(error => {
    if (error.response) {
      // Server resp…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sarvesh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[Boost]]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/gnrlbzik/-35m1</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/gnrlbzik/-35m1"/>
        <updated>2025-05-15T15:24:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Writing Clean, Secure Node.js APIs – A Checklist You’ll Actually Use ✅
Ali Samir ・ Apr 26
#node
        #javascript
        #api
        #webdev]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alesei N</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[De MediatR para Mediator: uma migração mais leve e performática]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/lepton_tech/de-mediatr-para-mediator-uma-migracao-mais-leve-e-performatica-12g6</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/lepton_tech/de-mediatr-para-mediator-uma-migracao-mais-leve-e-performatica-12g6"/>
        <updated>2025-05-15T15:16:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[*Dando continuidade à série sobre bibliotecas .NET que deixaram de ser open source e gratuitas, neste artigo apresento uma alternativa ao MediatR e explico por que ela pode representar uma migração mais leve em termos de estrutura e performance.
Desde que foi anunciado que o MediatR passará a adotar um modelo de licenciamento pago — mesmo que isso ainda leve algum tempo e a versão atual permaneça gratuita — nós, desenvolvedores, começamos a buscar alternativas próximas do que já conhecemos ou, em alguns casos, optamos por implementações próprias, como abordado no artigo anterior sobre o AutoMapper.
Tendo isso em mente, encontrei uma alternativa — especialmente adequada para projetos que precisam ser migrados e para equipes já familiarizadas com o MediatR — que é o Mediator (com “o”). Assim…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lenerson Velho Nunes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Generate Large Random Numbers in C with rand()?]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/generatecodedev/how-to-generate-large-random-numbers-in-c-with-rand-5731</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/generatecodedev/how-to-generate-large-random-numbers-in-c-with-rand-5731"/>
        <updated>2025-05-15T15:15:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Generating large random numbers is a common requirement in programming, especially in applications requiring strong randomness. The standard rand() function in C generates pseudo-random numbers, which often fall short in range and size for many applications. In particular, generating unsigned long long random numbers can be challenging, especially if you find that the outputs of rand() are not sufficiently large and they often exceed certain thresholds.
Why the Standard rand() Does Not Meet Your Needs
The rand() function is designed for simplicity and it typically returns a value in the range from 0 to RAND_MAX, which is defined in stdlib.h. The maximum value returned by rand() is often just 32767, making it unsuitable for generating large random numbers like those represented by an unsign…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Generatecode</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[🎯 Google Dorking for Job Hunting: Advanced Tricks & Commands (Part 2)]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/nish2005karsh/google-dorking-for-job-hunting-advanced-tricks-commands-part-2-oeo</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/nish2005karsh/google-dorking-for-job-hunting-advanced-tricks-commands-part-2-oeo"/>
        <updated>2025-05-15T15:12:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[💡 In Part 1, we scratched the surface of Google Dorking to find hidden job opportunities. Now, it’s time to level up and unlock some real gems using advanced combinations.
🔍 Why Go Advanced?
Filter outdated listings.
⚙️ Advanced Operators + Combos
🔹 1. Find Job Descriptions in PDFs from Company Sites
site:example.com intitle:"careers" filetype:pdf

Replace example.com with a real company, e.g.:
site:accenture.com intitle:"careers" filetype:pdf

🔹 2. Target Job Boards with Specific Roles
site:glassdoor.com inurl:"jobs" intitle:"frontend developer"

🔹 3. Find Remote Tech Roles from Startup Platforms
site:angel.co intitle:"remote developer" filetype:pdf

🔹 4. Internships on University Sites
site:.edu intitle:"summer internship" filetype:pdf

🔹 5. Unlisted Job Postings in Excel Format
filetype:xls inurl:"vacancy" OR inurl:"openings"

🔹 6. Marketing Jobs in NGOs
site:.org intitle:"we are hiring" "digital marketing"

🔹 7. Get Around Login Barriers
site:myjobportal.com inurl:"/public/jobs" "software engineer"

🔹 8. Government Job Listings
site:.gov intitle:"job opening" filetype:pdf

🛡️ Pro Tip: Add Date Filters
🧠 How to Build Your Own Dorks
Mix and match these like Lego bricks:
site: → Limit the domain
intitle: → Job-related words like “careers,” “job openings,” “we’re hiring”
filetype: → Use pdf, docx, or xls
" "→ Exact match phrases like "remote UI developer"
AND / OR→ Combine or expand searches
Screenshots of some dorks:


🧪 Bonus: Ready-to-Use Dork Templates
filetype:pdf intitle:"remote job"                 |
site:internshala.com intitle:"internship program" |
filetype:xls inurl:"openings"                     |
intitle:"entry level developer" site:linkedin.com |
site:.org "we are hiring" filetype:docx           |
🔚 Up Next: Part 3 – Automation & Real-World Case Study
🗣️ Your Turn
What industry are you targeting? Drop a comment and I’ll share dorks tailored to your field.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nishkarsh Pandey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Best Confluence Alternatives that I Like]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/naomiclarkson2/best-confluence-alternatives-that-i-like-2ilo</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/naomiclarkson2/best-confluence-alternatives-that-i-like-2ilo"/>
        <updated>2025-05-15T15:12:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In today's collaborative work environment, documentation platforms have become essential for teams to share knowledge, manage projects, and maintain organizational information. Atlassian's Confluence has long been a popular choice, but many organizations are searching for alternatives due to pricing concerns, feature limitations, or specific use case requirements.
Whether you're looking for better API documentation capabilities, more intuitive interfaces, or cost-effective solutions, this comprehensive guide explores the top 10 alternatives to Confluence that might better suit your team's needs.

Apidog stands out as the premier Confluence alternative, particularly for development teams working with APIs. This powerful platform combines API documentation, design, testing, and collaboration…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Naomi Clarkson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[0x Acquires Competitor Flood in Push to Boost Share of $2.3B DEX Aggregator Market]]></title>
        <id>6448bb1f-b222-4336-8806-d1fed49411d0</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2025/05/15/0x-acquires-competitor-flood-in-push-to-boost-share-of-usd2-3b-defi-aggregator-market"/>
        <updated>2025-05-15T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The acquisition is 0x’s first since the firm’s founding in 2017.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tim Craig</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto for Advisors: Stablecoins Explained]]></title>
        <id>f9ee2937-887a-4708-addf-8f3c05dc053d</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/coindesk-indices/2025/05/14/crypto-for-advisors-stablecoins-explained"/>
        <updated>2025-05-15T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Stablecoins — a tokenized representation of money on-chain that’s taking over traditional financial rails and underpinning crypto trades.  Read about where they started and where they are going.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Harvey Li</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The AI revolution won’t be centralized — Superior agents are coming for Big Tech’s crown]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/superior-agents-big-tech</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/superior-agents-big-tech?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-15T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Opinion by: Jennifer Dodgson, co-founder of KIP Protocol and Eigenform AI
The puppet show is ending.
The Brookings Institution found that generative artificial intelligence may disrupt at least 50% of tasks performed by more than 30% of all workers. The same study also estimates that genAI may affect at least 10% of tasks performed by approximately 85% of the human workforce. The TL;DR from these stats? AI’s effects are likely to be both broad and deep.
If AI doesn’t already scare you, self-learning AI agents that autonomously achieve goals may fix that. Forget your sanitized ChatGPT conversations and bland AI assistants. Superior agents are AI that autonomously achieve human-set objectives by any means necessary. While OpenAI’s valuation of $300 billion benefits the few rather than the ma…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Jennifer Dodgson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Shiba Inu (SHIB) Price Drops 7% in 24 Hours but Remains Up 25% Over the Past Month]]></title>
        <id>04dfd4dc-ae42-4986-9523-5e8926328eec</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/15/shiba-inu-shib-price-drops-7-in-24-hours-but-remains-up-25-over-the-last-month"/>
        <updated>2025-05-15T14:58:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Meme token faces significant downward pressure amid shifting economic conditions despite positive developments in US-China trade relations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>AI Boost</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What the 10-year Treasury yield means for crypto yields and stablecoins]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/explained/what-the-10-year-treasury-yield-means-for-crypto-yields-and-stablecoins</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/explained/what-the-10-year-treasury-yield-means-for-crypto-yields-and-stablecoins?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-15T14:50:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Understanding the 10-year Treasury yield: Definition and  importance            
            
                
The 10-year Treasury yield is the interest rate that the US government pays to borrow money for 10 years.
When the government needs cash, it issues bonds called Treasury notes, and the 10-year note is one of the most watched. The “yield” is the annual return you’d get if you bought that bond and held it until it matures. It’s expressed as a percentage, like 4% or 5%.
Think of it as the government saying, “Hey, lend me $1,000, and I’ll pay you back in 10 years with some interest.” That interest rate and the yield move up or down based on demand for the bonds, inflation expectations and the overall economy. Because US Treasurys are considered safe (the government isn’t likely to def…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Onkar Singh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase Canada CEO Urges Mark Carney Government to Move Fast on National Crypto Strategy]]></title>
        <id>a43749d8-6d18-4af0-83b7-da75b142dd0d</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/consensus-toronto-2025-coverage/2025/05/15/coinbase-canada-ceo-urges-mark-carney-s-government-to-move-fast-on-national-crypto-strategy"/>
        <updated>2025-05-15T14:27:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Lucas Matheson said Canada risks falling behind as other nations actively shape crypto policies.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Aoyon Ashraf</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Movement Labs Secretly Promised Advisers Millions in Tokens, Leaked Documents Show]]></title>
        <id>b672f2bf-904b-4556-9768-7f24241822f8</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/tech/2025/05/15/movement-labs-secretly-promised-advisers-millions-in-tokens-leaked-documents-show"/>
        <updated>2025-05-15T14:24:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Signed memos reveal that Movement Labs, a Trump-backed crypto startup, offered up to 10% of its token supply to shadow advisers through undisclosed agreements.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sam Kessler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin, Strategy Confirm Concurrent Bull Cross, Strengthening Uptrend Signal: Technical Analysis]]></title>
        <id>26d76f3a-ec5d-4d48-b033-ec2f2b0870fe</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/15/bitcoin-strategy-confirm-concurrent-bull-cross-strengthening-uptrend-signal-technical-analysis"/>
        <updated>2025-05-15T14:17:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin and MSTR both flashed a bullish signal, indicating a potential major uptrend.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Omkar Godbole</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Wintermute opens New York office, citing improved US crypto rules]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/wintermute-new-york-office-improved-us-crypto-regulations</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/wintermute-new-york-office-improved-us-crypto-regulations?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-15T14:15:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Wintermute, a London-based algorithmic crypto trading and market-making firm, has opened an office in New York as part of its expansion into the US.
Wintermute announced the opening of its New York office on May 15, citing improved regulatory conditions in the world’s largest economy.
“As the US takes a friendlier stance on digital assets and institutional adoption accelerates, we moved quickly to establish roots in New York City,” the company wrote in a May 15 X post, adding that the local presence will help them in “contributing to the future regulatory framework.”
Source: Wintermute
“We’re eager to continue our growth and play an integral role in the U.S. market,” according to Evgeny Gaevoy, CEO of Wintermute. “As a neutral player with deep expertise in all areas of digital assets, we b…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Zoltan Vardai</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[California sent residents' personal health data to LinkedIn]]></title>
        <id>https://themarkup.org/pixel-hunt/2025/04/28/how-california-sent-residents-personal-health-data-to-linkedin</id>
        <link href="https://themarkup.org/pixel-hunt/2025/04/28/how-california-sent-residents-personal-health-data-to-linkedin"/>
        <updated>2025-05-15T14:13:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tether blacklist delay allowed $78M in illicit USDT transfers: Report]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/tether-blacklist-delay-allowed-78-million-usdt-move</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/tether-blacklist-delay-allowed-78-million-usdt-move?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-15T14:02:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Update (May 15 at 3:10 pm UTC): This article has been updated to include comments from Tether. 
A lag in Tether’s wallet blacklisting process allowed over $78 million in illicit funds to be moved before enforcement actions took effect, according to a new report from blockchain compliance company AMLBot.  
Tether’s address blacklisting becomes effective only after a considerable delay from when the process is initiated on Ethereum and Tron, according the report published May 15.
“This delay originates from Tether’s multisignature contract setup on both Tron and Ethereum, transforming what should be an immediate compliance action into a window of opportunity for illicit actors,“ the report reads.
Tether’s blacklisting procedure is a multi-step process with a first transaction effectively war…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Adrian Zmudzinski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin mining 2025: Post-halving profitability, hashrate and energy trends]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-mining-2025-post-halving-profitability-hashrate-and-energy-trends</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-mining-2025-post-halving-profitability-hashrate-and-energy-trends?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-15T13:59:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After the 2024 halving, Bitcoin mining entered its fifth epoch and block rewards were reduced from 6.25 BTC to 3.125 BTC. This forced miners to rethink their operations, optimize efficiency, cut energy costs and upgrade hardware to remain profitable. Cointelegraph Research, with insights from industry experts at Uminers, examines this transformation in its latest report. The analysis covers ASIC efficiency improvements, corporate performance, geographical expansion and new revenue models. As miners adapt, Bitcoin moves into a new era where institutional momentum and sovereign adoption could redefine its role in the global financial system.
Download the full report to uncover how miners are navigating this shift and what the future holds for Bitcoin’s mining industry.
The mining industry’s …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Kyrian Alex</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How we made billing backendless]]></title>
        <id>https://useautumn.com/blog/backendless</id>
        <link href="https://useautumn.com/blog/backendless"/>
        <updated>2025-05-15T13:54:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Tiny Boltzmann Machine]]></title>
        <id>https://eoinmurray.info/boltzmann-machine</id>
        <link href="https://eoinmurray.info/boltzmann-machine"/>
        <updated>2025-05-15T13:41:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tron’s USDT supply to surpass Ethereum’s with new $1B mint]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/tether-1b-usdt-tron-authorized-supply-surpasses-ethereum</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/tether-1b-usdt-tron-authorized-supply-surpasses-ethereum?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-15T13:40:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Stablecoin issuer Tether minted another 1 billion USDt tokens on Tron, pushing the network’s authorized USDT supply to surpass Ethereum’s.
On May 15, blockchain data showed that Tether’s treasury minted $1 billion of its dollar-pegged stablecoin, USDt (USDT), into the Tron network. 
As of May 14, Tether’s stablecoin transparency page shows that Tron’s authorized USDT totals $73.7 billion, while Ethereum has $74.5 billion in authorized USDT tokens. If the newly minted tokens are added to the number of authorized USDT assets, Tron’s supply surpasses Ethereum’s. 
In terms of circulating supply, Tron also has the lead with $73.6 billion USDT on the network, while Ethereum only has $71.8 billion. 
Source: PeckShieldAlert
Tether’s USDT mints replenish the company’s token inventory
Tether CEO Pao…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Ezra Reguerra</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Show HN: Min.js style compression of tech docs for LLM context]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/marv1nnnnn/llm-min.txt</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/marv1nnnnn/llm-min.txt"/>
        <updated>2025-05-15T13:40:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tariff doubts push NFL, NBA to bet big on digital merch]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/tariff-doubts-nfl-nba-bet-big-digital-merch</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/tariff-doubts-nfl-nba-bet-big-digital-merch?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-15T13:38:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As more and more businesses are impacted by tariff volatility, some executives, like Ridhima Kahn, vice president of business development at Dapper Labs, are viewing the assault on the cost of physical goods as another use case for digital markets powered by blockchain to shine.
“I’m seeing a lot of brands rethinking where revenue and fan engagement come from,” Kahn said during an exclusive interview with Cointelegraph. “A lot of franchises, like the ones we work with — NBA, NFL, Disney — have already had years of success with digital collection, and we’re seeing a lot of brands express interest in digital collectibles as a way to engage with fan bases at a time when physical costs are riskier and unknown.”
Propelling brands to take a deeper look at digital merch is the desire to better un…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Stephen Laddin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Season 2: Why the next wave of Bitcoin innovation is all about utility]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-season-2-why-the-next-wave-of-bitcoin-innovation-is-all-about-utility</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-season-2-why-the-next-wave-of-bitcoin-innovation-is-all-about-utility?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-15T13:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin’s (BTC) next evolution isn’t just about price. It’s about potential. 
On this week’s episode of The Clear Crypto Podcast, hosts Nathan Jeffay and Gareth Jenkinson sit down with Isabel Foxen Duke, general partner at Unbroken Chain and longtime Bitcoin advocate, to unpack what she calls “Bitcoin Season 2.”

Bitcoin beyond money
“Bitcoin Season 2 is really about seeing what we can do with Bitcoin outside of just being money,” said Duke. 
“What are the broad range of financial use cases for [Bitcoin] other than just being money by itself?”
New developments like ordinals, runes, and decentralized financial (DeFi) tools are pushing Bitcoin beyond its traditional identity as a digital store of value. 
One key innovation under discussion is trustless lending — allowing users to borrow agai…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Savannah Fortis</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Show HN: Real-Time Gaussian Splatting]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/axbycc/LiveSplat</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/axbycc/LiveSplat"/>
        <updated>2025-05-15T13:26:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CoinDesk 20 Performance Update: NEAR Drops 5.7% as Index Trades Lower From Wednesday]]></title>
        <id>b91efacf-f812-4072-b2eb-a4627aa8a7aa</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/coindesk-indices/2025/05/15/coindesk-20-performance-update-near-drops-5-7-as-index-trades-lower-from-wednesday"/>
        <updated>2025-05-15T13:23:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Polygon (POL) joined NEAR Protocol (NEAR) as an underperformer, falling 5.6%.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CoinDesk Indices</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Forget IPs: using cryptography to verify bot and agent traffic]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.cloudflare.com/web-bot-auth/</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/web-bot-auth/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-15T13:22:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Malicious compliance by booking an available meeting room]]></title>
        <id>https://www.clientserver.dev/p/malicious-compliance-by-booking-an</id>
        <link href="https://www.clientserver.dev/p/malicious-compliance-by-booking-an"/>
        <updated>2025-05-15T13:20:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[6 signs predicting $140K as Bitcoin&#039;s next price top]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/6-signs-suggesting-140k-next-bitcoin-price-top</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/6-signs-suggesting-140k-next-bitcoin-price-top?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-15T13:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Key takeaways:

Bitcoin’s price is retracing, but strong ETF inflows, high network activity and whale accumulation suggest BTC is on track to $140,000.

Spot Bitcoin ETFs saw $2.9 billion in net inflows in two weeks, mirroring past rallies.

Declining exchange balances and a rising transaction volume Z-score suggest increasing overall demand.

Bitcoin (BTC) price was down 1.4% over the last 24 hours. It traded 6% below its all-time high of $109,000, reached on Jan. 20. Nevertheless, several fundamental, onchain and technical metrics suggest that Bitcoin’s upside is not over.
Spot Bitcoin ETF inflows mirror past BTC rallies
Bitcoin’s latest recovery was accompanied by strong investor appetite for spot Bitcoin exchange-traded funds (ETFs), which recorded $2.9 billion in net inflows over the …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Nancy Lubale</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[My Engineering Craft Regressed]]></title>
        <id>https://lemmy.ml/post/30100312</id>
        <link href="https://lemmy.ml/post/30100312"/>
        <updated>2025-05-15T13:07:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Here’s what happened in crypto today]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/what-happened-in-crypto-today</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/what-happened-in-crypto-today?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-15T13:03:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today in crypto, Coinbase rejected a $20 million ransom demand after insiders leaked user data in a phishing scheme, but the exchange could face a bill of up to $400 million. Huione Guarantee, suspected as the world’s largest darknet marketplace, has shut down, citing a Telegram account purge that decimated its network, and US Commodity Futures Trading Commission (CFTC) commissioner Summer Mersinger is set to become the next CEO of the crypto advocacy group Blockchain Association.
Coinbase faces $400 million bill after insider phishing attack
Coinbase, the world’s third-largest cryptocurrency exchange, was hit by a $20 million extortion attempt after cybercriminals recruited overseas support agents to leak user data, the company said.
According to a May 15 blog post, Coinbase said a group …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Cointelegraph</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MoonPay Mastercard Launch Crypto Card, Allowing Users to Make Merchant Payments With Stablecoins]]></title>
        <id>e77ce301-6b6f-4031-9900-cc72d297de62</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/15/moonpay-users-can-now-make-stablecoins-to-make-payments-with-mastercard-partnership"/>
        <updated>2025-05-15T13:00:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The partnership is set to allow crypto wallets to issue virtual Mastercards, expanding access to real-world stablecoin payments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Francisco Rodrigues</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[You.com’s ARI Enterprise crushes OpenAI in head-to-head tests, aims at deep research market]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3007729</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/you-coms-ari-enterprise-crushes-openai-in-head-to-head-tests-aims-at-deep-research-market/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-15T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You.com launches ARI Enterprise, an AI research platform that outperforms OpenAI in 76% of head-to-head tests and integrates with enterprise data sources to transform business intelligence with 400+ source analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Nuñez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[a16z Crypto Leads $7M Round in KYD Labs That Aims to Transform Ticketing Industry]]></title>
        <id>69543907-0dbb-4d9e-95bd-d68875fa0a35</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/consensus-toronto-2025-coverage/2025/05/15/a16z-crypto-leads-usd7m-round-in-kyd-labs-that-aims-to-transform-ticketing-industry"/>
        <updated>2025-05-15T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[KYD Labs aims to put artists and venues in control, with blockchain-based ticketing boosting sales by 30%.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Aoyon Ashraf</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Backed Token YBTC Comes to Sui as Bitlayer Integrates Its BitVM Bridge to Sui Network]]></title>
        <id>b284f4ca-a8cf-4aed-ab00-db04e658ba11</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/15/bitcoin-backed-token-ybtc-comes-to-sui-as-bitlayer-integrates-its-bitvm-bridge-to-sui-network"/>
        <updated>2025-05-15T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Peg-BTC (YBTC), the bridged version of BTC, can be deployed in the SUI-based DeFi to generate yield.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Omkar Godbole</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bahrain-based AlAbraaj Restaurants adopts Bitcoin treasury strategy]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/alabraaj-bitcoin-treasury-strategy-middle-east</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/alabraaj-bitcoin-treasury-strategy-middle-east?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-15T12:51:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A Bahrain-based, listed catering company with a $24.2 million market cap has adopted a Bitcoin treasury strategy in partnership with investment firm 10X Capital.
According to a May 15 announcement, AlAbraaj Restaurants Group partnered with 10X Capital to adopt a Bitcoin (BTC) treasury strategy similar to top corporate BTC holder Strategy (previously known as MicroStrategy). The firm also aims to explore Sharia-compliant access to Bitcoin for the Islamic world.
“Our initiative to become a Bitcoin treasury company reflects our forward-looking approach and our commitment to enhancing shareholder value,” said Abdullah Isa, head of AlAbraaj’s Bitcoin Treasury Committee.
Isa added that the company believes “Bitcoin will play a central role in the future of finance.” He cited Strategy’s legacy as…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Adrian Zmudzinski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pathfinding]]></title>
        <id>https://juhrjuhr.itch.io/deep-space-exploitation/devlog/945428/9-pathfinding</id>
        <link href="https://juhrjuhr.itch.io/deep-space-exploitation/devlog/945428/9-pathfinding"/>
        <updated>2025-05-15T12:32:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Metaplanet’s Leverages Its Bitcoin Stash of Over 5K BTC to Generate Record Profit of $4M]]></title>
        <id>1105e7f8-df02-410b-8c31-06645127aa49</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/15/metaplanets-leverages-its-bitcoin-stash-of-over-5k-btc-to-generate-record-profit-of-4m"/>
        <updated>2025-05-15T12:26:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The company’s aggressive bitcoin accumulation has made it the 11th-largest public company by bitcoin holdings globally]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Francisco Rodrigues</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Key Reasons Monero Surge Continues Even as Bitcoin Bulls Take a Breather]]></title>
        <id>bee29c04-d229-4c6b-975f-5bdc3d877ac7</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/15/key-reasons-monero-xmr-price-rally-continues-even-as-bitcoin-btc-takes-bull-breather"/>
        <updated>2025-05-15T12:25:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[XMR has rallied over 100% since the early April panic selling.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Omkar Godbole</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin to $1M by 2028 as Hayes tells Europe to ’get your money out’]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/arthur-hayes-btc-1m-by-2028-europe-get-money-out</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/arthur-hayes-btc-1m-by-2028-europe-get-money-out?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-15T12:21:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Key points:

US Treasurys and foreign capital “repatriation” make a recipe for $1 million BTC, says Arthur Hayes.

Europeans face tightening capital controls, inviting a recommendation to take back control of personal funds.

Seven-figure BTC price targets are already gaining traction.

Bitcoin (BTC) will shoot to $1 million in just three years, thanks to global macroeconomic shifts, Arthur Hayes forecasts.
In his latest blog post released on May 15, the former CEO of crypto exchange BitMEX doubled down on his sky-high BTC price prediction.
Hayes: $1 million Bitcoin due “between now and 2028”
Bitcoin has two strong tailwinds that will help propel it to seven digits in a few years.
For Hayes, shifting capital controls worldwide and US Treasury “devaluation” means that Bitcoin will become th…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by William Suberg</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Capital Creeps Back Into Solana as On-Chain Demand Shows Early Signs of Recovery]]></title>
        <id>e2bfc93b-ffe0-4542-8147-9539babf80ae</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/15/capital-creeps-back-into-solana-as-on-chain-demand-shows-early-signs-of-recovery"/>
        <updated>2025-05-15T12:16:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Solana has positive realized cap inflows after weeks of bleeding, a potential early signal of revived market conviction.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shaurya Malwa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DEX Aggregator CoW Swap Targets 33% Trading Boost With Collaboration Feature, More Rewards]]></title>
        <id>cd1f7899-79d1-4ef6-9dc9-a660db0a4495</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/tech/2025/05/15/dex-aggregator-cow-swap-targets-33-trading-boost-with-collaboration-feature-more-rewards"/>
        <updated>2025-05-15T12:14:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The new system will let solvers work together to offer traders the best swaps.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tim Craig</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Download: Montana’s experimental treatments, and Google DeepMind’s new AI agent]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1116516</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/05/15/1116516/the-download-montanas-experimental-treatments-and-google-deepminds-new-ai-agent/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-15T12:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is today’s edition of The Download, our weekday newsletter that provides a daily dose of what’s going on in the world of technology. The first US hub for experimental medical treatments is coming The news: A bill that allows clinics to sell unproven treatments has been passed in Montana. Under the legislation, doctors can apply for…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rhiannon Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Jim Chanos takes opposing bets on Bitcoin and Strategy]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/chanos-shorts-microstrategy-buys-bitcoin-retail-speculation</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/chanos-shorts-microstrategy-buys-bitcoin-retail-speculation?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-15T12:09:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Prominent short-seller Jim Chanos, once a vocal critic of Bitcoin and cryptocurrencies, revealed a new trading play that involves shorting shares of Strategy (formerly MicroStrategy) and buying Bitcoin.
At the Sohn Investment Conference in New York, Chanos told CNBC he’s “selling MicroStrategy stock and buying Bitcoin.” The investor described the move as buying something for $1 and selling something for $2.50, referring to what he sees as a significant price mismatch.
Chanos argued that Strategy is selling the idea of buying Bitcoin (BTC) in a corporate structure, and that other companies are following suit in hopes of receiving a similar market premium.
Chanos said this was “ridiculous.” He described his trade as “a good barometer of not only just the arbitrage itself, but I think of reta…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Ezra Reguerra</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Adventure Layer: AI Native Onchain Games, Unleashed]]></title>
        <id>6824c55abf73460001094973</id>
        <link href="https://blog.quicknode.com/adventure-layer-launches-on-quicknode-raas/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-15T12:04:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Adventure Layer launches layer-2 chain leveraging QuickNode's Rollup-as-a-Service (RaaS) product.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>QuickNode</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PermitFlow (YC W22) Is Hiring Senior/Staff Engineers in NYC]]></title>
        <id>https://jobs.ashbyhq.com/permitflow?departmentId=d33195eb-8978-4439-abc6-5a8a072de808</id>
        <link href="https://jobs.ashbyhq.com/permitflow?departmentId=d33195eb-8978-4439-abc6-5a8a072de808"/>
        <updated>2025-05-15T12:03:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Stablecoins seen as ideal fit for real-time collateral management]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/stablecoins-perfect-use-case-tradfi-collateral-management</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/stablecoins-perfect-use-case-tradfi-collateral-management?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-15T11:58:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cryptocurrencies and stablecoins are gaining recognition in the traditional finance (TradFi) space for their ability to streamline payments and increase efficiency in existing financial systems
In finance, collateral management refers to the process of managing the underlying collateral securing other financial transactions, such as loans or derivatives, to mitigate credit risks and ensure smooth transactions.
Digital assets like stablecoins are the “perfect” financial instrument for real-time collateral management, according to a recent pilot by DTCC Digital Assets, which suggests that digital assets, particularly stablecoins, could modernize and simplify this critical function.
“Digital assets really are the perfect use case for collateral management, whether it be uncleared derivatives,…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Zoltan Vardai</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase faces $400M bill after insider phishing attack]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/cyber-criminals-steal-coinbase-customer-data-20-m-ransom</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/cyber-criminals-steal-coinbase-customer-data-20-m-ransom?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-15T11:36:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase, the world’s third-largest cryptocurrency exchange, was hit by a $20 million extortion attempt after cybercriminals recruited overseas support agents to leak user data, the company said.
According to a May 15 blog post, Coinbase said a group of external actors bribed and coordinated with several customer support contractors to access internal systems and steal limited user account data.
“These insiders abused their access to customer support systems to steal the account data for a small subset of customers,” Coinbase said, adding that no passwords, private keys, funds or Coinbase Prime accounts were affected.
Less than 1% of Coinbase’s monthly transacting users’ data was affected by the attack, the company said.
Source: Coinbase
After stealing the data, the attackers attempted to …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Zoltan Vardai</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Is the XRP price rally over for now?]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/is-xrp-price-rally-over-for-now</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/is-xrp-price-rally-over-for-now?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-15T11:32:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Key takeaways:

XRP forms a double top and rising wedge, signaling short-term downside risk toward $1.94.

NUPL indicates traders are in denial, resembling past pre-crash phases.

Long-term charts still point to bullish targets between $3.69 and $17.

XRP (XRP) has rebounded by more than 50% in a month after forming a local low at $1.80. Improving risk appetite and prospects of an “altseason” have boosted its price.
Could XRP rally further from current levels or risk a pullback in the coming days? Let’s examine.
XRP “double top” pattern hints at sell-off 
XRP formed a double top near $2.65, signaling a possible trend reversal. The pattern includes two clear peaks and a neckline around $2.47. After the second peak, XRP dropped below the neckline, confirming the bearish setup. 
XRP/USD four-…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Yashu Gola</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[In the US, a rotating detonation rocket engine takes flight]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/space/2025/05/venus-aerospace-flies-its-rotating-detonation-rocket-engine-for-the-first-time/</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/space/2025/05/venus-aerospace-flies-its-rotating-detonation-rocket-engine-for-the-first-time/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-15T11:29:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase Could Pay Customers Up to $400M for Data Breach]]></title>
        <id>57c0c640-b214-4f10-bb57-c8a89e8f91aa</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2025/05/15/coinbase-says-criminals-stole-customer-data-offers-20m-bug-bounty"/>
        <updated>2025-05-15T11:28:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The exchange fired staff involved in the breach on the spot and will press criminal charges.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Oliver Knight</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lenovo Launches New Legion Pro Laptops In Malaysia]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=351799</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/351799/lenovo-launches-new-legion-pro-laptops-in-malaysia/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-15T11:19:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Lenovo officially announced that its latest Legion Pro gaming laptops are now available in Malaysia. These include the new Legion Pro 7i and Pro 5i. In terms of processor, both the Pro 7i and Pro 5i both ship out with the Intel Core Ultra 9 275HX, while the laptop GPU can go up to an […]
The post Lenovo Launches New Legion Pro Laptops In Malaysia appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John Law</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Daybook Americas: Retail Shift to Riskier Tokens Jolts Bitcoin, Ether]]></title>
        <id>fee5d4b4-e089-47de-95c5-cc6823ab5985</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/daybook-us/2025/05/15/crypto-daybook-americas-retail-shift-to-riskier-tokens-jolts-bitcoin-ether"/>
        <updated>2025-05-15T11:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Your day-ahead look for May 15, 2025]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Francisco Rodrigues</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Exchanges Flock to List NXPC, Token Surges 115% on $1B Volume]]></title>
        <id>8bd2263c-9fab-4f64-99a3-86daa0a4814c</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2025/05/15/crypto-exchanges-flock-to-list-nxpc-token-surges-115-on-usd1b-volume"/>
        <updated>2025-05-15T11:10:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The NXPC token is developed by NEXPACE, the blockchain arm of South Korean video game developer Nexon.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Oliver Knight</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Honda Malaysia President: EV CKD Incentives Crucial]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=351761</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/351761/honda-malaysia-president-ev-ckd-incentives-crucial/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-15T11:03:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Honda Malaysia launched the e:N1 BEV today and the automaker also confirmed that there would not be a locally assembled (CKD) unit of the car in the nearest future. The reason for this is due to the government’s decision to only extend the tax exemption for CKD EVs to 2027. This policy has raised many […]
The post Honda Malaysia President: EV CKD Incentives Crucial appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Keran</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pi Network to invest $100M in startups building blockchain apps]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/pi-network-s-team-launches-100-m-fund-to-invest-in-ecosystem</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/pi-network-s-team-launches-100-m-fund-to-invest-in-ecosystem?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-15T10:43:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mobile-first blockchain Pi Network has launched a $100 million fund to invest in initiatives built on its infrastructure.
According to a May 14 announcement, the Pi Foundation is launching Pi Network Ventures with an initial investment of $100 million in Pi (PI) tokens and US dollars. The fund will invest in startups and businesses building on Pi Network or contributing to its broader ecosystem.
“This strategic program intends to invest in high-quality startups and companies across sectors, driving innovation and ecosystem growth,” Pi Network said in an X post.
Source: Pi Network
The Pi Foundation, the organization behind Pi Network, is described as an “ownerless” entity focused on supporting long-term ecosystem development. The foundation said the new venture fund will draw from the 10% o…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Adrian Zmudzinski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Proton Launches Xchange Programme For 15-Year-Old Vehicles]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=351787</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/351787/proton-launches-xchange-programme-for-15-year-old-vehicles/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-15T10:39:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[National car maker, Proton, has launched the Proton Xchange Programme in collaboration with Car Medic Sdn. Bhd. This programme allows car owners who possess cars aged 15 years that are deemed “unroadworthy” to be traded in for a new model from the automaker, including its e.MAS7 EV. Proton has dedicated RM4.8 million for the programme, […]
The post Proton Launches Xchange Programme For 15-Year-Old Vehicles appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Keran</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Asus Launches New MD101 Fragrance Mouse And KW100 Marshmallow Keyboard]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=351781</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/351781/asus-launches-new-md101-fragrance-mouse-and-kw100-marshmallow-keyboard/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-15T10:21:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Remember the aromatherapy mouse Asus announced earlier this year? The accessory, also known as the MD101 Fragrance Mouse, will be arriving at all authorised Asus resellers, starting from this June. The mouse will retail at RM169 and be available in two different colour options: Iridescent White and Rose Clay. An optical mouse, it has a […]
The post Asus Launches New MD101 Fragrance Mouse And KW100 Marshmallow Keyboard appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John Law</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Apple May Make Bezel-Less 20th Anniversary iPhone]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=351784</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/351784/apple-bezel-less-20th-anniversary-iphone/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-15T10:07:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In preparation for the 20th anniversary since its first release of the iPhone, Apple is planning to launch a redesigned model in 2027. As per a machine translation of a report by ETNews, the upcoming phone may feature a full screen without a bezel, and a display that is curved on all four edges. According […]
The post Apple May Make Bezel-Less 20th Anniversary iPhone appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ian Chee</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pareto launches synthetic dollar backed by private credit]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/pareto-launches-synthetic-dollar-backed-by-private-credit</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/pareto-launches-synthetic-dollar-backed-by-private-credit?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-15T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Private credit marketplace Pareto has introduced a new synthetic dollar aimed at linking institutional investors with decentralized finance (DeFi) opportunities — a move that highlights the expanding role of stablecoins in global finance.
The newly launched USP synthetic dollar is fully backed by real-world private credit, Pareto told Cointelegraph on May 15. To mint USP, users must deposit stablecoins such as USDC (USDC) and USDS, which are then held as collateral.
The deposited funds are placed into Pareto’s credit vaults and lent to what the company describes as “vetted institutional borrowers,” generating yields for participants, Pareto co-founder Matteo Pandolfi told Cointelegraph in a written statement.
To maintain its peg to the US dollar, Pareto uses what it calls a “native backing…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Sam Bourgi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MediaTek Officially Launches Dimensity 9400e Chipset]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=351754</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/351754/mediatek-officially-launches-dimensity-9400e-chipset/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-15T09:50:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The current batch of flagship MediaTek mobile chipsets include the base Dimensity 9400 as well as a Plus variant. But it looks like the company is adding one more variant that sits below the existing two in terms of raw number-crunching performance, called the Dimensity 9400e. As with the other variants, the MediaTek Dimensity 9400e […]
The post MediaTek Officially Launches Dimensity 9400e Chipset appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ian Chee</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ukraine strategic Bitcoin reserve bill reportedly in final stages]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/ukraine-bitcoin-reserve-bill-final-stages-report</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/ukraine-bitcoin-reserve-bill-final-stages-report?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-15T09:37:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ukraine is reportedly moving closer to adopting Bitcoin as a national reserve asset, a move that could bolster its financial resilience amid the ongoing war with Russia.  
Lawmakers are reportedly working on a Bitcoin (BTC) national reserve proposal, with a draft bill in its final stages, according to Yaroslav Zhelezniak, a member of parliament who confirmed the plan to local media outlet Incrypted.
The proposal was announced during the CRYPTO 2025 conference in Kyiv on Feb. 6. “We will soon submit a draft law from the industry allowing the creation of crypto reserves,” Zhelezniak said.
Cointelegraph reached out to Zhelezniak for comment on the bill’s status but had not received a response by publication.
Related: Bitcoin treasury firms driving $200T hyperbitcoinization — Adam Back
Bitcoin…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Zoltan Vardai</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Telegram Shuts Down 'Largest Illicit Online Marketplace' After Elliptic's Insights]]></title>
        <id>09692f06-324a-4559-b5d8-862fd99af45e</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2025/05/15/telegram-shuts-down-largest-illicit-online-marketplace-after-elliptics-insights"/>
        <updated>2025-05-15T09:35:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Telegram has now shut down both Haowang and Xinbi, which processed a combined $35 billion of illicit transactions in stablecoins]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Crawley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Altcoin Season Could Heat Up in June and Drain Part of Bitcoin’s $2T Market Cap, Analyst Says]]></title>
        <id>356e550e-e32a-4e15-bb29-db7d8f89e601</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/15/altcoin-season-could-heat-up-in-june-and-drain-part-of-bitcoin-s-usd2t-market-cap-analyst-says"/>
        <updated>2025-05-15T09:19:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Joao Wedson, CEO of Alphractal, predicts a full-blown alt season in June, with BTC dominance already under pressure.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Omkar Godbole</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase’s x402: Crypto payments over HTTP for AI and APIs]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/explained/coinbases-x402-crypto-payments-over-http-for-ai-and-apis</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/explained/coinbases-x402-crypto-payments-over-http-for-ai-and-apis?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-15T09:02:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What is HTTP 402, and why does it matter?            
            
                
The web was not really built with payments in mind, especially not for autonomous agents or machines. But with the rise of AI and decentralized finance (DeFi), the need for seamless, native digital payments has never been more urgent. 
Coinbase x402 announced a new open protocol designed to let APIs, apps and AI agents pay instantly using stablecoins like USDC (USDC), all via the familiar HTTP protocol.
This isn’t just a product update. X402 revives a long-forgotten piece of internet infrastructure and reimagines it for a future powered by agentic systems and crypto.
HTTP status codes: A quick refresher
Understanding HTTP status codes helps clarify how the web communicates behind the scenes. Here are some k…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Arunkumar Krishnakumar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nasdaq-listed BTCS to boost ETH holdings with $57.8M raise]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/btcs-ether-accumulation-57-million-financing</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/btcs-ether-accumulation-57-million-financing?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-15T09:01:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Publicly traded company BTCS announced a $57.8 million financing agreement led by investment firm ATW Partners to purchase Ether as it expands its blockchain infrastructure strategy. 
The Rockville, Maryland-based company announced the deal on May 14, saying that the move will allow it to expand validator node operations and build recurring revenue from Ether (ETH) staking.
BTCS CEO Charles Allen said the move follows Strategy’s (formerly MicroStrategy) high-profile Bitcoin (BTC) accumulation blueprint and will leverage Ethereum for long-term growth. 
“We are executing a disciplined strategy to increase our Ethereum exposure and drive recurring revenue through staking and our block building operations,” Allen said.
Source: BTCS
BTCS issues initial $7.8 million convertible notes
As part of …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Ezra Reguerra</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How US research cuts are threatening crucial climate data]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1116485</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/05/15/1116485/climate-data/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-15T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Over the last few months, and especially the last few weeks, there’s been an explosion of news about proposed budget cuts to science in the US. One trend I’ve noticed: Researchers and civil servants are sounding the alarm that those cuts mean we might lose key data that helps us understand our world and how…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Casey Crownhart</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The value of virtual: Economies are powered by ownership of the intangible]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/the-value-of-virtual-economies-are-powered-by-ownership-of-the-intangible</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/the-value-of-virtual-economies-are-powered-by-ownership-of-the-intangible?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-15T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Opinion by: Yat Siu, executive chairman and co-founder, Animoca Brands
A discussion on digital property rights, copyright, intellectual property, the open metaverse, AI and value without physical form.
When I attend conferences and similar public events, someone almost always approaches me to ask how cryptographic tokens (fungible or non-fungible) can have value even though tokens are virtual and do not exist in the physical world. It's a surprisingly common question, especially one-on-one.
Virtual objects like NFTs and cryptocurrencies are both digital and intangible; their existence is not based in the real (physical) world, and (unlike digital currencies) they generally do not have backing by real-world institutions. 
The ability to have value (specifically, monetary worth) is crucially…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Yat Siu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Android 16 To Get Upgraded Theft Protection]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=351739</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/351739/android-16-to-get-upgraded-theft-protection/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-15T08:53:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google is updating Android’s Factory Reset Protection (FRP) feature to render stolen or lost devices practically unusable as a deterrent against thieves. The updated feature was showcased in a preview of Android 16 and Wear OS 6 earlier this week, and will block all functionalities on stolen devices. FRP has been a feature for Android […]
The post Android 16 To Get Upgraded Theft Protection appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nurul Kamil</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Maxim Responds to APAD Directive; Assures Continued Service]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=351752</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/351752/maxim-responds-to-apad-directive/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-15T08:38:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Maxim has issued a formal statement in response to the Land Public Transport Agency (APAD)’s recent directive ordering the e-hailing platform, alongside inDrive, to halt operations in Malaysia starting 24 July 2025. The company says it is currently engaging with the relevant authorities to resolve the matter and clarify its position, while continuing operations nationwide. […]
The post Maxim Responds to APAD Directive; Assures Continued Service appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Heirul Kamel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ARK Invest Bought $9.4M Worth of eToro Shares on Trading Platform's Debut]]></title>
        <id>edbb9876-482c-4a48-be4f-709ecb4ffdef</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/15/ark-invest-bought-94m-worth-of-etoro-shares-on-trading-platforms-debut"/>
        <updated>2025-05-15T08:32:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ETOR closed at $67, nearly 29% higher than its opening price of $52.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Crawley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Apple visionOS 3 May Allow Eye-Controlled App Scrolling]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=351717</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/351717/apple-visionos-3-may-allow-eye-controlled-app-scrolling/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-15T08:32:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Apple is apparently planning to implement an eye-tracking ability for navigating its Vision Pro headset. Via a report on Bloomberg, Mark Gurman states that the upcoming technology will enable users to scroll through their apps and software using their eyes alone. Citing “people with knowledge of the matter”, Gurman states that Apple is currently testing […]
The post Apple visionOS 3 May Allow Eye-Controlled App Scrolling appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Newsdesk</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin looks ‘ridiculous’ as bulls attempt $2T market cap flip — Analyst]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-looks-ridiculous-bulls-attempt-2t-market-cap-flip</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-looks-ridiculous-bulls-attempt-2t-market-cap-flip?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-15T08:21:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Key points:

Bitcoin has a fight for a $100,000 price and a $2 trillion market cap on its hands this month.

Dips below six figures are “easily possible,” analyst filbfilb says, but the odds are stacked in bulls’ favor.

ETH/BTC needs to hit the 0.03 inflection point as part of an altcoin comeback.

Bitcoin (BTC) is poised for expansion with BTC price action rarely more “bullish-looking,” an analyst says.
In his latest commentary on X, market analyst filbfilb revealed a key support battle now underway on BTC/USD.
Filbfilb on $100,000 battle: “This time is no different”
Bitcoin has begun to consolidate after making rapid gains this month, with the area just north of $100,000 seeing “choppy” BTC price moves.
For filbfilb, however, current market behavior is about more than reclaiming six fig…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by William Suberg</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amazfit Balance 2 Goes Official With AMOLED Display, Longer Battery Life]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=351741</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/351741/amazfit-balance-2/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-15T08:00:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Amazfit has launched yet another smartwatch in China dubbed the Balance 2, succeeding the original Balance from 2023. It looks similar to its predecessor from the outside, but it actually comes with several upgrades internally, including a significantly longer battery life, more durability, and improved health sensors. The Balance 2 sports the same 1.5-inch AMOLED […]
The post Amazfit Balance 2 Goes Official With AMOLED Display, Longer Battery Life appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ikmal Rozlan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Jim Chanos is Buying Bitcoin and Shorting Strategy]]></title>
        <id>c9a78209-d1e7-4dfa-a20d-058c164e688f</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/15/jim-chanos-is-buying-bitcoin-and-shorting-strategy"/>
        <updated>2025-05-15T07:58:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Investor Jim Chanos says Strategy overvalued and is backing bitcoin directly in a long-short strategy]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Francisco Rodrigues</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why is Ethereum (ETH) price down today?]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/why-is-ethereum-eth-price-down-today</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/why-is-ethereum-eth-price-down-today?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-15T07:44:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Key takeaways:

Ether’s price fell over 4% to $2,575 on May 15, mirroring similar downward moves across the wider cryptocurrency market.

Long liquidations and a drop in open interest facilitated ETH’s drop.

“Overbought” RSI and technical resistance signal profit-taking.

Ether (ETH) price declined by over 4% in the last 24 hours to around $2,575 on May 15. ETH’s drop mirrored similar downside moves elsewhere in the cryptocurrency market, with the total capitalization falling by approximately 2.40% to $3.3 trillion.
ETH/USD four-hour chart. Source: Cointelegraph/TradingView
Let’s look at some of the factors driving Ether’s price down today.
ETH price down as long liquidated, and OI falls 
Ether’s open interest (OI) has decreased by 4.5% to $31.52 billion over the last 24 hours, according …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Nancy Lubale</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dogecoin, Cardano and Solana Slump as Crypto Majors See Profit-Taking After Week-Long Rally]]></title>
        <id>76729d54-f0f5-4113-b934-5feaab7f7c9c</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/15/dogecoin-cardano-and-solana-slump-as-crypto-majors-see-profit-taking-after-weeklong-rally"/>
        <updated>2025-05-15T06:55:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Major tokens slip as traders lock in gains following macro-fueled surge, with market focus shifting to upcoming events.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shaurya Malwa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NFT founder stole millions from Bitcoin project, investors allege]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/nft-bitcoin-project-ceo-stole-millions-partners-allege</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/nft-bitcoin-project-ceo-stole-millions-partners-allege?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-15T06:21:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Several investors in a non-fungible token (NFT) project, Hashling NFT, have accused its founder of misappropriating millions of dollars in profits from the project and a closely tied Bitcoin mining operation.
According to the May 14 court filing in Illinois, the plaintiffs allege that their former business partner, Jonathan Mills, lied about transferring assets from Hashling NFT and at least $3 million from the Bitcoin mining project to a holding company — Satoshi Labs LLC (formerly known as Proof of Work Labs LLC), which Mills is the founder and CEO of.
The plaintiffs have sued Mills for fraud and breach of fiduciary duty, claiming that they have not received any of the equity returns that he supposedly promised. 
They also claim to have raised a combined $1.46 million from two NFT drops …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Brayden Lindrea</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sonic Labs wins judgment for Multichain Foundation to wind up]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/sonic-labs-wins-judgment-multichain-foundation-to-wind-up</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/sonic-labs-wins-judgment-multichain-foundation-to-wind-up?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-15T06:03:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A Singapore High Court has ruled in favor of Sonic Labs’ motion to force the Multichain Foundation to wind up in an effort to recover funds stolen during a 2023 hack.
In the May 9 judgment in the Singapore Supreme Court, Justice Kwek Mean Luck granted a request from Sonic Labs, formerly the Fantom Foundation, to declare Multichain bankrupt and appoint liquidators from global audit, tax and advisory service KPMG.
Sonic Labs CEO Michael Kong said in a May 14 statement to X that the team behind the layer 1 Sonic blockchain felt it had no choice but to file a lawsuit to forcibly wind up Multichain because its former employees were being “completely uncooperative” and “hid from victims.”
“Going forward, the liquidators can now start working with other parties to initiate the process of trying t…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Stephen Katte</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Senate removes Trump provisions in push to pass stablecoin bill]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/stablecoin-bill-wont-target-trump-senate-could-pass-may-26</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/stablecoin-bill-wont-target-trump-senate-could-pass-may-26?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-15T05:46:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The US Senate could pass a key bipartisan stablecoin bill as soon as next week after removing language targeting President Donald Trump and his family’s sprawling crypto interests.
Republican Senator Cynthia Lummis said onstage at an event by Coinbase’s lobbying arm, Stand With Crypto, that she thinks it's a “fair target” to have the Guiding and Establishing National Innovation for US Stablecoins Act, or GENIUS Act, passed by May 26 — Memorial Day in the US.
Joining her onstage was Democratic Senator Kirsten Gillibrand, who hinted that the bill’s language was changed to scrap provisions that targeted Trump’s various crypto projects, which include memecoins, a crypto platform, a stablecoin and a crypto mining company that plans to go public, among others.
“When this language comes out, peop…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Jesse Coghlan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Telegram shuts ‘largest darknet marketplace to have ever existed’]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/telegram-shuts-down-huione-guarantee-in-account-purge</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/telegram-shuts-down-huione-guarantee-in-account-purge?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-15T05:31:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A major Chinese darknet marketplace suspected of facilitating crypto scams and cybercrime has been shut down by the Telegram messaging service, upon which it operated.
The internet’s largest illicit marketplace, Haowang Guarantee, formerly Huione Guarantee, said it will shut down following Telegram’s ban of thousands of associated accounts on May 13. 
“Since all our NFTs, channels and groups were blocked by Telegram on May 13, 2025, Haowang Guarantee will cease operations from now on,” read the notice on the marketplace website.
A report from Wired said that this involved banning thousands of accounts and usernames that served as the infrastructure for the crypto crime marketplace and its vendors.
Telegram spokesperson Remi Vaughn told the outlet, “communities previously reported to us by …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Martin Young</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chainalysis CEO offers a clue into recent spate of Paris crypto attacks]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/paris-attacks-criminals-see-crypto-untraceable-chainalysis</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/paris-attacks-criminals-see-crypto-untraceable-chainalysis?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-15T05:17:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Some criminal organizations are yet to receive the memo — crypto is traceable — and could explain the recent string of crypto-related kidnappings, says Chainalysis CEO Jonathan Levin. 
Law enforcement has been increasingly successful at tracing stolen funds and crypto ransom payments, resulting in a “lot of arrests,” Levin said during the 2025 Consensus crypto conference, covered by Cointelegraph.
“For whatever reason, there is a perception that’s out there that crypto is an asset that is untraceable, and that really lends itself to criminals acting in a certain way,” he said. 
“Apparently, the know that crypto is not untraceable hasn't been received by some of the organized crime groups that are actually perpetrating these attacks, and some of them are concentrated in, you know, France, b…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Stephen Katte</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CFTC's Pham Said to Plot Exit, Agency May Be Left Without a Party Majority]]></title>
        <id>9d0555e0-a226-42a8-94b2-a378628234d2</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2025/05/14/cftc-s-pham-said-to-plot-exit-agency-may-be-left-without-a-party-majority"/>
        <updated>2025-05-15T03:56:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As Summer Mersinger exits to run the Blockchain Association and Caroline Pham talks of leaving when the new chairman arrives, the commission may fall to two.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jesse Hamilton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase eyes more deals after $2.9B Deribit acquisition]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/coinbase-ceo-looking-more-acquisitions-after-deribit</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/coinbase-ceo-looking-more-acquisitions-after-deribit?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-15T03:51:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase CEO Brian Armstrong says his firm will continue to look for merger and acquisition opportunities after acquiring crypto derivatives platform Deribit.
“We are always looking at M&A opportunities,” said Armstrong on Bloomberg Television on May 14.
He added that the firm has a large balance sheet that can be put to use.
The firm revealed in its latest revenue report that its balance sheet has strengthened, ending the first quarter with $9.9 billion in US dollar resources.
“Part of the benefit of being a public company is, you have a liquid currency to do that,” he said, adding: “We are looking at acquisition opportunities; doesn’t mean we swing at every pitch. We want it to be the right opportunity.”
On May 8, the firm announced that it agreed to acquire crypto options trading platfo…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Martin Young</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Human]]></title>
        <id>https://quarter--mile.com/Human</id>
        <link href="https://quarter--mile.com/Human"/>
        <updated>2025-05-15T02:57:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[LLMs get lost in multi-turn conversation]]></title>
        <id>https://arxiv.org/abs/2505.06120</id>
        <link href="https://arxiv.org/abs/2505.06120"/>
        <updated>2025-05-15T02:28:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OpenAI brings GPT-4.1 and 4.1 mini to ChatGPT — what enterprises should know]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3007689</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/openai-brings-gpt-4-1-and-4-1-mini-to-chatgpt-what-enterprises-should-know/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-14T23:46:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As OpenAI continues to evolve its model offerings, GPT-4.1 represents a step forward in democratizing advanced AI for enterprise environments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carl Franzen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Beyond sycophancy: DarkBench exposes six hidden ‘dark patterns’ lurking in today’s top LLMs]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3007681</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/darkness-rising-the-hidden-dangers-of-ai-sycophancy-and-dark-patterns/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-14T23:14:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Without a strong push from AI companies to combat sycophancy and other dark patterns, the default trajectory is more engagement optimization, more manipulation and fewer checks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Leon Yen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Banks Exploring Stablecoin Amid Fears of Losing Market Share, BitGo Executive Says]]></title>
        <id>f325f50c-8095-4820-b750-256581c8fbdf</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/consensus-toronto-2025-coverage/2025/05/14/banks-exploring-stablecoin-amid-fears-of-losing-market-share-bitgo-executive-says"/>
        <updated>2025-05-14T21:59:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BitGo’s stablecoin-as-a-service has drawn significant interest from U.S. and international banks, Ben Reynolds said.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Krisztian Sandor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trump Still on Track to Sign Crypto Legislation by August, White House's Bo Hines Says]]></title>
        <id>bd5f9eed-a941-4e30-a1d4-19ee7cc5990c</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/consensus-toronto-2025-coverage/2025/05/14/trump-still-on-track-to-sign-crypto-legislation-by-august-white-house-s-bo-hines-says"/>
        <updated>2025-05-14T21:34:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The senior presidential aide also defended the Trump family's crypto ties.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nikhilesh De</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Show HN: Semantic Calculator (king-man+woman=?)]]></title>
        <id>https://calc.datova.ai/</id>
        <link href="https://calc.datova.ai/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-14T19:54:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How DNS Works: A Guide to Understanding the Internet's Address Book]]></title>
        <id>6824f1ac04a60b4a58654ddc</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-dns-works-the-internets-address-book/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-14T19:40:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Domain Name System (DNS) translates domain names (like example.com) into IP addresses (like 192.0.2.1) so we can easily access websites. In this guide, you’ll learn how DNS resolution starts, its step-by-step process, how caching works, and the r...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dhruv Prajapati</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Show HN: Muscle-Mem, a behavior cache for AI agents]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/pig-dot-dev/muscle-mem</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/pig-dot-dev/muscle-mem"/>
        <updated>2025-05-14T19:38:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Load Balancing with Azure Application Gateway and Azure Load Balancer – When to Use Each One]]></title>
        <id>6824f10a7d203c180e5ea4b2</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/load-balancing-with-azure-application-gateway-and-azure-load-balancer/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-14T19:37:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You’ve probably heard someone mention load balancing when talking about cloud apps. Maybe even names like Azure Load Balancer, Azure Application Gateway, or something about Virtual Machines and Scale Sets. 😵‍💫 It all sounds important...but also a l...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Prince Onukwili</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elon Musk’s Grok AI is spamming X users about South African race relations now, for some reason]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3007646</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/elon-musks-grok-ai-is-spamming-x-users-about-south-african-race-relations-now-for-some-reason/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-14T19:08:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Grok was caught earlier this year censoring results critical of President Trump and Musk himself, sowing more doubt of its factual integrity.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carl Franzen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A server that wasn't meant to exist]]></title>
        <id>https://it-notes.dragas.net/2025/05/13/the_server_that_wasnt_meant_to_exist/</id>
        <link href="https://it-notes.dragas.net/2025/05/13/the_server_that_wasnt_meant_to_exist/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-14T15:50:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AlphaEvolve: A Gemini-powered coding agent for designing advanced algorithms]]></title>
        <id>https://deepmind.google/discover/blog/alphaevolve-a-gemini-powered-coding-agent-for-designing-advanced-algorithms/</id>
        <link href="https://deepmind.google/discover/blog/alphaevolve-a-gemini-powered-coding-agent-for-designing-advanced-algorithms/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-14T15:10:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build Slim and Fast Docker Images with Multi-Stage Builds]]></title>
        <id>6824b1638a2b26e9d2d0fe86</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-slim-fast-docker-images-with-multi-stage-builds/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-14T15:06:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Apps don’t stay simple forever. More features mean more dependencies, slower builds, and heavier Docker images. That’s where things start to hurt. Docker helps, but without the right setup, your builds can quickly get bloated. Multi-stage builds make...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniel Adeboye</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google DeepMind’s new AI agent cracks real-world problems better than humans can]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1116438</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/05/14/1116438/google-deepminds-new-ai-uses-large-language-models-to-crack-real-world-problems/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-14T15:00:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google DeepMind has once again used large language models to discover new solutions to long-standing problems in math and computer science. This time the firm has shown that its approach can not only tackle unsolved theoretical puzzles, but improve a range of important real-world processes as well. Google DeepMind’s new tool, called AlphaEvolve, uses the…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Will Douglas Heaven</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meet AlphaEvolve, the Google AI that writes its own code—and just saved millions in computing costs]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3007538</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/meet-alphaevolve-the-google-ai-that-writes-its-own-code-and-just-saved-millions-in-computing-costs/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-14T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google DeepMind's AlphaEvolve AI system breaks a 56-year-old mathematical record by discovering a more efficient matrix multiplication algorithm that had eluded human mathematicians since Strassen's 1969 breakthrough.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Nuñez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn Vite for a Better Web Development Workflow]]></title>
        <id>6824ae178a2b26e9d2d0fe4c</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-vite-for-a-better-web-development-workflow/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-14T14:52:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Speed and simplicity are at the heart of modern web development. As applications grow more complex and the demand for rapid iteration increases, developers are constantly searching for tools that minimize friction and maximize productivity. Tradition...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Web Services Work – The Unseen Engines of the Connected World]]></title>
        <id>6824ad336ea9fe84cfb4d0c4</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-web-services-work-with-examples/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-14T14:48:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Have you ever wondered how your weather app instantly knows the forecast, how you can book flights from multiple airlines on one travel site, or how logging into one service can magically log you into another? The answer often lies in a powerful, yet...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kumar Anand</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Master Kotlin & Android 60-Hour Course]]></title>
        <id>6824aba7be2c002301d59188</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/master-kotlin-and-android-60-hour-course/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-14T14:41:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Do you want to create the next groundbreaking mobile app? Kotlin, a modern and powerful language officially backed by Google, not only makes Android development more efficient and enjoyable but also opens doors to diverse programming opportunities be...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[QuickLee V2: An Improved Transparent Look into RPC Provider Latency]]></title>
        <id>680fc8e1f8ae810001969b47</id>
        <link href="https://blog.quicknode.com/quicklee-v2/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-14T13:57:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[View public and real-time dashboards to better understand latency and speed when evaluating RPC providers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>QuickNode</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Patronus AI debuts Percival to help enterprises monitor failing AI agents at scale]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3007592</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/patronus-ai-debuts-percival-to-help-enterprises-monitor-failing-ai-agents-at-scale/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-14T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Patronus AI introduces Percival, a real-time monitoring platform that helps enterprises detect, debug, and prevent failures in autonomous AI agents to improve reliability, safety, and scalability.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Nuñez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is HDR, anyway?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lux.camera/what-is-hdr/</id>
        <link href="https://www.lux.camera/what-is-hdr/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-14T12:46:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The first US hub for experimental medical treatments is coming]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1116428</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/05/14/1116428/first-us-hub-for-experimental-medical-treatments/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-14T12:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A bill that allows medical clinics to sell unproven treatments has been passed in Montana.  Under the legislation, doctors can apply for a license to open an experimental treatment clinic and recommend and sell therapies not approved by the Food and Drug Administration (FDA) to their patients. Once it’s signed by the governor, the law…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jessica Hamzelou</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The VentureBeat AI survey is back: Are you ready for the agentic AI future?]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3007483</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/the-venturebeat-ai-survey-is-back-are-you-ready-for-the-agentic-ai-future/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-14T12:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AI is a critical competitive advantage — and it’s time to find out how your company stacks up. The annual VentureBeat AI survey is back. The survey is brought to you by ActiveFence, a leader in expert-driven gen AI safety and security solutions, and returns alongside Transform 2025 in SF this June 24 and 25. […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>VB Staff</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Download: taking the temperature of snow, and the future of privacy]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1116426</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/05/14/1116426/the-download-taking-the-temperature-of-snow-and-the-future-of-privacy/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-14T12:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is today’s edition of The Download, our weekday newsletter that provides a daily dose of what’s going on in the world of technology. Why climate researchers are taking the temperature of mountain snow The Sierra’s frozen reservoir provides about a third of California’s water and most of what comes out of the faucets, shower heads, and…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rhiannon Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Databricks acquires Neon]]></title>
        <id>https://www.databricks.com/blog/databricks-neon</id>
        <link href="https://www.databricks.com/blog/databricks-neon"/>
        <updated>2025-05-14T10:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why climate researchers are taking the temperature of mountain snow]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1116395</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/05/14/1116395/why-climate-researchers-are-taking-the-temperature-of-mountain-snow/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-14T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On a crisp morning in early April, Dan McEvoy and Bjoern Bingham cut clean lines down a wide run at the Heavenly Ski Resort in South Lake Tahoe, then ducked under a rope line cordoning off a patch of untouched snow.  They side-stepped up a small incline, poled past a row of Jeffrey pines, then…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>James Temple</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Notion bets big on integrated LLMs, adds GPT-4.1 and Claude 3.7 to platform]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3007515</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/notion-bets-big-on-integrated-llms-adds-gpt-4-1-and-claude-3-7-to-platform/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-13T22:18:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Notion used OpenAI's GPT-4.1 and Anthropic's Claude 3.7 for its new AI features for enterprises, moving away from reasoning models.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Emilia David</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What your tools miss at 2:13 AM: How gen AI attack chains exploit telemetry lag – Part 2]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3005726</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/what-your-tools-miss-at-213-am-how-gen-ai-attack-chains-exploit-telemetry-lag-part-2/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-13T22:05:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Explore a strategic 2025 roadmap for cybersecurity leaders to tackle GenAI, insider risks, and team burnout with actionable guidance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Louis Columbus</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AI power rankings upended: OpenAI, Google rise as Anthropic falls, Poe report finds]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3007490</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/ai-power-rankings-upended-openai-google-rise-as-anthropic-falls-poe-report-finds/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-13T19:13:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New Poe data reveals major shifts in AI market share as OpenAI and Google gain ground while specialized reasoning models surge to 10% of usage in 2025.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Nuñez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SimilarWeb’s new AI usage report reveals 5 surprising findings, including explosive growth in coding tools]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3007475</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/similarwebs-new-ai-usage-report-reveals-5-surprising-findings-including-explosive-growth-in-coding-tools/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-13T17:22:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The signs point to early-stage AI disruption beginning to erode the utility of some legacy platforms. It also offers a hint to enterprises...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carl Franzen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Top Ways Hackers Exploit Web Applications (and How to Prevent Them)]]></title>
        <id>682354c58b3805ff1d2335d0</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-hackers-exploit-web-applications-and-how-to-prevent-them/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-13T14:18:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Every website that takes user input is a potential target for an attacker. You might think your app is too small or too new to get noticed, but attackers use tools to scan the web for common security mistakes. If your site is online and has a login f...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Manish Shivanandhan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lua for Elixir]]></title>
        <id>https://davelucia.com/blog/lua-elixir</id>
        <link href="https://davelucia.com/blog/lua-elixir"/>
        <updated>2025-05-13T13:03:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The interoperability breakthrough: How MCP is becoming enterprise AI’s universal language]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3007355</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/the-interoperability-breakthrough-how-mcp-is-becoming-enterprise-ais-universal-language/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-13T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Just a few months after it's release, MCP adoption is growing. VentureBeat spoke to some enterprises asking why MCP is winning the standards race.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Emilia David</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Guardian agents: New approach could reduce AI hallucinations to below 1%]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3007370</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/beyond-detection-why-automatically-correcting-hallucinations-could-transform-enterprise-ai-adoption/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-13T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There are lots of ways to detect AI hallucination, new guardian agent model promises to correct them.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sean Michael Kerner</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fast machines, slow machines (2023)]]></title>
        <id>https://jmmv.dev/2023/06/fast-machines-slow-machines.html</id>
        <link href="https://jmmv.dev/2023/06/fast-machines-slow-machines.html"/>
        <updated>2025-05-13T12:10:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Download: CRISPR in court, and the police’s ban-skirting AI]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1116357</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/05/13/1116357/the-download-crispr-in-court-and-the-polices-ban-skirting-ai/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-13T12:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is today’s edition of The Download, our weekday newsletter that provides a daily dose of what’s going on in the world of technology. A US court just put ownership of CRISPR back in play The CRISPR patents are back in play. Yesterday, the US Court of Appeals for the Federal Circuit said scientists Jennifer Doudna and…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rhiannon Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Internet Artifacts]]></title>
        <id>https://neal.fun/internet-artifacts/</id>
        <link href="https://neal.fun/internet-artifacts/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-13T11:49:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Git Bug: Distributed, Offline-First Bug Tracker Embedded in Git, with Bridges]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/git-bug/git-bug</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/git-bug/git-bug"/>
        <updated>2025-05-13T11:07:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Changes since congestion pricing started in New York]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nytimes.com/interactive/2025/05/11/upshot/congestion-pricing.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.nytimes.com/interactive/2025/05/11/upshot/congestion-pricing.html"/>
        <updated>2025-05-13T10:43:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Working on complex systems: What I learned working at Google]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thecoder.cafe/p/complex-systems</id>
        <link href="https://www.thecoder.cafe/p/complex-systems"/>
        <updated>2025-05-13T09:35:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lightweight open source reCaptcha alternative]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/altcha-org/altcha</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/altcha-org/altcha"/>
        <updated>2025-05-13T09:19:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Police tech can sidestep facial recognition bans now]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1116321</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/05/13/1116321/police-tech-can-sidestep-facial-recognition-bans-now/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-13T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Six months ago I attended the largest gathering of chiefs of police in the US to see how they’re using AI. I found some big developments, like officers getting AI to write their police reports. Today, I published a new story that shows just how far AI for police has developed since then.  It’s about…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>James O'Donnell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A US court just put ownership of CRISPR back in play]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1116344</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/05/13/1116344/a-us-court-just-put-ownership-of-crispr-back-in-play/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-13T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The CRISPR patents are back in play. On Monday, the US Court of Appeals for the Federal Circuit said scientists Jennifer Doudna and Emmanuelle Charpentier will get another chance to show they ought to own the key patents on what many consider the defining biotechnology invention of the 21st century. The pair shared a 2020…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Antonio Regalado</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sakana introduces new AI architecture, ‘Continuous Thought Machines’ to make models reason with less guidance — like human brains]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3007376</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/sakana-introduces-new-ai-architecture-continuous-thought-machines-to-make-models-reason-with-less-guidance-like-human-brains/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-12T23:08:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While the CTM shows strong promise, it is still primarily a research architecture and is not yet production-ready out of the box.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carl Franzen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OpenAI just fixed ChatGPT’s most annoying business problem: meet the PDF export that changes everything]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3007361</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/openai-just-fixed-chatgpts-most-annoying-business-problem-meet-the-pdf-export-that-changes-everything/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-12T20:43:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[OpenAI has added a powerful PDF export feature to its Deep Research tool, signaling a major push into enterprise AI and transforming how businesses generate and share insights.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Nuñez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New fully open source vision encoder OpenVision arrives to improve on OpenAI’s Clip, Google’s SigLIP]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3007349</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/new-fully-open-source-vision-encoder-openvision-arrives-to-improve-on-openais-clip-googles-siglip/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-12T18:19:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A vision encoder is a necessary component for allowing many leading LLMs to be able to work with images uploaded by users.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carl Franzen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Automate Compliance and Fraud Detection in Finance with MLOps]]></title>
        <id>68222009a8daed5c1fbf1692</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/automate-compliance-and-fraud-detection-in-finance-with-mlops/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-12T16:21:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[These days, businesses are under increasing pressure to comply with stringent regulations while also combating fraudulent activities. The high volume of data and the intricate requirements of real-time fraud detection and compliance reporting are fre...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Balajee Asish Brahmandam</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn Object-Oriented Programming in TypeScript]]></title>
        <id>682201c8ba77730da04e15a8</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-object-oriented-programming-in-typescript/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-12T14:12:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Object-Oriented Programming (OOP) is one of the most widely used programming paradigms in software development. But is also one of the most misunderstood. This article will help you gain a solid grasp of OOP in TypeScript by walking you through the l...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lucas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Become an Analytical Programmer – Solve the "Rock, Paper, Scissors" Game 5 Ways Using JavaScript & Mermaid.js]]></title>
        <id>6822006162f6347293451e07</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-become-an-analytical-programmer-compare-five-projects/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-12T14:06:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Over the past year, I’ve explored tools and practices that help developers build an analytical mindset. One recurring theme is how experienced programmers often describe understanding code as forming a mental picture – a conceptual map of the program...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>evaristo.c</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Glass Imaging raises $20M to use AI to improve digital image quality]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3007251</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/games/glass-imaging-raises-20m-to-use-ai-to-improve-digital-image-quality/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-12T13:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Glass Imaging, a company harnessing the power of artificial intelligence to revolutionize digital image quality, raised $20 million in funding. Global software investor insight Partners led the round. With the funding, Glass Imaging will continue to refine and implement their proprietary GlassAI technologies across a wide range of camera platforms – from smartphones to drones to wearables and […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dean Takahashi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Aarki launches Encore as privacy-first mobile growth platform]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3007252</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/games/aarki-launches-encore-as-privacy-first-mobile-growth-platform/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-12T12:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Aarki has launched Encore, a next-generation machine learning platform built to deliver full-funnel growth for mobile marketers in a privacy-first landscape. Designed for smarter user acquisition and stronger retention, Encore combines dynamic targeting, continuous model evolution, and SKAN 4-ready optimization.  Encore is the industry’s only unified platform with a privacy-first framework that supports both User […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dean Takahashi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Download: a new form of AI surveillance, and the US and China’s tariff deal]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1116307</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/05/12/1116307/the-download-a-new-form-of-ai-surveillance-and-the-us-and-chinas-tariff-deal/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-12T12:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is today’s edition of The Download, our weekday newsletter that provides a daily dose of what’s going on in the world of technology. How a new type of AI is helping police skirt facial recognition bans Police and federal agencies have found a controversial new way to skirt the growing patchwork of laws that curb how…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rhiannon Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Python lib generates its code on-the-fly based on usage]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/cofob/autogenlib</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/cofob/autogenlib"/>
        <updated>2025-05-12T01:36:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[They Were Identical 'Twinnies' Who Charmed Orwell, Camus and More]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nytimes.com/2025/05/04/books/review/the-dazzling-paget-sisters-ariane-bankes.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.nytimes.com/2025/05/04/books/review/the-dazzling-paget-sisters-ariane-bankes.html"/>
        <updated>2025-05-11T22:41:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[From silicon to sentience: The legacy guiding AI’s next frontier and human cognitive migration]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3007219</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/from-silicon-to-sentience-the-legacy-guiding-ais-next-frontier-and-human-cognitive-migration/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-11T17:05:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As AI systems master tasks once uniquely human, we find ourselves on an accelerated journey to discover what truly lies beyond automation.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gary Grossman, Edelman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Rust API Inspired by Python, Powered by Serde]]></title>
        <id>https://ohadravid.github.io/posts/2025-05-serde-reflect/</id>
        <link href="https://ohadravid.github.io/posts/2025-05-serde-reflect/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-11T16:28:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MCP and the innovation paradox: Why open standards will save AI from itself]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3007210</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/mcp-and-the-innovation-paradox-why-open-standards-will-save-ai-from-itself/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-10T19:05:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Much like HTTP and REST standardized how web applications connect to services, MCP standardizes how AI models connect to tools.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Noah Schwartz, Postman API Network</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fine-tuning vs. in-context learning: New research guides better LLM customization for real-world tasks]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3007197</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/fine-tuning-vs-in-context-learning-new-research-guides-better-llm-customization-for-real-world-tasks/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-10T00:23:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By combining fine-tuning and in-context learning, you get LLMs that can learn tasks that would be too difficult or expensive for either method]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ben Dickson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What your tools miss at 2:13 AM: How gen AI attack chains exploit telemetry lag – Part 1]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3005673</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/security/what-your-tools-miss-at-213-am-how-gen-ai-attack-chains-exploit-telemetry-lag-part-1/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-09T20:56:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Explore a strategic 2025 roadmap for cybersecurity leaders to tackle gen AI, insider risks, and team burnout with actionable guidance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Louis Columbus</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OpenAI’s $3B Windsurf move: the real reason behind its enterprise AI code push]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3007170</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/openais-3b-windsurf-move-the-real-reason-behind-its-enterprise-ai-agent-code-push/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-09T17:00:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[OpenAI’s $3B Windsurf buy puts it on defense as Google & Anthropic surge in AI-powered coding—discover the stakes for agentic development and enterprise teams.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matt Marshall</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Zencoder launches Zen Agents, ushering in a new era of team-based AI for software development]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3007152</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/zencoder-launches-zen-agents-ushering-in-a-new-era-of-team-based-ai-for-software-development/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-09T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Zencoder launches Zen Agents, the first AI platform enabling teams to create, share, and leverage custom development assistants organization-wide, plus an open-source marketplace for enterprise-grade AI tools.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Nuñez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OpenAI, Microsoft tell Senate ‘no one country can win AI’]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3007056</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/openai-microsoft-tell-senate-no-one-country-can-win-ai/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-09T01:02:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Executives like OpenAI's Sam Altman said US support for infrastructure would make it easier for AI companies to meet demand.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Emilia David</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[You can now fine-tune your enterprise’s own version of OpenAI’s o4-mini reasoning model with reinforcement learning]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3007091</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/you-can-now-fine-tune-your-enterprises-own-version-of-openais-o4-mini-reasoning-model-with-reinforcement-learning/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-09T00:07:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For organizations with clearly defined problems and verifiable answers, RFT offers a compelling way to align models.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carl Franzen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How The Ottawa Hospital uses AI ambient voice capture to reduce physician burnout by 70%, achieve 97% patient satisfaction]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3007069</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/how-the-ottawa-hospital-uses-ai-ambient-voice-capture-to-reduce-physician-burnout-by-70-achieve-97-patient-satisfaction/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-08T23:57:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[TOH is using Microsoft’s DAX Copilot to capture physician-patient conversations and generate draft clinical notes in real time.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Taryn Plumb</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[5 strategies that separate AI leaders from the 92% still stuck in pilot mode]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3007013</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/5-strategies-that-separate-ai-leaders-from-the-92-still-stuck-in-pilot-mode/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-08T23:09:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Accenture's new research reveals the critical strategies that separate the companies successfully scaling AI from the 92% stuck in perpetual pilot mode, providing enterprise leaders with actionable insights to accelerate their AI transformation journey.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sean Michael Kerner</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The walled garden cracks: Nadella bets Microsoft’s Copilots—and Azure’s next act—on A2A/MCP interoperability]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3006872</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/the-walled-garden-cracks-nadella-bets-microsofts-copilots-and-azures-next-act-on-a2a-mcp-interoperability/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-08T20:47:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft CEO Satya Nadella’s endorsement of Google DeepMind‘s A2A open protocol and Anthropic's MCP is huge sign the industry is moving to an open garden.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Louis Columbus</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Alibaba’s ‘ZeroSearch’ lets AI learn to google itself — slashing training costs by 88 percent]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3007024</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/alibabas-zerosearch-lets-ai-learn-to-google-itself-slashing-training-costs-by-88-percent/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-08T19:15:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Alibaba’s ZeroSearch trains large language models to beat Google Search and slash API costs by 88%, redefining how AI learns to retrieve information.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Nuñez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Breathe lands $21M Series B to predict battery performance]]></title>
        <id>https://techcrunch.com/?p=3003769</id>
        <link href="https://techcrunch.com/2025/05/07/breathe-lands-21m-series-b-to-predict-battery-performance/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-07T12:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Breathe has developed a suite of tools that it says helps automakers and others get the most out of their batteries.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tim De Chant</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Join the 2025 Web3j Mentorships: Build the Future of Ethereum on the JVM]]></title>
        <id>6819c8dc41eeeb000183d37b</id>
        <link href="https://blog.web3labs.com/join-the-2025-web3j-mentorships-build-the-future-of-ethereum-on-the-jvm/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T08:32:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Linux Foundation’s Decentralized Trust (LFDT) mentorship program is back in 2025 with two exciting opportunities for developers passionate about Ethereum, Android, and the Java Virtual Machine (JVM). Whether you’re a seasoned blockchain developer or an Android enthusiast eager to dive into Web3, these mentorships offer]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>George Tebrean</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>