<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2025-06-03T23:42:06.375Z</id>
    <title>AngJianming RSS Feed</title>
    <updated>2025-06-03T23:42:06.375Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bolt Hackathon Day 5/30: Spitballing]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/thankamatho/bolt-hackathon-day-530-spitballing-2728</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/thankamatho/bolt-hackathon-day-530-spitballing-2728"/>
        <updated>2025-06-03T23:17:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Splitting Project Ideas




Project size is leading to large token usage


Creating secondary projects for features/components that are still integrated with supabase (semi-tested, has both worked and not)


Using git urls as json packages (untested)




  
  
  AG-UI




Import AG-UI github repo using url, failed from npm packages among other things


Will attempt again later.


Mainly looking to make use of the shared layout system



Today Token use:
Bolt: .5m (Live token amount, started AI integration)
Gemini: 1.7m (Testing creating new projects under same supabase, testing map creator prompts, tested launch page prompt)
Total use:
Bolt: 5.9m
Gemini: 3.6m]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>thankamatho</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[pt-br] Você sabe o que significa HW e SW?! Eu não sabia até hoje]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/elasfalamtech/pt-br-o-que-e-hw-e-sf-4kmn</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/elasfalamtech/pt-br-o-que-e-hw-e-sf-4kmn"/>
        <updated>2025-06-03T23:14:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Entrei em um novo emprego (😃).
Estava fazendo os tramites de abrir chamado para TI quando me deparo com "SW installation". 
Pensei: "Que isso?"
Descobri que além de SW existe o HW.
SW = S oft w are (sistemas e aplicativos do pc)
H ard w are (peças e componentes físicos do pc)
Bom, essas siglas eu ainda não tinha visto na caminhada da tecnologia. Espero ter ajudado para que não seja novidade quando você se deparar com elas por aí.
*pc = computador
TI = área de tecnologia da informação]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Clarice Regina</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Web Mimarisi: Gelecek Şimdi]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/yunus_emremert_1756b71d3/web-mimarisi-gelecek-simdi-2nin</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/yunus_emremert_1756b71d3/web-mimarisi-gelecek-simdi-2nin"/>
        <updated>2025-06-03T23:13:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Web teknolojileri her geçen gün hızla gelişiyor ve web mimarisi, bu gelişmelerin merkezinde yer alıyor. Web mimarisi, web uygulamalarının temelini oluşturan yapı ve tasarım ilkelerini kapsar ve uygulamaların performansından, ölçeklenebilirliğinden ve genel kullanıcı deneyiminden doğrudan sorumlu olduğu için son derece önemlidir. Modern web mimarisi, web uygulamalarını daha hızlı, daha esnek ve daha güçlü hale getirmeyi amaçlayan yenilikçi yaklaşımlar ve teknolojiler getiriyor.
Web uygulamaları, günümüzün dinamik ve talepkar çevrimiçi dünyasının temelini oluşturur. Kullanıcılar artık sadece statik web sayfaları değil, etkileşimli ve yanıt veren web deneyimleri bekliyorlar. Bu beklentileri karşılamak için web mimarisi, geleneksel sunucu tabanlı modelden daha gelişmiş mimarilere doğru evrim g…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yunus Emre Mert</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[Free Blog Creation] I tried hosting a static site with Obsidian and GitHub Pages!]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/takumifujiwaradairy/free-blog-creation-i-tried-hosting-a-static-site-with-obsidian-and-github-pages-pdo</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/takumifujiwaradairy/free-blog-creation-i-tried-hosting-a-static-site-with-obsidian-and-github-pages-pdo"/>
        <updated>2025-06-03T23:13:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Preface


This is the website I created. *It is still under construction.
https://takumifujiwaradairy.github.io/my_public_notes/
In this article, I would like to introduce how to publish a static website for free using Obsidian and GitHub Pages.
In this article, I will omit detailed explanations of Obsidian and GitHub Pages.
For this project, I am using Quartz4 as the static site framework for publishing Obsidian!
https://github.com/jackyzha0/quartz
Fork it into your own repository. Note that GitHub Pages cannot be used for free unless it is a public repository!
Clone your repository locally.
$ git clone https://github.com/user-name/obsidian-quartz.git

Add Markdown files under the content directory.

/content/index.md will be the homepage.
npx quartz build  
rm -rf docs && mv public docs  
git add -A  
git commit -m “rebuild site with index.html”
git push origin main

Running these commands will automatically complete the setup.
Set it up so it looks like the screenshot, and you're good to go!

That's a quick overview of the deployment process.
There are still more settings to configure, so I'll cover those in another article if I get around to it.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Fujiwara Takumi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[🧠 How AI Is Revolutionizing Medical Education — A Developer’s Perspective]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/alireza_minagar_99f01ecb6/how-ai-is-revolutionizing-medical-education-a-developers-perspective-3om7</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/alireza_minagar_99f01ecb6/how-ai-is-revolutionizing-medical-education-a-developers-perspective-3om7"/>
        <updated>2025-06-03T23:06:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By: Alireza Minagar, MD, MBA, MS (Bionformatics) software engineer
From Cadavers to Code: A New Era of Physician Training
Textbooks and lectures
Cadaver dissection
Weeks-delayed exam feedback
But today, AI is shifting that paradigm entirely. Medical education is no longer a static, one-size-fits-all journey. It’s becoming adaptive, immersive, and developer-powered.
The AI-Driven Model
Adaptive learning paths tailored to their strengths and weaknesses
Real-time feedback on clinical decisions
Dynamic patient simulations that evolve based on learner input
These aren’t just digital flashcards. They’re full-blown AI-powered experiences designed to mimic the complexity of real-world healthcare — without putting a single patient at risk.
Simulating Smarter Scenarios
Large Language Models (LLMs) are now being used to simulate realistic conversations with patients:
Delivering bad news
Managing emotionally charged reactions
Navigating cultural and linguistic nuances
Behind the Scenes: Developer Technologies Powering the Shift
Tech    Function
Combine this with VR, and you’ve got physicians rehearsing high-stakes procedures in immersive, AI-guided simulations.
Real Results — and Real Responsibility
Faster learners
More diagnostic-savvy
Comfortable using tech as a clinical ally
But with innovation comes challenge:
Maintaining the human touch in care
Protecting student and patient data
Ensuring access across socioeconomic lines
Let’s Build the Future of Medicine
If you're a developer interested in AI, edtech, or healthcare innovation, this is your moment. Build the platforms. Train the models. Write the APIs. The next generation of doctors depends on what we ship today.
Let’s code the next generation of healers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alireza Minagar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Talk to AI (and Get Better Results)]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/_senhorbento/how-to-talk-to-ai-and-get-better-results-oia</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/_senhorbento/how-to-talk-to-ai-and-get-better-results-oia"/>
        <updated>2025-06-03T22:59:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Summary



Introduction
Context
First Example 
Second Example
Third Example
This short article aims to help beginner and curious users understand a simple approach to using AI effectively.
First of all, I'm not an AI expert, just someone who's curious about it and wants to help others make use of it. I'm doing this for fun, but I hope it ends up being helpful to someone out there!
Most sources emphasize that you need to provide context when asking AI questions to get accurate answers. However, what many don’t mention is that you can actually ask the AI itself what context or background information you should include to improve the quality of its response. This way, even if you’re unsure what details are relevant, the AI can guide you on how to frame your request for the best possible resul…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bento</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Bold Sweetness of a Raspberry Background]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/smartdev72/the-bold-sweetness-of-a-raspberry-background-3ggp</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/smartdev72/the-bold-sweetness-of-a-raspberry-background-3ggp"/>
        <updated>2025-06-03T22:52:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Looking for a background that blends energy with elegance? A raspberry background strikes the perfect balance.
Raspberry is a rich, vibrant hue—deeper than pink, livelier than red, and with just enough sweetness to feel playful without losing its sophistication. It’s a color that turns heads while still feeling polished, making it ideal for bold, expressive designs that want to feel confident and current.
Raspberry captures attention, but with charm. It’s a color that communicates passion, creativity, and personality. A raspberry background adds visual richness, giving your content a dynamic feel while remaining approachable and warm.
It’s especially effective when you want to feel fresh and fun—but still refined.
- Beauty & Fashion Brands: Raspberry adds a sense of bold femininity—perfect for cosmetics, clothing, or accessories.
- Event Promotions: Great for vibrant celebrations like galas, birthdays, or themed parties.
- Social Media Content: Scroll-stopping and full of energy, it makes quotes, promos, and visuals pop instantly.
- Modern Print Design: Whether it’s a flyer, packaging, or a digital invite, raspberry gives it life and style.
To enhance its richness:
Use white or light gray for clean, legible contrast.
Add gold or rose gold accents for a luxurious touch.
Pair with deep navy, plum, or black for a dramatic, high-contrast effect.
Combine with peach or blush tones for a softer, layered palette.
A raspberry background is bold, juicy, and packed with personality. It’s perfect when you want your visuals to feel passionate, lively, and modern. Whether you’re branding a product, designing an event, or crafting content, raspberry adds a splash of stylish energy that’s hard to ignore.
Sweet, strong, and endlessly versatile—raspberry is color done right.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Miguel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Reflexões Noturnas: Por que “Team Topologies” me fez repensar tudo sobre como a gente trabalha (e entrega valor)]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/maicon_luizanschau_2ec1f/reflexoes-noturnas-por-que-team-topologies-me-fez-repensar-tudo-sobre-como-a-gente-trabalha-e-5cj8</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/maicon_luizanschau_2ec1f/reflexoes-noturnas-por-que-team-topologies-me-fez-repensar-tudo-sobre-como-a-gente-trabalha-e-5cj8"/>
        <updated>2025-06-03T22:50:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hoje, depois de um dia puxado, me peguei pensando nos pontos que mais me marcaram do livro Team Topologies, do Matthew Skelton e Manuel Pais. Já tinha ouvido muita gente recomendando, mas confesso: só agora lendo com calma entendi o real impacto disso na nossa forma de trabalhar. E olha… como Tech Lead, foi impossível não revisitar cada decisão de estrutura que já ajudei a desenhar.
Sempre acreditei que tecnologia é meio, não fim. Mas o livro mostra que como a gente organiza os times importa tanto quanto a stack ou a arquitetura. Sabe aquela história da Inverse Conway Maneuver? De projetar a estrutura pensando na arquitetura que você quer alcançar e não aceitar que a arquitetura reflete os silos que existem? Isso ficou martelando na minha cabeça.
Comecei a pensar no meu time. Nas dependênc…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maicon Luiz Anschau</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Deep Sophistication of a Plum Background]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/smartdev72/the-deep-sophistication-of-a-plum-background-2o87</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/smartdev72/the-deep-sophistication-of-a-plum-background-2o87"/>
        <updated>2025-06-03T22:50:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Looking to create a mood that feels luxurious, mysterious, and timeless? A plum background delivers exactly that—and more.
Plum is a deep, rich hue that blends the regal tones of purple with the warmth of red. It’s bold without being brash, moody without feeling cold. A plum background adds depth, drama, and a sense of refined elegance to any design, making it a favorite among creatives who want to leave a lasting impression.
Plum symbolizes creativity, confidence, and quiet power. It’s often associated with sophistication, depth, and emotional intelligence. Unlike brighter purples or pinks, plum feels grounded—it holds weight, visually and emotionally.
Using a plum background in your design says: this isn’t just beautiful—it’s intentional.
- Luxury Branding: Ideal for high-end fashion, cosmetics, or boutique labels looking to convey richness and exclusivity.
- Event Invitations & Stationery: Perfect for evening weddings, galas, or autumn events where you want elegance with a touch of drama.
- Web Design & Portfolios: Makes visuals pop while keeping the tone sophisticated and creative.
- Social Media Graphics: Adds mood and mystery to quotes, promotions, or storytelling content.
To elevate your plum palette:
Pair with gold, brass, or rose gold for a regal, upscale look.
Use ivory or pale gray for soft contrast and readability.
Add blush pink or dusty rose for a romantic, layered tone.
Mix with forest green or navy for a rich, dramatic combo.
A plum background is more than just a dark color—it’s a design statement. It adds mood, weight, and style in one stroke. Whether you're building a brand, crafting a presentation, or designing social content, plum brings a sense of polish that never feels overdone.
Understated. Bold. Timeless. That’s the power of plum.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Miguel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Vibrant Blend of a Pink Orange Background]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/smartdev72/the-vibrant-blend-of-a-pink-orange-background-4j8h</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/smartdev72/the-vibrant-blend-of-a-pink-orange-background-4j8h"/>
        <updated>2025-06-03T22:48:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Looking for a background that’s bursting with personality? A pink orange background is your perfect match.
This playful color combination fuses the fun, flirty vibe of pink with the bold, sunny energy of orange. The result? A background that feels upbeat, modern, and full of life. Whether you’re designing for digital or print, a pink orange background adds instant warmth and visual excitement.
Pink brings charm and creativity. Orange adds confidence and vibrancy. Together, they create a lively and emotionally rich palette that feels youthful yet stylish. A pink orange background grabs attention—but it does it with joy, not force.
This makes it ideal for brands and creatives who want to stand out with positivity and flair.
- Social Media Graphics: Perfect for eye-catching posts, stories, and ads that pop in a crowded feed.
- Event Promotions: From summer parties to pop-up shops, this color combo radiates excitement.
- Youthful Branding: Great for fashion, beauty, or lifestyle brands targeting a fun-loving, trend-conscious audience.
- Product Packaging: Especially effective for cosmetics, stationery, or food items that want to feel fresh and energetic.
To make the most of this bold backdrop:
Use white or soft beige for clarity and contrast.
Pair with gold or rose gold accents for a luxe, feminine touch.
Add mint or turquoise for a vibrant, tropical twist.
Use deep plum or navy for balance and a modern edge.
A pink orange background isn’t just colorful—it’s expressive. It brings warmth, joy, and movement to your design. Whether you’re building a brand, sharing a message, or launching a product, this radiant blend makes your visuals feel alive.
If your project needs energy, attitude, and a whole lot of color—pink orange is the way to go.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Miguel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nvidia CEO Jensen Huang sings praises of processor in Nintendo Switch 2]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3010188</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/gaming-business/nvidia-ceo-jensen-huang-sings-praises-of-processor-in-nintendo-switch-2/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-03T22:48:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nvidia CEO Jensen Huang, a key supplier for the hybrid console, sang the praises of the Switch 2 and its main processor today.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dean Takahashi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Job for beginner, any help?]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/troy_25/job-for-beginner-any-help-4n91</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/troy_25/job-for-beginner-any-help-4n91"/>
        <updated>2025-06-03T22:46:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A post by T-Roy]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>T-Roy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Soft Boldness of a Pastel Red Background]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/smartdev72/the-soft-boldness-of-a-pastel-red-background-5h38</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/smartdev72/the-soft-boldness-of-a-pastel-red-background-5h38"/>
        <updated>2025-06-03T22:45:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you’re looking for a background that feels both gentle and confident, a pastel red background offers the perfect balance.
Pastel red tones down the intensity of classic red, softening it with a milky, airy finish. The result is a color that still carries the warmth and energy of red—but with a more welcoming, calming presence. It’s perfect for designs that want to express emotion without overwhelming the viewer.
Red is known for passion, excitement, and urgency. But in its pastel form, it takes on a more thoughtful and tender personality. A pastel red background is approachable, warm, and quietly energetic. It adds charm to your visuals while keeping the mood light and open.
This makes it a great choice when you want your design to feel emotionally resonant, but not overpowering.
- Lifestyle & Wellness Brands: Perfect for personal care, relationship-focused content, or heartfelt storytelling.
- Web Design & Blogs: Adds a warm touch to minimalist designs, giving them subtle personality.
- Event Invitations: Ideal for Valentine’s events, bridal showers, or spring celebrations—romantic, yet modern.
- Social Media Graphics: Stands out without screaming—great for quotes, promos, or announcements with a personal tone.
To complement this soft yet bold color:
Pair with white or soft gray for a clean, calm look.
Use peach, blush, or nude tones for a romantic, tonal palette.
Add sage green or muted blue for contrast with a natural vibe.
Try rose gold or brass accents to add elegance and warmth.
A pastel red background is all about quiet strength. It’s emotional without being dramatic, colorful without being loud. Whether you’re designing a brand, sharing a message, or setting a tone—pastel red adds heart, warmth, and visual appeal.
Soft doesn’t mean weak. With pastel red, you can be bold—and kind—all at once.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Miguel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Show HN: Ephe – A Minimalist Open-Source Markdown Paper for Today]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/unvalley/ephe</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/unvalley/ephe"/>
        <updated>2025-06-03T22:41:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Polish engineer creates postage stamp-sized 1980s Atari computer]]></title>
        <id>https://arstechnica.com/gadgets/2025/06/polish-engineer-creates-postage-stamp-sized-1980s-atari-computer/</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/gadgets/2025/06/polish-engineer-creates-postage-stamp-sized-1980s-atari-computer/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-03T22:35:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Here’s what happened in crypto today]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/what-happened-in-crypto-today</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/what-happened-in-crypto-today?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-06-03T22:00:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Need to know what happened in crypto today? Here is the latest news on daily trends and events impacting Bitcoin price, blockchain, DeFi, NFTs, Web3 and crypto regulation.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Cointelegraph</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[US military leadership to back Bitcoin strategic reserve — Senator Lummis]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/us-military-leadership-supports-strategic-bitcoin-reserve-sen-lummis</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/us-military-leadership-supports-strategic-bitcoin-reserve-sen-lummis?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-06-03T22:00:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Senator’s comments addressed the tensions between the US and China, citing US generals based in Southeast Asia.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Christopher Tepedino</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dems Say They're Blocked From Info on Verge of Crypto Market Structure Bill Hearings]]></title>
        <id>54325ef2-a05e-48a4-802e-06de6cd1387e</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2025/06/03/dems-say-they-re-blocked-from-info-on-verge-of-crypto-market-structure-bill-hearings"/>
        <updated>2025-06-03T21:42:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As the House is about to discuss its crypto market structure effort in hearings, staff for Democrats said the SEC has shut them out from technical information.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jesse Hamilton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Deep learning gets the glory, deep fact checking gets ignored]]></title>
        <id>https://rachel.fast.ai/posts/2025-06-04-enzyme-ml-fails/index.html</id>
        <link href="https://rachel.fast.ai/posts/2025-06-04-enzyme-ml-fails/index.html"/>
        <updated>2025-06-03T21:31:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CleanSpark ramps up Bitcoin mining by 9% in May, boosts hash rate, power capacity]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/cleanspark-bitcoin-mining-may-boosts-hash-rate-power-capacity</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/cleanspark-bitcoin-mining-may-boosts-hash-rate-power-capacity?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-06-03T21:30:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The miner's May output shows resilience but still lags behind competitors MARA and Riot Platforms.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Christopher Tepedino</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A deep dive into self-improving AI and the Darwin-Gödel Machine]]></title>
        <id>https://richardcsuwandi.github.io/blog/2025/dgm/</id>
        <link href="https://richardcsuwandi.github.io/blog/2025/dgm/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-03T21:19:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Activeloop (YC S18) Is Hiring Senior Back End and AI Search Engineers(Onsite, MV)]]></title>
        <id>https://careers.activeloop.ai/</id>
        <link href="https://careers.activeloop.ai/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-03T21:00:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Yoshua Bengio Launches LawZero: A New Nonprofit Advancing Safe-by-Design AI]]></title>
        <id>https://lawzero.org/en/news/yoshua-bengio-launches-lawzero-new-nonprofit-advancing-safe-design-ai</id>
        <link href="https://lawzero.org/en/news/yoshua-bengio-launches-lawzero-new-nonprofit-advancing-safe-design-ai"/>
        <updated>2025-06-03T20:57:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Can adults grow new brain cells?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.livescience.com/health/neuroscience/can-adults-grow-new-brain-cells</id>
        <link href="https://www.livescience.com/health/neuroscience/can-adults-grow-new-brain-cells"/>
        <updated>2025-06-03T20:46:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pump.fun Aiming to Raise $1B Via Token Sale at $4B Valuation: Blockworks]]></title>
        <id>37fbd8fe-cd3d-4952-905f-e94cf610c394</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/06/03/pumpfun-aiming-to-raise-1b-via-token-sale-at-4b-valuation-blockworks"/>
        <updated>2025-06-03T20:46:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Solana's SOL quickly fell about 2% on the news during late afternoon U.S. hours.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephen Alpher</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Phonely’s new AI agents hit 99% accuracy—and customers can’t tell they’re not human]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3010136</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/phonelys-new-ai-agents-hit-99-accuracy-and-customers-cant-tell-theyre-not-human/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-03T20:31:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Phonely, Maitai and Groq achieve breakthrough in AI phone support with sub-second response times and 99.2% accuracy, enabling human-level conversational AI for call centers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Nuñez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Show HN: AirAP AirPlay server - AirPlay to an iOS Device]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/neon443/AirAP</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/neon443/AirAP"/>
        <updated>2025-06-03T20:12:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Show HN: Gradle plugin for faster Java compiles]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/elide-dev/gradle</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/elide-dev/gradle"/>
        <updated>2025-06-03T19:59:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Destination: Jupiter]]></title>
        <id>https://clarkesworldmagazine.com/liptak_06_25/</id>
        <link href="https://clarkesworldmagazine.com/liptak_06_25/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-03T19:43:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Stablecoin Bills in House and Senate Still Need to Mesh on Several Points: French Hill]]></title>
        <id>35fa779c-3e4c-4ad5-9b5d-92f87295afbf</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2025/06/03/stablecoin-bills-in-house-and-senate-still-need-to-mesh-on-several-points-french-hill"/>
        <updated>2025-06-03T19:40:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The U.S. crypto bills are similar but must work out matters of acceptable foreign oversight, who regulates in the U.S. and on Big Tech issuers, the top lawmaker said.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jesse Hamilton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Show HN: An Alfred workflow to open GCP services and browse resources within]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/dineshgowda24/alfred-gcp-workflow</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/dineshgowda24/alfred-gcp-workflow"/>
        <updated>2025-06-03T19:25:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Miners Notch Gains as Meta Signs 20-Year AI Deal With Nuclear Plant]]></title>
        <id>d986cd59-9ee4-42c5-b474-8482ecd5925b</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/06/03/bitcoin-miners-notch-gains-as-meta-signs-20-year-ai-deal-with-nuclear-plant"/>
        <updated>2025-06-03T19:23:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The group may also be benefitting from a modest rise in the price of bitcoin on Tuesday.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tom Carreras</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ask HN: Options for One-Handed Typing]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=44173581</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=44173581"/>
        <updated>2025-06-03T19:17:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tokenized funds are scaling fast, hitting $5.7B — Moody’s]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/tokenized-funds-scaling-fast-hitting-5-7b-moodys</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/tokenized-funds-scaling-fast-hitting-5-7b-moodys?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-06-03T19:15:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Moody’s finds growing institutional demand for tokenized money market funds, citing benefits in liquidity, compliance and operational efficiency.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Ana Paula Pereira</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trump’s Team ‘Knows Nothing’ About Apparent ‘$TRUMP Wallet’ Launch]]></title>
        <id>af730443-cb10-431c-a7b4-31862d3e7c85</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2025/06/03/trumps-team-knows-nothing-about-apparent-trump-wallet-launch"/>
        <updated>2025-06-03T19:07:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A representative for the Trump Organization distanced the group from a new crypto app branded with the former president’s name.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Helene Braun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CVE-2024-47081: Netrc credential leak in PSF requests library]]></title>
        <id>https://seclists.org/fulldisclosure/2025/Jun/2</id>
        <link href="https://seclists.org/fulldisclosure/2025/Jun/2"/>
        <updated>2025-06-03T18:39:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Changing Directions]]></title>
        <id>https://jacobian.org/2025/jun/3/changing-directions/</id>
        <link href="https://jacobian.org/2025/jun/3/changing-directions/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-03T17:49:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Classover signs $500M convertible note deal for Solana reserve]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/classover-500m-convertible-note-deal-solana-reserve</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/classover-500m-convertible-note-deal-solana-reserve?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-06-03T17:41:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The K-12 education company has up to $900 million to purchase Solana tokens.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Christopher Tepedino</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[France Charges 25 People, Including 6 Minors, in Crypto Kidnapping Cases]]></title>
        <id>49810351-d743-443e-a078-3570a6970ed2</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2025/06/03/france-charges-25-people-including-6-minors-in-crypto-kidnapping-cases"/>
        <updated>2025-06-03T17:40:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The investigation is largely focused on the kidnapping attempt of the daughter and grandson of the CEO of crypto exchange Paymium, Pierre Noizat.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Camomile Shumba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Show HN: Localize React apps without rewriting code]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/lingodotdev/lingo.dev</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/lingodotdev/lingo.dev"/>
        <updated>2025-06-03T17:27:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Swift at Apple: Migrating the Password Monitoring Service from Java]]></title>
        <id>https://www.swift.org/blog/swift-at-apple-migrating-the-password-monitoring-service-from-java/</id>
        <link href="https://www.swift.org/blog/swift-at-apple-migrating-the-password-monitoring-service-from-java/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-03T17:03:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Miner MARA Holdings Posts Record Block Wins, Produces 950 BTC in May]]></title>
        <id>ae034c53-0e9b-4d1d-a0dd-8bc6c5436aef</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/06/03/bitcoin-miner-mara-holdings-posts-record-block-wins-produces-950-btc-in-may"/>
        <updated>2025-06-03T16:44:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The company's bitcoin output rose 35% month-over-month, hitting its highest level since the 2024 halving.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tom Carreras</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[(On | No) Syntactic Support for Error Handling]]></title>
        <id>https://go.dev/blog/error-syntax</id>
        <link href="https://go.dev/blog/error-syntax"/>
        <updated>2025-06-03T16:18:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Retail is back, but not where you think — Bitget COO]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/crypto-retail-traders-changed-bitget-executive</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/crypto-retail-traders-changed-bitget-executive?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-06-03T16:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Vugar Usi Zade dispelled the myth that retail investors are no longer interested in Bitcoin and cryptocurrency.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Sam Bourgi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OpenAI's $6.4 Billion Hardware Gamble Exposes the Closed AI Trap]]></title>
        <id>f1508be5-3847-4a81-acf7-0bb9df661c28</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/opinion/2025/06/03/openais-64-billion-hardware-gamble-exposes-the-closed-ai-trap"/>
        <updated>2025-06-03T16:02:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The group’s massive bet on Jony Ive's hardware venture isn't a strategy. It's desperation, says Shaw Walters, the founder of Eliza Labs, and creator of ElizaOS.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shaw Walters</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto policy trends to watch in 2025: Privacy, development and adoption]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/explained/crypto-policy-trends-to-watch-in-2025-privacy-development-and-adoption</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/explained/crypto-policy-trends-to-watch-in-2025-privacy-development-and-adoption?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-06-03T15:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As crypto goes mainstream, regulation is no longer a distant threat or bureaucratic detail — it’s the new foundation.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Sasha Shilina</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Is Bitcoin price going to crash again?]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/is-bitcoin-price-going-to-crash-again</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/is-bitcoin-price-going-to-crash-again?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-06-03T15:36:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin’s decreasing buyer momentum and high supply in profit could be an early sign that the top is in.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Nancy Lubale</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Epic Games reveals The State of Unreal for 2025]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3009941</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/games/epic-games-reveals-the-state-of-unreal-for-2025/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-03T15:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Epic Games unveiled the State of Unreal in a keynote speech by CEO Tim Sweeney at the Unreal Fest in Orlando, Florida.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dean Takahashi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Small World of English]]></title>
        <id>https://www.inotherwords.app/linguabase/</id>
        <link href="https://www.inotherwords.app/linguabase/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-03T15:14:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin taps $106K liquidity as bulls defend price with $260M bid]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-160k-liquidity-bulls-defend-price-260m-in-place</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-160k-liquidity-bulls-defend-price-260m-in-place?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-06-03T15:11:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BTC price action is already hunting liquidity immediately above price as support thickens, but market analysis doubts that new highs will come this week.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by William Suberg</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ATOM Surges 5% Before Forming Bearish Head-and-Shoulders Pattern]]></title>
        <id>bcbec2c1-e91e-4865-95bc-e85c4b2be59b</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/06/03/atom-surges-5-before-forming-bearish-head-and-shoulders-pattern"/>
        <updated>2025-06-03T15:09:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cosmos token shows mixed signals as Circle prepares for $7.2B NYSE valuation amid regulatory developments.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Oliver Knight</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Litecoin Breaks $90 Barrier as Traders Watch for Sustained Momentum]]></title>
        <id>5123c515-eebd-42bf-ab92-267c4a9e0673</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/06/03/litecoin-breaks-90-barrier-as-traders-watch-for-sustained-momentum"/>
        <updated>2025-06-03T15:06:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The U.S.'s latest tariff news, coupled with inflation in the eurozone falling below the ECB's target, shape LTC's macroeconomic outlook.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>AI Boost</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Agri-Tech Firm Dimitra Partners With MANTRA to Bring Cacao, Carbon Credits onto the Blockchain]]></title>
        <id>c01b61e7-a1f8-4471-bea9-cdb75b943ca2</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/06/03/agri-tech-firm-dimitra-partners-with-mantra-to-bring-cacao-carbon-credits-onto-the-blockchain"/>
        <updated>2025-06-03T15:04:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Despite MANTRA’s recent price crash, Dimitra CEO Jon Trask said that the project’s VARA license gave him the confidence to move forward with the partnership.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cheyenne Ligon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cango produced over $100M of Bitcoin in two months after mining pivot]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/better-cango-produced-100m-of-bitcoin-in-first-two-months-after-mining-pivot</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/better-cango-produced-100m-of-bitcoin-in-first-two-months-after-mining-pivot?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-06-03T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cango mined 954.5 BTC worth more than $100 million in April and May, following its full pivot to Bitcoin mining and sale of its legacy operations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Adrian Zmudzinski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DeFi must go back to its P2P roots to gain mass adoption]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/de-fi-must-go-back-to-p2-p-roots</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/de-fi-must-go-back-to-p2-p-roots?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-06-03T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[To achieve true mass adoption, DeFi must return to its P2P origins, empower people with permissionless interactions, and restore the transparency that early DeFi promised.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Jean Rausis</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AVAX Rises 3.8% on Strong Volume, Breaking Key Resistance Levels]]></title>
        <id>1940d850-ea80-4b0f-bdea-ab4c40d96fc6</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/06/03/avax-rises-3-8-on-strong-volume-breaking-key-resistance-levels"/>
        <updated>2025-06-03T14:56:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Avalanche’s token climbed from $20.52 to $21.31 on Tuesday.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>AI Boost</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto-Friendly Bank Revolut Eyes Expansion Into Derivatives]]></title>
        <id>62ff892a-44ff-4b7d-b387-c0e4a56d7b84</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2025/06/03/crypto-friendly-bank-revolut-eyes-expansion-into-derivatives"/>
        <updated>2025-06-03T14:56:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Revolut is recruiting a general manager of crypto derivatives who will be tasked with taking a new related offering "from zero to scale."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Crawley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Show HN: Controlling 3D models with voice and hand gestures]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/collidingScopes/3d-model-playground</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/collidingScopes/3d-model-playground"/>
        <updated>2025-06-03T14:45:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Michael Saylor vs. David Bailey: Different paths toward institutional Bitcoin adoption]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/explained/michael-saylor-vs-david-bailey-different-paths-toward-institutional-bitcoin-adoption</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/explained/michael-saylor-vs-david-bailey-different-paths-toward-institutional-bitcoin-adoption?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-06-03T14:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Saylor and Bailey are changing Bitcoin’s role in finance, driving corporate adoption and long-term treasury strategies.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Bradley Peak</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BNB Rises on Growing Regulatory Clarity, Renewed Trading Activity]]></title>
        <id>c6b42bee-ab4a-432c-b541-1d5824f952b6</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/06/03/bnb-rises-on-growing-regulatory-clarity-renewed-trading-activity"/>
        <updated>2025-06-03T14:42:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Coupled with strong accumulation patterns and substantial daily DEX volume, this suggests a potential bullish trend for BNB.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>AI Boost</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Show HN: PinSend – Share text between devices using a PIN(P2P, no login)]]></title>
        <id>https://pinsend.app/</id>
        <link href="https://pinsend.app/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-03T14:41:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TON Struggles Against $3.24 Resistance Level, Settles at $3.18]]></title>
        <id>14f345ae-9d78-4ba0-a56b-af8923621413</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/06/03/ton-struggles-against-324-resistance-level-settles-at-318"/>
        <updated>2025-06-03T14:39:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[TON-USD failed to establish momentum above the $3.24 resistance level, encountering significant selling pressure.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>AI Boost</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Riot Platforms Boosts Bitcoin Output to 514 BTC as Hashrate and Expansion Plans Ramp Higher]]></title>
        <id>43cfc281-0cb8-4593-a9e7-9e2fdf73242c</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/06/03/riot-platforms-boosts-bitcoin-output-to-514-btc-as-hashrate-and-expansion-plans-ramp-higher"/>
        <updated>2025-06-03T14:32:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The bitcoin miner also advanced plans to build massive data centers in Texas to support AI workloads.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tom Carreras</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What game companies can learn from AI analysis of 1.5M gamer conversations | Creativ Company]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3009963</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/games/what-game-companies-can-learn-from-ai-analysis-of-1-5m-gamer-conversations-creativ-company/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-03T14:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Creativ Company is emerging today as a new kind of market intelligence company. It uses AI to do do sentiment analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dean Takahashi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MARA increases Bitcoin production by 35% amid new hashrate highs]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/mara-increases-bitcoin-production-35-percent-new-hashrate-highs</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/mara-increases-bitcoin-production-35-percent-new-hashrate-highs?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-06-03T14:20:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With the latest mining production in May, Mara has increased its Bitcoin holdings to 49,179 BTC and has sold zero BTC, according to Chief Financial Officer Salman Khan.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Helen Partz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Open Source LLM Agent Handbook: How to Automate Complex Tasks with LangGraph and CrewAI]]></title>
        <id>683f04aedfb685791a4e8dd2</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/the-open-source-llm-agent-handbook/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-03T14:20:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ever feel like your AI tools are a bit...well, passive? Like they just sit there, waiting for your next command? Imagine if they could take initiative, break down big problems, and even work together to get things done. That's exactly what LLM agents...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Balajee Asish Brahmandam</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SUI Surges 5% Before Erasing Gains Amid Crypto Volatility]]></title>
        <id>58e5dd74-2682-4839-b7b6-2298a85ee340</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/06/03/sui-surges-5-before-erasing-gains-as-global-economic-tensions-fuel-crypto-volatility"/>
        <updated>2025-06-03T14:11:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The native token of the layer-1 blockchain platform broke key resistance on increased trading volume and bullish momentum, but erased some of its gains later.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Helene Braun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use ChatGPT to analyze crypto market movements]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/how-to-use-chatgpt-to-analyze-crypto-market-movements</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/how-to-use-chatgpt-to-analyze-crypto-market-movements?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-06-03T14:05:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Use ChatGPT to summarize market news, interpret on-chain data, compare token metrics, and spot sentiment shifts using structured prompts.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Callum Reid</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ASUS ROG Swift OLED PG32UCDP Lightning Review: Damn Near Perfect]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=354634</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/354634/asus-pg32ucdp-lightning-review/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-03T14:01:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ASUS sent over the ROG Swift OLED PG32UCDP to my lab for review. After using this gaming monitor as my daily driver for several months, I dread the day I have to return it to the brand. What Am I Looking At? Honestly, the PG32UCDP feels like a carry forward of last year’s PG32UCDM, with […]
The post ASUS ROG Swift OLED PG32UCDP Lightning Review: Damn Near Perfect appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John Law</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Symbiotic Launches 'Relay' to Bring Secure Staking Across Chains]]></title>
        <id>38b0f6bc-04fe-41ae-aafd-0c25dd8f0d71</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/tech/2025/06/03/symbiotic-launches-relay-to-bring-secure-staking-across-chains"/>
        <updated>2025-06-03T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[According to Symbiotic, the tech lets developers build verifiable, secure coordination layers for decentralized applications (dApps) across multiple chains.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Margaux Nijkerk</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto VC deals hit 2025 low despite $909M raised in May]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/crypto-vc-deal-count-2025-low-ma-2-9b-record</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/crypto-vc-deal-count-2025-low-ma-2-9b-record?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-06-03T13:59:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Analysts point to a combination of crypto and macro-specific factors, paired with the “seasonal patterns” of summer illiquidity as the main reasons for slowing investor appetite.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Zoltan Vardai</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Today's Corporate Bitcoin Holders Could be Tomorrow's Forced Sellers: StanChart]]></title>
        <id>9dad6d1f-1824-4363-be06-d56dfb01879d</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/06/03/todays-corporate-bitcoin-holders-could-be-tomorrows-forced-sellers-stanchart"/>
        <updated>2025-06-03T13:58:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sixty-one corporate treasuries now hold a combined 3.2% of the total bitcoin supply.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Will Canny</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[XRP Surges 3% as Global Tensions Boost Cross-Border Payment Utility]]></title>
        <id>de7b3a85-500b-4cc8-be40-4ceae2376e0c</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/06/03/xrp-surges-3-as-global-tensions-boost-cross-border-payment-utility"/>
        <updated>2025-06-03T13:55:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Market resilience amid geopolitical uncertainty positions XRP as a potential alternative to traditional settlement mechanisms.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shaurya Malwa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Is it a bull or bear market? How to tell the difference]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/is-it-a-bull-or-bear-market-how-to-tell-the-difference</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/is-it-a-bull-or-bear-market-how-to-tell-the-difference?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-06-03T13:48:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Identify a bull or bear market by watching price trends, trading volumes, investor sentiment, economic signals and whether optimism or fear drives the action.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Bradley Peak</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Shiba Inu Bull Momentum Limited After Buyers Offered Support]]></title>
        <id>70f2e08a-f8b9-45de-be3f-b8ab5c2f8758</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/06/03/shiba-inu-bull-momentum-limited-after-buyers-offered-support"/>
        <updated>2025-06-03T13:44:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SHIB failed to maintain gains above the 100-day simple moving average, closing at $0.00001317, a 2.9% gain over 24 hours.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>AI Boost</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[British Pound-Linked Stablecoin Unveiled at BCP Technologies]]></title>
        <id>25913daf-b2b0-453e-a46c-2d5a172d4205</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2025/06/03/uk-regulated-crypto-firm-bcp-technologies-unveils-gbp-stablecoin"/>
        <updated>2025-06-03T13:40:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The FCA-registered firm is claiming the first issuance of a UK-regulated stablecoin denominated in British pound sterling, Tokenised GBP (tGBP).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ian Allison</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Classover Taps $500M Convertible Note Deal to Boost Solana Treasury Strategy]]></title>
        <id>044367f9-e593-4301-b0d7-45a866f2f2b4</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/06/03/classover-taps-500m-convertible-note-deal-to-boost-solana-treasury-strategy"/>
        <updated>2025-06-03T13:27:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The company will allocate up to 80% of the proceeds from the notes towards SOL purchases.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Francisco Rodrigues</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Builder.ai Collapses: $1.5B 'AI' Startup Exposed as 'Indians']]></title>
        <id>https://www.ibtimes.co.uk/builderai-collapses-15bn-ai-startup-exposed-actually-indians-pretending-bots-1734784</id>
        <link href="https://www.ibtimes.co.uk/builderai-collapses-15bn-ai-startup-exposed-actually-indians-pretending-bots-1734784"/>
        <updated>2025-06-03T13:17:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CoinDesk 20 Performance Update: Solana (SOL) Gains 5.6% as Index Climbs Higher]]></title>
        <id>e4b95536-3c14-4796-a231-d7338d9542b5</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/coindesk-indices/2025/06/03/coindesk-20-performance-update-solana-sol-gains-5-6-as-index-climbs-higher"/>
        <updated>2025-06-03T13:16:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[NEAR Protocol (NEAR) was also among the top performers, rising 4.9% from Monday.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CoinDesk Indices</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[K33 Executes First Bitcoin Purchase Under New Treasury Strategy]]></title>
        <id>6ed5e92b-f2fc-4740-9f28-cf8ea95b5474</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/06/03/k33-executes-first-bitcoin-purchase-under-new-treasury-strategy"/>
        <updated>2025-06-03T13:11:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The initial 10 BTC acquisition signals long-term commitment to bitcoin integration, said the Sweden-based digital asset brokerage and research firm.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>James Van Straten</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crocodilus malware goes global with new crypto, banking heist features]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/crocodilus-android-trojan-targets-crypto-banking-apps</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/crocodilus-android-trojan-targets-crypto-banking-apps?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-06-03T13:07:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Crocodilus banking trojan is expanding globally with new campaigns targeting crypto wallets and banking apps, now reaching Europe and South America.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Amin Haqshanas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tether moves $3.9B in Bitcoin to Twenty One Capital]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/tether-bitcoin-transfer-twenty-one-capital</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/tether-bitcoin-transfer-twenty-one-capital?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-06-03T13:04:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tether and Bitfinex moved $3.9 billion in Bitcoin to Jack Mallers’ Twenty One Capital, now the third-largest corporate BTC holder after Strategy and MARA.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Ezra Reguerra</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CockroachDB’s distributed vector indexing tackles the looming AI data explosion enterprises aren’t ready for]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3009815</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/data-infrastructure/cockroachdbs-distributed-vector-indexing-tackles-the-looming-ai-data-explosion-enterprises-arent-ready-for/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-03T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Scaling distributed SQL queries needs more performance and efficiency in the agentic AI era. It’s a challenge Cockroach is looking to solve.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sean Michael Kerner</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Inside Intuit’s GenOS update: Why prompt optimization and intelligent data cognition are critical to enterprise agentic AI success]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3009858</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/inside-intuits-genos-update-why-prompt-optimization-and-intelligent-data-cognition-are-critical-to-enterprise-agentic-ai-success/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-03T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Intuit is using advanced genetic algorithms to help with prompt optimizations that could have significant impact for users.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sean Michael Kerner</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Car and chipmakers form group to develop open in-car connectivity]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3009910</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/games/car-and-chipmakers-form-group-to-develop-open-in-car-connectivity/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-03T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Automotive car makers, suppliers, semiconductor manufacturers and ecosystem partners announced the formation of the OpenGMSL Association.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dean Takahashi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vision Language Models Are Biased]]></title>
        <id>https://vlmsarebiased.github.io/</id>
        <link href="https://vlmsarebiased.github.io/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-03T12:47:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Show HN: I wrote a Java decompiler in pure C language]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/neocanable/garlic</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/neocanable/garlic"/>
        <updated>2025-06-03T12:14:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Covert Web-to-App Tracking via Localhost on Android]]></title>
        <id>https://localmess.github.io/</id>
        <link href="https://localmess.github.io/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-03T12:12:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Download: reasons to be optimistic about AI’s energy use, and Caiwei Chen’s three things]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1117693</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/06/03/1117693/the-download-reasons-to-be-optimistic-about-ais-energy-use-and-caiwei-chens-three-things/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-03T12:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is today’s edition of The Download, our weekday newsletter that provides a daily dose of what’s going on in the world of technology. Four reasons to be optimistic about AI’s energy usage Two weeks ago, we launched Power Hungry, a new series shining a light on the energy demands and carbon costs of the artificial intelligence…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rhiannon Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase data scandal sparks calls to scrap KYC]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/coinbase-data-scandal-scrap-kyc</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/coinbase-data-scandal-scrap-kyc?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-06-03T12:01:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A Coinbase insider scandal exposed 70,000 users’ personal data, triggering debates on rethinking crypto’s KYC systems.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Yohan Yun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin traders predict ‘larger correction’ as BTC price eyes sub-$100K liquidity]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-traders-predict-larger-correction-btc-price-sub-100k-liquidity</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-traders-predict-larger-correction-btc-price-sub-100k-liquidity?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-06-03T10:59:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin hovers around $105,000, but bulls struggle with upside momentum as $100,000 comes into the picture.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Nancy Lubale</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[James Wynn’s second $100M Bitcoin bet: ‘They are hunting me’]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/james-wynn-2nd-100m-bitcoin-bet-hunting-me</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/james-wynn-2nd-100m-bitcoin-bet-hunting-me?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-06-03T10:56:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Wynn has asked the crypto community for donations to help him fight the “market-making cabal” that he says is hunting for his liquidation.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Zoltan Vardai</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin miners sued over cryptography patents in US court case]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-patent-lawsuit-targets-marathon-core-scientific</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-patent-lawsuit-targets-marathon-core-scientific?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-06-03T10:36:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After buying 32,000 BlackBerry patents, Malikie Innovations sued Bitcoin miners Marathon Digital and Core Scientific over alleged use of its intellectual property.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Adrian Zmudzinski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Plutonium Mountain: The 17-year mission to guard remains of Soviet nuclear tests]]></title>
        <id>https://www.belfercenter.org/publication/plutonium-mountain-inside-17-year-mission-secure-legacy-soviet-nuclear-testing</id>
        <link href="https://www.belfercenter.org/publication/plutonium-mountain-inside-17-year-mission-secure-legacy-soviet-nuclear-testing"/>
        <updated>2025-06-03T10:06:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[There should be no Computer Art (1971)]]></title>
        <id>https://dam.org/museum/essays_ui/essays/there-should-be-no-computer-art/</id>
        <link href="https://dam.org/museum/essays_ui/essays/there-should-be-no-computer-art/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-03T10:05:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Shape of the Essay Field]]></title>
        <id>https://paulgraham.com/field.html</id>
        <link href="https://paulgraham.com/field.html"/>
        <updated>2025-06-03T09:55:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[LEGO, Aston Martin Unveil Technic Valkyrie Hypercar Set]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=354649</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/354649/lego-aston-martin-unveil-technic-valkyrie-hypercar-set/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-03T09:55:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[LEGO and Aston Martin have teamed up to create a new Technic set that brings the automaker’s hypercar, the Valkyrie, to life in brick form. This new set is also part of a wider collaboration between Lego Technic and the Gameloft Asphalt Legends UNITE gaming platform, where players can drive both the real-world Valkyrie and […]
The post LEGO, Aston Martin Unveil Technic Valkyrie Hypercar Set appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Keran</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Texas Representative Gill under fire over late $500K Bitcoin disclosures]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/texas-rep-brandon-gill-bitcoin-disclosures-stock-act</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/texas-rep-brandon-gill-bitcoin-disclosures-stock-act?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-06-03T09:35:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Texas Representative Brandon Gill faces scrutiny after filing late disclosures for $500,000 in Bitcoin trades, as questions over timing and STOCK Act violations arise.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Amin Haqshanas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Comms Minster: Meta, X Not Doing Enough To Fight Harmful Online Content]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=354640</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/354640/comms-minster-meta-x-not-doing-enough-fight-harmful-online-content/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-03T09:29:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comms minister Fahmi Fadzil says that social media giants Meta and X are not doing enough to tackle cyberbullying, scams, and other forms of harmful online content. FMT reports that he said this when launching the Communications and Multimedia Content Forum of Malaysia (CMCF) guidelines for the reporting and sharing of suicide-related content. “We cannot […]
The post Comms Minster: Meta, X Not Doing Enough To Fight Harmful Online Content appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ian Chee</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blockchain Group adds $68M in Bitcoin to corporate treasury]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/eu-blockchain-group-68m-bitcoin-treasury</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/eu-blockchain-group-68m-bitcoin-treasury?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-06-03T09:11:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Paris-based Blockchain Group acquired $68 million in Bitcoin, bringing its total holdings to 1,471 BTC amid rising institutional interest in crypto treasury strategies.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Zoltan Vardai</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Inside the effort to tally AI’s energy appetite]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1117685</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/06/03/1117685/inside-the-tedious-effort-to-tally-ais-energy-appetite/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-03T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After working on it for months, my colleague Casey Crownhart and I finally saw our story on AI’s energy and emissions burden go live last week.  The initial goal sounded simple: Calculate how much energy is used each time we interact with a chatbot, and then tally that up to understand why everyone from leaders…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>James O'Donnell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dubai regulator greenlights Ripple’s RLUSD stablecoin]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/dubai-land-department-real-estate-tokenization-ripple</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/dubai-land-department-real-estate-tokenization-ripple?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-06-03T08:55:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ripple’s RLUSD stablecoin will support the Dubai Land Department’s blockchain initiative to tokenize real estate title deeds on the XRP Ledger.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Ezra Reguerra</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gobind: AI Regulatory Framework In The Works]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=354646</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/354646/gobind-ai-regulatory-framework-in-the-works/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-03T08:37:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Malaysia aims to finalise its national regulatory framework for artificial intelligence (AI) by the end of June, Digital Minister Gobind Singh Deo confirmed. The framework, developed by the National Artificial Intelligence Office (NAIO), will serve as the foundation for the country’s governance of AI technologies, whether through new laws, regulatory guidelines or the adoption of […]
The post Gobind: AI Regulatory Framework In The Works appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Heirul Kamel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FCA-registered BCP launches British pound stablecoin]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/gpb-stablecoin-fca-registered-bcp-tgbp-launch</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/gpb-stablecoin-fca-registered-bcp-tgbp-launch?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-06-03T08:20:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BCP Technologies CEO says its new pound-backed stablecoin tGBP might be considered a “live proof-of-concept for future FCA stablecoin regulation.”]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Helen Partz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[KTM Offers 50% Discount On Komuter Fares Due To Train Delays]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=354637</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/354637/ktm-discount-komuter-train-delays/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-03T08:11:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[KTM Berhad has announced a two-day fare discount for the Klang Valley Komuter service. This comes as its signal system upgrade works, which was scheduled to take place between 31 May to 2 June, had been unexpectedly extended to 3 June, affecting daily commuters. The train operator is offering a 50% discount on all fares […]
The post KTM Offers 50% Discount On Komuter Fares Due To Train Delays appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ikmal Rozlan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Quarkdown: A modern Markdown-based typesetting system]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/iamgio/quarkdown</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/iamgio/quarkdown"/>
        <updated>2025-06-03T08:06:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gold fractal boosts Ether price potential to hit $6K]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/gold-fractal-boosts-ethereum-price-potential-6k</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/gold-fractal-boosts-ethereum-price-potential-6k?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-06-03T08:00:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fading Solana hype and rising institutional inflows are boosting Ether's fundamental strength.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Yashu Gola</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Malaysia To Tackle EV Battery Waste With Responsibility Policy]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=354630</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/354630/malaysia-tackle-ev-battery-waste-responsibility-policy/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-03T07:59:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Electric vehicles sales have seen a surge in the Malaysian market and there could be 900,000 depleted lithium-ion batteries by 2050. If this battery waste is not managed properly, it could cause major environmental and health risks. Thus, the government is emphasising ways to manage the used EV batteries. Recently, Natural Resources and Environmental Sustainability […]
The post Malaysia To Tackle EV Battery Waste With Responsibility Policy appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Keran</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Qualcomm Snapdragon X2 Elite May Get 18 Cores, 64GB RAM]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=354613</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/354613/qualcomm-snapdragon-x2-elite-18-cores-64gb-ram/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-03T07:45:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Qualcomm Snapdragon X Elite kicked off the wave of ARM-based Windows laptops. It’s no real surprise that the company is working on the next generation of laptop chips, and thanks to serial leakster Roland Quandt, we now know a bit of what it entails. This includes a simple, but maybe not necessarily as intuitive, […]
The post Qualcomm Snapdragon X2 Elite May Get 18 Cores, 64GB RAM appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ian Chee</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Revolut eyes crypto derivatives push, job listing suggests]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/revolut-crypto-derivatives-push-job-listing</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/revolut-crypto-derivatives-push-job-listing?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-06-03T07:40:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Revolut’s new job listing reveals plans to build a crypto derivatives business from scratch, leveraging its 50 million-strong global customer base.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Amin Haqshanas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rumoured ARM-Based NVIDIA APU Could Debut In Alienware Laptop Later This Year]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=354621</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/354621/nvidia-arm-based-apu-alienware/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-03T06:52:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Last week, Moore’s Law is Dead (MLID) made a claim that NVIDIA was making an ARM-based APU, with enough power to rival its last generation GeForce RTX 4070, and a potential launch window set between Q4 2025 and Q1 2026. Now, a new report suggests that the APU could see the light of day by […]
The post Rumoured ARM-Based NVIDIA APU Could Debut In Alienware Laptop Later This Year appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John Law</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ConSensys says Web3Auth acquisition to ‘greatly improve’ MetaMask UX]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/consensys-acquires-web3auth-improve-metamask-ux</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/consensys-acquires-web3auth-improve-metamask-ux?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-06-03T06:39:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ConSensys has acquired Web3Auth, which it says will help it improve the user experience for its popular MetaMask crypto wallet.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Tarang Khaitan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fun with Futex]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.fredrb.com/2025/06/02/futex-fun/</id>
        <link href="https://blog.fredrb.com/2025/06/02/futex-fun/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-03T06:37:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase aware of recently disclosed data leak since January: Reuters]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/coinbase-aware-recently-disclosed-data-leak-months-reuters</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/coinbase-aware-recently-disclosed-data-leak-months-reuters?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-06-03T06:15:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Reuters reports that Coinbase was made aware in January that an employee of an outsourcing company could have leaked its customer data, months before its recent public disclosure.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Martin Young</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[U Mobile’s U Home 5G Broadband Plan Now Includes Free “Game-Grade” 5G Router]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=354615</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/354615/u-mobile-u-home-5g-gaming-router/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-03T05:29:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[U Mobile has started offering new “game-grade” routers with its U Home 5G broadband plan. While the plan previously already included Wi-Fi 6 routers, the telco is now offering newer models optimised for gaming with faster speeds, lower latency, and wider coverage. According to the carrier, the routers feature 4×4 MIMO​ technology with support for […]
The post U Mobile’s U Home 5G Broadband Plan Now Includes Free “Game-Grade” 5G Router appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ikmal Rozlan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Leadership Transition At Proton: Ainol Azmil Appointed Acting Deputy CEO]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=354608</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/354608/leadership-transition-at-proton-ainol-azmil-appointed-acting-deputy-ceo/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-03T05:29:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There has been a leadership change at Proton, where Ainol Azmil will be covering deputy chief executive officer effective 10 June. He will be taking over the responsibilities from Roslan Abdullah who decided to step down after taking the position in January 2022. Ainol will continue his responsibility in corporate strategy and group technical procurement […]
The post Leadership Transition At Proton: Ainol Azmil Appointed Acting Deputy CEO appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Keran</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Metamorphosis of Prime Intellect (1994)]]></title>
        <id>https://localroger.com/prime-intellect/mopiall.html</id>
        <link href="https://localroger.com/prime-intellect/mopiall.html"/>
        <updated>2025-06-03T04:05:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Enterprise alert: PostgreSQL just became the database you can’t ignore for AI applications]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3009895</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/data-infrastructure/enterprise-alert-postgresql-just-became-the-database-you-cant-ignore-for-ai-applications/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-03T03:16:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Analysts provide insight on what the latest acquisition of a PostgreSQL database vendor means for enterprise data and AI.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sean Michael Kerner</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Front-End Monitoring Handbook: Track Performance, Errors, and User Behavior]]></title>
        <id>683e5606b7c8b1ebd3a32964</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/the-front-end-monitoring-handbook/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-03T01:55:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A complete frontend monitoring system is essential for tracking application performance, errors, and user behavior. It consists of three main components: data collection and reporting, data processing and storage, and data visualization. This article...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gordan Tan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How S&P is using deep web scraping, ensemble learning and Snowflake architecture to collect 5X more data on SMEs]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3009651</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/data-infrastructure/how-sp-is-using-deep-web-scraping-ensemble-learning-and-snowflake-architecture-to-collect-5x-more-data-on-smes/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-02T21:45:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Previously, S&P only had data on about 2 million SMEs, but its AI-powered RiskGauge platform expanded that to 10 million.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Taryn Plumb</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google quietly launches AI Edge Gallery, letting Android phones run AI without the cloud]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3009810</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/google-quietly-launches-ai-edge-gallery-letting-android-phones-run-ai-without-the-cloud/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-02T20:46:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google quietly launched AI Edge Gallery, an experimental Android app that runs AI models offline without internet, bringing Hugging Face models directly to smartphones with enhanced privacy.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Nuñez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OpenAI’s Sora is now available for FREE to all users through Microsoft Bing Video Creator on mobile]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3009808</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/openais-sora-is-now-available-for-free-to-all-users-through-microsoft-bing-video-creator-on-mobile/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-02T19:01:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[OpenAI‘s Sora was one of the most hyped releases of the AI era, launching in December 2024, nearly 10 months after it was first previewed to awe-struck reactions due to its — at the time, at least — unprecedented level of realism, camera dynamism, and prompt adherence and 60-second long generation clips. However, much of […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carl Franzen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Public Wi-Fi Is Dangerous – And How to Protect Yourself]]></title>
        <id>683deb300e5fd6529479c483</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/why-public-wi-fi-is-dangerous-and-how-to-protect-yourself/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-02T18:19:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Free Wi-Fi feels like a small win when you’re out. Coffee shops, airports, and hotels offer it like candy  –  just tap, connect, and you’re online.  But behind that convenience is a world of risk that most people never see coming. Let’s talk about wh...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Manish Shivanandhan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Code Linked Lists with TypeScript: A Handbook for Developers]]></title>
        <id>683dea64b88211830493d3aa</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-code-linked-lists-with-typescript-handbook/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-02T18:16:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A linked list is a data structure where each item, called a node, contains data and a pointer to the next node. Unlike arrays, which store elements in contiguous memory, linked lists connect nodes that can be scattered across memory. In this hands-on...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yazdun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Beginner’s Guide to Graphs — From Google Maps to Chessboards]]></title>
        <id>683dc829f7d4772789f06d02</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/a-beginners-guide-to-graphs/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-02T15:50:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Most of us use Google Maps without thinking twice. You open the app, check which route has the least traffic, and hit start. Then somewhere along the way – maybe you miss a turn (I do that often) – and Maps calmly recalculates your route, showing you...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tilda Udufo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Aethir enables better user acquisition via Instant Play streaming for Doctor Who: Worlds Apart]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3009700</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/games/aethir-enables-better-user-acquisition-via-instant-play-streaming-for-doctor-who-worlds-apart/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-02T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Aethir provides better computing efficiency with its Instant Play streaming solution for Doctor Who: Worlds Apart.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dean Takahashi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Download: US climate studies are being shut down, and building cities from lava]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1117675</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/06/02/1117675/the-download-us-climate-studies-are-being-shut-down-and-building-cities-from-lava/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-02T12:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is today’s edition of The Download, our weekday newsletter that provides a daily dose of what’s going on in the world of technology. The Trump administration has shut down more than 100 climate studies The Trump administration has terminated National Science Foundation grants for more than 100 research projects related to climate change, according to an…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rhiannon Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Trump administration has shut down more than 100 climate studies]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1117653</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/06/02/1117653/the-trump-administration-has-shut-down-more-than-100-climate-studies/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-02T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Trump administration has terminated National Science Foundation grants for more than 100 research projects related to climate change amid a widening campaign to slash federal funding for scientists and institutions studying the rising risks of a warming world. The move will cut off what’s likely to amount to tens of millions of dollars for…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>James Temple</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Model Context Protocol: A promising AI integration layer, but not a standard (yet)]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3009642</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/model-context-protocol-a-promising-ai-integration-layer-but-not-a-standard-yet/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-01T20:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Enterprises should experiment with MCP where it adds value, isolate dependencies and prepare for a multi-protocol future.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gopal Kuppuswamy, Cognida</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[When your LLM calls the cops: Claude 4’s whistle-blow and the new agentic AI risk stack]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3009673</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/when-your-llm-calls-the-cops-claude-4s-whistle-blow-and-the-new-agentic-ai-risk-stack/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-01T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Claude 4’s “whistle-blow” surprise shows why agentic AI risk lives in prompts and tool access, not benchmarks. Learn the 6 controls every enterprise must adopt.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matt Marshall</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The future of engineering belongs to those who build with AI, not without it]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3009633</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/the-future-of-engineering-belongs-to-those-who-build-with-ai-not-without-it/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-31T19:05:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As we look ahead, the relationship between engineers and AI systems will likely evolve from tool and user to something more symbiotic.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rizwan Patel, Altimetrik</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Micro Center nerd store fills the Fry’s vacuum with its return to Silicon Valley]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3009533</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/games/micro-center-nerd-store-fills-the-frys-vacuum-with-its-return-to-silicon-valley/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-31T13:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Micro Center, an electronics retailer, has opened a store in Silicon Valley in California And so the nerd kingdom has returned.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dean Takahashi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[QwenLong-L1 solves long-context reasoning challenge that stumps current LLMs]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3009560</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/qwenlong-l1-solves-long-context-reasoning-challenge-that-stumps-current-llms/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-30T23:39:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Alibaba's QwenLong-L1 helps LLMs deeply understand long documents, unlocking advanced reasoning for practical enterprise applications.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ben Dickson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ElevenLabs debuts Conversational AI 2.0 voice assistants that understand when to pause, speak, and take turns talking]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3009577</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/elevenlabs-debuts-conversational-ai-2-0-voice-assistants-that-understand-when-to-pause-speak-and-take-turns-talking/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-30T22:00:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With Conversational AI 2.0, ElevenLabs aims to provide tools and infrastructure for truly intelligent, context-aware enterprise voice agents.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carl Franzen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Which LLM should you use? Token Monster automatically combines multiple models and tools for you]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3009547</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/which-llm-should-you-use-token-monster-automatically-combines-multiple-models-and-tools-for-you/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-30T18:35:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This architecture lets Token Monster tap into a range of models from different providers without having to build separate integrations for each one.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carl Franzen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn to Build a Multilayer Perceptron with Real-Life Examples and Python Code]]></title>
        <id>6839f729798ea464918cffe8</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-a-multilayer-perceptron-with-examples-and-python-code/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-30T18:21:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The perceptron is a fundamental concept in deep learning, with many algorithms stemming from its original design. In this tutorial, I’ll show you how to build both single layer and multi-layer perceptrons (MLPs) across three frameworks: Custom class...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kuriko Iwai</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Microfrontends Work: From iframes to Module Federation]]></title>
        <id>6839c4a906e067fe415d54b4</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-microfrontends-work-iframes-to-module-federation/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-30T14:46:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microfrontends are transforming how teams build and deploy frontend applications at scale. This tutorial explores the architectural landscape, from traditional approaches to modern Module Federation implementations. By the end, you'll be equipped to ...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rahul gupta</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Build A Simple Portfolio Blog With Next.js]]></title>
        <id>6839c439ebab1f7974eac355</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-build-a-simple-portfolio-blog-with-nextjs/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-30T14:44:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I have written articles on different platforms including LinkedIn, The Network Bits (Substack), and freeCodeCamp. So I wanted to bring all of these articles together in a single place where someone could go and see all my work. A blog sounded like a ...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chidiadi Anyanwu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fueling seamless AI at scale]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1117440</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/05/30/1117440/fueling-seamless-ai-at-scale/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-30T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[From large language models (LLMs) to reasoning agents, today’s AI tools bring unprecedented computational demands. Trillion-parameter models, workloads running on-device, and swarms of agents collaborating to complete tasks all require a new paradigm of computing to become truly seamless and ubiquitous. First, technical progress in hardware and silicon design is critical to pushing the boundaries…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>MIT Technology Review Insights</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Sort Dates Efficiently in JavaScript]]></title>
        <id>6839b592f8650e337982bcba</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-sort-dates-efficiently-in-javascript/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-30T13:41:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Recently, I was working on a PowerApps Component Framework (PCF) project that required sorting an array of objects by date. The dates were in ISO 8601 format but without a time zone – for example, "2025-05-01T15:00:00.00". Without much thought, I wro...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brandon Wozniewicz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Survive in Tech When Everything's Changing w/ 21-year Veteran Dev Joe Attardi [Podcast #174]]]></title>
        <id>6839abf3d23bb1460e9ea0ea</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-survive-in-tech-when-everythings-changing-w-21-year-veteran-dev-joe-attardi-podcast-174/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-30T13:00:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On this week's episode of the podcast, freeCodeCamp founder Quincy Larson interviews Joe Attardi. He's a software engineer and prolific author of programming books. We talk about: How software development has changed over the past 21 years Tips for s...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Download: sycophantic LLMs, and the AI Hype Index]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1117620</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/05/30/1117620/the-download-sycophantic-llms-and-the-ai-hype-index/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-30T12:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is today’s edition of The Download, our weekday newsletter that provides a daily dose of what’s going on in the world of technology. This benchmark used Reddit’s AITA to test how much AI models suck up to us Back in April, OpenAI announced it was rolling back an update to its GPT-4o model that made ChatGPT’s…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rhiannon Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This benchmark used Reddit’s AITA to test how much AI models suck up to us]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1117551</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/05/30/1117551/this-benchmark-used-reddits-aita-to-test-how-much-ai-models-suck-up-to-us/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-30T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Back in April, OpenAI announced it was rolling back an update to its GPT-4o model that made ChatGPT’s responses to user queries too sycophantic.  An AI model that acts in an overly agreeable and flattering way is more than just annoying. It could reinforce users’ incorrect beliefs, mislead people, and spread misinformation that can be…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rhiannon Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FLUX.1 Kontext enables in-context image generation for enterprise AI pipelines]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3009464</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/flux-1-kontext-enables-in-context-image-generation-for-enterprise-ai-pipelines/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-29T23:32:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[FLUX.1 Kontext from Black Forest Labs aims to let users edit images multiple times through both text and reference images without losing speed.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Emilia David</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Emotive voice AI startup Hume launches new EVI 3 model with rapid custom voice creation]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3009430</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/emotive-voice-ai-startup-hume-launches-new-evi-3-model-with-rapid-custom-voice-creation/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-29T18:50:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While EVI 3’s specific API pricing has not been announced yet (marked as TBA), the pattern suggests it will be usage-based.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carl Franzen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Powering High-Performance Web3 Experiences: Gravity (by Galxe) Launches on QuickNode]]></title>
        <id>683622d561c46d0001eed5d9</id>
        <link href="https://blog.quicknode.com/gravity-alpha-launch/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-29T13:54:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Explore Galxe Gravity’s omnichain power on QuickNode. Build scalable, identity-centric dApps effortlessly with dedicated endpoints and developer tools.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>QuickNode</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DeepSeek R1-0528 arrives in powerful open source challenge to OpenAI o3 and Google Gemini 2.5 Pro]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3009405</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/deepseek-r1-0528-arrives-in-powerful-open-source-challenge-to-openai-o3-and-google-gemini-2-5-pro/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-29T13:22:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Additionally, the model’s hallucination rate has been reduced, contributing to more reliable and consistent output.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carl Franzen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Snowflake’s open-source text-to-SQL and Arctic inference models solve enterprise AI’s two biggest deployment headaches]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3009218</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/how-snowflakes-open-source-text-to-sql-and-arctic-inference-models-solve-enterprise-ais-two-biggest-deployment-headaches/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-29T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New open-source efforts from Snowflake aim to help solve that unsolved challenges of text-to-SQL and inference performance for enterprise AI.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sean Michael Kerner</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Encharge AI unveils EN100 AI accelerator chip with analog memory]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3009330</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/games/encharge-ai-unveils-en100-ai-accelerator-chip-with-analog-memory/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-29T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[EnCharge AI, a startup that raised $144 million to date, announced the EnCharge EN100, an AI accelerator built on analog in-memory computing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dean Takahashi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Peer launches Global Simulation as real-time digital Earth with AI agents]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3009041</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/games/peer-launches-global-simulation-as-real-time-digital-earth-with-ai-agents/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-29T12:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Peer launched Global Simulation, a real-time digital Earth where players use avatars to connect by location and build relationships in a living, spatial network.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dean Takahashi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Download: the next anti-drone weapon, and powering AI’s growth]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1117539</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/05/29/1117539/the-download-the-next-anti-drone-weapon-and-powering-ais-growth/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-29T12:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is today’s edition of The Download, our weekday newsletter that provides a daily dose of what’s going on in the world of technology. This giant microwave may change the future of war Imagine: China deploys hundreds of thousands of autonomous drones in the air, on the sea, and under the water—all armed with explosive warheads or…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rhiannon Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What will power AI’s growth?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1117500</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/05/29/1117500/ai-energy-growth-nuclear-natural-gas/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-29T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s been a little over a week since we published Power Hungry, a package that takes a hard look at the expected energy demands of AI. Last week in this newsletter, I broke down the centerpiece of that package, an analysis I did with my colleague James O’Donnell. (In case you’re still looking for an…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Casey Crownhart</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This giant microwave may change the future of war]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1117502</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/05/29/1117502/epirus-drone-zapping-microwave-us-military-defense/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-29T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Imagine: China deploys hundreds of thousands of autonomous drones in the air, on the sea, and under the water—all armed with explosive warheads or small missiles. These machines descend in a swarm toward military installations on Taiwan and nearby US bases, and over the course of a few hours, a single robotic blitzkrieg overwhelms the US…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sam Dean</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DanaBot takedown shows how agentic AI cut months of SOC analysis to weeks]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008704</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/security/agentic-ai-defeated-danabot-exposing-key-lessons-for-soc-teams/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-29T00:23:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Agentic AI played a decisive role in dismantling DanaBot, a Russian malware platform responsible for more than 50 million dollars in damages.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Louis Columbus</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[s3: The new RAG framework that trains search agents with minimal data]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3009182</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/s3-the-new-rag-framework-that-trains-search-agents-with-minimal-data/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T22:51:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[S3 decouples RAG search from generation, boosting efficiency and generalization for enterprise LLM applications with minimal data.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ben Dickson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mistral launches new code embedding model that outperforms OpenAI and Cohere in real-world retrieval tasks]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3009248</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/mistral-launches-new-code-embedding-model-that-outperforms-openai-and-cohere-in-real-world-retrieval-tasks/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T22:11:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mistral's Codestral Embed will help make RAG use cases faster and find duplicate code segments using natural language.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Emilia David</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nvidia CEO takes a shot at U.S. policy cutting off AI chip sales to China]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3009278</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/games/nvidia-ceo-takes-a-shot-at-u-s-policy-cutting-off-ai-chip-sales-to-china/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T21:36:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nvidia CEO Jensen Huang tiptoed into politics with a comment taking a shot at the U.S. policy that has cut off sales of his chips to China.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dean Takahashi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[QuickNode Accelerator - ChaiNova]]></title>
        <id>68377c476b77cd0001482835</id>
        <link href="https://blog.quicknode.com/quicknode-accelerator-chainova/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T21:31:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ChaiNova joins QuickNode’s Accelerator to bring inclusive Web3 access from local shops to global enterprises.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>QuickNode</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[QuickNode Accelerator - SettleX]]></title>
        <id>6813ad1304ef2c0001211afb</id>
        <link href="https://blog.quicknode.com/quicknode-accelerator-settlex/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T16:00:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discover SettleX, a modular cross-chain clearing layer improving capital efficiency, privacy, and liquidity across the DeFi landscape.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>QuickNode</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[QuickNode Accelerator - taro/NYU]]></title>
        <id>68222cb536cbae0001089a2b</id>
        <link href="https://blog.quicknode.com/quicknode-accelerator-taro/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T15:59:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Taro is a privacy-first blockchain project from NYU and Microsoft, enhancing financial transparency and accountability in organizations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>QuickNode</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[QuickNode Accelerator - Mements]]></title>
        <id>68222d3a36cbae0001089a38</id>
        <link href="https://blog.quicknode.com/quicknode-accelerator-mements/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T15:59:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mements is building infrastructure for verifiable AI, with timestamped prompts, provable video streaming, and the launch of MemeChain.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>QuickNode</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[QuickNode Accelerator - EcoFundMe]]></title>
        <id>6822330f36cbae0001089a61</id>
        <link href="https://blog.quicknode.com/quicknode-accelerator-ecofundme/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T15:59:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[EcoFundMe connects donors to verified climate projects with tokenized contributions, DAO governance, and transparent onchain funding.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>QuickNode</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[QuickNode Accelerator - Rivalz Network]]></title>
        <id>68248d91bf7346000109494e</id>
        <link href="https://blog.quicknode.com/quicknode-accelerator-rivalz-network/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T15:59:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Rivalz is building verifiable AI infrastructure, enabling smart contracts to query AI oracles, real-world data, and autonomous agents.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>QuickNode</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[QuickNode Accelerator - Hangry Animals]]></title>
        <id>68236ae084101f00013a5cd0</id>
        <link href="https://blog.quicknode.com/quicknode-accelerator-hangry-animals/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T15:58:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hangry Animals blends storytelling, Web3, and social good into a transmedia universe where players own, earn, and impact real causes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>QuickNode</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[QuickNode Accelerator - Boost Ad Network]]></title>
        <id>6813cc2f04ef2c0001211b24</id>
        <link href="https://blog.quicknode.com/quicknode-accelerator-boost-ad-network/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T15:58:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Boost is an onchain-native, privacy-first ad network with verifiable auctions, real attribution, and campaign analytics for Web3.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>QuickNode</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[QuickNode Accelerator - Diamondz Shadow Movies]]></title>
        <id>6824f61dbf734600010949a1</id>
        <link href="https://blog.quicknode.com/quicknode-accelerator-diamondz-shadow-movies/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T15:58:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Diamondz Shadow is creating a blockchain-powered entertainment ecosystem spanning games, film, tokenized media, and real-world utility.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>QuickNode</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[QuickNode Accelerator - Badchain]]></title>
        <id>6825fdc9bf734600010949cf</id>
        <link href="https://blog.quicknode.com/quicknode-accelerator-badchain/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T15:57:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Badchain is Solana’s culture layer, where behavior drives rewards through meme quests, raffles, and community-led incentives.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>QuickNode</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[QuickNode Accelerator - CVEX]]></title>
        <id>68248962bf7346000109492e</id>
        <link href="https://blog.quicknode.com/quicknode-accelerator-cvex/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T15:57:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CVEX is launching Smart Clearing for DeFi, a decentralized derivatives protocol unlocking capital efficiency and scalable markets.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>QuickNode</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[QuickNode Accelerator - Archer Protocol]]></title>
        <id>68248c8fbf7346000109493f</id>
        <link href="https://blog.quicknode.com/quicknode-accelerator-archer-protocol/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T15:57:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Archer is redesigning Web3 UX with natural language trading, multichain intents, and a non-custodial platform for everyone.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>QuickNode</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[QuickNode Accelerator - SNFT Chain]]></title>
        <id>6813ac5b04ef2c0001211aee</id>
        <link href="https://blog.quicknode.com/quicknode-accelerator-snft/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T15:55:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SNFT Chain connects digital assets and physical devices through scalable L2 infrastructure built for creators and tokenized experiences.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>QuickNode</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[QuickNode Accelerator - Creator Network]]></title>
        <id>682234a636cbae0001089a75</id>
        <link href="https://blog.quicknode.com/quicknode-accelerator-creator-network/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T15:55:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Creator Network is a modular L2 for AI-native applications, empowering builders, creators, and ecosystems with low fees and fast UX.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>QuickNode</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>