<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2025-05-08T16:50:22.037Z</id>
    <title>AngJianming RSS Feed</title>
    <updated>2025-05-08T16:50:22.037Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Integrating MLflow with KubeFlow (Revised Edition)]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/prezaei/integrating-mlflow-with-kubeflow-revised-edition-3mf</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/prezaei/integrating-mlflow-with-kubeflow-revised-edition-3mf"/>
        <updated>2025-05-08T16:39:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[MLflow—a robust open-source platform that simplifies the management of the machine learning lifecycle, including experimentation, reproducibility, and deployment. By integrating MLflow into Kubeflow, users can leverage MLflow’s intuitive UI and comprehensive model registry capabilities to enhance their machine learning workflows.
In the modern enterprise landscape, the demand for streamlined and scalable Machine Learning Operations (MLOps) frameworks has never been greater. With increasing complexities in model development, tracking, deployment, and monitoring, organizations need tools that seamlessly integrate to ensure efficiency and reliability. MLflow and Kubeflow are two such tools that, when integrated, provide a robust end-to-end solution for managing machine learning workflows. MLf…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pejman Rezaei</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[Boost]]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/omarnaguib/-3o4k</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/omarnaguib/-3o4k"/>
        <updated>2025-05-08T16:38:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tool translation: the joy of efficient software
Omar Naguib ・ Apr 23
#programming
        #productivity
        #softwaredevelopment]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Omar Naguib</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Jinja: The Templating Wizard That Saves Devs From Keyboard Trauma]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/medrix/jinja-the-templating-wizard-that-saves-devs-from-keyboard-trauma-55n6</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/medrix/jinja-the-templating-wizard-that-saves-devs-from-keyboard-trauma-55n6"/>
        <updated>2025-05-08T16:37:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[💡 What is Jinja?


🧙‍♂️ Jinja is a modern and designer-friendly templating language for Python, used to generate files dynamically. Think of it like Mad Libs for config files, where you can inject variables into a template and programmatically generate output.
It’s used heavily in:
Any scenario where you want to avoid copy-paste hell 🔥
Infrastructure as Code (Ansible, SaltStack)
Web frameworks (like Flask or Django)
Easy to learn if you have experience some template engine such as Laravel Blade, Twig, Haml, 11ty
### 🎯 Why Use Jinja?
Use Jinja when you want to:
Reduce human errors by avoiding repetitive copy-paste
Dynamically change parameters like server names, ports, or environments
Reusable: You can write once and render thousands of variations. Efficiency FTW.
Clean separation: Keep…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>samnang rosady</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Latency and Throughput: Optimizing Application Performance]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/boris_burakovski_c7420552/latency-and-throughput-optimizing-application-performance-4bhe</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/boris_burakovski_c7420552/latency-and-throughput-optimizing-application-performance-4bhe"/>
        <updated>2025-05-08T16:37:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When discussing latency and throughput, they are often framed in the context of networking. However, these metrics are just as critical when evaluating application and server performance. In applications, latency measures how quickly a request is processed and responded to, while throughput reflects how many requests or transactions a system can handle within a given timeframe. Optimizing both is essential to ensure fast, efficient operations, especially in high-demand environments. Understanding how these metrics apply to applications—and how to balance them—can drastically improve user experience and system scalability.
Definition: Latency is the time it takes for a request to be processed and a response to be returned. It refers to the delay between a user action (like clicking a button…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Boris Burakovski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WordPress Nonces: Your First Line of Defense Against CSRF]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/farhan-developer/wordpress-nonces-your-first-line-of-defense-against-csrf-p77</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/farhan-developer/wordpress-nonces-your-first-line-of-defense-against-csrf-p77"/>
        <updated>2025-05-08T16:37:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ever wondered how WordPress prevents those sneaky, behind-the-scenes attacks? My new piece uncovers the unsung hero: WordPress Nonces. Understanding this core security feature is non-negotiable for any serious WordPress developer. Discover the power: https://farhanali.me/wordpress-nonces-your-first-line-of-defense-against-csrf/]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Farhan Ali</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[207/365 | ¥10M Job Challenge - Updates frequency]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/kameken100/207365-y10m-job-challenge-updates-frequency-1pjd</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/kameken100/207365-y10m-job-challenge-updates-frequency-1pjd"/>
        <updated>2025-05-08T16:29:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Actually, I think it makes more sense to update weekly. Weekdays should be focused on getting results, and then over the weekend, I can take time to reflect on the week’s progress and plan goals for the next one — that seems more practical.
That said, I’ll do my best to keep up this daily habit until I hit 365 days. Like I mentioned before, it’s a daily reminder of the goals that really matter to me.
This idea gave me some better direction — it’s Friday, let’s keep it up!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>転職カメ</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Zero-Downtime Django Deployments on Kubernetes — Blue-Green Strategy & Safe Migrations]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/pranav_dixit_8b5a2ad19270/zero-downtime-django-deployments-on-kubernetes-blue-green-strategy-safe-migrations-7p1</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/pranav_dixit_8b5a2ad19270/zero-downtime-django-deployments-on-kubernetes-blue-green-strategy-safe-migrations-7p1"/>
        <updated>2025-05-08T16:28:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[🚀 Say goodbye to downtime during Django deployments!

This guide dives deep into how to safely deploy Django apps on Kubernetes using a Blue-Green strategy, all while ensuring your database migrations don’t break production.
This blog is perfect for:
🧑‍💻 Django developers deploying on Kubernetes
🛠️ DevOps engineers building robust CI/CD pipelines
⚙️ Teams that want rollback-safe deployments
✅ Setting up Blue-Green deployments in Kubernetes

✅ Handling safe database migrations without breaking live traffic

✅ Automating with GitHub Actions

✅ Avoiding common migration pitfalls

✅ Using readiness probes for validation

✅ Building a rollback strategy that just works
Django 4.x
PostgreSQL
Kubernetes (kubectl, manifests, jobs)
GitHub Actions for CI/CD
Docker
Learn how to break down your schema changes in three safe steps:  
Add with null=True

Backfill data via job

Remove null=True with confidence



This helps you avoid:
NodeNotFoundError
Locking your production DB
Breaking running containers
🧵 Full blog with step-by-step implementation and diagrams:

👉 Zero-Downtime Django Deployments on Kubernetes
Let’s connect and chat about scalable Django deployments!

🐦 @pranavdixit20 on Twitter

💼 LinkedIn

💻 Projects on GitHub]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pranav Dixit</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[High tariffs become 'real' with our first $36K bill]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.adafruit.com/2025/05/08/high-tariffs-become-real-with-our-first-36k-bill/</id>
        <link href="https://blog.adafruit.com/2025/05/08/high-tariffs-become-real-with-our-first-36k-bill/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-08T16:27:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[send mail with php]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/luca_8e2b21/send-mail-with-php-3h6l</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/luca_8e2b21/send-mail-with-php-3h6l"/>
        <updated>2025-05-08T16:27:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I have a problem that I can't figure out, it doesn't send confirmation emails after booking or to the owner, if someone can help me figure out where the error is
I would like to understand where the error is that prevents sending
<?php
// Log degli errori per debug
// Verifica metodo
// Ottieni e decodifica JSON
// Funzione di sanificazione
// Estrai e normalizza
// Normalizza l'orario nel formato HH:MM con lo zero iniziale
$service = isset($data['service']) ? sanitizeInput($data['service']) : '';
// Validazione
if (!empty($email) && !filter_var($email, FILTER_VALIDATE_EMAIL)) {
if (!empty($date) && !preg_match('/^\d{4}-\d{2}-\d{2}$/', $date)) {
if (!empty($time) && !preg_match('/^([01][0-9]|2[0-3]):[0-5][0-9]$/', $time)) {
$validServices = ['haircut', 'haircut-beard', 'beard', 'shave', 'k…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luca D</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Burgerinator 3D: Interactive Burger Builder]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/preetha_vaishnavi_2b82358/burgerinator-3d-interactive-burger-builder-28j</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/preetha_vaishnavi_2b82358/burgerinator-3d-interactive-burger-builder-28j"/>
        <updated>2025-05-08T16:21:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Check out this Pen I made!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>preetha vaishnavi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Notes on building a SCIM endpoint from scratch]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/saif_shines/notes-on-building-a-scim-endpoint-from-scratch-cgc</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/saif_shines/notes-on-building-a-scim-endpoint-from-scratch-cgc"/>
        <updated>2025-05-08T16:20:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ever had to deal with automated user provisioning?


If you’ve ever integrated an enterprise identity provider (like Okta or Azure AD), chances are you’ve bumped into SCIM 2.0. It’s one of those specs that sounds simple—“standardized user provisioning”—until you dig in and realize...it’s a protocol prescribing with its own schema, rules, and quirks.
At Scalekit, we were testing out what it’s like to build a production-ready SCIM 2.0 endpoint, and I want to share what I learned—so you don’t spend hours banging your head against a hard surface :-D 
Let’s roll...
First things first: What is SCIM?
SCIM (System for Cross-domain Identity Management) is a standard designed to make user provisioning and deprovisioning across services easier for enterprises. It prescribes a implementation for the y…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Saif</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ketika Golang Dipilih untuk Kirim Pesan Yang Sibuk]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/hasan197/ketika-golang-dipilih-untuk-kirim-pesan-yang-sibuk-jak</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/hasan197/ketika-golang-dipilih-untuk-kirim-pesan-yang-sibuk-jak"/>
        <updated>2025-05-08T16:20:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bayangkan sebuah kota metropolitan di zaman belum ada telepon dan internet. Ribuan surat datang setiap hari ke kantor pos pusat, dan harus dibagikan ke rumah-rumah atau kantor di seluruh penjuru kota. Jika hanya satu tukang pos yang bertugas, tentu surat akan menumpuk, pengiriman jadi lambat, dan banyak pesan penting yang terlambat sampai. Tapi bagaimana jika ada puluhan, bahkan ratusan tukang pos yang bisa bekerja bersama, saling membantu, dan semuanya bisa berkoordinasi dengan baik? Inilah gambaran sederhana mengapa sistem pengiriman pesan yang canggih membutuhkan teknologi yang tepat.
Mengapa Golang? Karena Golang seperti pasukan tukang pos super cepat yang bisa bergerak serempak tanpa saling tabrakan. Dalam dunia komputer, ini disebut concurrency—kemampuan melakukan banyak hal sekaligu…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mohamad Hasan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CSS image slider w/ next/prev buttons]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/preetha_vaishnavi_2b82358/css-image-slider-w-nextprev-buttons-1m84</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/preetha_vaishnavi_2b82358/css-image-slider-w-nextprev-buttons-1m84"/>
        <updated>2025-05-08T16:18:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Check out this Pen I made!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>preetha vaishnavi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Progress toward fusion energy gain as measured against the Lawson criteria]]></title>
        <id>https://www.fusionenergybase.com/articles/continuing-progress-toward-fusion-energy-breakeven-and-gain-as-measured-against-the-lawson-criteria</id>
        <link href="https://www.fusionenergybase.com/articles/continuing-progress-toward-fusion-energy-breakeven-and-gain-as-measured-against-the-lawson-criteria"/>
        <updated>2025-05-08T15:49:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Tops $100K for First Time in 3 Months; Are Upside Targets Too Low?]]></title>
        <id>3caf7639-a5b3-40db-87a5-ecfb096e2838</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/02/bitcoin-tops-usd100k-for-first-time-in-3-months-are-upside-targets-too-low"/>
        <updated>2025-05-08T15:38:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The price has jumped 33% in a few weeks after plunging to $75,000 in the days following President Trump's early April Liberation Day tariff announcement.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephen Alpher</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OpenAI names Instacart leader Fidji Simo as new CEO of Applications]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3006978</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/openai-names-instacart-leader-fidji-simo-as-new-ceo-of-applications/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-08T15:25:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Simo’s appointment may also hint at a broader productization push within OpenAI. Her background at Facebook and Instacart underscores...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carl Franzen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin price reclaims $100K for first time since January]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-hits-100k-first-time-since-january</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-hits-100k-first-time-since-january?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-08T15:22:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin has reclaimed the $100,000 price level for the first time since January, reflecting renewed bullish sentiment among investors.
Bitcoin (BTC) reclaimed the $100,000 mark on May 8 at 3:22 pm UTC, surging 4.2% from the intraday low of $95,967, according to data from CoinGecko.
It marked the third time that BTC has broken through the six-figure level since first achieving it on Dec. 5, 2024. A second all-time high followed on Jan. 20 ahead of US President Donald Trump’s inauguration.
Bitcoin price chart in the past year. Source: CoinGecko
Unlike the previous $100,000 hits, the new price spike came as Bitcoin market dominance surged above 60%, reflecting potential bearish sentiment for altcoins.
Bitcoin dominance below 60% in past $100,000 breakthroughs
Bitcoin dominance — the asset’s s…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Helen Partz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ex-Celsius CEO asks to travel for a wedding after sentencing]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/alex-mashinsky-celsius-sentencing-wedding-travel</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/alex-mashinsky-celsius-sentencing-wedding-travel?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-08T15:17:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Former Celsius CEO Alex Mashinsky will probably be allowed to travel for his daughter’s wedding regardless of the outcome of his May 8 sentencing hearing.
In a May 8 filing in the US District Court for the Southern District of New York, Judge John Koeltl approved an application for Mashinsky to travel from New York to Memphis, Tennessee, between May 26 and May 29 for his daughter’s wedding. The approval was available on the public docket as of May 8, but appeared to have been removed at the time of publication.
Alex Mashinsky’s request to travel for his daughter’s wedding. Source: PACER
Judge Koeltl will determine in a May 8 hearing whether Mashinsky serves prison time following a plea deal with prosecutors.
The former Celsius CEO appeared ready to go to trial in 2024 until his lawyers los…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Turner Wright</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Senate Republicans Making Plea to Get on With Stablecoin Debate]]></title>
        <id>f0785da5-57a1-4ecf-99a9-1f64bb84ac8f</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2025/05/08/senate-republicans-making-plea-to-get-on-with-stablecoin-debate"/>
        <updated>2025-05-08T15:08:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Once-allied Democrats continue to drag their heels on the first big crypto bill, leaving a key vote in doubt as GOP Majority Leader Thune calls for action.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jesse Hamilton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto for Advisors: Trends in Tokenizing Real-World Assets]]></title>
        <id>b842342d-8b85-40e5-a277-0d942aa00390</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/coindesk-indices/2025/05/07/crypto-for-advisors-trends-in-tokenizing-real-world-assets"/>
        <updated>2025-05-08T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tokenization turns real-world assets into blockchain tokens, boosting efficiency, liquidity and accessibility. Learn about why Ethereum is the current leader in this space.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tedd Strazimiri</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[User experience could be crypto’s superpower—or its kryptonite]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/user-experience-crypto-s-superpower</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/user-experience-crypto-s-superpower?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-08T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Opinion by Jonathan Farnell, CEO of Freedx
It’s 2025, and over 560 million people worldwide are already using cryptocurrency — roughly 17 times the population of Tokyo. That’s a vibrant community, yet for every user who’s embraced it, billions more stand on the sidelines, put off by the complicated interactions and clunky interfaces of protocols, platforms, decentralized apps (DApps), and mobile applications. Why? Blockchain technology offers game-changing potential — decentralized ownership, secure trades — but let’s face it: Most people still find it intimidating, risky, and confusing. User experience (UX) might just be the deciding factor in whether cryptocurrency achieves mass adoption or remains a niche segment.
Take complexity. A 2024 Chainalysis report pointed out that 43% of would-…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Jonathan Farnell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Breakout Alert: Ether, Bitcoin Cash-Bitcoin Ratio Break Downtrends as DOGE, SHIB Bottom Out]]></title>
        <id>47d52b24-b2a0-49d4-97e9-7912e7196447</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/08/breakout-alert-ether-bitcoin-cash-bitcoin-ratio-break-downtrends-doge-shib-bottom-out"/>
        <updated>2025-05-08T14:42:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ETH, BCH and top memecoins are flashing bullish chart patterns.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Omkar Godbole</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Huawei unveils laptop running self-developed HarmonyOS as Windows licence expire]]></title>
        <id>https://www.scmp.com/tech/big-tech/article/3309569/huawei-unveils-first-laptop-running-self-developed-harmonyos-windows-licence-expires</id>
        <link href="https://www.scmp.com/tech/big-tech/article/3309569/huawei-unveils-first-laptop-running-self-developed-harmonyos-windows-licence-expires"/>
        <updated>2025-05-08T14:24:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GSR’s Josh Riezman on Regulation, Risk, and Readying Crypto for the Next Phase]]></title>
        <id>07207794-a009-461a-839b-c1e82dc89e52</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/consensus-toronto-2025-coverage/2025/05/08/gsrs-josh-riezman-on-regulation-risk-and-readying-crypto-for-the-next-phase"/>
        <updated>2025-05-08T14:11:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The market-maker, investor and asset manager aims to be a “one-stop shop for market participants,” says its Chief Strategy Officer. Riezman is a speaker at Consensus 2025 May 14-16.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Francisco Rodrigues</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Superstate Expands Into Tokenized Equities; SOL Strategies to Be First Listing]]></title>
        <id>6b1ea7b7-1c49-4659-84bd-828e67ef0d0f</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2025/05/08/superstate-expands-into-tokenized-equities-sol-strategies-to-be-first-listing"/>
        <updated>2025-05-08T14:00:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The company's "Opening Bell" platform lets SEC-registered shares trade on-chain, bridging crypto and public equity markets.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Krisztian Sandor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[20 years to give away virtually all my wealth]]></title>
        <id>https://www.gatesnotes.com/home/home-page-topic/reader/n20-years-to-give-away-virtually-all-my-wealth</id>
        <link href="https://www.gatesnotes.com/home/home-page-topic/reader/n20-years-to-give-away-virtually-all-my-wealth"/>
        <updated>2025-05-08T13:59:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trump's NIH axed research grants even after a judge blocked the cuts]]></title>
        <id>https://www.propublica.org/article/trump-nih-cuts-transgender-research-grants</id>
        <link href="https://www.propublica.org/article/trump-nih-cuts-transgender-research-grants"/>
        <updated>2025-05-08T13:57:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin miner Hut 8 grows hashrate 79% despite $134M quarterly loss]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/hut8-q1-2025-hashrate-expansion-loss</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/hut8-q1-2025-hashrate-expansion-loss?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-08T13:51:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency mining firm Hut 8 increased its hashrate by 79% during the first quarter of the year.
According to Hut8’s latest quarterly report released on May 8, the firm saw a net loss of $134.3 million despite revenue of $21.8 million. The firm’s CEO, Asher Genoot, explained that this was a result of large-scale investments. 
“As reflected in our results, the first quarter was a deliberate and necessary phase of investment,” Genoot said. “We believe the returns on this work will become increasingly visible in the quarters ahead.”
Hut 8 operations reached a total energy capacity of 1,020 megawatts as of March 31, enough to power well over 800,000 average homes in the United States. The company also has the right to scale up its operation by another 2,600 MW.
Related: Bitcoin mining — In…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Adrian Zmudzinski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How the Democrats’ Path to 2026 Victory Goes Through Decentralized Crypto]]></title>
        <id>d5c765d2-6ca8-4def-bfa3-90b824eacb57</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/opinion/2025/05/08/how-the-democrats-path-to-2026-victory-goes-through-decentralized-crypto"/>
        <updated>2025-05-08T13:41:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The current draft of the GENIUS Act elevates centralized entities in overseeing stablecoins. Democrats should take the right stand against it, says Hermine Wong.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hermine Wong</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google to back three new nuclear projects]]></title>
        <id>https://www.esgtoday.com/google-to-back-three-new-advanced-nuclear-projects/</id>
        <link href="https://www.esgtoday.com/google-to-back-three-new-advanced-nuclear-projects/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-08T13:36:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Here’s what happened in crypto today]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/what-happened-in-crypto-today</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/what-happened-in-crypto-today?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-08T13:33:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today in crypto, Coinbase has agreed to acquire crypto options trading platform Deribit in a deal worth $2.9 billion, Arizona’s governor signed a “Bitcoin Reserve Fund” into law, and Robinhood plans a blockchain for tokenized securities offerings in Europe.
Coinbase to acquire options trading platform Deribit for $2.9 billion
Coinbase, the largest cryptocurrency exchange in the US by trading volume, has agreed to acquire Deribit, one of the world’s biggest crypto derivatives trading platforms.
Coinbase Global will acquire Deribit for about $2.9 billion, the exchange announced on May 8.
The acquisition will allow Coinbase to expand into the profitable crypto derivatives market and continue scaling the platform’s global growth, Greg Tusar, Coinbase’s vice president of institutional product, …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Cointelegraph</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[QueryHub]]></title>
        <id>https://www.queryhub.ai/blog/introducing-queryhub</id>
        <link href="https://www.queryhub.ai/blog/introducing-queryhub"/>
        <updated>2025-05-08T13:32:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Beyond digital gold, Bitcoin’s next chapter is about to be unlocked — Dan Held]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/beyond-digital-gold-bitcoin-s-next-chapter-is-about-to-be-unlocked-dan-held</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/beyond-digital-gold-bitcoin-s-next-chapter-is-about-to-be-unlocked-dan-held?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-08T13:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin (BTC) has long been branded as “digital gold,” a store of value for believers in scarcity, decentralization and self-sovereignty. As institutional interest grows, geopolitics shift, and new layers emerge on Bitcoin’s stack, is it time for the narrative to evolve? 
In this episode of The Clear Crypto Podcast, hosts Nathan Jeffay and Gareth Jenkinson speak with longtime Bitcoiner and entrepreneur Dan Held, who argues that Bitcoin’s next chapter may unlock broader functionality, from programmable use cases to more nuanced messaging that reaches far beyond crypto-native circles.

Political shifts
With US President Donald Trump openly backing Bitcoin — and reportedly owning it himself — Held said he sees a regulatory and reputational change. 
“We have the most open administration toward…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Savannah Fortis</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[In $2.9B Deal, Coinbase Buys Deribit to Expand in U.S. Crypto Options Market]]></title>
        <id>ffc60f4b-07d3-4d1b-9f08-d1a7f0756444</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2025/05/08/coinbase-buys-deribit-for-usd2-9b"/>
        <updated>2025-05-08T13:28:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The deal includes $700 million in cash and 11 million shares of Coinbase Class A common stock.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Helene Braun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microservices are a tax your startup probably can't afford]]></title>
        <id>https://nexo.sh/posts/microservices-for-startups/</id>
        <link href="https://nexo.sh/posts/microservices-for-startups/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-08T13:23:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Much-Awaited Fed Rate Cut May Not Come Before Q4, ING Says]]></title>
        <id>ac1a01b7-2e50-4379-8bfc-99f09b2c5134</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/08/much-awaited-fed-rate-cut-may-not-come-before-q4-ing-says"/>
        <updated>2025-05-08T13:19:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Delayed rate cuts could be more aggressive when they happen, the investment bank said.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Omkar Godbole</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase to acquire options trading platform Deribit for $2.9B]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/coinbase-acquire-deribit-2-9-billion</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/coinbase-acquire-deribit-2-9-billion?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-08T13:19:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase, the largest cryptocurrency exchange in the US by trading volume, has agreed to acquire Deribit, one of the world’s biggest crypto derivatives trading platforms.
Coinbase Global will acquire Deribit for about $2.9 billion, the exchange announced on May 8.
The acquisition will allow Coinbase to expand into the profitable crypto derivatives market and continue scaling the platform’s global growth, Greg Tusar, Coinbase’s vice president of institutional product, said in the announcement.
“With Deribit’s strong presence and professional client base, Coinbase is making its most substantial move yet to accelerate our international growth strategy,” he said.
Source: Coinbase
Deribit founders to step away
Following the deal’s success, expected later in 2025, Deribit founders John and Mariu…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Helen Partz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Stripe Unveils Payments Products Powered by 'Gale-Force Tailwind' Stablecoins]]></title>
        <id>9923b217-87db-4304-b19a-16c50bdbe5c2</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2025/05/08/stripe-unveils-payments-products-powered-by-gale-force-tailwind-stablecoins"/>
        <updated>2025-05-08T13:17:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Stripe has launched a new money management service powered by stablecoins]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Crawley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Browser-based crypto mining in 2025: Still viable or virtually dead?]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/what-is-browser-based-cryptocurrency-mining-and-how-does-it-work</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/what-is-browser-based-cryptocurrency-mining-and-how-does-it-work?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-08T13:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Key takeaways
After the shutdown of Coinhive in 2019, browser mining has made a comeback with new tools like CryptoTab Browser, Pi Network and YouHolder.
Mining with a browser can cost more in electricity than the crypto earned, especially for users with mid-range devices.
Despite being less energy-intensive than ASIC farms, browser mining still adds up in terms of cumulative power draw and puts a strain on your device’s hardware.
Browser mining is evolving with the help of WebAssembly (Wasm), improving script efficiency and creating a smoother user experience. 

Browser-based crypto mining sounds like a dream: Just open a webpage, let it run, and your computer starts earning crypto in the background. No bulky ASICs, no GPU farms, no long setup tutorials — just your browser doing the heavy…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Bradley Peak</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CoinDesk 20 Performance Update: Index Surges 6.2% as All Assets Trade Higher]]></title>
        <id>a9b0fc2d-06ea-4e1d-a957-2971d71b5c2a</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/coindesk-indices/2025/05/08/coindesk-20-performance-update-index-surges-6-2-as-all-assets-trade-higher"/>
        <updated>2025-05-08T13:13:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sui (SUI) jumped 16.4% and Bitcoin Cash (BCH) gained 15.6%, leading the index higher.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CoinDesk Indices</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ask HN: What are good high-information density UIs (screenshots, apps, sites)?]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=43925732</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=43925732"/>
        <updated>2025-05-08T13:05:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Perodua Showcases Latest EMO EV Concept At MAS 2025]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=351067</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/351067/perodua-showcases-latest-emo-ev-concept-at-mas-2025/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-08T13:05:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Perodua has pulled the covers off the latest iteration of its Electric Motion Online (EMO) EV concept at the Malaysia Autoshow 2025 (MAS 2025), held at MAEPS Serdang. This is the third showing in the series following the miniature eMO-II from KLIMS last year, and it’s shaping up to be the last stop before the […]
The post Perodua Showcases Latest EMO EV Concept At MAS 2025 appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Keran</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[98% of Tokens on Pump.Fun Have Been Rug Pulls or an Act of Fraud, New Report Says]]></title>
        <id>c35992fb-4d61-468c-910b-25590be1b9e5</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2025/05/07/98-of-tokens-on-pump-fun-have-been-rug-pulls-or-an-act-of-fraud-new-report-says"/>
        <updated>2025-05-08T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Seven millions tokens have been launched in pump.fun since its inception in 2024.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Oliver Knight</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin DeFi sees surge in mining participation despite drop in TVL]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/rootstock-bitcoin-defi-mining-tvl-drop-q1-2025</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/rootstock-bitcoin-defi-mining-tvl-drop-q1-2025?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-08T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Smart contract platform Rootstock, the home of decentralized finance (DeFi) on Bitcoin, saw a sharp increase in network security and mining engagement in the first quarter of 2025, even as activity cooled.
Merged mining participation surged to an all-time high of 81%, up from 56.4% in Q4 2024, driven by the integration of major mining pools Foundry and SpiderPool, according to Messari’s first “State of Rootstock” report for 2025, shared with Cointelegraph.
The heightened miner interest boosted Rootstock’s hash power to over 740 exahashes per second, surpassing the total Bitcoin network hashrate recorded in October 2024. As a result, the network is now considered to be in a “mature phase” of merged mining growth.
The increased security coincided with a 60% reduction in transaction fees, imp…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Amin Haqshanas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sweat wallet adds AI assistant, expands to multichain DeFi]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/sweat-wallet-launches-ai-agent-mia-crosschain-defi</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/sweat-wallet-launches-ai-agent-mia-crosschain-defi?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-08T12:49:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sweat, a move-to-earn platform that rewards users for physical activity, has launched a personalized AI agent and expanded its multichain infrastructure. The update is designed to improve user onboarding by offering interactive guidance and simplifying asset management across blockchains.
The AI agent, named Mia (short for Movement in Action), is powered by Near.AI — an open-source AI model platform with crosschain capabilities. Integrated into the Sweat wallet, Mia helps users to bridge, swap and manage their crypto rewards without needing deep crypto knowledge..
Sweat is rolling out support for Base, Ethereum, Arbitrum and BNB Chain. Within the app, users can now bridge assets and swap native tokens across networks, with the option to pay gas fees in Sweat (SWEAT) tokens.
Sweat co-founde…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Lyne Qian</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ether-Bitcoin Ratio Signals ETH Is 'Extremely Undervalued,' but Headwinds Remain: CryptoQuant]]></title>
        <id>d159c2bf-79a9-41ee-821a-8a7c1ac6973c</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/08/ether-bitcoin-ratio-signals-eth-is-extremely-undervalued-but-headwinds-remain-cryptoquant"/>
        <updated>2025-05-08T12:23:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Undervaluation signals have previously preceded ETH rallies, but surging supply, flat demand, and weakened burn mechanics complicate the outlook.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shaurya Malwa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Yes, the Apple II MouseCard IRQ Is Synced to the VBL]]></title>
        <id>https://www.colino.net/wordpress/en/archives/2025/05/08/yes-the-apple-ii-mousecard-irq-is-synced-to-the-vbl/</id>
        <link href="https://www.colino.net/wordpress/en/archives/2025/05/08/yes-the-apple-ii-mousecard-irq-is-synced-to-the-vbl/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-08T12:19:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum price finally ‘breaking out,’ data suggests — Is $3K ETH next?]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/ethereum-price-finally-breaking-out-data-suggests-3-k-eth-is-next</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/ethereum-price-finally-breaking-out-data-suggests-3-k-eth-is-next?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-08T12:18:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Key takeaways:

Ether breaks multimonth downtrend as traders target $3,000 ETH price.

Ethereum TVL surges 41% to $52.8 billion in 30 days, with a 22% rise in daily transactions to 1.34 million, signaling strong network recovery.

Technicals show ETH price faces major resistance at $2,100-$2,800.

Ether is setting up for a recovery toward the $3,000 psychological level, backed by recovering network activity, increasing TVL, and strong technicals. 
Ether price seeks a return to $3K
Ether (ETH) looks to end its downtrend that has been in play since mid-December after it turned away from its 10-month high of $4,100.
Crypto technical analyst Mikybull Crypto shared a chart showing the ETH price breaking above a six-month descending trendline, with $2,000 and $2,250 being key resistance levels t…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Nancy Lubale</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Download: AI benchmarks, and Spain’s grid blackout]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1116202</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/05/08/1116202/the-download-ai-benchmarks-and-spains-grid-blackout/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-08T12:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is today’s edition of The Download, our weekday newsletter that provides a daily dose of what’s going on in the world of technology. How to build a better AI benchmark It’s not easy being one of Silicon Valley’s favorite benchmarks.  SWE-Bench (pronounced “swee bench”) launched in November 2024 as a way to evaluate an AI model’s…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rhiannon Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Will protein design tools solve the snake antivenom shortage?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.owlposting.com/p/will-protein-design-tools-solve-the</id>
        <link href="https://www.owlposting.com/p/will-protein-design-tools-solve-the"/>
        <updated>2025-05-08T12:05:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Artifact (YC W25) Is Hiring]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ycombinator.com/companies/artifact-2/jobs/8j2BXI0-forward-deployed-software-engineer</id>
        <link href="https://www.ycombinator.com/companies/artifact-2/jobs/8j2BXI0-forward-deployed-software-engineer"/>
        <updated>2025-05-08T12:01:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is VanEck’s Onchain Economy ETF ($NODE) and how does it work?]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/explained/what-is-vanecks-onchain-economy-etf-node-and-how-does-it-work</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/explained/what-is-vanecks-onchain-economy-etf-node-and-how-does-it-work?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-08T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What is ​VanEck's Onchain Economy ETF ($NODE)            
            
                
VanEck’s Onchain Economy ETF ($NODE) exposes investors to companies driving blockchain adoption across multiple industries. The fund is scheduled to begin trading on May 14, 2025, following its inception on May 13, 2025.
As the global economy shifts to a digital core, NODE offers active equity investment in real-world companies shaping that future. This ETF is actively managed, meaning a portfolio manager and not just an algorithm, selects the included stocks.
The ETF may allocate up to 25% of its assets to crypto-linked exchange-traded products (ETPs) via a Cayman Islands subsidiary, providing indirect exposure to digital assets while adhering to US tax regulations. With a management fee of 0.69%, $NOD…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Dilip Kumar Patairya</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft-backed Space and Time mainnet launches with major builders]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/space-and-time-mainnet-launch-microsoft-chainlink</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/space-and-time-mainnet-launch-microsoft-chainlink?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-08T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Space and Time, a blockchain project supported by Microsoft, has launched its public, permissionless mainnet to bring zero-knowledge (ZK)-proven data infrastructure to crypto applications.
Built by MakeInfinite Labs, Space and Time offers a decentralized, verifiable database for smart contracts to query historical, crosschain and offchain data, according to a news release shared with Cointelegraph.
The platform indexes data from major networks like Ethereum and makes it accessible through a decentralized network of validators. Developers can query this data using Space and Time’s Proof of SQL — a sub-second ZK coprocessor that delivers cryptographic proofs with every query.
“Prior to Space and Time, onchain applications had no way to query basic user data from a database of blockchain acti…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Amin Haqshanas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Synology Launches DiskStation DS1825+ And DS1525+]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=351009</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/351009/synology-launches-diskstation-ds1825-and-ds1525/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-08T11:43:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Synology announced two new DiskStation Network-attached Storage (NAS) models today. The two models are the DS1825+ and DS1525+, and both have been released less than a month after the launch of the DS925+. The DS1825+ is the largest of the two, featuring an 8-bay expansion unit with support of up to 360TB of raw storage. […]
The post Synology Launches DiskStation DS1825+ And DS1525+ appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John Law</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sei Wants to Cut Cosmos Compatibility and Go All-In on Ethereum]]></title>
        <id>401d9b07-b64d-4971-9ce2-273beddb9547</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/tech/2025/05/08/sei-wants-to-cut-cosmos-compatibility-and-go-all-in-on-ethereum"/>
        <updated>2025-05-08T11:41:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The move comes as blockchain infrastructure builders compete to draw in developers and expand their orbits.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tim Craig</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Daybook Americas: Trump Trade Tease Lifts Market While Movement's Fees Evaporate]]></title>
        <id>a217fcca-2115-4bc3-99e2-7a27cb4cc7c1</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/daybook-us/2025/05/08/crypto-daybook-americas-trump-trade-tease-lifts-market-while-movement-s-fees-evaporate"/>
        <updated>2025-05-08T11:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Your day-ahead look for May 8, 2025]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Omkar Godbole</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Doodles NFT sales surge 97% ahead of DOOD token airdrop]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/doodles-nft-sales-surge-97-ahead-dood-token-airdrop</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/doodles-nft-sales-surge-97-ahead-dood-token-airdrop?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-08T10:59:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Doodles’ non-fungible token (NFTs) sales surged by 97% in the last 24 hours as digital collectible traders anticipate the project’s token generation event and airdrop. 
On May 8, data from CryptoSlam showed Doodles NFT sales topping $1.1 million, nearly doubling the previous day’s total. The spike placed Doodles in the third spot for daily NFT sales, following DMarket and Courtyard NFTs.
Over the past week, Doodles recorded $2.6 million in total sales volume, up 368% from the week prior and ranking fifth among all NFT collections, according to CryptoSlam.
The surge comes ahead of the launch of Doodles’ long-awaited DOOD token. The project announced on May 7 that the token generation event will take place on May 9.
Source: Doodles
Doodles to launch DOOD token and airdrop 
Doodles announced …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Ezra Reguerra</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Samsung Galaxy S25 Edge To Launch On 13 May]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=351013</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/351013/samsung-galaxy-s25-edge-launch-13-may/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-08T10:47:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Samsung is officially introducing the latest addition to its Galaxy S25 family, the Galaxy S25 Edge, during a virtual event on 13 May 2025 at 9AM KST, or 8AM here in Malaysia. The blog post announcing the smartphone’s launch date keeps details on the device scarce, although much has already been speculated about the phone. […]
The post Samsung Galaxy S25 Edge To Launch On 13 May appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nurul Kamil</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pectra features already in use: Ethereum EIP-7702 wallets roll out]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/ethereum-wallets-integrate-eip7702-account-abstraction</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/ethereum-wallets-integrate-eip7702-account-abstraction?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-08T10:35:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Ethereum Pectra upgrade introduced a significant upgrade in account abstraction accessibility, with multiple wallets already implementing the change.
Pectra introduced Ethereum Improvement Proposal (EIP) 7702, a change that Ivo Georgiev, founder and CEO of self-custodial smart wallet Ambire, described as “the single greatest UX upgrade to Ethereum so far.” Ambire is among the wallet providers that have already rolled out support for the new features since Pectra went live yesterday.
Ambire’s announcement shared with Cointelegraph explains that EIP-7702 brings smart account functionality to existing user accounts, letting them temporarily act as smart contracts. This results in the advantages of account abstraction being accessible without creating new dedicated onchain addresses, rende…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Adrian Zmudzinski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OPPO Reno14 Series Renders Leak; Base, Pro Models Identical]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=351045</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/351045/oppo-reno14-series-renders-leak-base-pro-models-identical/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-08T10:27:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Leakster @evleaks posted a series of pictures on X of what is apparently the OPPO Reno14. The renders somewhat support a previous leak which indicated that the phone will have a triple-camera setup at its back. The post also displays the various colours the device could be made available in, which are white, black, and […]
The post OPPO Reno14 Series Renders Leak; Base, Pro Models Identical appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Newsdesk</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New bull cycle? Bitcoin&#039;s return to $100K hints at ‘significant price move’]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/new-bull-cycle-bitcoin-return-100k-significant-price-move</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/new-bull-cycle-bitcoin-return-100k-significant-price-move?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-08T10:07:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Key points:

Bitcoin’s realized cap is beating records and has almost reached the $900 billion mark.

The market is laying the foundations for a “potentially significant price breakout,” new analysis says.

Profit-taking is not hindering the overall bull market rebound.

Bitcoin (BTC) is setting new all-time highs in network value as BTC price action eyes a return to six figures.
Data from onchain analytics platform CryptoQuant confirms new record highs for Bitcoin’s realized cap.
Bitcoin realized cap reflects “growing conviction”
Bitcoin is worth more than ever in US dollar terms if its market cap is measured by the value at which the extant supply last moved onchain.
Known as realized cap, this figure has seen continued all-time highs since mid-April as BTC/USD stages a sustained recover…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by William Suberg</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sonos And IKEA Are Ending Their Partnership]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=351017</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/351017/sonos-and-ikea-are-ending-their-partnership/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-08T10:05:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sonos and IKEA are callling it quits. The audio brand confirmed to several news outlets that, in conjunction with the ending of its relationship with the furniture brand, it is ceasing the production of its Symfonisk lineup, and that all current inventory will be phased out globally. “Over the past eight years, we’ve had the […]
The post Sonos And IKEA Are Ending Their Partnership appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John Law</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ripple M&A Target Hidden Road to Open New Office in Abu Dhabi With a Potential Royal Family Addition]]></title>
        <id>b7655877-9cc9-4190-a8f7-469578554c03</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2025/05/08/ripple-m-and-a-target-hidden-road-to-open-new-office-in-abu-dhabi-with-a-potential-royal-family-addition"/>
        <updated>2025-05-08T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The firm has received in-principle approval from the Financial Services Regulatory Authority (FSRA) of ADGM.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Will Canny</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spotify Rolls Out App Update For Better Playlist Management]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=350991</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/350991/spotify-rolls-out-app-update-for-better-playlist-management/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-08T09:58:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Spotify announced that it is rolling out an update that benefits free and paying users alike. Naturally the latter category will be getting more additions, but free users are by no means getting the short end of the stick here, as the update essentially brings with it better playlist management. For its app, Spotify says […]
The post Spotify Rolls Out App Update For Better Playlist Management appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ian Chee</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Jetour Previews T2 And eVT5 SUVs At MAS 2025]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=351027</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/351027/jetour-previews-t2-and-evt5-suvs-at-mas-2025/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-08T09:52:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jetour has unveiled two upcoming SUVs for the Malaysian market at MAS 2025 today. The first being the T2 off-roader with a PHEV powertrain option, while the second is the all-electric eVT5.  The Jetour T2 offers rugged styling and solid off-road credentials. Its upright proportions and wide stance give it the presence of a traditional […]
The post Jetour Previews T2 And eVT5 SUVs At MAS 2025 appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Heirul Kamel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Did solar power cause Spain’s blackout?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1116166</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/05/08/1116166/spain-blackout-grid/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-08T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At roughly midday on Monday, April 28, the lights went out in Spain. The grid blackout, which extended into parts of Portugal and France, affected tens of millions of people—flights were grounded, cell networks went down, and businesses closed for the day. Over a week later, officials still aren’t entirely sure what happened, but some…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Casey Crownhart</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to build a better AI benchmark]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1116192</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/05/08/1116192/how-to-build-a-better-ai-benchmark/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-08T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s not easy being one of Silicon Valley’s favorite benchmarks.  SWE-Bench (pronounced “swee bench”) launched in November 2024 to evaluate an AI model’s coding skill, using more than 2,000 real-world programming problems pulled from the public GitHub repositories of 12 different Python-based projects.  In the months since then, it’s quickly become one of the most…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Russell Brandom</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Using NASA’s SMAP satellite to detect L-band interference]]></title>
        <id>https://radioandnukes.substack.com/p/how-dare-you-transmit-at-14-ghz</id>
        <link href="https://radioandnukes.substack.com/p/how-dare-you-transmit-at-14-ghz"/>
        <updated>2025-05-08T08:52:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why is the crypto market up today?]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/why-is-the-crypto-market-up-today</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/why-is-the-crypto-market-up-today?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-08T08:39:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Key takeaways:

The crypto market is up 2.5% on May 8, with its capitalization above $3 trillion for the first time in over eight weeks. 

Fed's steady rates and stagflation fears boost Bitcoin as a store of value.

Anticipated US-UK trade deal and a technical rebound fuel market optimism.

The cryptocurrency market is up today, with the total market capitalization rising by approximately 2.5% in the last 24 hours to reach $3.06 trillion on May 8. 
Today’s gains were led by Bitcoin (BTC) and Ether (ETH), which have risen around 2.3% and 4%, respectively.
Crypto market performance May 8. Source: Coin360
Stagflation fears “good” for crypto assets
The Federal Reserve’s decision to keep interest rates steady at 4.25%-4.50% on May 7 has bolstered crypto’s appeal. Fed Chair Jerome Powell’s post-…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Nancy Lubale</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trump Administration To Replace Biden-Era AI Chip Rule]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=350927</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/350927/trump-administration-to-replace-biden-era-ai-chip-rule/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-08T08:38:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[According to a spokeswoman for the US Department of Commerce, the Trump administration is planning to rescind and modify a Biden-era rule concerning the export of AI chips. The regulation, known as the Framework for Artificial Intelligence Diffusion, was geared to restrict exports of AI chips to secure advanced computing power for the US and […]
The post Trump Administration To Replace Biden-Era AI Chip Rule appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nurul Kamil</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Zeekr 7X Previewed At MAS 2025; Starts From RM182,000 For First 500 Buyers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=350996</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/350996/zeekr-7x-mas-2025/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-08T08:30:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Chinese automaker Zeekr has previewed its 7X today at the Malaysia Auto Show 2025. The SUV comes in three variants for the local market: RWD Standard, RWD Long Range, and AWD Performance. The official price of the Zeekr 7X has yet to be revealed by the company. However, there is an indicative price for the […]
The post Zeekr 7X Previewed At MAS 2025; Starts From RM182,000 For First 500 Buyers appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Keran</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dogecoin, Cardano’s ADA Lead Market Gains as Bitcoin Traders Eye Next Fed Meeting]]></title>
        <id>5e2a94b2-3f81-41be-927f-e2ee28e945a4</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/08/dogecoin-cardanos-ada-lead-market-gains-as-bitcoin-traders-eye-next-fed-meeting"/>
        <updated>2025-05-08T08:29:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Analysts say they expect a 100 basis-point cut in 2025, with easing likely to start after July.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shaurya Malwa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Can you mine Bitcoin with a gaming PC? Here’s what you need to know]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/explained/can-you-mine-bitcoin-with-a-gaming-pc</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/explained/can-you-mine-bitcoin-with-a-gaming-pc?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-08T08:01:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Is your gaming PC capable of mining crypto?            
            
                
As of May 2025, Bitcoin mining is looking attractive again. With Bitcoin (BTC) trading around $95,000 and transaction fees hitting new highs after the 2024 halving, mining rewards — though smaller — are worth chasing. From home setups to industrial-scale farms, the question of whether Bitcoin mining is profitable is back in the spotlight.
And if you’re a gamer, chances are you’ve looked at your rig and wondered: Can a gaming PC mine crypto? After all, modern gaming computers are packed with powerful GPUs, solid cooling and lots of downtime, especially if you’re not gaming daily. It’s a fair question: Can you mine Bitcoin with a gaming PC?
The short answer: Yes, but it won’t be worth it. 
The long answer: …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Bradley Peak</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Binance Founder CZ Confirms He Has Applied for Trump Pardon After Prison Term]]></title>
        <id>1a32ab37-3525-4123-a961-6a2665fb3453</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2025/05/08/binance-founder-cz-confirms-he-has-applied-for-trump-pardon-after-prison-term"/>
        <updated>2025-05-08T07:59:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Changpeng Zhao submitted the request weeks ago, citing media reports and after pardons other influential figures in the crypto space were pardoned.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Francisco Rodrigues</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[60K Bitcoin addresses leaked as LockBit ransomware gang gets hacked]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/lockbit-ransomware-breach-bitcoin-addresses-leaked</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/lockbit-ransomware-breach-bitcoin-addresses-leaked?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-08T07:31:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Almost 60,000 Bitcoin addresses tied to LockBit’s ransomware infrastructure were leaked after hackers breached the group’s dark web affiliate panel. 
The leak included a MySQL database dump shared publicly online. It contained crypto-related information that could help blockchain analysts trace the group’s illicit financial flows.  
Ransomware is a type of malware used by malicious actors. It locks its target’s files or computer systems, making them inaccessible. The attackers typically demand a ransom payment, often in digital assets like Bitcoin (BTC), in exchange for a decryption key to unlock the files.
LockBit is one of the most notorious crypto ransomware groups. In February 2024, 10 countries launched a joint operation to disrupt the group, saying that the organization had caused bi…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Ezra Reguerra</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trump crypto adviser David Bailey raises $300M for Bitcoin investment firm]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/trump-advisor-david-bailey-nakamoto-bitcoin-fund</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/trump-advisor-david-bailey-nakamoto-bitcoin-fund?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-08T07:18:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[David Bailey, CEO of crypto media company BTC Inc. and a close adviser to US President Donald Trump on digital assets, has reportedly raised $300 million to launch a new Bitcoin investment firm.
The venture, named Nakamoto after the pseudonymous creator of Bitcoin, Satoshi Nakamoto, aims to become a publicly traded company focused on acquiring and holding the cryptocurrency, CNBC reported, citing people familiar with the matter. The Information was first to cover the story.
The funding round, which has been quietly in motion since January, includes $200 million in equity and $100 million in convertible debt, a source familiar with the matter told CNBC.
While the firm has not officially announced the raise, an official reveal and merger with a Nasdaq-listed company is expected as early as n…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Amin Haqshanas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Audi Q7 S Line Mild-Hybrid SUV Launches In Malaysia; Starts At RM459,990]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=350970</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/350970/audi-q7-s-line-mild-hybrid-suv-msia-launch/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-08T07:11:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The first locally assembled Audi Q7 S Line SUV has officially launched in Malaysia today at the Malaysia Autoshow 2025. The car is manufactured at the Volkswagen Group Malaysia’s assembly plant in Pekan, Pahang – the only Audi production facility in the Southeast Asia region. To recap, the Audi Q7 S Line is powered by […]
The post Audi Q7 S Line Mild-Hybrid SUV Launches In Malaysia; Starts At RM459,990 appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Heirul Kamel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Imagination unveils E-Series GPUs for graphics and AI at the edge]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3006922</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/games/imagination-unveils-e-series-gpus-for-graphics-and-ai-at-the-edge/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-08T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Imagination Technologies is unveiling its E-Series graphics processing units (GPUs) for graphics and AI processing at the edge.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dean Takahashi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Arthur Hayes Says Bitcoin Will Hit $1M by 2028 as U.S.-China Craft Hollow Trade Deal]]></title>
        <id>c46bbc9e-02f9-449f-9fb8-90651557413d</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/08/arthur-hayes-says-bitcoin-will-hit-usd1m-by-2028-as-u-s-china-craft-hollow-trade-deal"/>
        <updated>2025-05-08T06:21:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The former BitMEX CEO says the U.S. Treasury, not the Federal Reserve, is driving global liquidity.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sam Reynolds</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nvidia welcomes Trump’s proposal to rescind global chip restrictions]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3006921</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/gaming-business/nvidia-welcomes-trumps-proposal-to-rescind-global-chip-restrictions/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-08T06:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Donald Trump's administration is expected to rescind Joe Biden's curbs on AI chip sales as part of a broader effort to revise semiconductor restrictions, Bloomberg reported.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dean Takahashi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[US banks can handle customer crypto assets held in custody, regulator confirms]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/occ-allows-banks-handle-customer-crypto-assets-held-in-custody</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/occ-allows-banks-handle-customer-crypto-assets-held-in-custody?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-08T06:11:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The US Office of the Comptroller of the Currency (OCC) has confirmed banks under its jurisdiction can trade crypto on behalf of customers and outsource some crypto activities to third parties. 
Acting comptroller Rodney Hood said in a May 7 letter that banks and federal savings associations can buy and sell crypto they hold in custody at customers’ direction.
The OCC added in a press release that financial institutions can also outsource bank-permissible crypto activities, including custody and execution services, to third parties in compliance with applicable law.
“Additionally, these banks may provide other custody services, including record keeping, tax or reporting services for their customers,” Hood said in a May 7 video posted to X. 

OCC-regulated banks may buy and sell assets held …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Stephen Katte</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[G7 summit could discuss North Korea’s crypto hacks: Report]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/g7-summit-could-discuss-north-korea-crypto-hacks-bloomberg</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/g7-summit-could-discuss-north-korea-crypto-hacks-bloomberg?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-08T05:58:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Group of Seven (G7) leaders could discuss North Korea’s escalating cyberattacks and crypto thefts at an upcoming summit in Canada, mid-next month.
Conflicts in Ukraine and Gaza will dominate discussions, but North Korea’s increasing cyber threats and crypto hacks have become a major concern requiring a coordinated international response, Bloomberg reported on May 7, citing people familiar with the plans.
The people said North Korea’s nefarious cyber operations are alarming, as the stolen crypto has become a key funding source for the regime and its programs. 
North Korean-affiliated hacking groups such as the Lazarus Group have already stolen billions of dollars worth of crypto this year, including pulling off the $1.4 billion hack on Bybit in February, the largest ever for the crypto indu…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Martin Young</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What’s Next for Bitcoin With Crypto Market Cheering Trump's Trade Deal Hype?]]></title>
        <id>dc4f5ec8-9943-449d-b7a5-6c7f011a7885</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/08/what-s-next-for-bitcoin-with-crypto-market-cheering-trump-s-trade-deal-hype"/>
        <updated>2025-05-08T05:57:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Several factors suggest the $100K breakout may not be a smooth ride.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Omkar Godbole</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mycoria is an open and secure overlay network that connects all participants]]></title>
        <id>https://mycoria.org/</id>
        <link href="https://mycoria.org/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-08T05:40:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin nears $100K as Trump set to reveal trade deal with UK]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-price-100k-donald-trump-uk-trade-deal-looms</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-price-100k-donald-trump-uk-trade-deal-looms?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-08T05:31:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoiners expect Bitcoin to soon break past $100,000 and potentially hit a new all-time high as US President Donald Trump is set to announce a trade deal with the UK.
Trump said in a May 7 Truth Social post that a “major trade deal” with a “big, and highly respected, country” would be announced on May 8, which The New York Times reported would be the UK, citing three people familiar with the plans.
Bitcoin inches toward $100,000
When Trump published his post, Bitcoin (BTC) was trading at around $97,759 and has since crept up closer to the psychological $100,000 price level to trade at $99,140 at the time of publication, according to CoinMarketCap data.
Bitcoin is trading at $99,140 at the time of publication. Source: CoinMarketCap
Several Bitcoiners and analysts are crediting the rally to…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Ciaran Lyons</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Texas House committee passes Bitcoin reserve bill for full floor vote]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/texas-house-committee-passes-bitcoin-reserve-bill-for-full-floor-vote</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/texas-house-committee-passes-bitcoin-reserve-bill-for-full-floor-vote?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-08T05:14:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A Texas House Committee has passed a Republican-backed bill to create a Bitcoin reserve, which now only needs a successful full floor vote before heading to the governor’s desk.
The Texas House Committee on Delivery of Government Efficiency passed Senate Bill 21 with no amendments on May 7 in a 9-4 vote along party lines. The bill has already passed the Texas Senate, in a 25-5 vote on March 6.  
SB 21 would establish the “Texas Strategic Bitcoin Reserve,” controlled by the state’s comptroller — currently Glenn Hegar — who would be permitted to invest in digital assets that have obtained a market cap of at least $500 billion over the last twelve months, which would currently only include Bitcoin (BTC).
Source: Pierre Rochard

Republican Senator Charles Schwertner initially introduced SB 21 …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Brayden Lindrea</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Nears $100K as Trump Teases ‘Big’ Trade Deal]]></title>
        <id>60a835d9-02a8-4a4f-afd9-9d9150723191</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/08/bitcoin-nears-100k-as-trump-teases-big-trade-deal"/>
        <updated>2025-05-08T04:20:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Favorable tariff decisions can ease concerns around mounting costs, which may impede appetite for investing in risk assets.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shaurya Malwa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin returns to $98K as Fed holds rates steady despite Trump’s demand]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-price-98k-federal-reserve-interest-rate-cuts-donald-trump-demands</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-price-98k-federal-reserve-interest-rate-cuts-donald-trump-demands?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-08T02:49:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin has reclaimed $98,000 for the first time in almost three months after the US Federal Reserve said it would keep interest rates the same for another month.
The Fed’s decision to keep interest rates unchanged comes despite mounting pressure from US President Donald Trump, who just weeks ago threatened to fire Fed chair Jerome Powell for being “too late” in cutting rates.
Fed cites higher unemployment, inflation risk
Powell said on May 7 that the Federal Reserve rate-setting committee held rates in the 4.25% to 4.50% range due to the rising risks of higher unemployment and higher inflation.
He added inflation has “come down a great deal but has been running above our 2% longer objective.” Powell said surveys in households and businesses showed a “sharp decline in sentiment” mainly due…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Ciaran Lyons</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin miner Core Scientific posts $580M Q1 profit but misses revenue estimates]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/core-scientific-misses-q1-revenue-posts-580-million-q1-profit</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/core-scientific-misses-q1-revenue-posts-580-million-q1-profit?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-08T02:32:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nasdaq-listed Bitcoin mining firm Core Scientific Inc. posted a net profit of $580 million with its first quarter results, but missed analyst revenue estimates after a drop in its mining profits.
Core Scientific’s Q1 2025 results, published on May 7, saw it more than double its $210 million net income from the year-ago quarter, while its total revenue reached $79.5 million, missing Zacks analysts' estimates by 8.11%, and falling from its $179.3 million in revenues for Q1 2024. 
The firm’s primary source of revenue came from $67.2 million in self-mining revenue, $3.8 million in hosted mining revenue, and $8.6 million in colocation, formerly listed as high-performance computing (HPC) hosting.
Source: Core Scientific
Core Scientific said its drop in Bitcoin (BTC) mined and revenue was due to …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Stephen Katte</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Arizona governor signs law for state to keep unclaimed crypto]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/arizona-governor-signs-bitcoin-reserve-keep-unclaimed-crypto</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/arizona-governor-signs-bitcoin-reserve-keep-unclaimed-crypto?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-08T02:05:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Arizona Governor Katie Hobbs has signed a bill into law allowing the US state to keep unclaimed crypto and establish a “Bitcoin Reserve Fund” that won’t use any taxpayer money or state funds.
Hobbs signed House Bill 2749 into law on May 7, which allows Arizona to claim ownership of abandoned digital assets if the owner fails to respond to communications within three years.
The state’s custodians can stake the crypto to earn rewards or receive airdrops, which can then be deposited into what Arizona has called a Bitcoin and Digital Asset Reserve Fund.
“This law ensures Arizona doesn’t leave value sitting on the table and puts us in a position to lead the country in how we secure, manage, and ultimately benefit from abandoned digital currency,” the bill’s sponsor, Jeff Weninger, said in a May…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Brayden Lindrea</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Binance founder CZ Zhao asked Trump to pardon money laundering conviction]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/changpeng-zhao-cz-binance-asked-trump-pardon</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/changpeng-zhao-cz-binance-asked-trump-pardon?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-08T00:04:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Binance founder and convicted felon Changpeng Zhao says that he applied for a pardon from US President Donald Trump shortly after denying reports that he was seeking one.
Zhao, also known as CZ, said on a Farokh Radio podcast episode aired May 6 that he “wouldn’t mind” a pardon and that his lawyers have already filed the paperwork on his behalf
“I got lawyers applying,” Zhao said, adding that he submitted the request after Bloomberg and The Wall Street Journal reported in March that he was seeking a pardon from Trump amid discussions of a business deal between the Trump family and Binance.US.
Zhao denied the reports at the time, but said on the podcast that he thought “if they’re writing this article, I may as well just officially apply.”
He added that Trump’s pardon of three BitMEX founde…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Brayden Lindrea</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Stripe rolls out stablecoin accounts in over 100 countries]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/stripe-announces-stablecoin-financial-accounts</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/stripe-announces-stablecoin-financial-accounts?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-07T22:15:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Stripe, a global payments platform, has introduced stablecoin-based accounts to clients in over 100 countries. 
According to a May 7 announcement, the new feature will allow the platform's clients "to send, receive, and hold US-dollar stablecoin account balances, similar to how a traditional fiat bank account works."
The product's technical page shows that the new account feature will support Circle's USDC (USDC) and Bridge's USDB (USDB) stablecoins. Stripe acquired the Bridge platform in October 2024.
The product will be available to clients in more than 100 countries, including Argentina, Chilé, Turkey, Colombia, and Peru, among others.
Stripe's newly launched product comes at a time when stablecoins are increasingly seen as stores of value in developing economies struggling with high in…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Vince Quill</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Anthropic launches Claude web search API, betting on the future of post-Google information access]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3006849</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/anthropic-launches-claude-web-search-api-betting-on-the-future-of-post-google-information-access/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-07T22:01:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Anthropic launches web search API for Claude as Apple considers AI search alternatives to Google, signaling a major shift in how users discover information online.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Nuñez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Robinhood plans blockchain for US asset trading in Europe: Report]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/robinhood-blockchain-us-asset-trading-tokenization-europe</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/robinhood-blockchain-us-asset-trading-tokenization-europe?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-07T21:54:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Brokerage fintech Robinhood is reportedly developing a blockchain network that will enable retail investors in Europe to trade US securities.
According to a May 7 Bloomberg report citing sources familiar with the matter, the move seeks to expand the company's local presence by offering trading of tokenized securities, such as stocks. 
Two crypto firms, Arbitrum and the Solana Foundation, are reportedly vying to become partners in the project. Tokenization is the process of turning real-world assets, like stocks, real estate, or commodities, into digital tokens that can be traded on a blockchain.
Tokenizing securities instead of providing direct exposure can offer several advantages: reduced costs by eliminating traditional financial infrastructure, enhanced accessibility, faster settlement…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Christopher Tepedino</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[June Huh dropped out to become a poet, now he’s won a Fields Medal (2022)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.quantamagazine.org/june-huh-high-school-dropout-wins-the-fields-medal-20220705/</id>
        <link href="https://www.quantamagazine.org/june-huh-high-school-dropout-wins-the-fields-medal-20220705/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-07T21:34:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OCC: Banks Can Buy and Sell Their Customers' Crypto Assets Held in Custody]]></title>
        <id>cd316845-0400-4981-b1ec-3fabddcf4997</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2025/05/07/occ-banks-can-buy-and-sell-their-customers-crypto-assets-held-in-custody"/>
        <updated>2025-05-07T21:31:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new policy directive from the U.S. regulator of national banks says the institutions can also outsource crypto custody and execution to outside parties.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jesse Hamilton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fed Stagflation Risk Signal Could Be Bullish for Bitcoin, Analyst Says]]></title>
        <id>bc2bd97c-6b5b-43ac-9eb8-3a5b840fd4a1</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/07/fed-stagflation-risk-signal-could-be-bullish-for-bitcoin-analyst-says"/>
        <updated>2025-05-07T21:09:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Holding rates steady, the U.S. central bank took note of the possibility of higher inflation and unemployment.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Krisztian Sandor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trump Crypto Adviser David Bailey in Talks to Launch Bitcoin Investment Company: The Information]]></title>
        <id>af82fce7-9435-4c50-8ffe-492d8243bd17</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/07/trump-crypto-advisor-david-bailey-in-talks-to-launch-bitcoin-investment-company-the-information"/>
        <updated>2025-05-07T20:46:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bailey, who advised President Donald Trump on crypto policy during his 2024 presidential campaign, is reportedly raising $300 million to buy bitcoin.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Helene Braun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Robinhood Developing Blockchain-Based Program To Trade U.S. Securities in Europe: Bloomberg]]></title>
        <id>5bfab0b3-4c79-4a29-8794-3f6c2b2a9e5f</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2025/05/07/robinhood-developing-blockchain-based-program-to-trade-u-s-securities-in-europe-bloomberg"/>
        <updated>2025-05-07T19:49:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The brokerage firm is reportedly considering Arbitrum, Ethereum and Solana for the new platform.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Helene Braun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Open source Google Analytics replacement]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/rybbit-io/rybbit</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/rybbit-io/rybbit"/>
        <updated>2025-05-07T17:45:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ty: A fast Python type checker and language server]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/astral-sh/ty</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/astral-sh/ty"/>
        <updated>2025-05-07T17:32:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Code a Dropbox Clone with NextJS]]></title>
        <id>681b80ee1a1a4e16cffa1a50</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/code-a-dropbox-clone-with-nextjs/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-07T15:49:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Building modern full-stack applications requires a strong grasp of various interconnected technologies. And what better way to learn than by creating a real-world project that mimics a widely used tool like Dropbox? That’s exactly what this new cours...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Roundtables: A New Look at AI’s Energy Use]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1116168</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/05/07/1116168/roundtables-a-new-look-at-ais-energy-use/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-07T15:38:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Wednesday, May 21, 2025 Big Tech’s appetite for energy is growing rapidly as adoption of AI accelerates. But just how much energy does even a single AI query use? And what does it mean for the climate? Join editor in chief Mat Honan, senior climate reporter Casey Crownhart, and AI reporter James O’Donnell for a…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>MIT Technology Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mistral comes out swinging for enterprise AI customers with new Le Chat Enterprise, Medium 3 model]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3006803</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/mistral-comes-out-swinging-for-enterprise-ai-customers-with-new-le-chat-enterprise-medium-3-model/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-07T15:13:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mistral AI is making a concerted push to lower the barriers to scalable, privacy-respecting AI adoption for modern enterprises.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carl Franzen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Recursive Types in TypeScript: A Brief Exploration]]></title>
        <id>681b77a47396438eaee0c5ce</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/recursive-types-in-typescript-a-brief-exploration/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-07T15:09:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It is said that there are two different worlds in TypeScript that exist side by side: the type world and the value world. Consider this line of code: const firstName: string = 'Maynard'; While firstName and 'Maynard' live in the value world, string ...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eda Eren</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Waiting for Postgres 18: Accelerating Disk Reads with Asynchronous I/O]]></title>
        <id>https://pganalyze.com/blog/postgres-18-async-io</id>
        <link href="https://pganalyze.com/blog/postgres-18-async-io"/>
        <updated>2025-05-07T14:57:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mistral ships Le Chat – enterprise AI assistant that can run on prem]]></title>
        <id>https://mistral.ai/news/le-chat-enterprise</id>
        <link href="https://mistral.ai/news/le-chat-enterprise"/>
        <updated>2025-05-07T14:24:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The business of the future is adaptive]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1116098</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/05/07/1116098/the-business-of-the-future-is-adaptive/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-07T14:14:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Manufacturing is in a state of flux. From supply chain disruptions to rising costs, tougher environmental regulations, and a changing consumer market, the sector faces a series of competing challenges. But a new way of operating offers a way to tackle complexities head-on: adaptive production hardwires flexibility and resilience into the enterprise, drawing on powerful…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>MIT Technology Review Insights</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Front-End Performance Optimization Handbook – Tips and Strategies for Devs]]></title>
        <id>681b5e61b1ed0b90facd0adf</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/the-front-end-performance-optimization-handbook/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-07T13:21:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When you’re building a website, you’ll want it to be responsive, fast, and efficient. This means making sure the site loads quickly, runs smoothly, and provides a seamless experience for your users, among other things. So as you build, you’ll want to...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gordan Tan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Breathe lands $21M Series B to predict battery performance]]></title>
        <id>https://techcrunch.com/?p=3003769</id>
        <link href="https://techcrunch.com/2025/05/07/breathe-lands-21m-series-b-to-predict-battery-performance/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-07T12:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Breathe has developed a suite of tools that it says helps automakers and others get the most out of their batteries.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tim De Chant</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Netflix unveils new TV experience with GenAI search and AI-based recommendations]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3006789</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/games/netflix-unveils-new-tv-experience-with-genai-search-and-ai-based-recommendations/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-07T12:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Netflix unveiled its new TV experience that features generative AI search, AI-based recommendations and an enhanced design.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dean Takahashi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Download: Neuralink’s AI boost, and Trump’s tariffs]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1116147</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/05/07/1116147/the-download-neuralinks-ai-boost-and-trumps-tariffs/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-07T12:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is today’s edition of The Download, our weekday newsletter that provides a daily dose of what’s going on in the world of technology. This patient’s Neuralink brain implant gets a boost from generative AI Last November, Bradford G. Smith got a brain implant from Elon Musk’s company Neuralink. The device, a set of thin wires attached…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rhiannon Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This patient’s Neuralink brain implant gets a boost from generative AI]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1116139</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/05/07/1116139/this-brain-implant-gets-a-boost-from-generative-ai/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-07T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Last November, Bradford G. Smith got a brain implant from Elon Musk’s company Neuralink. The device, a set of thin wires attached to a computer about the thickness of a few quarters that sits in his skull, lets him use his thoughts to move a computer pointer on a screen.  And by last week he…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Antonio Regalado</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS report: Generative AI overtakes security in global tech budgets for 2025]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3006670</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/aws-report-generative-ai-overtakes-security-in-global-tech-budgets-for-2025/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T21:33:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New AWS report reveals 45% of global IT leaders now prioritize generative AI over cybersecurity in 2025 tech budgets as companies race to hire AI talent and implement AI strategies despite persistent skills shortages.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Nuñez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Engineered adipocytes implantation suppresses tumor progression in cancer models]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nature.com/articles/s41587-024-02551-2</id>
        <link href="https://www.nature.com/articles/s41587-024-02551-2"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T20:33:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Secure Mobile APIs in Flutter]]></title>
        <id>681a707658599a397b11b418</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-secure-mobile-apis-in-flutter/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T20:26:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As mobile applications continue to evolve in functionality and scope, securing the APIs that power these apps has become more critical than ever. In the context of Flutter, a framework that enables cross-platform development, understanding how to sec...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Atuoha Anthony</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meet the new king of AI coding: Google’s Gemini 2.5 Pro I/O Edition dethrones Claude 3.7 Sonnet]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3006623</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/meet-the-new-king-of-ai-coding-googles-gemini-2-5-pro-i-o-edition-dethrones-claude-3-7-sonnet/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T18:39:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One of the standout features of the update is its ability to build full, interactive web apps or simulations from a single prompt.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carl Franzen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Create Documentation with docs.page – A Beginner's Tutorial]]></title>
        <id>681a558b9791d0e469b84519</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-create-documentation-with-docspage/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T18:31:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One of the most tedious tasks for every startup, company, and open-source project is often building and managing documentation – especially for medium to large-scale documentation websites. docs.page is an open-source documentation tool that helps yo...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rajdeep Singh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lightricks just made AI video generation 30x faster — and you won’t need a $10,000 GPU]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3006613</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/lightricks-just-made-ai-video-generation-30x-faster-and-you-wont-need-a-10000-gpu/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T17:56:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Lightricks unveils groundbreaking LTXV-13B AI video model that runs 30X faster than competitors on consumer hardware through innovative "multiscale rendering" technology.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Nuñez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ServiceNow lets users see more of their AI]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3006589</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/servicenow-lets-users-see-more-of-their-ai/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ServiceNow also announced a way for agents to communicate with others along with its new observability platform.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Emilia David</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build Your Own Local AI: Create Free RAG and AI Agents with Qwen 3 and Ollama]]></title>
        <id>681a35d4d5da806f5e9467b1</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-a-local-ai/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T16:16:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The landscape of Artificial Intelligence is rapidly evolving, and one of the most exciting trends is the ability to run powerful Large Language Models (LLMs) directly on your local machine. This shift away from reliance on cloud-based APIs offers sig...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chaitanya Rahalkar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Create Serverless AI Agents with Langbase Docs MCP Server in Minutes]]></title>
        <id>681a2ce0aebfc718f4e6da03</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-create-serverless-ai-agents-with-langbase-docs-mcp-server-in-minutes/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T15:38:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Building serverless AI agents has recently become a lot simpler. With the Langbase Docs MCP server, you can instantly connect AI models to Langbase documentation – making it easy to build composable, agentic AI systems with memory without complex inf...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maham Codes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mass spectrometry method identifies pathogens within minutes instead of days]]></title>
        <id>https://phys.org/news/2025-05-mass-spectrometry-method-pathogens-minutes.html</id>
        <link href="https://phys.org/news/2025-05-mass-spectrometry-method-pathogens-minutes.html"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T15:13:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Report: OpenAI is buying AI-powered developer platform Windsurf — what happens to its support for rival LLMs?]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3006587</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/report-openai-is-buying-ai-powered-developer-platform-windsurf-what-happens-to-its-support-for-rival-llms/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T14:37:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[OpenAI could see which types of developers use rival models such as the Meta Llama variants and Anthropic's Claude, and for what purposes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carl Franzen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Startup Korl unveils multimodal, multi-agent tool for custom communication across disparate systems]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3006451</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/how-openai-gemini-and-anthropic-help-korl-prepare-customer-materials-in-minutes/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Korl's platform works across multiple systems, using multi-agent and multimodal AI to create highly-customized customer messaging.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Taryn Plumb</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ōura adds AI-driven meal and glucose tracking features with Stelo by Dexcom]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3006449</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/games/oura-adds-ai-driven-meal-and-glucose-tracking-features-with-stelo-by-dexcom/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ōura, maker of a health-monitoring smart ring, announced that it will use AI to track and analyze two new metabolic health features: meals and glucose.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dean Takahashi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Download: a longevity influencer’s new religion, and humanoid robots’ shortcomings]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1116114</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/05/06/1116114/the-download-a-longevity-influencers-new-religion-and-humanoid-robots-shortcomings/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T12:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is today’s edition of The Download, our weekday newsletter that provides a daily dose of what’s going on in the world of technology. Bryan Johnson wants to start a new religion in which “the body is God” Bryan Johnson is on a mission to not die. The 47-year-old multimillionaire has already applied his slogan “Don’t Die”…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rhiannon Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Inheritance was invented as a performance hack (2021)]]></title>
        <id>https://catern.com/inheritance.html</id>
        <link href="https://catern.com/inheritance.html"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T10:59:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why the humanoid workforce is running late]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1116108</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/05/06/1116108/why-the-humanoid-workforce-is-running-late/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On Thursday I watched Daniela Rus, one of the world’s top experts on AI-powered robots, address a packed room at a Boston robotics expo. Rus spent a portion of her talk busting the notion that giant fleets of humanoids are already making themselves useful in manufacturing and warehouses around the world.  That might come as…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>James O'Donnell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Join the 2025 Web3j Mentorships: Build the Future of Ethereum on the JVM]]></title>
        <id>6819c8dc41eeeb000183d37b</id>
        <link href="https://blog.web3labs.com/join-the-2025-web3j-mentorships-build-the-future-of-ethereum-on-the-jvm/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T08:32:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Linux Foundation’s Decentralized Trust (LFDT) mentorship program is back in 2025 with two exciting opportunities for developers passionate about Ethereum, Android, and the Java Virtual Machine (JVM). Whether you’re a seasoned blockchain developer or an Android enthusiast eager to dive into Web3, these mentorships offer]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>George Tebrean</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[IBM thinks that over a billion new applications will be built with gen AI : Here’s how they’re going to help that happen with agentic AI]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3006455</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/agents-are-key-to-enterprise-ai-success-heres-ibms-plan-on-how-to-make-it-happen/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T04:01:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[IBM details its plans to help enterprises to actually do more with AI, with an expanded set of agentic AI capabilities.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sean Michael Kerner</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to harden GitHub Actions]]></title>
        <id>https://www.wiz.io/blog/github-actions-security-guide</id>
        <link href="https://www.wiz.io/blog/github-actions-security-guide"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T02:07:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meta, Cisco put open-source LLMs at the core of next-gen SOC workflows]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3006384</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/rsac-2025-cisco-and-meta-put-open-source-ai-at-the-heart-of-enterprise-threat-defense/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T00:08:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cisco’s Foundation-sec-8B LLM & Meta’s AI Defenders redefine cybersecurity with open-source AI for scalable SOCs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Louis Columbus</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Imagineers defend new Walt Disney robot]]></title>
        <id>https://www.yahoo.com/entertainment/articles/keeps-walt-alive-medium-pioneered-170000117.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.yahoo.com/entertainment/articles/keeps-walt-alive-medium-pioneered-170000117.html"/>
        <updated>2025-05-05T19:36:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nvidia launches fully open source transcription AI model Parakeet-TDT-0.6B-V2 on Hugging Face]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3006438</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/nvidia-launches-fully-open-source-transcription-ai-model-parakeet-tdt-0-6b-v2-on-hugging-face/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-05T19:17:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An attractive proposition for commercial enterprises and indie developers looking to build speech recognition and transcription services...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carl Franzen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bridging the gap between keyword and semantic search with SPLADE (2024)]]></title>
        <id>http://arcturus-labs.com/blog/2024/10/09/bridging-the-gap-between-keyword-and-semantic-search-with-splade/</id>
        <link href="http://arcturus-labs.com/blog/2024/10/09/bridging-the-gap-between-keyword-and-semantic-search-with-splade/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-05T19:13:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Improve Your C++ Skills by Coding an Audio Plugin]]></title>
        <id>68190b8f1abafc5ea9d7efbf</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/improve-you-c-skills-by-coding-an-audio-plugin/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-05T19:03:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Do you want to build a practical project to help improve your C++ skills? Have you ever wanted to create your own unique audio effects? Then diving into C++ audio plugin development with the JUCE framework might be your next great step We just publis...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Visa launches ‘Intelligent Commerce’ platform, letting AI agents swipe your card—safely, it says]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3006416</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/visa-launches-intelligent-commerce-platform-letting-ai-agents-swipe-your-card-safely-it-says/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-05T18:01:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Visa launches Intelligent Commerce platform enabling AI assistants to make secure purchases with your credit card, transforming online shopping with personalized automation and consumer-controlled spending limits.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Nuñez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Heat stress mitigation by trees and shelters at bus stops]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S136192092500063X</id>
        <link href="https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S136192092500063X"/>
        <updated>2025-05-05T16:41:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How linear regression works intuitively and how it leads to gradient descent]]></title>
        <id>https://briefer.cloud/blog/posts/least-squares/</id>
        <link href="https://briefer.cloud/blog/posts/least-squares/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-05T15:05:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build a Dynamic Wardrobe App with React Drag and Drop]]></title>
        <id>6818d1793c6be4514080aea9</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-build-a-dynamic-wardrobe-app-with-react-drag-and-drop/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-05T14:55:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Have you ever found yourself stuck deciding what color outfit to wear? Maybe you’re mixing and matching different tops and bottoms, unsure if the colors go together. It’s a common dilemma – so common that many of us turn to friends or family for a se...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Timothy Olanrewaju</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bryan Johnson wants to start a new religion in which “the body is God”]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1116090</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/05/05/1116090/bryan-johnson-new-religion-body-is-god/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-05T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bryan Johnson is on a mission to not die. The 47-year-old multimillionaire has already applied his slogan “Don’t Die” to events, merchandise, and a Netflix documentary. Now he’s founding a Don’t Die religion. Johnson, who famously spends millions of dollars on scans, tests, supplements, and a lifestyle routine designed to slow or reverse the aging…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jessica Hamzelou</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Obama’s BlackBerry got secured (2013)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.electrospaces.net/2013/04/how-obamas-blackberry-got-secured.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.electrospaces.net/2013/04/how-obamas-blackberry-got-secured.html"/>
        <updated>2025-05-05T07:54:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Using Coalton to implement a quantum compiler (2022)]]></title>
        <id>https://coalton-lang.github.io/20220906-quantum-compiler/</id>
        <link href="https://coalton-lang.github.io/20220906-quantum-compiler/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-05T06:31:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Extending a Language – Writing Powerful Macros in Scheme]]></title>
        <id>https://mnieper.github.io/scheme-macros/README.html</id>
        <link href="https://mnieper.github.io/scheme-macros/README.html"/>
        <updated>2025-05-05T06:07:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The great cognitive migration: How AI is reshaping human purpose, work and meaning]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3006326</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/the-great-cognitive-migration-ai-will-win-at-intelligence-but-only-we-can-make-it-matter/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-04T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Humans need to embrace domains where AI still falters, and where human creativity, ethics and emotion emain indispensable.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gary Grossman, Edelman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Not everything needs an LLM: A framework for evaluating when AI makes sense]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3006312</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/not-everything-needs-an-llm-a-framework-for-evaluating-when-ai-makes-sense/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-03T19:35:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The answer to 'What customer needs requires an AI solution?' isn’t always 'Yes.' LLMs are still expensive and not always accurate.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sharanya Rao</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[RSAC 2025: Why the AI agent era means more demand for CISOs]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3006066</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/security/rsac-2025-why-the-ai-agent-era-means-more-demand-for-cisos/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-02T23:02:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[RSAC 2025 made one thing clear: AI agents are entering security workflows, but boards want proof they work.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Louis Columbus</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Write Good API Documentation]]></title>
        <id>68151f0be5850fcb8543375a</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-write-good-api-docs/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-02T19:37:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Imagine purchasing a standing fan straight out of the box, all parts dismantled, and you have no manual or guide to put them together. Did you imagine that just now? Cool. Here is another scenario: imagine purchasing an LG product, such as a smart TV...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Okoro Emmanuel Nzube</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OpenAI overrode concerns of expert testers to release sycophantic GPT-4o]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3006276</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/openai-overrode-concerns-of-expert-testers-to-release-sycophantic-gpt-4o/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-02T17:57:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Once again, it shows the importance of incorporating more domains beyond the traditional math and computer science into AI development.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carl Franzen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Roblox breaks ground on data center in Brazil for early 2026]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3006251</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/games/roblox-breaks-ground-on-data-center-in-brazil-for-early-2026/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-02T16:55:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At Gamescom Latam, Roblox announced it has broken ground on a new data center in Brazil -- slated to go live in early 2026.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dean Takahashi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hidden costs in AI deployment: Why Claude models may be 20-30% more expensive than GPT in enterprise settings]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3006096</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/hidden-costs-in-ai-deployment-why-claude-models-may-be-20-30-more-expensive-than-gpt-in-enterprise-settings/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-01T20:14:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It is a well-known fact that different model families can use different tokenizers. However, there has been limited analysis on how the process of “tokenization” itself varies across these tokenizers. Do all tokenizers result in the same number of tokens for a given input text? If not, how different are the generated tokens? How significant […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lavanya Gupta</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Astronomer’s $93M raise underscores a new reality: Orchestration is king in AI infrastructure]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3006195</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/astronomer-93m-raise-underscores-a-new-reality-orchestration-is-king-in-ai-infrastructure/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-01T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Astronomer secures $93 million in Series D funding to solve the AI implementation gap through data orchestration, helping enterprises streamline complex workflows and operationalize AI initiatives at scale.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Nuñez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft launches Phi-4-Reasoning-Plus, a small, powerful, open weights reasoning model!]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3006213</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/microsoft-launches-phi-4-reasoning-plus-a-small-powerful-open-weights-reasoning-model/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-01T12:41:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The release demonstrates that with carefully curated data and training techniques, small models can deliver strong reasoning performance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carl Franzen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Salesforce takes aim at ‘jagged intelligence’ in push for more reliable AI]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3006124</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/salesforce-tackles-jagged-intelligence-problem-with-new-ai-benchmarks-and-models/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-01T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Salesforce unveils groundbreaking AI research tackling "jagged intelligence," introducing new benchmarks, models, and guardrails to make enterprise AI agents more intelligent, trusted, and consistently reliable for business use.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Nuñez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[UiPath’s new orchestrator guides AI agents to follow your enterprise’s rules]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3006059</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/uipaths-new-orchestrator-guides-ai-agents-to-follow-your-enterprises-rules/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T21:20:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[UiPath's agent orchestration layer Maestro moves prompts through three layers: the agent, a human and the robotic process automation system.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Emilia David</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Web3j Six Month Project Update]]></title>
        <id>68109495670a1300013504c2</id>
        <link href="https://blog.web3labs.com/web3j-six-month-project-update/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T09:10:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[November 2024 - April 2025
This report summarizes the activities and accomplishments of Web3j, an LF Decentralized Trust project, from November 2024 to April 2025. During this period, the project made significant strides in improving the framework’s functionality, enhancing user engagement, and bolstering overall community interaction. 
Key]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>George Tebrean</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[QuickNode: Building the Infrastructure for the Next Generation of Blockchain]]></title>
        <id>6807d5787fb8500001c39b99</id>
        <link href="https://blog.quicknode.com/quicknode-building-the-infrastructure-for-the-next-generation-of-blockchain/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-28T16:02:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Join QuickNode co-founder Dmitry Shklovsky as he discusses blockchain infrastructure, building decentralized applications, and the future of Web3 development on TheCube's Crypto Trailblazer Series.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>QuickNode</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>