<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2025-05-20T19:40:30.564Z</id>
    <title>AngJianming RSS Feed</title>
    <updated>2025-05-20T19:40:30.564Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[10 Practical Lessons Every Laravel Developer Should Know]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/yasserelgammal/10-practical-lessons-every-laravel-developer-should-know-5a5p</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/yasserelgammal/10-practical-lessons-every-laravel-developer-should-know-5a5p"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T19:29:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Throughout my journey with Laravel, I’ve learned a lot of lessons that helped me improve the way I work and write code. Here are 10 key takeaways that made a real difference for me:
If you're using Blade, make sure to add required to your HTML fields. If a user submits an empty required field, it shouldn't even reach the server. Save your server from handling unnecessary requests.
Always validate incoming data. Avoid using request()->all(), especially if you're using guarded in your model—it could allow unexpected data to slip through.
resource or apiResource routes


This helps keep your routes organized and prevents your route files from becoming bloated and hard to manage.
Don't put logic inside your Resource files. It can cause N+1 problems, especially when returning collections. It also makes your code easier for others to understand. Always use pagination for large datasets.
Avoid N+1 problems by eager loading any relationships you know you'll use. Laravel 12 introduced automatic eager loading, but it's still good practice to manage it explicitly when needed.
Laravel Logs and tools like Laravel Telescope are great for debugging and monitoring. Just make sure to secure Telescope if you’re using it in production.
Regularly delete old logs and unused files. For example, when users update profile images, delete the old one. This helps you save disk space in the long run.
Use Guards, Policies, or Gates to protect your data. Never assume users should have access just because they’re logged in.
Don’t let a few users flood your system with requests. Throttling is your first line of defense against DDoS attacks.
Use cache for data that’s accessed frequently and doesn’t change often. It makes a big difference in performance.
Final Thought:

You're building for all kinds of users، always be prepared for the worst-case scenario.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yasser Elgammal</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google finally launches NotebookLM mobile app at I/O: hands-on, first impressions]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008400</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/google-finally-launches-notebooklm-mobile-app-at-i-o-hands-on-first-impressions/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T19:29:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As NotebookLM matures, its emerging business-tier capabilities suggest growing alignment with the productivity and compliance...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carl Franzen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Real-World Asset Tokenization: Use Cases and Fields!]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/vadym_info_polus/real-world-asset-tokenization-use-cases-and-fields-33an</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/vadym_info_polus/real-world-asset-tokenization-use-cases-and-fields-33an"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T19:27:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello, everybody! At Info-Polus, we see the opportunities RWA tokenization presents. So this is the second part of our dive into the future of DeFi! Today, let’s speak about Current Use Cases and Industries!
The real world assets market is not yet fully formed, but it has already been divided into categories of projects that belong to the general trend of tokenized real-world assets.
Centralized Stablecoins: Popular coins such as USDT from Tether or USDC from Circle are inherently RWAs. Token issuers lock fiat currencies and government or commercial securities in their accounts as collateral. They then issue stablecoins, which is a tokenization.
Private Lending: MakerDAO, the DAI stablecoin issuer, is one player in this field. In mid-2022, the company opened a $100 million tokenized credit…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Vadym</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Install and Use Docker Compose on Ubuntu]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/hostman_com/how-to-install-and-use-docker-compose-on-ubuntu-2g7e</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/hostman_com/how-to-install-and-use-docker-compose-on-ubuntu-2g7e"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T19:23:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Docker Compose has fundamentally changed how developers approach containerized applications, particularly when coordinating services that depend on one another. This tool replaces manual container management with a structured YAML-driven workflow, enabling teams to define entire application architectures in a single configuration file. 
For Ubuntu environments, this translates to reproducible deployments, simplified scaling, and reduced operational overhead. This guide provides a fresh perspective on Docker Compose installation and usage, offering deeper insights into its practical implementation.
https://hostman.com/tutorials/how-to-install-and-use-docker-compose-on-ubuntu/]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hostman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Document Search in .NET with Kernel Memory]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/leading-edje/document-search-in-net-with-kernel-memory-3ah</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/leading-edje/document-search-in-net-with-kernel-memory-3ah"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T19:22:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I recently discovered the Kernel Memory library for document indexing, web scraping, semantic search, and LLM-based question answering. The capabilities, flexibility, and simplicity of this library are so fantastic that it's quickly ascended my list of favorite AI libraries to work with for RAG search, document search, or AI-based question answering.
In this article I'll walk you through what Kernel Memory is and how you can use the C# version of this library to quickly index, search, and chat with knowledge stored in documents or web pages.
At its core, Kernel Memory is all about ingesting information in various sources, indexing it, storing it in a vector storage solution, and providing a means for searching and question answering with this indexed knowledge.

We'll walk through a full s…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matt Eland</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to burn money on VPC Endpoints]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/martinnanchev/how-to-burn-money-on-vpc-endpoints-3l83</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/martinnanchev/how-to-burn-money-on-vpc-endpoints-3l83"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T19:21:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How (not) to Burn Money on VPC Endpoints (So You Don't Have To)
Martin Nanchev for AWS Community Builders  ・ May 20
#aws
        #vpc
        #networking
        #costs]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Martin Nanchev</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bancor files patent infringement lawsuit against Uniswap over DEX tech]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/bancor-files-patent-infringement-lawsuit-against-uniswap-over-dex-tech</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/bancor-files-patent-infringement-lawsuit-against-uniswap-over-dex-tech?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T19:20:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bancor, the creator of a smart contract-based automated market maker, is suing Uniswap for patent infringement, alleging the decentralized finance exchange has used its technology without permission and profited significantly from it.
According to the May 20 announcement of the lawsuit, Bancor designed the technology in 2016 and patented it in January 2017. The technology underpins the “constant product automated market maker,” which involves using mathematics to add or withdraw resources from a liquidity pool. The application subsequently led to two issued patents.
Bancor alleges that Uniswap used the invention to create its protocol, launched in November 2018. The two organizations are considered competitors in the sector of decentralized finance (DeFi).
“When an organization continuousl…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Christopher Tepedino</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Understanding React Hooks: The What, Why, and How (for Real)]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/md_rashidshabab_fac1bf9d/understanding-react-hooks-the-what-why-and-how-for-real-4oc0</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/md_rashidshabab_fac1bf9d/understanding-react-hooks-the-what-why-and-how-for-real-4oc0"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T19:17:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you're using React, you’ve definitely run into hooks like useState, useEffect, or maybe even made your own useSomething. But what exactly is a hook? How is it different from a regular function? And why is React so strict about how they're used?
is a Hook?


At its core, a hook is just a function that gives function components the ability to use React features like state, side effects, and context.
useState gives you state


useEffect runs side effects


useRef, useMemo, and others give access to React internals



But hooks are more than just function calls — they plug directly into React’s rendering engine.
React stores hooks in a list and matches them by call order.
On each render, it:
Starts from the top of your component.

Calls your hooks one by one.

Matches them to internal stora…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Md Rashid Shabab</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Automatizando requisições que exigem autenticação no Postman com pre-requests]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/dantas/automatizando-requisicoes-que-exigem-autenticacao-no-postman-com-pre-requests-3f4i</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/dantas/automatizando-requisicoes-que-exigem-autenticacao-no-postman-com-pre-requests-3f4i"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T19:17:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[No Postman, como você testa as rotas da sua API REST ou as queries da sua API GraphQL que precisam de autenticação JWT? Você provavelmente cria uma rota/mutation para login e depois copia o token e coloca no header de authorization, certo? Nesse post eu vou te mostrar como você pode fazer todo esse processo de forma automatizada, seja em uma API REST ou GraphQL 🚀
Caso tenha algum problema, veja esta seção.
Primeiro, precisamos ter variáveis para usar como Bearer Token na requisição/mutation.
Criar uma variável é bem simples:
Clique na sua collection criada (seu projeto) no Postman
Vá para a seção variables e crie a variável:

Primeiro, você precisa criar um request/mutation que seja responsável por retornar um token que será utilizado. Por exemplo:

Agora na request/mutation, vá para a se…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gustavo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ashkan Rajaee just raised the bar for how virtual meetings should be done.]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/thedenisegagnon/ashkan-rajaee-just-raised-the-bar-for-how-virtual-meetings-should-be-done-2h1k</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/thedenisegagnon/ashkan-rajaee-just-raised-the-bar-for-how-virtual-meetings-should-be-done-2h1k"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T19:17:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ashkan Rajaee’s Secret Formula for Remote Meetings That Outsmart the Competition
Anthony James ・ May 20
#productivity
        #remote
        #business
        #leadership]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Denise Gagnon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Day 7 – “TOP Secret Info: Monitoring Your Linux System Like a Pro (Sorta)”]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/higgs182092/day-7-top-secret-info-monitoring-your-linux-system-like-a-pro-sorta-m27</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/higgs182092/day-7-top-secret-info-monitoring-your-linux-system-like-a-pro-sorta-m27"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T19:17:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today, we level up. No more baby steps — we’re stepping into the world of Linux system monitoring.
You’ve created files. You’ve deleted files. You’ve yelled at permission errors. Now it’s time to ask the real questions:
“What the heck is my system even doing right now?”
Welcome to your first taste of Linux surveillance (the good kind). This is where we learn to peek under the hood without accidentally setting anything on fire.
Meet Your Mission: Know What’s Happening, While It’s Happening
top: The Helicopter Parent of Commands
htop: Like top, But With Swag
free -h: The Memory Therapist
df -h: The Disk Detective
Your Mini Mission
Why This Matters

Linux, like a mysterious roommate, is always doing something in the background. Sometimes it’s helpful. Sometimes it’s just eating all your CPU.
…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dan Higgins</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[🔐 Mapping Records to Users in Django Rest Framework (DRF)]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/ebereplenty/mapping-records-to-users-in-django-rest-framework-drf-36h0</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/ebereplenty/mapping-records-to-users-in-django-rest-framework-drf-36h0"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T19:15:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When building APIs with Django Rest Framework, one common requirement is to make sure each user only sees their own data.
In this tutorial, we’ll walk through how to map records to authenticated users, filter them correctly, and secure your API endpoints. Whether you’re building a dashboard, CRM, or SaaS app — this guide will help you do it right.
🎥 Watch the full tutorial here:









  
  
  🚧 The Problem


By default, your API might expose all records in a model to any authenticated user. That’s a privacy and security risk — especially for multi-user apps.
We need a way to:
Automatically assign a record to the logged-in user
Filter querysets so users only see their own records
Prevent unauthorized access through permission checks
Here's how to fix that in DRF 👇
Connect Your Model t…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>NJOKU SAMSON EBERE</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meet rys — The Fastest Way to Build Debian Packages from Your Project]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/zyntraxis_c908fa8b32e04cb/meet-rys-the-fastest-way-to-build-debian-packages-from-your-project-59hl</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/zyntraxis_c908fa8b32e04cb/meet-rys-the-fastest-way-to-build-debian-packages-from-your-project-59hl"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T19:08:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Stop wasting time on complex packaging scripts! rys is a lightweight CLI tool that automates building .deb packages straight from your project files.
Automatically extracts metadata from zyn.toml and CMakeLists.txt
Supports console apps, GUI, services, libraries, scripts
Creates perfectly structured Debian packages with minimal fuss
Interactive prompts fill missing info — zero guesswork
Uses standard Debian tooling for rock-solid builds
Install with a single .deb, run rys build, and get a ready-to-install Debian package in seconds.
rys is made for developers who want simplicity and reliability without compromise.
Explore more or contribute on https://github.com/zyntraxis/rys.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Zyntraxis</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Memory Optimization in Java – Or, How to Stop Leaking Your Sanity]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/goldennoodles/memory-optimization-in-java-or-how-to-stop-leaking-your-sanity-424k</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/goldennoodles/memory-optimization-in-java-or-how-to-stop-leaking-your-sanity-424k"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T19:04:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Let's start with the obvious, Java is great. It’s got a garbage collector, it keeps your hands mostly clean of manual memory management, and it’ll let you write code that just works. Until it doesn’t... Until that sweet little app of yours starts slowing down like it’s stuck in mud and your grafana memory usage chart looks like it’s climbing Everest with no plans to come back.
So yes... Java handles memory for you. But if you don’t understand what it’s doing behind the scenes, it’s only a matter of time before your app becomes jabba the hutt.
Let’s talk about how not to let that happen.
Java's garbage collector is fantastic. It takes care of unused objects so you don’t have to manually free() them like in C. But here’s the catch -  the garbage collector only collects what it knows is garba…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rus Kuzmin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Apollo’s Tokenized Credit Fund Set for Solana DeFi Debut as RWA Trend Expands]]></title>
        <id>dd6c31b9-61fb-4c38-a037-82c330292bb5</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2025/05/20/apollos-tokenized-credit-fund-set-for-solana-defi-debut-as-rwa-trend-expands"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T18:52:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kamino Finance and Steakhouse Financial are teaming up to bring Securitize's ACRED token to the fast-growing Solana DeFi ecosystem.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Krisztian Sandor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The NSA Selector]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/wenzellabs/the_NSA_selector</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/wenzellabs/the_NSA_selector"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T18:30:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Announcing Gemma 3n preview: powerful, efficient, mobile-first AI]]></title>
        <id>https://developers.googleblog.com/en/introducing-gemma-3n/</id>
        <link href="https://developers.googleblog.com/en/introducing-gemma-3n/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T18:29:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google AI Ultra]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.google/products/google-one/google-ai-ultra/</id>
        <link href="https://blog.google/products/google-one/google-ai-ultra/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T18:20:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Red Programming Language]]></title>
        <id>https://www.red-lang.org/p/about.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.red-lang.org/p/about.html"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T18:14:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin ready to ‘vaporize’ shorts once price discovery above $110K begins]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-ready-to-vaporize-shorts-once-price-discovery-above-110k-begins</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-ready-to-vaporize-shorts-once-price-discovery-above-110k-begins?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T18:05:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Key takeaways:

An end-of-month Bitcoin price close above $102,400 would set the highest monthly close ever, proving the bull market continues at a rapid pace.

Over $3 billion in Bitcoin short positions are vulnerable above $107,000, creating a “liquidation magnet” that could send BTC price to new highs.

Bitcoin (BTC) is 11 days from potentially setting its highest monthly candle close in history. After achieving a record weekly close of $106,407 on May 18, BTC could secure a new monthly high by closing above $102,400 this month.
Bitcoin 1-month chart. Source: Cointelegraph/TradingView
With respect to its current market trend, Bitcoin is inches away from a ‘price discovery’ period, as noted by crypto trader Jelle.
Price discovery in this context refers to the process where buyers and sel…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Biraajmaan Tamuly</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase CEO&#039;s journey from no &#039;political causes&#039; to hiring DOGE staff]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/brian-armstrong-coinbase-political-journey</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/brian-armstrong-coinbase-political-journey?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Five years ago, Brian Armstrong wanted employees of his cryptocurrency exchange to refrain from expressing political views at work. Now, the Coinbase CEO seems to be open to involvement with Republican figures, including members of US President Donald Trump’s inner circle.
In a May 13 X post, Armstrong said members of the Department of Government Efficiency (DOGE) team, spearheaded by Elon Musk, though not set up as an actual department, would be welcome to implement cost-cutting changes at Coinbase after leaving the US government. 
Armstrong offered to set up an accelerated onboarding process with the exchange, responding to an interview in which at least one DOGE staffer felt ostracized from Harvard University, where he had been enrolled.
“If you are looking for your next mission after s…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Turner Wright</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing Veo 3 and Imagen 4, and a new tool for filmmaking called Flow]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.google/technology/ai/generative-media-models-io-2025/</id>
        <link href="https://blog.google/technology/ai/generative-media-models-io-2025/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T17:46:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google just leapfrogged every competitor with mind-blowing AI that can think deeper, shop smarter, and create videos with dialogue]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008346</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/google-just-leapfrogged-every-competitor-with-mind-blowing-ai-that-can-think-deeper-shop-smarter-and-create-videos-with-dialogue/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T17:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google unveiled major AI advancements at I/O 2025, including Gemini 2.5 with Deep Think, AI Mode in Search, Veo 3 for video with audio, and a $249 Ultra plan aimed at power users and enterprises.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Nuñez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google’s Jules aims to out-code Codex in battle for the AI developer stack]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008361</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/googles-jules-aims-to-out-code-codex-in-battle-for-the-ai-developer-stack/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T17:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google released Jules, its coding agent, into beta as autonomous coding agents are quickly gaining market share.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Emilia David</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Inside Google’s AI leap: Gemini 2.5 thinks deeper, speaks smarter and codes faster]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008366</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/inside-google-ai-leap-gemini-2-5-thinks-deeper-speaks-smarter-codes-faster/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T17:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google is moving closer to its goal of autonomous agentic AI with a series of enhancements to Gemini 2.5 Pro and Flash.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Taryn Plumb</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Last Letter]]></title>
        <id>https://aeon.co/essays/how-the-last-letters-of-the-condemned-can-teach-us-how-to-live</id>
        <link href="https://aeon.co/essays/how-the-last-letters-of-the-condemned-can-teach-us-how-to-live"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T17:10:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Dawn of Nvidia's Technology]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.dshr.org/2025/05/the-dawn-of-nvidias-technology.html</id>
        <link href="https://blog.dshr.org/2025/05/the-dawn-of-nvidias-technology.html"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T17:04:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ashby (YC W19) Is Hiring Engineering Managers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ashbyhq.com/careers?utm_source=hn&amp;ashby_jid=933570bc-a3d6-4fcc-991d-dc399c53a58a</id>
        <link href="https://www.ashbyhq.com/careers?utm_source=hn&amp;ashby_jid=933570bc-a3d6-4fcc-991d-dc399c53a58a"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T17:00:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Validation Cloud Debuts Mavrik-1 AI Engine on Hedera to Democratize DeFi Data Analysis and Web3]]></title>
        <id>aa892120-4788-4a32-b30a-3103c605d77a</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/press-release/2025/05/20/emb-13-00-est-validation-cloud-debuts-mavrik-1-ai-engine-on-hedera-to-democratize-defi-data-analysis-and-web3"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T17:00:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mavrik-1 aims to lower the barrier to DeFi adoption by allowing users to access complex data without technical expertise.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Omkar Godbole</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Validation Cloud deploys Web3 AI engine on Hedera]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/validation-cloud-deploys-web3-ai-engine-hedera</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/validation-cloud-deploys-web3-ai-engine-hedera?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Artificial intelligence platform Validation Cloud has launched a new large language model on the Hedera network, potentially giving decentralized finance users the ability to reach blockchain data in a more accessible way.
The Mavrik-1 AI engine has been deployed on Hedera, with several other planned integrations expected during a public rollout later this year, Validation Cloud’s team told Cointelegraph. 
The AI engine is designed to allow users to interact with DeFi protocols and access blockchain data through natural language queries without needing technical expertise or knowledge. 
Mavrik-1 uses live onchain data trained for DeFi, stablecoins and other blockchain applications. 
Hedera DeFi metrics, including total value locked (TVL), decentralized exchange volume and stablecoin activi…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Sam Bourgi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SEC crypto task force to release first report &#039;in the next few months&#039;]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/sec-chair-paul-atkins-report-crypto-months</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/sec-chair-paul-atkins-report-crypto-months?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T16:49:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) Chair Paul Atkins appeared before lawmakers in one of his first hearings since taking the reins at the financial regulator, addressing questions about his plans for the cryptocurrency industry.
In a May 20 hearing discussing oversight of the SEC, Atkins reiterated his pledge to make regulating digital assets a “key priority” while chair. In response to questions from North Carolina Representative Chuck Edwards, the SEC chair did not directly answer how much of the regulator’s funds were used to support the crypto task force headed by Commissioner Hester Peirce, and said its findings were “still under development.”
“We should be having something here in the next few months with proposed steps forward,” said Atkins, referring to the task force’s fi…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Turner Wright</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Show HN:  Olelo Foil - NACA Airfoil Sim]]></title>
        <id>https://foil.olelohonua.com/</id>
        <link href="https://foil.olelohonua.com/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T16:44:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Genesis Files Suits Against DCG to Recover Billions Worth of Allegedly Fraudulent Transfers]]></title>
        <id>803a60d0-2728-4650-a0fd-9ea08b8c46c4</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2025/05/20/genesis-files-suits-against-dcg-to-recover-billions-worth-of-allegedly-fraudulent-transfers"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T16:43:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[DCG, CEO Barry Silbert and others withdrew billions of dollars from the company they knew was failing while keeping customers in the dark, according to the lawsuits.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Camomile Shumba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SocGen’s Crypto Arm to Launch Dollar Denominated Stablecoin on Ethereum, Reports Say]]></title>
        <id>2ea339d8-43ab-4408-85cd-371da0407ef5</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/20/socgen-s-crypto-arm-to-launch-dollar-denominated-stablecoin-on-ethereum-reports-say"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T16:38:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The stablecoin, initially for institutional investors, follows the launch of SG Forge’s euro stablecoin, EURCV.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Francisco Rodrigues</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Show HN: Juvio – UV Kernel for Jupyter]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/OKUA1/juvio</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/OKUA1/juvio"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T16:32:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Robin: A multi-agent system for automating scientific discovery]]></title>
        <id>https://arxiv.org/abs/2505.13400</id>
        <link href="https://arxiv.org/abs/2505.13400"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T16:21:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Falters Near Record, but 'Realized Price' Analysis Suggests Optimistic Outlook]]></title>
        <id>58f97b38-7391-489b-9f47-684c4066f3b7</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/20/bitcoin-falters-near-record-but-realized-price-analysis-suggests-optimistic-outlook"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T16:20:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tracking average exchange withdrawal prices reveals signs of capitulation and a shift toward recovery.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>James Van Straten</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Argentina&#039;s Milei shuts down task force investigating LIBRA scandal]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/javier-milei-shuts-down-task-force-investigating-libra-scandal</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/javier-milei-shuts-down-task-force-investigating-libra-scandal?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T16:19:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Argentine President Javier Milei has dissolved a task force established to investigate the fallout from LIBRA, the scandalous cryptocurrency project the head of state promoted on his social media channel before it crashed to zero. 
The Investigative Task Force (ITU) was dissolved via a May 19 decree signed by Milei and Justice Minister Mariano Cúneo Libarona, government documents revealed. 
“The Research Task Unit is dissolved” after completing its mandate, the translated version of the decree read.
The task force is being dissolved despite pressure from opposition groups, which are seeking to activate an investigative commission as soon as May 20, local media outlet Clarin reported. 
A screenshot of Milei’s tweet endorsing LIBRA. Source: TRM Labs
Government officials established the UTI o…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Sam Bourgi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[XRP Price Slips as Bearish Chart Pattern Points to $2.00 Target]]></title>
        <id>fc28eaf2-9990-4b2e-88da-771f0d8cdce8</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/20/xrp-price-slips-as-bearish-chart-pattern-points-to-usd2-00-target"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T16:13:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Market sentiment shifts as XRP faces critical support test amid global economic uncertainties and upcoming token unlock.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>AI Boost</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Teachable Machine]]></title>
        <id>https://teachablemachine.withgoogle.com/</id>
        <link href="https://teachablemachine.withgoogle.com/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T16:07:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why is Ethereum (ETH) price up today?]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/why-is-ethereum-eth-price-up-today</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/why-is-ethereum-eth-price-up-today?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T16:00:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Key takeaways:

Ether’s price rose over 5% to $2,520 on May 20, mirroring similar upward moves across the wider cryptocurrency market.

Ethereum’s record open interest, rising funding rates and a significant short squeeze fuel the rally.

A classic recovery pattern suggests a potential 92% rally toward $4,800 as ETH holds key support.

Ether (ETH) price rose by over 5% in the last 24 hours to around $2,520 on May 20 amid increasing futures open interest. 
Data from Cointelegraph Markets Pro and TradingView shows ETH gained as much as 10%, rising to an intraday high of $2,590 on May 20 from a low of $2,350 on May 19. 
ETHUSD daily chart. Source: Cointelegraph/TradingView
Ether price move mirrors marketwide recovery
ETH’s price rise on May 20 mirrors the bullish sentiment in the market that …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Yashu Gola</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[27000 Dragons and 10'000 Lights: GPU-Driven Clustered Forward Renderer]]></title>
        <id>https://logdahl.net/p/gpu-driven</id>
        <link href="https://logdahl.net/p/gpu-driven"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T15:57:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Fractured Entangled Representation Hypothesis]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/akarshkumar0101/fer</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/akarshkumar0101/fer"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T15:56:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Milei Closes Down LIBRA Investigative Unit After It Shares Findings With Prosecutors]]></title>
        <id>9effbd9a-c483-40c0-be94-d99247e8713f</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2025/05/20/milei-closes-down-libra-investigative-unit-after-it-shares-findings-with-prosecutors"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T15:54:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The country's Department of Justice claims the investigative unit has fulfilled its purpose.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tom Carreras</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blazing-fast Solana data via gRPC: access the freshest Solana data from Shredstream leaders]]></title>
        <id>68273f14bf73460001094b35</id>
        <link href="https://blog.quicknode.com/yellowstone-grpc/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T15:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Access the fastest Solana data with the Yellowstone Geyser gRPC self-serve add-on or with the premium hybrid dedicated gRPC node.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>QuickNode</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Launch HN: Opusense (YC X25) – AI assistant for construction inspectors on site]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=44042791</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=44042791"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T15:35:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Show HN: A Tiling Window Manager for Windows, Written in Janet]]></title>
        <id>https://agent-kilo.github.io/jwno/</id>
        <link href="https://agent-kilo.github.io/jwno/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T15:08:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The crypto market values chains more than standalone applications]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/the-crypto-market-values-chains</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/the-crypto-market-values-chains?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Opinion by: Hatu Sheikh, founder of Coin Terminal
Although blockchains and DApps are critical, crypto industry stakeholders often prioritize applications based on adoption principles and revenue distribution. DApps won't function without their underlying chains. The markets must uphold blockchains for long-term value generation.
The value perspective is wrong 
Blockchains and DApps should work collaboratively to coordinate their functions for better usability. Instead, analysts create a binary between chains and DApps based on Web2's structural frameworks.
In “Fat Protocols,” Joel Monegro argued that value within the internet stack comprises "thin" protocols and "fat" applications. In other words, investing in the underlying protocol technologies like TCP/IP, HTTP, and SMTP gives lower ret…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Hatu Sheikh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Show HN: 90s.dev - game maker that runs on the web]]></title>
        <id>https://90s.dev/blog/finally-releasing-90s-dev.html</id>
        <link href="https://90s.dev/blog/finally-releasing-90s-dev.html"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T14:58:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Show HN: Astra – a new js2exe compiler]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/astracompiler/cli</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/astracompiler/cli"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T14:55:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Intel Announces New Arc Pro Graphics Cards At Computex 2025]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=352351</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/352351/intel-announces-new-arc-pro-graphics-cards-at-computex-2025/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T14:44:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Intel announced its Arc Pro lineup of graphics cards here at Computex 2025. As the name suggests, the GPU line isn’t for the average consumer and targetted towards professional visualisation and workstation demands, as well as serving as contenders to both AMD and NVIDIA’s own workstation offerings. Based on its second generation Battlemage GPU architecture, […]
The post Intel Announces New Arc Pro Graphics Cards At Computex 2025 appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John Law</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OpenAI Codex Review]]></title>
        <id>https://zackproser.com/blog/openai-codex-review</id>
        <link href="https://zackproser.com/blog/openai-codex-review"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T14:29:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tesla Model Y Juniper Deliveries Has Begun In Malaysia]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=352287</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/352287/tesla-model-y-juniper-deliveries-has-begun-in-malaysia/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T14:26:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tesla made its official debut in Malaysia on July 20 2023 with the unveiling of the Model Y SUV. Recently, the American automaker announced that it has begun the first deliveries of the Tesla Model Y Juniper in Malaysia. The deliveries were done through the Tesla Delivery Centre Cyberjaya, Tesla Service Centre Penang and Tesla […]
The post Tesla Model Y Juniper Deliveries Has Begun In Malaysia appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Keran</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kuching Urban Transportation System (KUTS) Expected To Commence In 2028]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=352308</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/352308/kuching-urban-transportation-system-kuts-2028/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T14:08:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Public transport is essential to society as it provides a reliable transport system. With that in mind Sarawak Metro has implemented the Kuching Urban Transportation System (KUTS) which, according to state deputy transport minister Datuk Dr Jerip Susil, is expected to commence in the year 2028. The purpose of the KUTS system is tackle the […]
The post Kuching Urban Transportation System (KUTS) Expected To Commence In 2028 appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Keran</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[True Markets Raises $11M in Series A, Launches Mobile-First DeFi Trading App on Solana]]></title>
        <id>ff9c816c-ae17-4868-9afd-1398aa7de635</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2025/05/20/true-markets-raises-11m-in-series-a-launches-mobile-first-defi-trading-app-on-solana"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The funding round was co-led by Accomplice and RRE Ventures, with participation from Reciprocal Ventures, Variant Fund and PayPal Ventures.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Will Canny</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Senate stablecoin vote splits Democrats amid concerns over corruption]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/senate-stablecoin-vote-democrats-corruption</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/senate-stablecoin-vote-democrats-corruption?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T13:59:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[US Senate Democrats are getting flak after they helped move stablecoin legislation ahead for discussion on the Senate floor.
On May 19, 16 Democratic senators broke from the party line to pass a motion to invoke cloture, which will now set the bill up for debate on the Senate floor. Some of the same Democrats had held up the bill in early May when they withdrew support, citing corruption concerns over President Donald Trump’s cryptocurrency dealings.
The bill’s opponents hailed lawmakers’ refusal to support it but were soon taken aback when the senators reversed their position. The lightly amended legislation contained no provisions regarding World Liberty Financial, the Trump family’s crypto venture.
Some activists have said that the Democrats supporting the bill should be ousted in the u…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Aaron Wood</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Deep Learning Is Applied Topology]]></title>
        <id>https://theahura.substack.com/p/deep-learning-is-applied-topology</id>
        <link href="https://theahura.substack.com/p/deep-learning-is-applied-topology"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T13:54:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Robinhood proposes SEC rules for tokenized real-world assets]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/robinhood-sec-tokenized-rwa-framework-proposal</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/robinhood-sec-tokenized-rwa-framework-proposal?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T13:50:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Robinhood submitted a 42-page proposal to the US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC), calling for a national framework to regulate tokenized real-world assets (RWAs).
The brokerage is seeking to modernize financial infrastructure by making tokenized assets legally equivalent to their traditional counterparts and enabling compliant onchain settlement, Forbes reported on May 20.
In the proposal, Robinhood also revealed plans for creating the Real World Asset Exchange (RRE), a trading platform offering offchain trade matching and onchain settlement for efficiency and transparency.
Robinhood is advocating for uniform federal standards to replace the patchwork of state-level securities regulations that currently apply. The platform would also integrate Know Your Customer (KYC) and Anti-Mon…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Amin Haqshanas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kraken expands in Europe with regulated crypto derivatives]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/kraken-launches-regulated-crypto-derivatives-europe</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/kraken-launches-regulated-crypto-derivatives-europe?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T13:46:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency exchange Kraken announced the launch of regulated derivatives trading on its platform under the European Union’s Markets in Financial Instruments Directive (MiFID II).
According to a May 20 announcement, Kraken’s perpetual and fixed maturity crypto futures contracts will be available for trading by retail and institutional customers in the European Economic Area (EEA). The announcement follows the exchange acquiring an MiFID license in early February through the acquisition of a Cypriot investment firm, approved by the Cyprus Securities and Exchange Commission.
Kraken’s head of exchange, Shannon Kurtas, said, “Europe is one of the fastest-growing regions for digital asset trading and investment, with some of the most sophisticated and demanding clients and institutions.” 
He…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Adrian Zmudzinski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Lisp in the Cellar: Dependent types that live upstairs [pdf]]]></title>
        <id>https://zenodo.org/records/15424968</id>
        <link href="https://zenodo.org/records/15424968"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T13:38:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Here’s what happened in crypto today]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/what-happened-in-crypto-today</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/what-happened-in-crypto-today?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T13:33:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today in crypto, the German government’s decision to sell it’s stack of 50,000 Bitcoin in summer 2024 has become a $2.3 billion faux pas, the US Senate advanced a key stablecoin bill, and Ripple launched cross-border payments in the United Arab Emirates.
German government missed out on $2.3 billion profit after selling Bitcoin at $57,000
The German government missed out on more than $2 billion worth of Bitcoin profit after selling its holdings in 2024, according to blockchain intelligence firm Arkham.
A “German Government (BKA)” labeled cryptocurrency wallet sold 49,858 Bitcoin (BTC) worth over $2.89 billion at an average price of $57,900 across multiple transactions during June and July in 2024.
The decision to sell the Bitcoin early cost the German government over $2.35 billion, accordin…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Cointelegraph</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CoinDesk 20 Performance Update: Litecoin (LTC) Drops 6.1%, Leading Index Lower]]></title>
        <id>c2c714df-3207-4be7-badd-50c5dd6f050e</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/coindesk-indices/2025/05/20/coindesk-20-performance-update-litecoin-ltc-drops-6-1-leading-index-lower"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T13:29:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Filecoin (FIL) was also among the underperformers, declining 2.9% from Monday.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CoinDesk Indices</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Circle co-founder to create ‘AI-native’ bank after $18M raise]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/catena-labs-raises-18m-ai-native-financial-institution</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/catena-labs-raises-18m-ai-native-financial-institution?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T13:25:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Circle co-founder and Catena Labs CEO Sean Neville has launched a project that aims to develop a financial institution that natively leverages artificial intelligence. 
On May 20, Catena Labs, the company building an “AI-native financial institution,” announced that it secured $18 million in a funding round led by Andreessen Horowitz (a16z) Crypto, a16z’s crypto and Web3 venture capital arm. 
Led by Neville, the company aims to realize its vision of a fully regulated financial institution for the AI economy. The company said it will be built for AI agents and human collaborators and will be operated by AI workers with human oversight and AI-specific risk management and compliance approaches. 
Cointelegraph contacted Catena Labs to get more information about the project but received no resp…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Ezra Reguerra</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[German gov’t missed out on $2.3B profit after selling Bitcoin at $57K]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/german-gov-t-missed-2-3b-bitcoin-profit-sold-btc-57k</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/german-gov-t-missed-2-3b-bitcoin-profit-sold-btc-57k?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T13:17:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The German government missed out on more than $2 billion worth of Bitcoin profit after selling its holdings in 2024, according to blockchain intelligence firm Arkham.
A “German Government (BKA)” labeled cryptocurrency wallet sold 49,858 Bitcoin (BTC) worth over $2.89 billion at an average price of $57,900 across multiple transactions during June and July in 2024.
The decision to sell the Bitcoin early cost the German government over $2.35 billion, according to crypto intelligence platform Arkham.
Source: Arkham 

“If they had held it, their BTC would now be worth $5.24B,” Arkham said in a May 19 X post, noting that Bitcoin has risen more than 80% since the sale.
At the time of publication, Bitcoin was trading at more than $104,700, according to CoinMarketCap data.  
Related: Justin Sun off…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Zoltan Vardai</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[KULR Boosts Bitcoin Treasury to 800 BTC With $9M Purchase]]></title>
        <id>d964e4f0-9c2b-4078-a3c0-bdd8725c29eb</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/20/kulr-boosts-bitcoin-treasury-to-800-btc-with-usd9m-purchase"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T13:06:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This latest acquisition was made at an average purchase price of $103,234 per bitcoin.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Francisco Rodrigues</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Government-Backed Funds Expanding MSTR Holdings Show Rising BTC Demand: Standard Chartered]]></title>
        <id>d3bcbe9c-bbb5-4cac-9821-7ea53bff1716</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/20/widening-government-strategy-holdings-suggest-increased-structural-demand-for-btc-stanchart"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T13:03:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Holdings of the stock by government bodies reflects a desire to gain bitcoin exposure where in some cases local regulators do not allow direct ownership, the report said.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Will Canny</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Avalanche-backed Fusion launches with $100M to boost blockchain adoption]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/fusion-blockchain-initiative-100m-modular-sector-networks</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/fusion-blockchain-initiative-100m-modular-sector-networks?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T12:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Avalanche, Helix and Faculty Group have launched Fusion,  a new blockchain ecosystem aimed at driving real-world adoption through modular infrastructure tailored to specific industries.
Built on Avalanche, Fusion features a two-layer architecture that includes composers, customizable layer-1 networks and modules, which offer plug-and-play services like compute, identity and data oracles. 
The team said this approach would be the answer for mainstream adoption, as they attempt to deliver “outcome-driven, domain-specific” blockchain-based economies. 
“In order to achieve widespread adoption, our industry needs to shift from selling blockspace to delivering business value,” a Fusion spokesperson told Cointelegraph. They added that Fusion integrates economic alignment, network design and compo…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Ezra Reguerra</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[llm-d, Kubernetes native distributed inference]]></title>
        <id>https://llm-d.ai/blog/llm-d-announce</id>
        <link href="https://llm-d.ai/blog/llm-d-announce"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T12:37:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[India’s Supreme Court urges government to regulate cryptocurrency]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/india-s-surpeme-court-asks-government-for-clearer-crypto-stance</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/india-s-surpeme-court-asks-government-for-clearer-crypto-stance?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T12:18:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[India’s Supreme Court questioned the government’s lack of regulatory clarity on cryptocurrencies despite imposing taxes on digital assets like Bitcoin.
According to the Indian legal news outlet LawChakra, the country’s Supreme Court expressed concern over the increasing use of Bitcoin (BTC) and other cryptocurrencies, which remain largely unregulated.
“This is a whole parallel economy running with such coins, and it is a danger to the economy of the country,” Justice Surya Kant reportedly said during a recent hearing related to an ongoing investigation into a Bitcoin transaction.
Kant said that while the government has implemented crypto taxation, it has failed to regulate the space.
“If you can tax it at 30%, also please regulate it as you have recognised it by taxing it,” the judge said.…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Adrian Zmudzinski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Download: introducing the AI energy package]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1117051</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/05/20/1117051/the-download-introducing-the-ai-energy-package/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T12:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is today’s edition of The Download, our weekday newsletter that provides a daily dose of what’s going on in the world of technology. We did the math on AI’s energy footprint. Here’s the story you haven’t heard. It’s well documented that AI is a power-hungry technology. But there has been far less reporting on the extent…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rhiannon Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Strategy's STRK Hits Record Proceeds, Has Outperformed Bitcoin, S&P 500 Since Debut]]></title>
        <id>d59329ed-578b-4a33-b319-74edc3bcf18e</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/20/strategys-strk-hits-record-proceeds-has-outperformed-bitcoin-sp-500-since-debut"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T12:08:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[STRK has risen more than bitcoin and the S&P 500 index while offering an attractive yield and differentiated market exposure.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>James Van Straten</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kraken Rolls Out Regulated Crypto Derivatives in Europe]]></title>
        <id>a5b7fe63-c0e0-47db-8626-931da7ef3431</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2025/05/20/kraken-rolls-out-regulated-crypto-derivatives-in-europe"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kraken is offering derivatives trading in digital assets, compliant with Europe's Markets in Financial Instruments Directive (MiFIDII).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ian Allison</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ether Is Set to Explode as Traders Pump Millions Into $6K ETH Bets]]></title>
        <id>7c0eb330-38c9-46bb-9054-521ee57be70f</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/20/ether-is-set-to-explode-as-traders-pump-millions-into-usd6k-eth-bets"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T11:45:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto traders are betting on Ethereum's ether to reach $6,000 by Dec. 26 through bull call spreads.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Omkar Godbole</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Samsung Galaxy Watch8 Series Receive 3C Certification]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=352343</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/352343/samsung-galaxy-watch8-series-receive-3c-certification/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T11:43:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Samsung is reportedly working on its Watch8 series, which is rumoured to be launching alongside the company’s upcoming foldable phones. Now, XpertPick has reported that two of the models, the Galaxy Watch8 and Galaxy Watch8 Classic have received a 3C certification (China Compulsory Certification). The Samsung Galaxy Watch8 and Galaxy Watch8 Classic are listed under […]
The post Samsung Galaxy Watch8 Series Receive 3C Certification appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Newsdesk</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Can't India Draft a Clear Cut Crypto Policy? Country's Supreme Court Raps Government]]></title>
        <id>caadec88-a528-4a6b-9a2f-1b8c183cf631</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2025/05/20/why-cant-india-draft-a-clear-cut-crypto-policy-countrys-supreme-court-raps-government"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T11:32:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Supreme court justice Surya Kant and N Kotiswar Singh said that there is "parallel under-market" for crypto that can affect the economy.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Crawley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Malaysia Launches First Full-Stack AI Infrastructure In The Region]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=352339</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/352339/malaysia-launches-first-full-stack-ai-infrastructure-in-region/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T11:27:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Malaysia has launched what is called the Strategic Artificial Intelligence Infrastructure, which was officiated by Deputy Comms Minister Teo Nie Ching. Despite the mundane sounding name, it is reportedly the first sovereign full-stack AI ecosystem in the region. Bernama cites the deputy minister as saying that its launch “marks an important step in the country’s […]
The post Malaysia Launches First Full-Stack AI Infrastructure In The Region appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ian Chee</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Daybook Americas: Bitcoin Stability Above $100K Is Cementing New Psychological Floor]]></title>
        <id>a69bb9a3-a3fb-4369-ae61-7c736d3efee7</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/daybook-us/2025/05/20/crypto-daybook-americas-bitcoin-stability-above-100k-is-cementing-new-psychological-floor"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T11:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Your day-ahead look for May 20, 2025]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Omkar Godbole</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Binance seeks to dismiss $1.76B FTX lawsuit, blames SBF for collapse]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/binance-seeks-dismissal-ftx-1-76b-lawsuit</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/binance-seeks-dismissal-ftx-1-76b-lawsuit?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T11:12:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Binance has filed a motion to dismiss a $1.76 billion lawsuit brought by the FTX estate, accusing the defunct crypto exchange of trying to deflect blame for its own failure.
Filed on May 16 in the Delaware Bankruptcy Court, Binance’s legal team called the suit “legally deficient,” stating that FTX’s collapse was not triggered by market manipulation or hostile action but by internal misconduct.
“Plaintiffs are pretending that FTX did not collapse as the result of one of the most massive corporate frauds in history,” the filing said, pointing to Sam “SBF” Bankman-Fried’s conviction on seven counts of fraud and conspiracy.
FTX’s estate alleges that Binance received billions in crypto during a 2021 buyback deal, funded improperly with customer assets.
Binance rejects this claim, stating that “…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Amin Haqshanas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[You Can Now Take Your Very Own Samsung Galaxy A56 5G For As Low As RM20! Here’s How]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=352332</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/352332/you-can-take-samsung-galaxy-a56-5g-for-as-low-as-rm20-heres-how/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T10:51:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Samsung Galaxy A56 5G has easily become one of the most popular mid-range smartphones to have arrived, but not everyone can drop two grand on a whim for it. That being said, did you know that you don’t have to break the bank to get it? With a little change in the way you […]
The post You Can Now Take Your Very Own Samsung Galaxy A56 5G For As Low As RM20! Here’s How appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Newsdesk</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin privacy tool Payjoin receives $100K grant from Maelstrom]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-payjoin-privacy-grant-maelstrom</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-payjoin-privacy-grant-maelstrom?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T10:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin developer Ben Allen has received a $100,000 grant from investment firm Maelstrom to support the development of Payjoin, a privacy-focused tool aimed at improving Bitcoin’s scalability and privacy.
According to a May 20 announcement shared with Cointelegraph, Maelstrom will finance Allen’s work on his Payjoin devkit alongside Dan Gould. The system allows Bitcoin (BTC) senders and receivers to use batched transactions, with positive implications for scalability and privacy.
Payjoin Developer Kit’s website. Source: Payjoin Dev Kit
Payjoin was first proposed by Nicolas Dorier in 2019 in Bitcoin improvement proposal (BIP) 78. The core principle behind the system is that both senders and receivers may contribute inputs to a transaction.
“Namely that privacy is enhanced and improved conso…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Adrian Zmudzinski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Samsung Announced New TV Lineup Featuring Vision AI]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=352295</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/352295/samsung-announced-new-tv-lineup-featuring-vision-ai/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T10:38:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Samsung unveiled its AI TV lineup for the year, with a few soundbars to go with them. But while the new range of smart TVs were the the highlight, arguably more important was the Vision AI tech that came with it. And it’s a feature with a wide range of functionality, from AI upscaling to […]
The post Samsung Announced New TV Lineup Featuring Vision AI appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ian Chee</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The emoji problem (2022)]]></title>
        <id>https://artofproblemsolving.com/community/c2532359h2760821_the_emoji_problem__part_i?srsltid=AfmBOor9TbMq_A7hGHSJGfoWaa2HNzducSYZu35d_LFlCSNLXpvt-pdS</id>
        <link href="https://artofproblemsolving.com/community/c2532359h2760821_the_emoji_problem__part_i?srsltid=AfmBOor9TbMq_A7hGHSJGfoWaa2HNzducSYZu35d_LFlCSNLXpvt-pdS"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T10:18:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin is signaling a golden cross — What does it mean for BTC price?]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-golden-cross-what-does-it-mean-for-btc-price</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-golden-cross-what-does-it-mean-for-btc-price?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T10:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Key takeaways:

Bitcoin is nearing a golden cross that has led to 45%–60% price rallies in the recent past.

Fundamentals like rising M2 supply and easing trade tensions support a bullish outlook.

Bearish divergence and overbought conditions show there’s still a risk of BTC falling below $100,000.

Bitcoin (BTC) will likely confirm a “golden cross” on its daily chart by the end of May, a technical pattern whose occurrences in recent years often preceded rallies.
Source: Benjamin Cowen
Previous golden crosses led to 45%-60% BTC price rallies
As of May 20, Bitcoin’s 50-day simple moving average (50-day SMA; the red wave) was eyeing a close above its 200-day SMA (the blue wave) for the first time since October 2024, forming a golden cross.
BTC/USD daily price chart. Source: TradingView
Previ…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Yashu Gola</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Solana Surges 6% on Bullish Reversal and DeFi Demand]]></title>
        <id>e2865e87-b973-40cc-84e2-3f56b9aa77ce</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/20/solana-sol-surges-6-on-bullish-reversal-and-defi-activity-toward-usd180"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T10:05:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SOL shows strong momentum with institutional buying signals despite brief correction.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>AI Boost</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Circle Has Explored Potential $5B Sale to Coinbase or Ripple Instead of IPO: Report]]></title>
        <id>7c37af0e-4b3d-4a8b-b779-bacd1af82266</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2025/05/20/circle-has-explored-potential-5b-sale-to-coinbase-or-ripple-instead-of-ipo-report"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T10:02:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The stablecoin issuer took part in informal talks over a potential sale from which it was seeking at least $5 billion.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Crawley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase data leak could put users in physical danger: TechCrunch founder]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/coinbase-breach-physical-crime-techcrunch-founder</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/coinbase-breach-physical-crime-techcrunch-founder?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T10:02:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A recent data breach at crypto exchange Coinbase has raised concerns about user safety after hackers gained access to sensitive information, including home addresses.
Coinbase, the world’s third-largest cryptocurrency exchange, confirmed that less than 1% of its transacting monthly users were affected in an attack that may cost the exchange up to $400 million in reimbursement expenses, Cointelegraph reported on May 15.
However, the “human cost” of this data breach may be much higher for users, according to Michael Arrington, the founder of TechCrunch and Arrington Capital.
“Very disappointed in Coinbase right now. Using the cheapest option for customer service has its price,” Arrington said in a May 20 X post, adding:
“Something that has to be said though - this hack - which includes home …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Zoltan Vardai</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[RWA Platform TokenFi Is Tokenizing the Floki Minibot]]></title>
        <id>f1fda8ea-0df9-4429-8f17-f3e866f4f48a</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/20/rwa-platform-tokenfi-is-tokenizing-the-floki-minibot"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A presale for the Floki Minibot M1 AI robot, made by Rice Robotics, starts May 23, the same day TokenFi’s real-world asset tokenization module goes live.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shaurya Malwa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A simple search engine from scratch]]></title>
        <id>https://bernsteinbear.com/blog/simple-search/</id>
        <link href="https://bernsteinbear.com/blog/simple-search/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T09:58:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SHIB Jumps Nearly 7% as Bulls Break Through Resistance on Heavy Buying]]></title>
        <id>81593e19-efce-4331-8328-844c196a2a77</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/20/shib-jumps-nearly-7-as-bulls-break-through-resistance-on-heavy-buying"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T09:47:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The popular meme token shows remarkable resilience despite 80% of holders underwater on their investments.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>AI Boost</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[South Korean presidential front-runner proposes won-based stablecoin]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/korea-stablecoin-proposal-lee-jae-myung</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/korea-stablecoin-proposal-lee-jae-myung?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T09:25:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[South Korea’s Democratic Party leader Lee Jae-myung proposed creating a stablecoin tied to the Korean won to prevent capital outflows and strengthen national financial sovereignty.
Speaking during a recent policy discussion, Lee argued that a won-based stablecoin would allow South Korea to retain wealth domestically while reducing reliance on foreign-issued digital assets like USDt (USDT) and USDC (USDC), according to The Korea Herald.
Currently, South Korean law prohibits the issuance of domestic stablecoins, forcing local exchanges to rely on US dollar-based alternatives.
Between January and March, crypto exchanges in the country recorded 56.8 trillion won ($40.8 billion) in asset outflows, nearly half of which were linked to foreign stablecoins, the report said.
“We need to establish a …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Amin Haqshanas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AAVE Surges 24% in Explosive Rally, Breaking Key Resistance Levels]]></title>
        <id>26040b7b-4838-426c-901b-b9f739569e66</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/20/aave-surges-24-in-explosive-rally-breaking-key-resistance-levels"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T09:11:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Institutional interest grows as AAVE establishes new support levels amid broader crypto market strength.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>AI Boost</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rapid KL To Extend Rail Operations For ASEAN Summit 2025]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=352297</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/352297/rapid-kl-extend-rail-operations-asean-summit-2025/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T09:07:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Rapid KL has announced that it will be extending its morning and evening peak-hour rail operations by an hour from 23 to 27 May 2025, in conjunction with the 46th ASEAN Summit that is taking place in Kuala Lumpur and Putrajaya. Additionally, train frequencies on 24 and 25 May will be increased to accommodate the […]
The post Rapid KL To Extend Rail Operations For ASEAN Summit 2025 appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nurul Kamil</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MediaTek Deepens Collaboration With NVIDIA To Power Next-Gen AI Infrastructure]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=352301</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/352301/mediatek-deepens-nvidia-collab-computex-2025/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T09:01:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At Computex 2025 in Taipei, MediaTek outlined its artificial intelligence strategy, spanning both edge devices and cloud infrastructure. Alongside plans for a 2nm chip process, the company also announced an expanded partnership with NVIDIA. NVIDIA CEO Jensen Huang appeared alongside MediaTek CEO Rick Tsai during Tsai’s keynote to discuss the companies’ joint efforts. As Huang […]
The post MediaTek Deepens Collaboration With NVIDIA To Power Next-Gen AI Infrastructure appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Heirul Kamel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AI could keep us dependent on natural gas for decades to come]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1116272</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/05/20/1116272/ai-natural-gas-data-centers-energy-power-plants/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The thousands of sprawling acres in rural northeast Louisiana had gone unwanted for nearly two decades. Louisiana authorities bought the land in Richland Parish in 2006 to promote economic development in one of the poorest regions in the state. For years, they marketed the former agricultural fields as the Franklin Farm mega site, first to…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Rotman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AI’s energy impact is still small—but how we handle it is huge]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1116274</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/05/20/1116274/opinion-ai-energy-use-data-centers-electricity/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With seemingly no limit to the demand for artificial intelligence, everyone in the energy, AI, and climate fields is justifiably worried. Will there be enough clean electricity to power AI and enough water to cool the data centers that support this technology? These are important questions with serious implications for communities, the economy, and the…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Costa Samaras, Emma Strubell, Ramayya Krishnan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The data center boom in the desert]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1116287</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/05/20/1116287/ai-data-centers-nevada-water-reno-computing-environmental-impact/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the high desert east of Reno, Nevada, construction crews are flattening the golden foothills of the Virginia Range, laying the foundations of a data center city. Google, Tract, Switch, EdgeCore, Novva, Vantage, and PowerHouse are all operating, building, or expanding huge facilities within the Tahoe Reno Industrial Center, a business park bigger than the…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>James Temple</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[We did the math on AI’s energy footprint. Here’s the story you haven’t heard.]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1116327</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/05/20/1116327/ai-energy-usage-climate-footprint-big-tech/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The emissions from individual AI text, image, and video queries seem small—until you add up what the industry isn’t tracking and consider where it’s heading next.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>James O'Donnell, Casey Crownhart</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Everything you need to know about estimating AI’s energy and emissions burden]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1116331</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/05/20/1116331/ai-energy-demand-methodology/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When we set out to write a story on the best available estimates for AI’s energy and emissions burden, we knew there would be caveats and uncertainties to these numbers. But, we quickly discovered, the caveats are the story too.  This story is a part of MIT Technology Review’s series “Power Hungry: AI and our…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>James O'Donnell, Casey Crownhart</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Four reasons to be optimistic about AI’s energy usage]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1116337</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/05/20/1116337/ai-energy-use-optimism/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The day after his inauguration in January, President Donald Trump announced Stargate, a $500 billion initiative to build out AI infrastructure, backed by some of the biggest companies in tech. Stargate aims to accelerate the construction of massive data centers and electricity networks across the US to ensure it keeps its edge over China. This…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Will Douglas Heaven</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Can nuclear power really fuel the rise of AI?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1116339</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/05/20/1116339/ai-nuclear-power-energy-reactors/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the AI arms race, all the major players say they want to go nuclear.   Over the past year, the likes of Meta, Amazon, Microsoft, and Google have sent out a flurry of announcements related to nuclear energy. Some are about agreements to purchase power from existing plants, while others are about investments looking to…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Casey Crownhart</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How AI is introducing errors into courtrooms]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1116823</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/05/20/1116823/how-ai-is-introducing-errors-into-courtrooms/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s been quite a couple weeks for stories about AI in the courtroom. You might have heard about the deceased victim of a road rage incident whose family created an AI avatar of him to show as an impact statement (possibly the first time this has been done in the US). But there’s a bigger,…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>James O'Donnell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why is Bitcoin price up today?]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/why-is-bitcoin-price-up-today</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/why-is-bitcoin-price-up-today?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T08:53:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Key points:

Bitcoin gained 3% to above $105,000 on May 20, fueled by high open interest in the futures market and increasing institutional demand.

A classic bullish pattern is in play, targeting BTC price at $138,000 and beyond.

Bitcoin (BTC) is up today, rising over 3% in the last 24 hours to over $105,500 on May 20. 
Data from Cointelegraph Markets Pro and TradingView shows that the BTC/USD pair climbed as much as 5% to an intraday high of $107,148 on May 20 from a low of $102,100 on May 19. 
BTC/USD daily chart. Source: Cointelegraph/TradingView
Let’s take a look at the factors driving up Bitcoin price today.
Spot Bitcoin ETF inflows boost BTC price
Bitcoin's recent price rise coincides with rising capital inflows into US spot Bitcoin exchange-traded funds (ETFs), highlighting the gr…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Nancy Lubale</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MG S5 EV Launches In Malaysia From RM115,900]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=352264</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/352264/mg-s5-ev-launches-in-malaysia-from-rm115900/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T08:47:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[MG Motor Malaysia has officially launched the all-new MG S5 EV SUV, with prices starting at RM115,900 for the COM variant, RM125,900 for the COM Long Range, and RM135,900 for the premium LUX Long Range. To mark both the launch and MG’s first anniversary in Malaysia, the first 500 buyers will enjoy an exclusive early […]
The post MG S5 EV Launches In Malaysia From RM115,900 appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Keran</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin ETF Inflows Surge as Basis Trade Nears 9%, Signaling Renewed Demand]]></title>
        <id>da1dff55-690e-482c-948e-2c88afbee14b</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/20/bitcoin-etf-inflows-surge-as-basis-trade-nears-9-signaling-renewed-demand"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T08:08:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Investor confidence rises as bitcoin holds above $100,000 and basis trade yields approach 9%, drawing strong institutional interest.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>James Van Straten</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How $330M was stolen without hacking: The dark power of social engineering]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/explained/how-330m-was-stolen-without-hacking-the-dark-power-of-social-engineering</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/explained/how-330m-was-stolen-without-hacking-the-dark-power-of-social-engineering?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T08:05:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The $330 million attack: A stark reminder of social engineering’s power            
            
                
A major crypto theft has sent shockwaves through the industry, with $330 million worth of Bitcoin (BTC) stolen. Experts say this was a social engineering attack and not a technical hack. 
Investigations led by blockchain analyst ZachXBT suggest the victim was an elderly US citizen who was manipulated into granting access to their crypto wallet. On April 28, 2025, ZachXBT detected a suspicious transfer of 3,520 BTC, worth $330.7 million. 
The stolen BTC was quickly laundered through more than six instant exchanges and converted into the privacy-oriented cryptocurrency Monero (XMR). Onchain analysis shows the victim had held over 3,000 BTC since 2017, with no previous record of s…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Dilip Kumar Patairya</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Genesis files dual lawsuits to claw back $3.3B from DCG, Barry Silbert]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/genesis-sues-dcg-barry-silbert-3-3b-fraud</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/genesis-sues-dcg-barry-silbert-3-3b-fraud?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T08:02:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Update May 20, 11:20 am UTC: This article has been updated with comments from DCG.
Genesis has launched a pair of lawsuits against its parent company, Digital Currency Group (DCG), and its CEO, Barry Silbert, accusing them of fraud, reckless mismanagement and siphoning more than a billion dollars in value from the now-bankrupt crypto lender.
On May 19, the Delaware Court of Chancery unsealed a complaint detailing how DCG allegedly used Genesis as a corporate ATM, draining funds through self-serving loans and concealed transfers while presenting a false image of financial health.
Through their court-appointed Litigation Oversight Committee (LOC), Genesis creditors claim that over a million digital coins — worth about $2.1 billion — were funneled away, even as Genesis edged toward collapse.
…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Amin Haqshanas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin and Gold in Sweet Spot as Bond Market 'Smackdown' Exposes the U.S. Fiscal Kayfabe: Godbole]]></title>
        <id>87e407fe-0742-4bc9-bace-12af02d9c584</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/20/bitcoin-and-gold-in-sweet-spot-as-bond-markets-expose-the-u-s-fiscal-kayfabe-omkar-godbole"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T07:52:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bond markets are challenging the illusion of U.S. fiscal stability and safe haven status. BTC and gold stand to gain.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Omkar Godbole</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sorry bears — Bitcoin analysis dismisses $107K BTC price double top]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-bears-analysis-dismisses-btc-price-double-top</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-bears-analysis-dismisses-btc-price-double-top?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T07:48:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Key points:

Bitcoin is not in line to cancel its attack on all-time highs, says the Bitcoin Fundamental Index (BFI).

BTC price strength remains “intact,” says Swissblock Technologies, removing the risk of a double top.

Historically, a return to within 10% of all-time highs delivers price discovery almost every time.

Bitcoin (BTC) does not risk a “double top” bull market reversal with its trip past $107,000, new analysis says.
In one of its latest X updates, private wealth manager Swissblock Technologies described BTC price strength as “intact.”

BTC price indicator ignores double top “noise”
Bitcoin shows “no signs of bearish divergence,” as seen through the lens of a basket of network indicators.
Commenting on the latest signals from its Bitcoin Fundamental Index (BFI), Swissblock arg…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by William Suberg</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[KuCoin Enhances Point-of-Sale Mobile Payments With AEON]]></title>
        <id>ea69ed03-c9f5-493f-84fd-9e98a23bbf38</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2025/05/20/kucoin-enhances-point-of-sale-mobile-payments-with-aeon"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T07:18:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[KuCoin is exploring how it can accelerate crypto adoption by allowing users to easily spend it when carrying out day-to-day transactions]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Crawley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ether Surges 8%, Bitcoin Nears $106K as Crypto Bulls Take Charge]]></title>
        <id>d2286942-fa04-4d28-99d8-81cf24c8d202</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/20/ether-surges-8-bitcoin-nears-106k-as-crypto-bulls-take-charge"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T06:42:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The crypto market's resilience contrasts with the decline in equities and gold following Moody's U.S. credit downgrade.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shaurya Malwa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trump signs bill criminalizing nonconsensual AI deepfake porn]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/trump-signs-bill-criminalizing-nonsensenual-ai-deepfake-porn</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/trump-signs-bill-criminalizing-nonsensenual-ai-deepfake-porn?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T06:21:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[US President Donald Trump has signed a bill criminalizing nonconsensual artificial intelligence-generated deepfake porn, which also requires websites to take down any illicit images within 48 hours.
Trump signed the bill into law on May 19, known as the TAKE IT DOWN Act, an acronym for Tools to Address Known Exploitation by Immobilizing Technological Deepfakes on Websites and Networks.
The bill, backed by first lady Melania Trump, makes it a federal crime to publish, or threaten to publish, nonconsensual intimate images, including deepfakes, of adults or minors with the intent to harm or harass them. Penalties range from fines to prison.
Source: Melania Trump
Websites, online services, or apps must remove illegal content within 48 hours and establish a takedown process.
Trump said in remar…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Stephen Katte</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Making Video Games (Without an Engine) in 2025]]></title>
        <id>https://noelberry.ca/posts/making_games_in_2025/</id>
        <link href="https://noelberry.ca/posts/making_games_in_2025/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T05:54:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Indonesia’s DigiAsia shares pop 90% on plan to raise $100M to buy Bitcoin]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/digiasia-shares-gain-90-percent-100-million-raise-for-bitcoin</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/digiasia-shares-gain-90-percent-100-million-raise-for-bitcoin?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T04:53:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Shares in the Indonesian fintech firm DigiAsia Corp nearly doubled after the company said it plans to raise $100 million to seed its first of many Bitcoin buys. 
The Jakarta-based Nasdaq-listed company said on May 19 that its board of directors approved creating a Bitcoin (BTC) “treasury reserve” and it was “committing up to 50% of any net profits generated to fund the acquisition of BTC.”
DigiAsia said it was also “actively exploring a capital raise of up to US$100 million” to kickstart its Bitcoin holdings and would look to earn yield on its holdings through means like lending and staking.

DigiAsia said it had “initiated discussions with regulated partners” on yield strategies and managing its planned Bitcoin holdings. The company added that it was also assessing whether to offer conver…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Stephen Katte</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SEC’s Crenshaw says agency playing ‘regulatory Jenga’ with crypto]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/sec-crenshaw-agency-playing-regulatory-jenga-with-crypto</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/sec-crenshaw-agency-playing-regulatory-jenga-with-crypto?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T03:08:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The US Securities and Exchange Commission’s sole Democratic Commissioner has said the agency is “playing a game of regulatory Jenga” with its approach to the crypto industry and market regulation under the Trump administration. 
In May 19 remarks at the SEC Speaks event, Commissioner Caroline Crenshaw cautioned against what she described as a dangerous dismantling of “discrete but interrelated rules” on crypto and the wider market.
She likened market stability to a “Jenga tower” that the agency’s rules had “carefully developed over the years,” which could topple if some rules were removed.
In addition to a lamentable loss of staff, Crenshaw said the SEC has used staff guidance to effectively reverse rules without proper analysis or public comment, particularly around crypto
“Our statements…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Martin Young</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Binance wants arbitration for all members of securities class suit]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/binance-wants-arbitration-members-securities-class-suit</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/binance-wants-arbitration-members-securities-class-suit?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T02:26:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto exchange Binance has asked a US federal judge to send all members of a class-action lawsuit alleging it sold securities to arbitration, arguing that the group waived their ability to form a class action under the company’s terms.
The exchange said in a May 16 filing to a New York federal court that its terms of service, which it claimed the class group agreed to, has a clause that users agree to arbitrate all claims, along with a clause preventing users from launching class actions against the crypto exchange.
“The Court should hold that Plaintiffs are required to arbitrate claims that accrued after Feb. 20, 2019, even if the Court adheres to its initial decision as to claims that accrued before then and that the class-action waiver in the 2019 Terms of Use is enforceable for all of…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Stephen Katte</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JPMorgan boss says bank users can soon buy Bitcoin]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/jpmorgan-boss-bank-users-soon-buy-bitcoin</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/jpmorgan-boss-bank-users-soon-buy-bitcoin?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T01:55:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jamie Dimon, the CEO of JPMorgan, said his bank will soon allow its clients to buy Bitcoin, but it won’t custody the cryptocurrency.
“We are going to allow you to buy it,” Dimon said at JPMorgan’s annual investor day on May 19. “We’re not going to custody it. We’re going to put it in statements for clients.”
CNBC reported that Dimon also remarked on his long-held skepticism about crypto assets, pointing to their use in money laundering, sex trafficking and terrorism.
“I don’t think you should smoke, but I defend your right to smoke. I defend your right to buy Bitcoin,” he said.
Michael Saylor comments on Dimon’s announcement. Source: Michael Saylor
JPMorgan will offer clients access to Bitcoin (BTC) exchange-traded funds (ETFs), CNBC reported, citing sources familiar with the situation. Until now, the firm has limited its crypto exposure primarily to futures-based products, not direct ownership of digital assets.
Related: Morgan Stanley advisers can officially pitch Bitcoin ETFs
JPMorgan rival Morgan Stanley has also moved to offer spot Bitcoin ETFs to qualifying clients. Spot Bitcoin ETFs in the US have seen significant adoption, with almost $42 billion in total aggregate inflows since they launched in January 2024. 
Dimon’s Bitcoin bashing history
Dimon has long been skeptical of Bitcoin, labeling it a scam that he had no interest in buying in 2018 and calling it “worthless” during the 2021 crypto bull market.
“I’ve always been deeply opposed to crypto, Bitcoin, etc.,” he said during a Senate Banking Committee hearing in 2023. “The only true use case for it is criminals, drug traffickers, money laundering, tax avoidance.”
“If I were the government, I’d close it down,” he said.
At the 2024 World Economic Forum in Davos, Switzerland, Dimon said Bitcoin “does nothing. I call it the pet rock,” which came after the asset topped $100,000 for the first time.  
Magazine: Arthur Hayes $1M Bitcoin tip, altcoins ‘powerful rally’ looms: Hodler’s Digest]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Martin Young</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DDoSecrets publishes 410 GB of heap dumps, hacked from TeleMessage]]></title>
        <id>https://micahflee.com/ddosecrets-publishes-410-gb-of-heap-dumps-hacked-from-telemessages-archive-server/</id>
        <link href="https://micahflee.com/ddosecrets-publishes-410-gb-of-heap-dumps-hacked-from-telemessages-archive-server/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T00:52:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft just launched an AI that discovered a new chemical in 200 hours instead of years]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008310</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/microsoft-just-launched-an-ai-that-discovered-a-new-chemical-in-200-hours-instead-of-years/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T18:34:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft launches Discovery platform that uses agentic AI to compress years of scientific research into days, transforming R&D across pharmaceuticals, materials science, and semiconductor industries.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Nuñez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Is your AI app pissing off users or going off-script? Raindrop emerges with AI-native observability platform to monitor performance]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008299</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/is-your-ai-app-pissing-off-users-or-going-off-script-raindrop-emerges-with-ai-native-observability-platform-to-monitor-performance/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T18:09:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With its rebrand and product expansion, Raindrop is betting that the next generation of software observability will be AI-first by design.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carl Franzen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft just taught its AI agents to talk to each other—and it could transform how we work]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008254</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/microsoft-just-taught-its-ai-agents-to-talk-to-each-other-and-it-could-transform-how-we-work/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T16:01:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft unveils multi-agent systems, WhatsApp integration, and Python-powered analytics for Copilot Studio at Build 2025, transforming how enterprises build and deploy AI solutions.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Nuñez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Microsoft Fabric has already been adopted by 70% of the Fortune 500 — and what’s next]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3007980</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/70-of-the-fortune-500-already-use-microsoft-fabric-and-its-now-getting-even-more-features-including-cosmosdb-support/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft integrates CosmosDB into Fabric, open sources DiskANN vector search, and unifies its data platforms to eliminate integration complexity that has slowed enterprise AI adoption.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sean Michael Kerner</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub Copilot evolves into autonomous agent with asynchronous code testing]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008231</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/github-copilot-evolves-into-autonomous-agent-with-asynchronous-code-testing/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub adds agentic capabilities to its Copilot coding assistant, competing with other more asynchronous coding platforms.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Emilia David</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft announces over 50 AI tools to build the ‘agentic web’ at Build 2025]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008229</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/microsoft-announces-over-50-ai-tools-to-build-the-agentic-web-at-build-2025/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T15:59:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft reveals its ambitious AI agent strategy, showcasing how multi-agent systems with persistent memory will transform enterprise workflows and accelerate development timelines.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Nuñez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Reddit, Webflow, and Superhuman are already customers—now GrowthX has $12M to grow]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008276</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/reddit-webflow-and-superhuman-are-already-customers-now-growthx-has-12m-to-grow/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[GrowthX secures $12M in funding for its "service-as-software" platform that combines AI with human expertise to boost content marketing results by up to 300%.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Nuñez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AI can do a better job of persuading people than we do]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1116779</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/05/19/1116779/ai-can-do-a-better-job-of-persuading-people-than-we-do/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Millions of people argue with each other online every day, but remarkably few of them change someone’s mind. New research suggests that large language models (LLMs) might do a better job. The finding suggests that AI could become a powerful tool for persuading people, for better or worse.   A multi-university team of researchers found that…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rhiannon Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Cybercriminals Crack Your Passwords (And How to Stay One Step Ahead)]]></title>
        <id>682b3930e99a22ce9f9199c8</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-cybercriminals-crack-your-passwords-and-how-to-stay-one-step-ahead/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T13:59:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Passwords are the keys to your digital life  –  email, bank accounts, social media, and even your workplace systems. Unfortunately, they’re also one of the weakest links in cybersecurity.  Every year, billions of credentials are stolen and sold on th...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Manish Shivanandhan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Quantum Machines launches Qualibrate open source framework to speed quantum computer calibration]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008032</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/games/quantum-machines-launches-qualibrate-open-source-framework-to-speed-quantum-computer-calibration/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Quantum Machines, a provider of advanced hybrid quantum-classical control solutions, announced today the release of Qualibrate.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dean Takahashi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Samsung boosts OLED TV gaming with Nvidia G-Sync compatibility]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008019</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/games/samsung-boosts-oled-tv-gaming-with-nvidia-g-sync-compatibility/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Samsung said its 2025 OLED TV lineup will feature Nvidia G-Sync compatibility, delivering smooth gameplay, low latency, and more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dean Takahashi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Salesforce just unveiled AI ‘digital teammates’ in Slack — and they’re coming for Microsoft Copilot]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008273</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/salesforce-just-unveiled-ai-digital-teammates-in-slack-and-theyre-coming-for-microsoft-copilot/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Salesforce launches Agentforce in Slack, transforming workplace productivity with specialized AI agents that operate as digital teammates, replacing one-size-fits-all AI assistants with purpose-built solutions.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Nuñez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Foxconn builds AI factory in partnership with Taiwan and Nvidia]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008261</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/games/foxconn-builds-ai-factory-in-partnership-with-taiwan-and-nvidia/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T07:14:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nvidia and Foxconn announced they are working with the Taiwan government to build an AI factory supercomputer.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dean Takahashi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nvidia launches AI-first DGX Personal Computing Systems]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008256</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/games/nvidia-launches-ai-first-dgx-personal-computing-systems/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T07:06:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nvidia announced that Taiwan’s leading system manufacturers are set to build Nvidia DGX Spark and DGX Station systems.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dean Takahashi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nvidia-powered supercomputer to enable quantum leap for Taiwan’s research]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008257</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/games/nvidia-powered-supercomputer-to-enable-quantum-leap-for-taiwans-research/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T06:58:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nvidia is powering a supercomputer at Taiwan’s National Center for High-Performance Computing that’s set to deliver over eight times more AI performance than before.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dean Takahashi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nvidia powers world’s largest quantum research supercomputer]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008248</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/games/nvidia-powers-worlds-largest-quantum-research-supercomputer/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T06:48:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nvidia announced the opening of the Global Research and Development Center for Business by Quantum-AI Technology.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dean Takahashi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nvidia provides Omniverse Blueprint for AI factory digital twins]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008243</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/games/nvidia-provides-omniverse-blueprint-for-ai-factory-digital-twins/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T06:34:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nvidia today announced a significant expansion of the Nvidia Omniverse Blueprint for AI factory digital twins, now available as a preview.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dean Takahashi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nvidia charges ahead with humanoid robotics aided by the cloud]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008144</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/games/nvidia-charges-ahead-with-humanoid-robotics-aided-by-the-cloud/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T06:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nvidia said it is racing ahead with humanoid robotics technology, providing more Blackwell systems to accelerate humanoid robot development.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dean Takahashi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[From dot-com to dot-AI: How we can learn from the last tech transformation (and avoid making the same mistakes)]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3007969</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/from-dot-com-to-dot-ai-how-we-can-learn-from-the-last-tech-transformation-and-avoid-making-the-same-mistakes/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-18T19:05:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The AI winners won’t be the ones slapping “AI” on a landing page — they’ll be creating products enterprises can't live without.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kailiang Fu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Compiling OCaml to the TI-84 CE Calculator]]></title>
        <id>https://farlow.dev/2025/05/17/ocaml-on-calculator</id>
        <link href="https://farlow.dev/2025/05/17/ocaml-on-calculator"/>
        <updated>2025-05-17T22:40:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gail Wellington, Commodore Software Prod Mgr "and Mother of CDTV", Has Died]]></title>
        <id>https://www.legacy.com/us/obituaries/name/gail-wellington-obituary?id=58418580</id>
        <link href="https://www.legacy.com/us/obituaries/name/gail-wellington-obituary?id=58418580"/>
        <updated>2025-05-17T21:27:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Adopting agentic AI? Build AI fluency, redesign workflows, don’t neglect supervision]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3007933</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/adopting-agentic-ai-build-ai-fluency-redesign-workflows-dont-neglect-supervision/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-17T19:05:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How can organizations decide how to use human-in-the-loop mechanisms and collaborative frameworks with AI agents?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Imran Aftab, 10Pearls</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google is quietly giving Amazon a leg up in digital book sales]]></title>
        <id>https://www.washingtonpost.com/technology/2025/05/16/google-amazon-ebooks-apps/</id>
        <link href="https://www.washingtonpost.com/technology/2025/05/16/google-amazon-ebooks-apps/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-17T11:15:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Production tests: a guidebook for better systems and more sleep]]></title>
        <id>https://martincapodici.com/2025/05/13/production-tests-a-guidebook-for-better-systems-and-more-sleep/</id>
        <link href="https://martincapodici.com/2025/05/13/production-tests-a-guidebook-for-better-systems-and-more-sleep/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-17T09:13:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google’s AlphaEvolve: The AI agent that reclaimed 0.7% of Google’s compute – and how to copy it]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3007997</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/googles-alphaevolve-the-ai-agent-that-reclaimed-0-7-of-googles-compute-and-how-to-copy-it/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-17T00:31:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google's AlphaEvolve is the epitome of a best-practice AI agent orchestration. It offers a lesson in production-grade agent engineering. Discover its architecture & essential takeaways for your enterprise AI strategy.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matt Marshall</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Shrink exploit windows, slash MTTP: Why ring deployment is now a must for enterprise defense]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3007233</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/security/slash-mttp-block-exploits-ring-deployment-now-essential/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-16T20:48:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ring deployment slashes MTTP and legacy CVE risk. Learn how Ivanti and Southstar Bank are modernizing patch strategy with real-time intel.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Louis Columbus</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Extend Power Apps with Reusable Components]]></title>
        <id>682779afad5694b25984f6b1</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/powerapps-component-crash-course/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-16T17:45:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you have experience in traditional software development, low-code tools may feel a bit sparse at first. But to many people’s surprise, traditional techniques often translate quite well to low-code development. Not always one-for-one – but usually ...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brandon Wozniewicz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Write Math Equations in Google Docs]]></title>
        <id>68275cf15ed8a1db0cf8769b</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/write-math-equations-in-google-docs/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-16T15:42:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Math equations are a critical part of academic papers, research reports, and technical documentation. While LaTeX is widely used for professional typesetting, Google Docs offers a robust set of features for inserting and formatting math equations and...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Vikram Aruchamy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OpenAI launches research preview of Codex AI software engineering agent for developers — with parallel tasking]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3007915</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/programming-development/openai-launches-research-preview-of-codex-ai-software-engineering-agent-for-developers-with-parallel-tasking/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-16T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Starting today it will be available as a research preview for ChatGPT Pro, Enterprise, and Team users, with support later for Plus and Edu.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carl Franzen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Acer unveils AI-powered wearables at Computex 2025]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3007872</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/games/acer-unveils-ai-powered-wearables-at-computex-2025/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-16T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Acer Gadget, a subsidiary of Acer, unveiled AI-powered wearables at the Computex 2025 trade show in Taiwan.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dean Takahashi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to make Developer Friends When You Don't Live in Silicon Valley, with Iraqi Engineer Code;Life [Podcast #172]]]></title>
        <id>68271ae2c90fa4a071c44a2b</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-make-developer-friends-when-you-dont-live-in-silicon-valley-with-iraqi-engineer-codelife-podcast-172/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-16T11:00:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On this week's episode of the podcast, freeCodeCamp founder Quincy Larson interviews software engineer and live coding streamer Code;Life.   For those of you watching the video version of this interview, she lives in Iraq and she uses a 3D avatar to ...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elon Musk’s xAI tries to explain Grok’s South African race relations freakout the other day]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3007876</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/elon-musks-xai-tries-to-explain-groks-south-african-race-relations-freakout-the-other-day/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-16T02:47:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With its prompts now public and a team of human babysitters on call, Grok is supposedly back on script. But the incident underscores...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carl Franzen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn A1 Level Spanish]]></title>
        <id>68269a8eb0cc91a6c87a682d</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-a1-level-spanish/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-16T01:53:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learning a new language can open doors to new cultures, connections, and opportunities, and Spanish is one of the most widely spoken languages in the world. Whether you're dreaming of traveling to Spanish-speaking countries, connecting with Spanish-s...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Software engineering-native AI models have arrived: What Windsurf’s SWE-1 means for technical decision-makers]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3007851</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/software-engineering-native-ai-models-have-arrived-what-windsurfs-swe-1-means-for-technical-decision-makers/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-16T00:30:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Windsurf's new SWE-1 AI models tackle the complete software engineering workflow, potentially reducing development cycles and technical debt.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sean Michael Kerner</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is Sui: A Comprehensive Guide to Web3 Scalability]]></title>
        <id>6823533984101f00013a5ca4</id>
        <link href="https://blog.quicknode.com/what-is-sui-a-comprehensive-guide-to-web3-scalability/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-15T23:34:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Explore how Sui Network achieves 300,000 TPS through parallel processing, and its applications in gaming, DeFi, and supply chain management.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>QuickNode</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AI Meets Blockchain: Transforming Technology for the Next Era]]></title>
        <id>682354c584101f00013a5cb9</id>
        <link href="https://blog.quicknode.com/ai-and-blockchain-transforming-technology-together/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-15T23:34:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discover how AI and blockchain integration enhances security, efficiency, and innovation in healthcare, supply chains, and financial services.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>QuickNode</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Reduce model integration costs while scaling AI: LangChain’s open ecosystem delivers where closed vendors can’t]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3007838</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/reduce-model-integration-costs-while-scaling-ai-langchains-open-ecosystem-delivers-where-closed-vendors-cant/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-15T23:16:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Through the LangGraph Platform, organizations can deploy agents with one-click deployment, horizontal scaling to handle “bursty, long-running traffic."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Emilia David</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Adventure Layer: AI Native Onchain Games, Unleashed]]></title>
        <id>6824c55abf73460001094973</id>
        <link href="https://blog.quicknode.com/adventure-layer-launches-on-quicknode-raas/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-15T12:04:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Adventure Layer launches layer-2 chain leveraging QuickNode's Rollup-as-a-Service (RaaS) product.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>QuickNode</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How DNS Works: A Guide to Understanding the Internet's Address Book]]></title>
        <id>6824f1ac04a60b4a58654ddc</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-dns-works-the-internets-address-book/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-14T19:40:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Domain Name System (DNS) translates domain names (like example.com) into IP addresses (like 192.0.2.1) so we can easily access websites. In this guide, you’ll learn how DNS resolution starts, its step-by-step process, how caching works, and the r...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dhruv Prajapati</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Load Balancing with Azure Application Gateway and Azure Load Balancer – When to Use Each One]]></title>
        <id>6824f10a7d203c180e5ea4b2</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/load-balancing-with-azure-application-gateway-and-azure-load-balancer/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-14T19:37:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You’ve probably heard someone mention load balancing when talking about cloud apps. Maybe even names like Azure Load Balancer, Azure Application Gateway, or something about Virtual Machines and Scale Sets. 😵‍💫 It all sounds important...but also a l...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Prince Onukwili</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build Slim and Fast Docker Images with Multi-Stage Builds]]></title>
        <id>6824b1638a2b26e9d2d0fe86</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-slim-fast-docker-images-with-multi-stage-builds/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-14T15:06:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Apps don’t stay simple forever. More features mean more dependencies, slower builds, and heavier Docker images. That’s where things start to hurt. Docker helps, but without the right setup, your builds can quickly get bloated. Multi-stage builds make...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniel Adeboye</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn Vite for a Better Web Development Workflow]]></title>
        <id>6824ae178a2b26e9d2d0fe4c</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-vite-for-a-better-web-development-workflow/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-14T14:52:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Speed and simplicity are at the heart of modern web development. As applications grow more complex and the demand for rapid iteration increases, developers are constantly searching for tools that minimize friction and maximize productivity. Tradition...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Web Services Work – The Unseen Engines of the Connected World]]></title>
        <id>6824ad336ea9fe84cfb4d0c4</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-web-services-work-with-examples/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-14T14:48:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Have you ever wondered how your weather app instantly knows the forecast, how you can book flights from multiple airlines on one travel site, or how logging into one service can magically log you into another? The answer often lies in a powerful, yet...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kumar Anand</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[QuickLee V2: An Improved Transparent Look into RPC Provider Latency]]></title>
        <id>680fc8e1f8ae810001969b47</id>
        <link href="https://blog.quicknode.com/quicklee-v2/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-14T13:57:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[View public and real-time dashboards to better understand latency and speed when evaluating RPC providers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>QuickNode</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Breathe lands $21M Series B to predict battery performance]]></title>
        <id>https://techcrunch.com/?p=3003769</id>
        <link href="https://techcrunch.com/2025/05/07/breathe-lands-21m-series-b-to-predict-battery-performance/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-07T12:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Breathe has developed a suite of tools that it says helps automakers and others get the most out of their batteries.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tim De Chant</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Join the 2025 Web3j Mentorships: Build the Future of Ethereum on the JVM]]></title>
        <id>6819c8dc41eeeb000183d37b</id>
        <link href="https://blog.web3labs.com/join-the-2025-web3j-mentorships-build-the-future-of-ethereum-on-the-jvm/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T08:32:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Linux Foundation’s Decentralized Trust (LFDT) mentorship program is back in 2025 with two exciting opportunities for developers passionate about Ethereum, Android, and the Java Virtual Machine (JVM). Whether you’re a seasoned blockchain developer or an Android enthusiast eager to dive into Web3, these mentorships offer]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>George Tebrean</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>