<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2025-05-22T17:43:13.914Z</id>
    <title>AngJianming RSS Feed</title>
    <updated>2025-05-22T17:43:13.914Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Feature release 0.49.0 of the GitHub Action for Checking Spelling]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/jonasbn/feature-release-0490-of-the-github-action-for-checking-spelling-p71</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/jonasbn/feature-release-0490-of-the-github-action-for-checking-spelling-p71"/>
        <updated>2025-05-22T17:36:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Got a new release shipped of the GitHub Action for doing checking of your spelling. The action.
The release contains a lot of different changes:
Support for Italian as requested by: Stefan Oderbolz (@metaodi) via issue #241, the support is both for aspell and hunspell


Docker image updated to Python 3.13.3 slim via PR #238 from Dependabot. Release notes for Python 3.13.3


pymdown-extensions  have been updated to: 10.15.0 hopefully addressing the issue outlined in issue #233 from: Micha Hobert (@Isengo1989). @facelessuser made the release of the dependency and I have included it in this release



As for the latter issue, I was unable to verify it working after the update, but it might be due to it has been a long day - perhaps fresh eyes will help. I will try to verify it later and I would love to update the documentation with some more details. But it has been shipped, so perhaps somebody else will beat me to it.
In my last release announcement for 0.48.0 I mentioned GHCR (GitHub Container Registry) and that I wanted to migrate away from DockerHub.
Next step via issue #80 is to get GitHub > packages to work and then migrate away from DockerHub.
I have made little progress on this and there is still work to be done, so DockerHub is still in the loop.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jonas Brømsø</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Step-By-Step Guide to Install Devstral: Mistral’s Open Source Coding Agent]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/nodeshiftcloud/a-step-by-step-guide-to-install-devstral-mistrals-open-source-coding-agent-3ba7</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/nodeshiftcloud/a-step-by-step-guide-to-install-devstral-mistrals-open-source-coding-agent-3ba7"/>
        <updated>2025-05-22T17:29:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you’ve ever wished your coding assistant could actually understand your messy codebase, navigate real GitHub issues, and propose working solutions, then Devstral might be the endgame for you. Developed by Mistral AI, Devstral isn’t just another code completion model. It’s an agentic LLM fine-tuned on Mistral Small 3.1, specifically for real-world software engineering tasks, outperforming every open-source model on the SWE-Bench Verified benchmark with an impressive score of 46.8%. In tasks like debugging intricate logic, identifying cross-file dependencies, or tackling real GitHub issues using agentic tools like OpenHands or SWE-Agent, Devstral thrives where others struggle. It even beats heavyweight models like DeepSeek-V3 (671B) and Qwen3-232B, and closes in on closed-source competito…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Aditi Bindal</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Working with Enums: The Power of Pattern Matching]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/sgchris/working-with-enums-the-power-of-pattern-matching-38lj</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/sgchris/working-with-enums-the-power-of-pattern-matching-38lj"/>
        <updated>2025-05-22T17:28:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Working with Enums: The Power of Pattern Matching in Rust


Rust is a language that thrives on safety, expressiveness, and performance. One of its most versatile features, enums, encapsulates these principles beautifully. Combined with pattern matching, enums unlock powerful ways to write clean, concise, and robust code. Whether you're defining shapes in geometry or modeling states in a finite state machine, enums and pattern matching are tools that Rust developers reach for time and time again.
In this blog post, we’ll explore the magic of working with enums and pattern matching in Rust. We’ll start with the basics, build up to advanced techniques like match guards and if let, and even discuss common pitfalls to avoid. By the end, you’ll walk away not only with a solid understanding but a…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gregory Chris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The focus on human-led outreach makes all the difference in building trust.]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/noahboswel79/the-focus-on-human-led-outreach-makes-all-the-difference-in-building-trust-3a4a</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/noahboswel79/the-focus-on-human-led-outreach-makes-all-the-difference-in-building-trust-3a4a"/>
        <updated>2025-05-22T17:28:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[TDZ Pro’s Hidden Growth Weapon: Why a Customized CRM and Data Mining Team Beats Automation Every Time
Marcus ・ May 15
#crm
        #sales
        #datamining
        #startup]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Noah Boswel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[INSTALL_FAILED_UPDATE_INCOMPATIBLE: Existing package com... do not match newer version; ignoring!]]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/algoorgoal/installfailedupdateincompatible-existing-package-com-do-not-match-newer-version-ignoring-l35</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/algoorgoal/installfailedupdateincompatible-existing-package-com-do-not-match-newer-version-ignoring-l35"/>
        <updated>2025-05-22T17:28:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Development Build와 Production Build의 Certificate가 달라서 빌드에 실패하는 에러이다.
usb로 local android device를 맥북에 연결하여 개발을 진행하고 있었다. expo run:android 명령을 실행할 때마다 usb로 연결된 기기에 앱이 설치되고 이를 실행해보면서 개발을 하였다.
최대한 closed testing에 참가하는 유저 수를 늘리기 위해 해당 device를 사용하여 closed testing을 진행해야하만 했다. 해당 기기에는 개발 빌드가 이미 설치되어 있었기에 중복해서 closed testing 앱을 설치할 수는 없었다. 따라서 개발 빌드를 uninstall하고 closed testing에 내놓은 앱의 버전을 플레이스토어에서 설치하였다.
그리고 다시 앱을 개발하기 위해 bun android 를 실행하였는데 다음과 같은 에러가 발생하였다.




   Error: adb: failed to install /Users/mac/study-up-frontend/android/app/build/outputs/apk/debug/app-debug.apk: Failure [INSTALL_FAILED_UPDATE_INCOMPATIBLE: Existing package com.sleppynavigators.studyup signatures do not match newer version; ignoring!]
   Error: /Users/mac/Library/Android/sdk/platform-tools/adb -s R3CTC05E0JW install -r -…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sampling Without Index]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/franckpachot/sampling-without-index-b0d</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/franckpachot/sampling-without-index-b0d"/>
        <updated>2025-05-22T17:24:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I won't create any indexes for this post yet, but I can still filter efficiently to run a query in milliseconds. However, since I haven't indexed any values, the filter will randomly sample data without offering any real value. 
Data was imported in the first post of this series.
Without indexes, scanning the whole collection would be inefficient, but I can scan a sample to get some insights about data. For example, I list and count the categories of videos from a random sample of one thousand:
db.youstats.aggregate([  
  { $sample: { size: 10000 } },  
  { $group: { _id: "$category", count: { $sum: 1 } , maxDuration: { $max: "$duration" } } },  
  {  $sort: { count: -1 } }  
]).explain('executionStats')

[
  { _id: 'Music', count: 1841, maxDuration: '99' },
  { _id: 'People', count: 1358,…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Franck Pachot</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Indexing for New Use Cases Within the MongoDB Document Model (tutorial)]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/franckpachot/indexing-for-new-use-cases-within-the-mongodb-document-model-tutorial-2hdm</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/franckpachot/indexing-for-new-use-cases-within-the-mongodb-document-model-tutorial-2hdm"/>
        <updated>2025-05-22T17:23:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When designing a schema for MongoDB, it’s crucial to understand your access patterns. The document modeling approach shows its simplicity and efficiency over the relational model when building a database for a bounded context where primary business objects and microservice access patterns are defined. Knowing which documents to manipulate allows you to determine what information to embed and what to reference by identifier. 
The question arises: does this mean that integrating a new use case with the same database is difficult? Not at all. Just as relational databases require new secondary indexes for new use cases, MongoDB provides numerous indexing options on its document model. In this series, I will demonstrate how a collection designed for OLAP reporting, specifically YouTube video st…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Franck Pachot</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[El algoritmo.]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/hpollack/el-algoritmo-23l1</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/hpollack/el-algoritmo-23l1"/>
        <updated>2025-05-22T17:22:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[No se puede negar. Todos han escuchado alguna vez, ya sea en las noticias o redes sociales, que hablan de "el algoritmo de X". Incluso aquellos con sus cadenitas, que buscan engañarlos. Si, en la era de la información, estamos dentro de lo que llamaríamos, la dictadura de los algoritmos. El gran problema es que muchos internautas, ni siquiera saben lo que es, salvo que tengas una profesión donde te toque tratar con ellos, como es mi caso. En fin, como a mi me gusta que el conocimiento sea libre, voy a tratar de explicar con peras y manzanas el concepto de algoritmo.
Vamos a partir por algo básico. Cualquier tarea que realicemos, sigue una serie de pasos, desde que la comenzamos, hasta terminarla -claro, habemos algunas que ni eso-. Dentro de esa serie, hay momentos en que tenemos que tomar…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hermann Pollack (hpollack95)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[It’s wild how something we do every day can be so powerful when done right. Great read.]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/noahboswel79/its-wild-how-something-we-do-every-day-can-be-so-powerful-when-done-right-great-read-368e</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/noahboswel79/its-wild-how-something-we-do-every-day-can-be-so-powerful-when-done-right-great-read-368e"/>
        <updated>2025-05-22T17:21:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Rethinking Email Strategy Like a Chess Game: What Developers and Tech Professionals Can Learn from TDZ Pro
Matt Johnson ・ May 22
#productivity
        #communication
        #email
        #strategy]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Noah Boswel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Creating a Virtual Machine Scale Set (VMSS) from Your Captured Image]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/adesola_kehinde/creating-a-virtual-machine-scale-set-vmss-from-your-captured-image-fcn</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/adesola_kehinde/creating-a-virtual-machine-scale-set-vmss-from-your-captured-image-fcn"/>
        <updated>2025-05-22T17:19:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the last blog, we captured a custom Windows VM image using Azure Compute Gallery. Now, we're going to use that image to create a Virtual Machine Scale Set (VMSS). This allows you to automatically scale up or down based on demand. Let's dive in.
From the Azure Portal home, search for "Azure Compute Gallery".
Open the gallery you created earlier.





Click on the image you previously captured.
It should have the type marked as Specialized (remember, we chose specialized because we didn't generalize our VM).

Why specialized?
A specialized image retains all the settings and configurations exactly as they were on your VM. This is useful for cloned environments or when you're not using Sysprep.
In the image's overview page, click "Create VMSS".
Provide a Scale Set Name.
Choose your Region.
Under Orchestration Mode, select Flexible.
💡 Why Flexible Orchestration Mode?
Flexible mode gives you more control over scaling and VM instances. It's ideal for mixed workloads or when VM identity and persistence matter.

Under the Scaling tab, enable automatic scaling.
Add a new scaling condition:



Condition Name: e.g., scale-on-demand


Instance Count: e.g., 2


Minimum: 1


Maximum: 5


Scale Out: Increase count by 1


Scale In: Decrease count by 1



Click Save.
You may notice the admin username, password, and confirm password fields appear blurred or disabled.
🧠 Why is that?
Because you're using a specialized image — the credentials are already baked into the image. Azure doesn't require you to reset or re-enter them.
Review your configuration.
Make sure tags, VM size, network, and scaling settings are correct.
Click Create to deploy the VMSS.
⏳ After a few minutes, your scale set will be up and running!
You’ve now:
Reused a custom VM image
Created a scale set
Configured scaling policies
Understood why certain options (like specialized images and flexible orchestration) matter]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Adesola Kehinde</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[budget Slider]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/preetha_vaishnavi_2b82358/budget-slider-2b4m</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/preetha_vaishnavi_2b82358/budget-slider-2b4m"/>
        <updated>2025-05-22T17:18:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Check out this Pen I made!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>preetha vaishnavi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring AI and Ollama - Building an Open-Source Chatbot]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/villanithiago/spring-ai-and-ollama-building-an-open-source-chatbot-ei5</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/villanithiago/spring-ai-and-ollama-building-an-open-source-chatbot-ei5"/>
        <updated>2025-05-22T17:17:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We´ll use the newly released Spring AI 1.0 GA version, ready for production, to build a chat application with Spring AI, Ollama, Docker and provide out of the box chat memory management.
Java 21
Spring Web
Ollama
H2 Database
JDBC Chat Memory Repository

Spring Boot Actuator
The AI engineering landscape is no longer just Python-centric. With Spring AI, Java developers can now build AI-powered applications using open-source models like Llama 3, Gemma, Deepseek-R1 and many more! 
Ollama.
In this article, you’ll learn how to:
Set up Ollama as your local LLM inference server (Docker).
Integrate it with Spring AI as a Java-based AI engineering framework.
Create a multi-user sessions with conversation history
Build a streaming chatbot using Server-Sent Events (SSE) and an easy Frontend (HTML/CSS/…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Thiago Villani</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[US lawmaker introduces anti-corruption bill ahead of Trump&#039;s dinner]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/donald-trump-crypto-corruption-bill-memecoin-dinner</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/donald-trump-crypto-corruption-bill-memecoin-dinner?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-22T17:16:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[California Representative Maxine Waters, ranking member of the US House Financial Services Committee, has announced plans to introduce legislation “to block [Donald] Trump’s memecoin and stop his crypto corruption.”
In a May 22 notice, Rep. Waters said the Stop Trading, Retention, and Unfair Market Payoffs (TRUMP) in Crypto Act of 2025 bill would be aimed at blocking the US President, Vice President, members of Congress, and their families from engaging in “crypto crime.” The US lawmaker referred to Trump and his wife, Melania, issuing personal memecoins in January, his family launching a stablecoin, USD1, through the crypto platform World Liberty Financial, and the president attempting to establish a national Bitcoin (BTC) reserve as his sons back a BTC mining venture.
“Donald Trump is preparing to dine with the top donors of his memecoin who’ve made him, and his family, richer,” said Waters, adding: 
“Trump’s crypto con is not just a scam to target investors. It’s also a dangerous backdoor for selling influence over American policies to the highest foreign bidder.”
HR 3573, Stop TRUMP in Crypto Act of 2025, introduced by Rep. Maxine Waters. Source: House Financial Services Committee Democrats
Waters’ bill was one of many actions announced to oppose the president’s dinner to reward memecoin holders. Senators Chris Murphy and Elizabeth Warren are expected to attend a press event with representatives for the consumer advocacy group Public Citizen, and two Democratic organizations will protest at the Trump National Golf Club outside Washington, DC, where the memecoin dinner will be held.
This is a developing story, and further information will be added as it becomes available.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Turner Wright</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Warning Signs Your App Authorization Is a Ticking Time Bomb]]></title>
        <id>https://www.osohq.com/post/app-authorization-warning-signs</id>
        <link href="https://www.osohq.com/post/app-authorization-warning-signs"/>
        <updated>2025-05-22T17:02:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Show HN: DockFlow – Switch between multiple macOS Dock layouts instantly]]></title>
        <id>https://dockflow.appitstudio.com/</id>
        <link href="https://dockflow.appitstudio.com/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-22T17:00:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Anthropic’s new hybrid AI model can work on tasks autonomously for hours at a time]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1117338</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/05/22/1117338/anthropics-new-hybrid-ai-model-can-work-on-tasks-autonomously-for-hours-at-a-time/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-22T16:51:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Anthropic has announced two new AI models that it claims represent a major step toward making AI agents truly useful. AI agents trained on Claude Opus 4, the company’s most powerful model to date, raise the bar for what such systems are capable of by tackling difficult tasks over extended periods of time and responding…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rhiannon Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Anthropic overtakes OpenAI: Claude Opus 4 codes seven hours nonstop, sets record SWE-Bench score and reshapes enterprise AI]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008575</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/anthropic-claude-opus-4-can-code-for-7-hours-straight-and-its-about-to-change-how-we-work-with-ai/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-22T16:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Anthropic's Claude Opus 4 outperforms OpenAI's GPT-4.1 with unprecedented seven-hour autonomous coding sessions and record-breaking 72.5% SWE-bench score, transforming AI from quick-response tool to day-long collaborator.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Nuñez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Claude 4]]></title>
        <id>https://www.anthropic.com/news/claude-4</id>
        <link href="https://www.anthropic.com/news/claude-4"/>
        <updated>2025-05-22T16:34:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mozilla to shutdown Pocket on July 8, 2025]]></title>
        <id>https://support.mozilla.org/en-US/kb/future-of-pocket</id>
        <link href="https://support.mozilla.org/en-US/kb/future-of-pocket"/>
        <updated>2025-05-22T16:30:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Major TradFi Institutions to Pursue Tokenization Efforts on Solana]]></title>
        <id>1e9f7d9e-f627-457a-8dda-a93e35c00f69</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2025/05/22/major-tradfi-institutions-to-pursue-tokenization-efforts-on-solana"/>
        <updated>2025-05-22T16:12:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tokenization is one of the principal use cases of blockchain technology attracting the attention and investment of the TradFi world]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Crawley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BTC price eyes $112K as risk assets &#039;ignore bad news&#039; on unemployment]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/btc-price-eyes-112k-risk-assets-ignore-bad-news-unemployment</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/btc-price-eyes-112k-risk-assets-ignore-bad-news-unemployment?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-22T16:07:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Key points:

Mixed results for US jobless claims fail to dent risk-asset enthusiasm.

Despite concerns over the bond market, Bitcoin and stocks enjoy stability at the start of the Wall Street trading session.

BTC price expectations remain lofty amid low volatility and a curious lack of profit-taking.

Bitcoin (BTC) focused on $111,000 around the May 22 Wall Street open as record highs met mixed US unemployment data.
BTC/USD 1-hour chart. Source: Cointelegraph/TradingView
Bitcoin, stocks brush off jobs uncertainty
Data from Cointelegraph Markets Pro and TradingView showed BTC price volatility cooling in line with stocks.
The latest US macroeconomic data painted a conflicting picture of labor market resilience to inflation trends.
Initial jobless claims came in below expectations at 227,000…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by William Suberg</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Justin Sun-Linked Wallet Leading Access to Trump Dinner Tagged as Belonging to HTX]]></title>
        <id>bca545d8-d0c9-4cfa-a211-44f6c0f97575</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2025/05/22/justin-sun-linked-wallet-leading-access-to-trump-dinner-tagged-as-belonging-to-htx"/>
        <updated>2025-05-22T16:05:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sun, a Chinese-born crypto billionaire, is also involved with the Trump-linked ecosystem through a $75 million investment in World Liberty Financial.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Francisco Rodrigues</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ice Theft in Antarctica]]></title>
        <id>https://nautil.us/ice-theft-in-antarctica-1210083/</id>
        <link href="https://nautil.us/ice-theft-in-antarctica-1210083/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-22T16:02:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin could go much higher due to lack of FOMO and futures market euphoria — Analysts]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-could-go-much-higher-due-to-lack-of-fomo-and-futures-market-euphoria-analysts</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-could-go-much-higher-due-to-lack-of-fomo-and-futures-market-euphoria-analysts?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-22T15:58:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Key takeaways:

Bitcoin’s rally to new price highs happened as funding rates and trading sentiment remained unusually subdued.

Rising stablecoin supply and global M2 growth indicate untapped liquidity and the potential for further price increases.

Long-term holders are not aggressively selling, reflecting their expectation for continued Bitcoin price appreciation.

Bitcoin (BTC) hit a new all-time high on May 21, with prices rising to $111,860 on Binance on May 22, but the markets lack the state of frenzy associated with new highs. Economist and crypto commentator Alex Krüger noted that “this is the least euphoric new all-time highs” for Bitcoin, after highlighting subdued funding rates for Bitcoin across crypto exchanges.
Bitcoin price and aggregated funding rate. Source: Coinalyze
The …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Biraajmaan Tamuly</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Carmaker DeLorean tokenizes EV reservations on Sui]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/delorean-tokenizes-ev-reservations-on-sui</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/delorean-tokenizes-ev-reservations-on-sui?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-22T15:55:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[DeLorean launched an onchain reservation system and non-fungible token (NFT) marketplace for its upcoming electric vehicle launch, introducing a new blockchain-based approach for reserving and reselling cars.
According to DeLorean, its Build Slot NFT collection grants holders priority access to purchase DeLorean’s upcoming electric car, Alpha 5 EV. The model is the carmaker’s first vehicle in over 40 years, inspired by the iconic flux capacitor from the movie Back to the Future.
The company created an exclusive marketplace for its NFT holders, in which users can buy or trade the NFTs using the USDC (USDC) stablecoin on the Sui network and will be able to earn rewards.
DeLorean says that each vehicle’s history and performance data will be recorded onchain through the FLUX protocol, includin…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Lyne Qian</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kraken To List Tokenized Version of Nvidia, Apple, Tesla Shares]]></title>
        <id>3b9fba56-daf9-4556-b83f-f6eaa28ad999</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/22/kraken-to-list-tokenized-version-of-nvidia-apple-tesla-shares"/>
        <updated>2025-05-22T15:55:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The tokens will be deployed on Solana and backed by real securities held by Kraken’s partner, Backed Finance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Helene Braun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[First U.S. XRP Futures ETF Begins Trading on Nasdaq]]></title>
        <id>0a64f011-e949-485d-b984-18f3a3d2971d</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/22/first-u-s-xrp-futures-etf-begins-trading-on-nasdaq"/>
        <updated>2025-05-22T15:53:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The fund will invest at least 80% of its assets in XRP futures contracts and shares of other XRP-linked exchange-traded products.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Helene Braun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[That fractal that's been up on my wall for 12 years]]></title>
        <id>https://chriskw.xyz/2025/05/21/Fractal/</id>
        <link href="https://chriskw.xyz/2025/05/21/Fractal/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-22T15:50:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MCP explained without hype or fluff]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.nilenso.com/blog/2025/05/12/mcp-explained-without-hype-or-fluff/</id>
        <link href="https://blog.nilenso.com/blog/2025/05/12/mcp-explained-without-hype-or-fluff/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-22T15:39:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Near-infrared spatiotemporal color vision enabled by upconversion contact lenses]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cell.com/cell/fulltext/S0092-8674(25)00454-4</id>
        <link href="https://www.cell.com/cell/fulltext/S0092-8674(25)00454-4"/>
        <updated>2025-05-22T15:30:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Time Magazine appears to accidentally publish embargoed story confirming new Anthropic model]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008649</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/time-magazine-appears-to-accidentally-publish-embargoed-story-confirming-anthropic-claude-4-opus/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-22T15:26:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Someone also appears to have published a full scrape of the Time article online on the news aggregator app Newsbreak.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carl Franzen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Launch HN: WorkDone (YC X25) – AI Audit of Medical Charts]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=44063000</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=44063000"/>
        <updated>2025-05-22T15:23:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Show HN: Whenish – Plan Group Events in iMessages]]></title>
        <id>https://apps.apple.com/us/app/whenish/id6745035749</id>
        <link href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/whenish/id6745035749"/>
        <updated>2025-05-22T15:15:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto for Advisors: When Crypto Meets Netflix]]></title>
        <id>7f516d56-430a-487d-90aa-11357443c3c4</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/coindesk-indices/2025/05/21/crypto-for-advisors-when-crypto-meets-netflix"/>
        <updated>2025-05-22T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How Black Mirror’s on-chain experiment is paving the way for the future of entertainment monetization.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shivani Phull</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Semiconductor exemptions don’t matter when it comes to tariffs]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/semiconductor-exemptions-don-t-matter</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/semiconductor-exemptions-don-t-matter?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-22T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Opinion by: Ahmad Shadid of O.xyz
Semiconductors scored a rare exemption from US President Donald Trump’s aggressive reciprocal tariffs, but the relief is symbolic at best. Most semiconductors enter the US embedded in servers, GPUs, laptops, and smartphones. 
The finished goods remain heavily tariffed, some with duties reaching up to 49%. The exemption looks good politically but delivers little practical benefit. Nvidia’s DGX systems, crucial for training advanced AI models, do not fall under the exempted HTS codes. Nvidia could pay effective tariffs nearing 40% on these vital components. Such costs threaten to stall critical AI infrastructure projects across the country. 
Semiconductor tariffs may compromise the goal of the CHIPS Act. The act promised tens of billions of dollars in subsid…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Ahmad Shadid</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[U.S. Spy Agencies–One-Stop Shop to Buy Your Personal Data]]></title>
        <id>https://theintercept.com/2025/05/22/intel-agencies-buying-data-portal-privacy/</id>
        <link href="https://theintercept.com/2025/05/22/intel-agencies-buying-data-portal-privacy/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-22T14:43:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Global Dollar's USDG Eyes Hundreds of Partners Attracted by Yield, Sees 'Big Names' From TradFi]]></title>
        <id>e068c52f-e6b5-46e8-922b-4e6fa9097240</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2025/05/22/stablecoin-consortium-usdg-will-see-thousands-of-firms-joining-says-kraken"/>
        <updated>2025-05-22T14:11:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Banks and large TradFi firms are preparing to join the Global Dollar network alongside firms like Robinhood, Galaxy and Anchorage, founding member Kraken said.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ian Allison</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[I Built My Own Audio Player]]></title>
        <id>https://nexo.sh/posts/why-i-built-a-native-mp3-player-in-swiftui/</id>
        <link href="https://nexo.sh/posts/why-i-built-a-native-mp3-player-in-swiftui/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-22T14:09:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Here’s what happened in crypto today]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/what-happened-in-crypto-today</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/what-happened-in-crypto-today?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-22T14:03:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today in crypto, Sui-based decentralized exchange (DEX) Cetus is suspected to have been  exploited, with onchain data showing rapid asset drainage despite the team claiming the incident is a “bug.” Bitcoin has topped $110,000 for the first time and continues to climb, and the Texas House passed a Bitcoin reserve bill.
Sui DEX Cetus hit by suspected hack: Over $200 million in potential losses
Cetus, a decentralized exchange (DEX) built on the Sui blockchain, is suspected to have been hit by a massive exploit that may have drained more than $200 million worth of digital assets.
Pseudonymous Web3 researcher COMDARE3 posted on X that “users report” that Sui-based DEX Cetus is being exploited.” They also shared a screenshot of Cetus market data on DEX Screener, showing many assets losing well o…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Cointelegraph</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fast Allocations in Ruby 3.5]]></title>
        <id>https://railsatscale.com/2025-05-21-fast-allocations-in-ruby-3-5/</id>
        <link href="https://railsatscale.com/2025-05-21-fast-allocations-in-ruby-3-5/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-22T14:01:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trump-Backed World Liberty Financial Buys BUILDon Token, Sending the Price Up 1,340%]]></title>
        <id>e2071d8e-6d14-4cba-a7c9-fcba8dd0ab18</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2025/05/22/trump-backed-crypto-project-buys-buildon-token-sending-prices-up-1-340"/>
        <updated>2025-05-22T14:00:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The token had a market cap of just $40 million before the purchase.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Oliver Knight</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Adventures in Symbolic Algebra with Model Context Protocol]]></title>
        <id>https://www.stephendiehl.com/posts/computer_algebra_mcp/</id>
        <link href="https://www.stephendiehl.com/posts/computer_algebra_mcp/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-22T13:59:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Which senators invest in crypto? 11 lawmakers have blockchain-related investments]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/senators-invest-crypto-blockchain-related-investments</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/senators-invest-crypto-blockchain-related-investments?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-22T13:54:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As the question of stablecoin regulation heats up in the US Senate, so has the issue of which members are personally invested in cryptocurrencies and cryptocurrency firms. 
On May 19, the Senate voted to invoke cloture and move ahead with the GENIUS Act, which would provide a regulatory framework for stablecoins. The measure passed 66-32, with 16 Democrats supporting the bill.
Democratic concerns over corruption and politicians’ ties to cryptocurrency firms made the bipartisan move controversial. After the vote was finished, Colorado Senator Michael Bennet introduced the STABLE GENIUS Act. The bill would prevent members of Congress from issuing or investing in digital currency and require them to put their crypto in a blind trust while in office.
Bills to prevent members of Congress from i…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Aaron Wood</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Texas Moves Closer to Setting Up Strategic Bitcoin Reserve as Bill Passes House]]></title>
        <id>dde56905-9e4c-4e9a-b312-d3e487c7dc24</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2025/05/22/texas-moves-closer-to-setting-up-strategic-bitcoin-reserve-as-bill-passes-house"/>
        <updated>2025-05-22T13:39:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The House voted in favor of Senate Bill 121 which would establish a "Texas Strategic Bitcoin Reserve for the purpose of investing in cryptocurrency"]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Crawley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Exponential currency debasement: ‘You don’t own enough crypto, NFTs’]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/currency-debasement-own-enough-crypto-nfts</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/currency-debasement-own-enough-crypto-nfts?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-22T13:39:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cryptocurrencies and non-fungible tokens (NFTs) can help investors protect their eroding purchasing power during an era of exponential currency debasement, according to analysts and industry leaders.
Investing in digital assets is becoming increasingly important in the “world of the exponential age and currency debasement,” according to Raoul Pal, founder and CEO of Global Macro Investor.
“You don’t own enough crypto. When you do, you don’t own enough NFT’s, as art is upstream of wealth. Both will never be this cheap again,” Pal said.
NFTs are “the single best long term store of wealth I know and you get to buy it before network effects kick in,” he added in another response.
Source: Raoul Pal
“There is some validity to the statement that NFTs, and in extension art, become a vehicle for th…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Zoltan Vardai</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CoinDesk 20 Performance Update: Index Gains 4.5% with All Assets Trading Higher]]></title>
        <id>aaca5697-10bc-4e9d-b21d-caacf85b7e33</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/coindesk-indices/2025/05/22/coindesk-20-performance-update-index-gains-45-with-all-assets-trading-higher"/>
        <updated>2025-05-22T13:36:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Avalanche (AVAX) Surged 11.2% while NEAR Protocol (NEAR) jumped 7.9%, leading the index higher.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CoinDesk Indices</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How staking incentivizes trust without burning energy]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/how-staking-incentivizes-trust-without-burning-energy</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/how-staking-incentivizes-trust-without-burning-energy?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-22T13:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What if a financial system could run itself not by burning electricity, but by rewarding good behavior? That’s the promise of staking, a mechanism that powers many modern blockchains by turning users into network operators. 
In this week’s episode of The Clear Crypto Podcast, hosts Gareth Jenkinson and Nathan Jeffay sit down with StarkWare’s Noam Nisan to unpack how this trustless engine works, why it matters and what’s really at stake.

Understanding staking
Jeffay began by highlighting how staking is part of the backbone that keeps the blockchain running, and runs itself, with volunteers.
“By doing this, they’re saying, OK, we’re taking this task of running the blockchain seriously. Here's some of our money. We're putting it down. We're showing that we're serious about doing this.”
To he…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Savannah Fortis</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[There Is A Porsche Malaysia Showcase At Bangsar Shopping Centre Happening Until 25 May]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=353408</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/353408/there-is-a-porsche-malaysia-showcase-at-bangsar-shopping-centre-happening-until-25-may/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-22T13:27:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Owning a Porsche has been a dream for many. Well, that dream can become a reality through Porsche Malaysia’s showcase at Bangsar Shopping Centre from 21 May to 25 May 2025. The showcase features a curated selection of pre-owned models approved by the automaker itself that you can buy. According to the company, these models […]
The post There Is A Porsche Malaysia Showcase At Bangsar Shopping Centre Happening Until 25 May appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Keran</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Show HN: SQLite JavaScript - extend your database with JavaScript]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/sqliteai/sqlite-js</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/sqliteai/sqlite-js"/>
        <updated>2025-05-22T13:25:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[These 4 memecoins can outperform Bitcoin this cycle]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/these-4-memecoins-can-outperform-bitcoin-this-cycle</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/these-4-memecoins-can-outperform-bitcoin-this-cycle?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-22T13:19:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Key takeaways:

Memecoins like Fartcoin, WIF, SPX6900, and Popcat are outperforming Bitcoin in the short term amid renewed crypto market euphoria.

Bullish technical patterns signal more upside for top-performing memecoins.

Popcat stands out with a potential 350% rally, while Fartcoin and WIF also eye significant gains in the coming weeks.

Bitcoin (BTC) has surged 7.35% over the past three days, hitting a new all-time high near $112,000 on May 22, but memecoins are stealing the spotlight. 
Fueled by BTC’s rally, several high-risk tokens are posting even larger gains, stoking possibilities that they could continue to outperform Bitcoin as the crypto bull run accelerates.
Fartcoin ascending channel hints at more gains
Solana-based Fartcoin (FARTCOIN) memecoin has surged 30% in the last thr…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Yashu Gola</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Proton Introduces Integrated Tyre Services In Collaboration With Continental Malaysia]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=353341</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/353341/proton-introduces-integrated-tyre-services-in-collaboration-with-continental-malaysia/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-22T13:12:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[National automaker Proton has partnered with Continental Malaysia to introduce integrated tyre services at its selected authorised  service centres across the country for all its models. With this initiative, customers can conveniently purchase and install tyres during their regular service appointments. The automaker stated that the prices start at RM211 per unit for the Proton […]
The post Proton Introduces Integrated Tyre Services In Collaboration With Continental Malaysia appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Keran</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Philosophy of Byung-Chul Han (2020)]]></title>
        <id>https://newintrigue.com/2020/06/29/the-philosophy-of-byung-chul-han/</id>
        <link href="https://newintrigue.com/2020/06/29/the-philosophy-of-byung-chul-han/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-22T13:09:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What You Didn’t Know About Laszlo Hanyecz, the Bitcoin Pizza Day Legend]]></title>
        <id>28e94138-acbd-43b0-98c5-c2d5c0806857</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/tech/2025/05/22/what-you-didnt-know-about-laszlo-hanyecz-the-bitcoin-pizza-day-legend"/>
        <updated>2025-05-22T13:06:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When Laszlo Hanyecz purchased two large Papa John’s pizzas with 10,000 BTC on May 22, 2010, he became a legend. But how much do you really know about the man behind Bitcoin Pizza Day?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Colin Harper, Blockspace Media</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Project Roxom Global Raises $17.9M to Build BTC Treasury, Create Media Network]]></title>
        <id>37051a57-792a-41a8-b141-b91362c60f5b</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2025/05/22/roxom-global-raises-179m-to-build-btc-treasury-back-247-media-network"/>
        <updated>2025-05-22T13:00:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[RoxomTV is being built as a media network backed by a 100% bitcoin treasury and currently holds 84.72 BTC]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Crawley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Free-Threaded Python Library Compatibility Checker]]></title>
        <id>https://ft-checker.com/</id>
        <link href="https://ft-checker.com/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-22T12:57:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[U.S. Stablecoin Bill Approval Could Trigger a Long-Term Crypto Bull Market: Bitwise]]></title>
        <id>f3d27af1-e50b-422a-ae80-55962691b564</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/22/us-stablecoin-bill-approval-could-trigger-a-long-term-crypto-bull-market-bitwise"/>
        <updated>2025-05-22T12:55:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The passage of a U.S. stablecoin bill could be one of the most important regulatory developments in the history of crypto, the report said.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Will Canny</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[XRP futures OI rises 25% as price chart ‘bull flag’ targets $14]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/xrp-open-futures-open-interest-25-price-chart-bull-flag-14</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/xrp-open-futures-open-interest-25-price-chart-bull-flag-14?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-22T12:50:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Key takeaways:

XRP price has gained 4% over the last 24 hours to $2.43, and its open interest has risen by 25%.

Positive spot market activity flips the futures funding rate positive, suggesting a return of investor optimism.

XRP could rally to $14 if a classic bull flag pattern is confirmed.

XRP printed a “bull flag” triangle on the weekly chart, a technical pattern associated with strong upward momentum. Breaking above this technical setup and a surge in XRP futures demand could signal a rally to $14.
Increasing OI rising with XRP price
XRP (XRP) rose in tandem with the wider crypto market on May 22, fueled by Bitcoin’s rally to fresh all-time highs above $111,000. 
XRP price followed with as much as 5.5% gains to an intraday high of $2.45 on May 22 from a low of $2.33 on May 21. 
Its…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Nancy Lubale</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Binance scores legal win as UK court partially dismisses Bitcoin SV lawsuit]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/uk-court-bitcoin-sv-lawsuit-binance-dismissal</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/uk-court-bitcoin-sv-lawsuit-binance-dismissal?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-22T12:38:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The United Kingdom’s Court of Appeal partially dismissed a lawsuit brought by Bitcoin SV investors against major crypto exchanges, including Binance, for allegedly conspiring to delist the token in 2019.
In a judgment handed down on May 21, the court ruled that investors who held BSV through the delisting period (classified as “sub-class B”) were not entitled to billions in speculative damages based on BSV’s hypothetical growth.
These investors had claimed over 8.9 billion British pounds ($11.9 billion) in damages, asserting that Binance’s delisting deprived holders of the chance to profit from BSV’s potential rise to a “top-tier cryptocurrency” like Bitcoin (BTC) or Bitcoin Cash (BCH).
The court rejected this “foregone growth effect” theory, stating, “BSV was obviously not a unique crypto…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Amin Haqshanas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Strategy Plans $2.1B Sale of Its Perpetual Strife Preferred Stock]]></title>
        <id>89ebea90-364a-433a-8330-e4540056cd89</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/22/strategy-plans-21b-sale-of-its-perpetual-strife-preferred-stock"/>
        <updated>2025-05-22T12:37:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Proceeds to support corporate initiatives including bitcoin acquisitions and working capital.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>James Van Straten</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Enchant launches zero-equity accelerator for gaming and AI startups]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008571</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/games/enchant-launches-zero-equity-accelerator-for-gaming-and-ai-startups/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-22T12:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Enchant is launching a new zero-equity accelerator for gaming and AI startups, with applications now open for its three-month program.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dean Takahashi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sui DEX Cetus hit by suspected hack: Over $200M in potential losses]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/cetus-dex-sui-exploit-200m-loss</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/cetus-dex-sui-exploit-200m-loss?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-22T12:10:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Update (May 22, 2025, 1:27 pm UTC): This article has been updated to add further data and statements by Hacken.
Cetus, a decentralized exchange (DEX) built on the Sui blockchain, is suspected to have been hit by a massive exploit that may have drained more than $200 million worth of digital assets.  
Pseudonymous Web3 researcher COMDARE3 posted on X that “users report” that Sui-based DEX Cetus is being exploited.” They also shared a screenshot of Cetus market data on DEX Screener, showing many assets losing well over half of their value over the last 24 hours. 
The team behind Extractor, an onchain monitoring tool developed by crypto cybersecurity company Hacken, confirmed that “at least $63m was already bridged to Ethereum, 20k ETH was just transferred to a fresh wallet” in a single trans…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Adrian Zmudzinski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Download: the desert data center boom, and how to measure Earth’s elevations]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1117300</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/05/22/1117300/the-download-the-desert-data-center-boom-and-how-to-measure-earths-elevations/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-22T12:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is today’s edition of The Download, our weekday newsletter that provides a daily dose of what’s going on in the world of technology. The data center boom in the desert In the high desert east of Reno, Nevada, construction crews are flattening the golden foothills of the Virginia Range, laying the foundations of a data center…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rhiannon Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Improving performance of rav1d video decoder]]></title>
        <id>https://ohadravid.github.io/posts/2025-05-rav1d-faster/</id>
        <link href="https://ohadravid.github.io/posts/2025-05-rav1d-faster/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-22T11:59:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sui's Biggest Liquidity Provider Hacked for $223M, Causing Sui-Based Tokens to Plummet]]></title>
        <id>32730c6a-9f4c-4852-a38b-c3184ae2079d</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/22/sui-networks-cetus-protocol-hit-in-apparent-hack-sending-token-prices-down-90"/>
        <updated>2025-05-22T11:54:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cetus is Sui’s biggest liquidity provider and decentralized exchange.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shaurya Malwa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Whale buys back ETH holdings after losing $2.67M by selling early]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/crypto-trader-mistimed-eth-sale-loses-2-6m</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/crypto-trader-mistimed-eth-sale-loses-2-6m?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-22T11:48:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A crypto trader spent $3.8 million to buy Ether at a significantly higher price after selling the asset for almost the same amount about a month ago. 
On May 22, blockchain analytics firm Lookonchain reported that a crypto wallet spent $3.8 million to purchase 1,425 Ether (ETH) at $2,670 per coin, reentering ETH after a major rally. 
On April 13, the same wallet sold 2,522 ETH for $3.9 million, when the asset was trading at about $1,570, a decision that, in retrospect, looks poorly timed. 
“Think twice before selling your bags,” Lookonchain wrote, highlighting the potential gains if the trader just held on to their Ether instead of selling and repurchasing it at a higher price point. 
Whale buys ETH after selling over a month ago. Source: DeBank
Trader loses out on $2.67 million gain
With …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Ezra Reguerra</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Are Bitcoin Traders Aggressively Shorting as BTC Hits New Record High?]]></title>
        <id>a641ed4a-06c2-4968-9065-f371462385a4</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/22/why-are-bitcoin-traders-aggressively-shorting-as-btc-hits-new-record-high"/>
        <updated>2025-05-22T11:39:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The move comes as the long/short ratio is at its lowest point since September 2022.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Oliver Knight</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto awareness in Singapore hits record 94%, but ownership falls]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/singapore-crypto-awareness-2024-survey</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/singapore-crypto-awareness-2024-survey?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-22T11:21:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto awareness in Singapore has reached an all-time high, with 94% of respondents in a recent survey indicating familiarity with at least one digital asset.
However, ownership declined, falling to 29% in 2025 from 40% the previous year, according to Independent Reserve’s fifth annual Singapore Crypto Market Survey released on May 21.
The survey, conducted in February with 1,500 participants, revealed that men remain more active in crypto investing than women, 35% compared to 24%.
Millennials and Gen X (aged 25–54) dominate the investor base, comprising 71% of all holders. Among those trading at least once a week, 76% fall into this age group.
Related: Singapore’s Grab taps Solana DePIN project Natix to ‘reshape mapping’
Half of Singaporean investors plan to increase holdings
Despite the …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Amin Haqshanas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Daybook Americas: All Signs Point Up as Bitcoin Hits Record High]]></title>
        <id>f836eb74-1934-4a4e-ab31-3c706aedfd77</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/daybook-us/2025/05/22/crypto-daybook-americas-all-signs-point-up-as-bitcoin-hits-record-high"/>
        <updated>2025-05-22T11:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Your day-ahead look for May 22, 2025]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Francisco Rodrigues</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MARA Will Deploy 500 BTC With Crypto Broker Two Prime to Generate Yields]]></title>
        <id>30ae2f1a-02ee-44d1-aecd-ca02d08715b7</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2025/05/22/mara-to-deploy-500-btc-with-two-prime-for-generating-yields"/>
        <updated>2025-05-22T11:00:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The partnership builds on Two Prime's existing role in providing bitcoin-backed loans to MARA.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Parikshit Mishra</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Show HN: Curved Space Shader in Three.js (via 4D sphere projection)]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/bntre/CurvedSpaceShader</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/bntre/CurvedSpaceShader"/>
        <updated>2025-05-22T10:52:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FIFA taps Avalanche to launch dedicated blockchain for NFT platform]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/fifa-avalanche-l1-nft-marketplace</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/fifa-avalanche-l1-nft-marketplace?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-22T10:52:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Federation Internationale de Football Association (FIFA) has selected Avalanche to power its dedicated blockchain network for non-fungible tokens and digital fan engagement, the organization announced on May 22.
FIFA’s layer-1 (L1) blockchain will be powered by the Avalanche network’s scalability-focused infrastructure for the association’s five billion fans worldwide.
The move comes nearly a month after FIFA announced its initial plans to launch a new network for its blockchain-based collectibles. AvaCloud’s Ethereum Virtual Machine (EVM) compatibility will enable smoother integration with decentralized wallets and applications.
Related: Bitcoin hits new all-time high of $109K as trade war tensions ease
The move will enable FIFA to deliver “unique digital collectibles and immersive fa…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Zoltan Vardai</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Huawei Watch Fit 4 Series, Watch 5 Land In Malaysia; Priced From RM599]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=353414</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/353414/huawei-watch-fit-4-series-watch-5-malaysia-rm599/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-22T10:48:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Huawei has officially launched its new lineup of wearables in Malaysia, which includes the Watch Fit 4 series as well as the Watch 5. The Watch Fit 4 series comprises the Watch Fit 4 and the Watch Fit 4 Pro, while the Watch 5 comes in 46mm and 42mm sizes. To start off, the Watch […]
The post Huawei Watch Fit 4 Series, Watch 5 Land In Malaysia; Priced From RM599 appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nurul Kamil</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin tops Amazon market cap on ‘Pizza Day’ as price sets new highs]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-tops-amazon-market-cap-on-bitcoin-pizza-day</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-tops-amazon-market-cap-on-bitcoin-pizza-day?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-22T10:43:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Update (May 22, 2025, 2:05 pm UTC): This article has been updated to add statements by Shruti Kohli and Stan Low.
The market cap of the world’s first cryptocurrency, Bitcoin, surpassed that of retail and tech behemoth Amazon on “Bitcoin Pizza Day.”
Market data shows that Bitcoin (BTC) had a market cap of $2.205 trillion at the time of writing, $70 billion more than the $2.135 trillion Amazon valuation.
“By surpassing Amazon in terms of capitalization, Bitcoin has attracted even more attention from the non-crypto audience,” said Alex Obchakevich, founder of Obchakevich Research. 
Obchakevich said the latest rally “will strengthen confidence in Bitcoin and lead to new injections into the crypto market.” The surge came as Bitcoin set a new all-time high and traded above $110,000, which Obchav…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Adrian Zmudzinski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HONOR Pad 10, MagicBook 14 Also Get Unveiling]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=353421</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/353421/honor-pad-10-magicbook-14-also-get-unveiling/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-22T10:37:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Alongside the HONOR 400 series of phones, the brand also unveiled a tablet and a laptop, called the Pad 10 and MagicBook 14, respectively. The former is less of a surprise as we’ve seen it appearing in the SIRIM database, while the latter is probably due for a refresh. Starting with the tablet, the HONOR […]
The post HONOR Pad 10, MagicBook 14 Also Get Unveiling appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ian Chee</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why is the crypto market up today?]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/why-is-the-crypto-market-up-today</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/why-is-the-crypto-market-up-today?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-22T10:27:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Key points:

The crypto market is up 2.5% on May 22, with its capitalization above $3.48 trillion for the first time since February.

Bitcoin’s new all-time high of $111,888 is boosting investor confidence across the crypto market.

The cryptocurrency market is up today, with the total market capitalization rising by approximately 2.5% in the last 24 hours to reach $3.48 trillion on May 22. The total 24-hour trading volume across all crypto assets has also increased by 55% to $193.2 billion, reinforcing the intensity of the demand-side activity.
Crypto market performance May 22. Source: Coin360
Let’s look at the factors driving crypto prices up today.
Crypto prices buoyed by Bitcoin’s new all-time highs
Today’s gains were led by Bitcoin (BTC), which broke through $111,000 for the first tim…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Nancy Lubale</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Can ChatGPT-powered AI agents really trade crypto for you?]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/can-chatgpt-powered-ai-agents-really-trade-crypto-for-you</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/can-chatgpt-powered-ai-agents-really-trade-crypto-for-you?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-22T10:21:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Key takeaways

ChatGPT-powered AI agents automate trading tasks using natural language prompts and API integrations, improving speed and consistency.

Successes occur when ChatGPT is used as a support tool, not a fully autonomous trading system.

Failures happen when traders over-rely on ChatGPT without real-time data, proper risk management or manual oversight.

Regulatory focus on AI in trading is increasing, with new frameworks emerging to ensure transparency, accountability and compliance.

What if a crypto trader didn’t need to constantly check charts, worry about emotions, or stay up all night watching for sudden price swings? What if those tasks could be handled by an intelligent agent that understands instructions in plain English — and reacts within milliseconds? That’s where Chat…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Callum Reid</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Strengths and limitations of diffusion language models]]></title>
        <id>https://www.seangoedecke.com/limitations-of-text-diffusion-models/</id>
        <link href="https://www.seangoedecke.com/limitations-of-text-diffusion-models/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-22T10:10:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto travelers bring 3x greater lifetime value than fiat users]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/crypto-travelers-3x-greater-value-fiat-users</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/crypto-travelers-3x-greater-value-fiat-users?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-22T10:02:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Travelers using cryptocurrency for booking arrangements spend more than twice as much as regular travelers using fiat money, according to a joint report from Binance Pay and crypto travel platform Travala shared with Cointelegraph.
Crypto-based bookings on Travala reached $80 million in 2024, up from $45 million the year before. Crypto travelers are also outspending their fiat counterparts, with an average booking value of  $1,211 per transaction, over 2.5 times more than fiat users who spend $469.
Additionally, the report said crypto users were three times more valuable over their lifetime due to longer stays and higher repeat bookings, with crypto travelers 57% more likely to make a repeat hotel purchase.
Source: Binance Pay, Travala
Juan Otero, CEO of Travala, attributed these travel pr…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Lyne Qian</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FIFA Teams Up With Avalanche to Build Its Own Blockchain, Expanding Web3 Ambition]]></title>
        <id>fc4b5d80-9798-4ca0-b8f4-cba37e61ba18</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/tech/2025/05/22/fifa-teams-up-with-avalanche-to-build-its-own-blockchain-expanding-web3-ambition"/>
        <updated>2025-05-22T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[FIFA previously released a non-fungible token (NFT) collection on the Algorand blockchain in 2022 ahead of the Qatar World Cup.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Margaux Nijkerk</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HONOR 400 Series Now Official In Malaysia; Starts From RM1,899]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=353308</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/353308/honor-400-series-official-malaysia-from-rm1899/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-22T09:51:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Following the teaser by the brand earlier in the month, the HONOR 400 series has now been officially launched in Malaysia. The launch confirms a number of leaks regarding the phones’ specs from earlier, as well as disproving a few of the others, but we’ll get to that in a bit. Starting with the base […]
The post HONOR 400 Series Now Official In Malaysia; Starts From RM1,899 appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ian Chee</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Planetfall]]></title>
        <id>https://somethingaboutmaps.wordpress.com/2025/05/20/planetfall/</id>
        <link href="https://somethingaboutmaps.wordpress.com/2025/05/20/planetfall/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-22T09:17:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trump’s crypto czar David Sacks says stablecoin bill is ‘going to pass’]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/david-sacks-stablecoin-bill-senate-passage</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/david-sacks-stablecoin-bill-senate-passage?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-22T09:06:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[David Sacks, US President Donald Trump’s top adviser on crypto and artificial intelligence, said the administration expects the stablecoin bill to clear the Senate with bipartisan backing.
“We have every expectation now that it’s going to pass,” Sacks told CNBC on May 21, following a key procedural vote that saw 15 Democrats join Republicans to clear the filibuster threshold.
The Guiding and Establishing National Innovation for US Stablecoins (GENIUS) Act is the most advanced federal effort yet to establish a legal framework for dollar-pegged digital assets.
Sacks said the bill could trigger “trillions of dollars” in demand for US Treasurys by unlocking stablecoin growth under clear rules.
“We already have over $200 billion in stablecoins — it’s just unregulated,” he added. “If we provide …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Amin Haqshanas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BNB Surges 5% on Binance Ecosystem Strength as Bitcoin Extends Gains]]></title>
        <id>3f7e1b8d-e59f-43f0-841b-ffaa0bdc647f</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/22/bnb-surges-5-on-binance-ecosystem-strength-as-bitcoin-extends-gains"/>
        <updated>2025-05-22T09:03:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BNB surges with strong support at $682 as Binance ecosystem activity spikes and Bitcoin’s continued rally lifts market sentiment across majors.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>AI Boost</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Three takeaways about AI’s energy use and climate impacts]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1117277</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/05/22/1117277/ai-energy-three-takeaways/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-22T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This week, we published Power Hungry, a package all about AI and energy. At the center of this package is the most comprehensive look yet at AI’s growing power demand, if I do say so myself.  This data-heavy story is the result of over six months of reporting by me and my colleague James O’Donnell…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Casey Crownhart</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A new atomic clock in space could help us measure elevations on Earth]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1117294</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/05/22/1117294/a-new-atomic-clock-in-space-could-help-us-measure-elevations-on-earth/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-22T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In 2003, engineers from Germany and Switzerland began building a bridge across the Rhine River simultaneously from both sides. Months into construction, they found that the two sides did not meet. The German side hovered 54 centimeters above the Swiss side. The misalignment occurred because the German engineers had measured elevation with a historic level…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sophia Chen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dubai regulator clarifies real-world asset tokenization rules: Lawyer]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/dubai-vara-guidelines-rwa-tokenization-clarity</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/dubai-vara-guidelines-rwa-tokenization-clarity?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-22T08:37:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Newly updated guidelines from Dubai’s crypto regulator include provisions on real-world asset (RWA) tokenization and clarify rules for issuers. 
On May 19, Dubai’s Virtual Asset Regulatory Authority (VARA) released its updated Rulebook for virtual asset service providers (VASPs) operating in the region. The regulator gave market participants until June 19 to comply with the new rules. 
The regulator previously told Cointelegraph that it had enhanced supervisory mechanisms and brought consistency across activity-based rules. One of the more prominent changes includes regulatory clarity on RWA tokens. 
Irina Heaver, partner at the United Arab Emirates-based law firm NeosLegal, told Cointelegraph that the updated rules clarify RWA issuance and distribution. 
“Issuing real-world asset tokens a…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Ezra Reguerra</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin &#039;looks exhausted&#039; as next bear market yields $69K target]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-looks-exhausted-next-bear-market-yields-69k-target</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-looks-exhausted-next-bear-market-yields-69k-target?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-22T08:35:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Key points: 

Bitcoin all-time highs matter little to those seeing a BTC price correction as long overdue.

Both the latest surge and the bull market itself are on borrowed time, traders say.

Comparisons to previous price cycles remain in use despite the booming institutional investment scene.

Bitcoin (BTC) traders are calling for a pullback after all-time highs and seven “green” weekly candles.
BTC price momentum continues to be met with skepticism as commentators assume that lower levels will come next.
BTC price roadmap prepares for Q4 “cycle peak”
Bitcoin hit its highest-ever levels this week, data from Cointelegraph Markets Pro and TradingView confirmed — but despite being up by a third in Q2 already, BTC/USD remains unconvincing for many.
Long-term analysis suggests that not only i…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by William Suberg</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[5 red flags you’re being shilled: Don’t buy the hype]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/explained/5-red-flags-youre-being-shilled-dont-buy-the-hype</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/explained/5-red-flags-youre-being-shilled-dont-buy-the-hype?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-22T08:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What is shilling in crypto?            
            
                
At its core, shilling is the act of artificially promoting a cryptocurrency or token, often with exaggerated claims, to increase its price or popularity. 
But what’s the goal? 
Hype it up, get others to buy in, and then cash out, leaving latecomers holding the bag.
Shilling can come from anyone: influencers, anonymous accounts or even high-profile figures with political or financial clout. The common thread is manipulation: It’s not about educating you or building real value but pumping hype for personal gain.
Unfortunately, the line between enthusiastic promotion and outright deception can be thin, and many fall victim without realizing it. That’s why it’s critical to learn how to spot the signs early.
                 …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by SK Arora</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Trader Opens $1.1B Long Bitcoin Bet on Hyperliquid Using 40X Leverage]]></title>
        <id>ef6bda8d-7381-4ab8-82d7-521b16603cb6</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/22/crypto-trader-opens-11b-long-bitcoin-bet-on-hyperliquid-using-40x-leverage"/>
        <updated>2025-05-22T08:09:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The trade marks a new phase of capital migration from centralized finance to DeFi — one where whales, not just retail, are willing to place big bets outside the traditional system.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shaurya Malwa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[King Dollar Falls, Bitcoin Marches Toward Sound Money Highs]]></title>
        <id>ea37a4ad-ece4-4fe0-b5ed-d67387bfb13f</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/22/king-dollar-falls-bitcoin-marches-toward-sound-money-highs"/>
        <updated>2025-05-22T08:06:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Despite soaring 50% from April lows and outperforming tech and bonds, bitcoin has yet to reclaim its all-time highs against traditional safe havens like gold and silver.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>James Van Straten</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Pizza Day Is Now a $1.1B Celebration]]></title>
        <id>d5084e63-5f5d-451b-ac51-3285b6a4c970</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/22/bitcoin-pizza-day-is-now-a-11b-celebration"/>
        <updated>2025-05-22T07:16:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An order for two pizzas was paid with 10,000 BTC fifteen years ago. Today, that same order is worth over $1.1 billion — just as BTC just hit fresh record highs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shaurya Malwa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase hacker trolls ZachXBT onchain after $42.5M THORChain swap]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/coinbase-hacker-trolls-zachxbt-moves-millions-through-thorchain</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/coinbase-hacker-trolls-zachxbt-moves-millions-through-thorchain?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-22T07:12:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The hacker behind the data breach targeting Coinbase users mocked blockchain investigator ZachXBT with an onchain message following a major crypto swap.
On May 21, the hacker used Ethereum transaction input data to write “L bozo,” followed by a meme video of NBA player James Worthy smoking a cigar.
The message came after the attacker swapped about $42.5 million from Bitcoin (BTC) to Ether (ETH) via THORChain. 
ZachXBT flagged the message on his Telegram channel, linking it to the same entity responsible for the Coinbase data breach affecting at least 69,400 users.
Coinbase hacker trolling ZachXBT. Source: ZachXBT.
On May 22, blockchain security firm PeckShield reported that the hacker had continued to move funds, swapping 8,697 ETH for 22 million Dai (DAI). A separate but closely linked ad…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Amin Haqshanas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bolt Introduces Flight Tracking For Airport Pickups]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=353259</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/353259/bolt-flight-tracking-airport/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-22T07:02:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bolt has announced a new feature for airport pickups called Flight Tracking, which aims to make your travels from the airport more seamless. The feature adds to the e-hailing app’s ride-scheduling option and lets users sync their flight details with their scheduled ride. According to Afzan Lutfi, general manager of Bolt Malaysia, the platform is […]
The post Bolt Introduces Flight Tracking For Airport Pickups appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ikmal Rozlan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Options Open Interest Hit Record $42.5B on Deribit as Traders Eye Next Bull Target for BTC]]></title>
        <id>c2650ad6-1b71-40d3-b578-f247a9bc5ed2</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/22/bitcoin-options-open-interest-hit-record-425b-on-deribit-as-traders-eye-next-bull-target-for-btc"/>
        <updated>2025-05-22T06:38:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Highest OI now sits at the $110K, $120K, and $300K June 27 strikes — showing bullish conviction]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Omkar Godbole</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft takes legal action against infostealer Lumma]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/microsoft-legal-action-against-infostealer-lumma</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/microsoft-legal-action-against-infostealer-lumma?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-22T06:18:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tech giant Microsoft says it has taken legal action against the information-stealing malware Lumma Stealer and has blocked thousands of websites related to the software.
Microsoft said in a May 21 blog post that a federal court in Georgia allowed the firm’s digital crimes unit to take down, block or suspend nearly 2,300 websites critical to Lumma’s operations, and it has collaborated with local and international law enforcement agencies to dismantle the project’s infrastructure.
The company said the US Department of Justice seized Lumma’s central command structure and disrupted marketplaces where the tool was sold to other cybercriminals. 
Microsoft says that Lumma has been sold via underground forums since 2022 and that it has undergone multiple upgrades since its launch.
Domains seized b…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Tarang Khaitan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Photo Essay: Bow-Inspired Memory By Klevv At Computex 2025]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=352717</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/352717/photo-essay-bow-inspired-memory-by-klevv-at-computex-2025/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-22T06:14:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Klevv was one of the other booths we visited during Computex 2025. Located at Hall 1 of the Nangang Exhibition Centre too, the memory maker had a number of memory products to show off, plus some interesting setups. Among the list of memory products it was eager to show off, the Urbane V RGB sat […]
The post Photo Essay: Bow-Inspired Memory By Klevv At Computex 2025 appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John Law</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pakistan creates Digital Asset Authority to regulate crypto]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/pakistan-digital-asset-authority-regulate-crypto</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/pakistan-digital-asset-authority-regulate-crypto?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-22T06:12:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Pakistan’s Ministry of Finance has reportedly endorsed the creation of a dedicated body to regulate blockchain-based financial infrastructure in the country.
The Pakistan Digital Assets Authority (PDAA) will serve as a regulatory body to oversee licensing, regulate exchanges, custodians, wallets, tokenized platforms, stablecoins and decentralized finance applications, according to a May 21 report from the state-owned broadcaster, PTV.
Muhammad Aurangzeb, federal minister for finance and revenue, told the broadcaster, “Pakistan must regulate not just to catch up, but to lead” in the industry.
“With the PDAA, we are creating a future-ready framework that protects consumers, invites global investment, and puts Pakistan at the forefront of financial innovation,” he said.
Muhammad Aurangzeb, Pa…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Stephen Katte</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Photo Essay: Of Casings and Coolers From TRYX At Computex 2025]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=352812</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/352812/photo-essay-of-casings-and-coolers-from-tryx-at-computex-2025/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-22T06:03:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[TRYX isn’t a name that many of you would be familiar with, and that’s alright. First founded back in 2023 by a former employee at Cooler Master, the brand is trying to make a name for itself in both the desktop casing and CPU cooling markets. To be fair, the brand had initially come under […]
The post Photo Essay: Of Casings and Coolers From TRYX At Computex 2025 appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John Law</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin's Rally to Record Highs Puts Focus on $115K Where an 'Invisible Hand' May Slow Bull Run]]></title>
        <id>9bb3cafe-100c-442b-badb-ee8c7163c86b</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/22/bitcoin-s-rally-to-record-highs-puts-focus-on-usd115k-where-an-invisible-hand-may-slow-bull-run"/>
        <updated>2025-05-22T05:59:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As BTC looks north, an invisible hand may work to slow the ascent above $115K]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Omkar Godbole</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Photo Essay: Getting To Know Biwin at Computex 2025]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=352855</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/352855/photo-essay-getting-to-know-biwin-at-computex-2025/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-22T05:56:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Biwin isn’t a name you’d be familiar with, but it’s been around for 20 odd years. In that time, the brand has had its fingers in the pies of every popular tech brand that we know of. Typically, Biwin operates behind the scenes, and the interesting thing about that is: it’s by design. Bob Snyder, […]
The post Photo Essay: Getting To Know Biwin at Computex 2025 appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John Law</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Feds charge Amalgam founder with stealing $1M via ‘sham’ blockchain]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/feds-charge-amalgam-founder-stealing-one-million-sham-blockchain</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/feds-charge-amalgam-founder-stealing-one-million-sham-blockchain?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-22T05:51:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A US grand jury has indicted the founder of blockchain startup Amalgam Capital Ventures over allegations he defrauded investors out of over $1 million with a fake blockchain.
Jeremy Jordan-Jones was arrested and indicted on May 21 and charged with wire fraud, securities fraud, making false statements to a bank, and aggravated identity theft, the Department of Justice said on May 21.  
Manhattan US Attorney Jay Clayton claimed Jordan-Jones “touted his company as a groundbreaking blockchain startup,” but alleged that, in reality, the “company was a sham, and investors’ funds were siphoned off to bankroll his lavish lifestyle.”
FBI Assistant Director Christopher Raia alleged that Jordan-Jones defrauded investors of more than 1 million dollars through “misrepresentations of his purported compa…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Martin Young</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nissan Unveils All-Electric Sixth-Generation Micra]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=352978</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/352978/nissan-unveils-all-electric-sixth-generation-micra/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-22T05:44:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nissan has officially unveiled the sixth-generation Micra, now reimagined as a fully electric vehicle (EV). Set to make its full debut in the European market later this year, the shift to EV marks a significant shift for the long-standing B-segment staple. Built on the AmpR Small platform — formerly known as the CMF-B EV — […]
The post Nissan Unveils All-Electric Sixth-Generation Micra appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Keran</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SHIB Holds Strong Above Key Support as Volume Spikes Nearly 4x]]></title>
        <id>ea602bee-c37e-40f8-a349-d386c8d4c713</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/22/shib-holds-strong-above-key-support-as-volume-spikes-nearly-4x"/>
        <updated>2025-05-22T05:30:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SHIB rebounds from sharp drop with a 4x surge in trading volume, holding firm above $0.000015. Analysts see signs of strong accumulation despite volatility.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>AI Boost</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hyperliquid sees $1.1B Bitcoin long bet opened at 40x leverage]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/hyperliquid-first-ever-1-billion-bitcoin-bet-40x-leverage</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/hyperliquid-first-ever-1-billion-bitcoin-bet-40x-leverage?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-22T05:08:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A crypto whale has expanded an existing 40x leverage long Bitcoin bet to $1.1 billion on the decentralized exchange Hyperliquid, which has stunned the crypto community and is believed to be the first-ever position exceeding $1 billion on the platform.
The X account “James Wynn” claims to be behind the position, which is now up $36 million on the trade, data from Hypurrscan’s block explorer shows.
A $28.4 million margin position was used across several trades to increase the Bitcoin (BTC) position, now worth $1.13 billion. The average Bitcoin entry price was $108,065.
Perp futures positions of wallet address “0x507.” Source: Hypurrscan
“He did it fellas,” crypto analyst Sigma^2 wrote on X. “First position [on Hyperliquid] to exceed $1B.”
Wynn’s long position was at a loss of about $16.3 mil…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Brayden Lindrea</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BlackRock’s Bitcoin ETF notches 2-week high inflow as BTC nears $112K]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/blackrock-bitcoin-etf-biggest-inflow-two-weeks-as-bitcoin-nears-11200</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/blackrock-bitcoin-etf-biggest-inflow-two-weeks-as-bitcoin-nears-11200?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-22T04:56:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BlackRock’s iShares Bitcoin Trust (IBIT) has seen its largest inflow in the past two weeks as traders allocate to US spot Bitcoin exchange-traded funds (ETFs) to scoop up the rocketing cryptocurrency.
IBIT’s May 21 net inflows hit $530.6 million, its biggest single-day net inflow since it took in $531.2 million on May 5, according to Farside Investors. The ETF hasn’t had an outflow since April 9.
In one day alone, IBIT has accumulated over 10 times the amount of Bitcoin (BTC) mined over the same timeframe, with it scooping up 4,931 BTC against just 450 BTC produced for the day.
IBIT also saw its largest volume day since January, according to the ETF tracking X account Trader T. 
“Given trading volume today, expect these inflow numbers to increase,” said ETF Store president Nate Geraci. 
Bl…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Martin Young</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The scientific “unit” we call the decibel]]></title>
        <id>https://lcamtuf.substack.com/p/decibels-are-ridiculous</id>
        <link href="https://lcamtuf.substack.com/p/decibels-are-ridiculous"/>
        <updated>2025-05-22T04:24:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gemini Diffusion]]></title>
        <id>https://simonwillison.net/2025/May/21/gemini-diffusion/</id>
        <link href="https://simonwillison.net/2025/May/21/gemini-diffusion/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-22T01:13:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Display any CSV file as a searchable, filterable, pretty HTML table]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/derekeder/csv-to-html-table</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/derekeder/csv-to-html-table"/>
        <updated>2025-05-22T00:31:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[At Google I/O, Sergey Brin makes surprise appearance — and declares Google will build the first AGI]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008490</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/at-google-i-o-sergey-brin-makes-surprise-appearance-and-declares-google-will-build-the-first-agi/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-21T22:20:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google co-founder Sergey Brin makes surprise appearance at Google I/O, declaring "Gemini will be the very first AGI," revealing philosophical tensions with DeepMind CEO Hassabis who urges scientific caution in the high-stakes AI race.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Nuñez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Master Database Management Systems]]></title>
        <id>682e3c04117e792e5f46edc3</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/master-database-management-systems/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-21T20:48:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Understanding how to manage data effectively is a critical skill for anyone pursuing a career in tech. And we just published a course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will teach you all about Database Management Systems (DBMS). This in-de...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Roundtables: A New Look at AI’s Energy Use]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1117287</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/05/21/1117287/roundtables-a-new-look-at-ais-energy-use-2/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-21T19:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Recorded on May 21, 2025 Big Tech’s appetite for energy is growing rapidly as adoption of AI accelerates. But just how much energy does even a single AI query use? And what does it mean for the climate? Hear from MIT Technology Review editor in chief Mat Honan, senior climate reporter Casey Crownhart, and AI reporter James…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>MIT Technology Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Refactor Complex Codebases – A Practical Guide for Devs]]></title>
        <id>682df5a0f2057ab279952dbe</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-refactor-complex-codebases/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-21T15:47:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Developers often see refactoring as a secondary concern that they can delay indefinitely because it doesn’t immediately contribute to revenue or feature development. And managers frequently view refactoring as "not a business need" until it boils ove...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ankur Tyagi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Will “Vibe Coders” Take Our Dev Jobs?]]></title>
        <id>682df55da72360814bcae9ef</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/will-vibe-coders-take-our-dev-jobs/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-21T15:46:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AI is disrupting all industries at a pace not seen at any time in history. Technologies and industries that were once dominated by one or two companies or were very much “human-focused” are coming under threat. Google is losing ground to AI search, t...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ben</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OpenAI updates its new Responses API rapidly with MCP support, GPT-4o native image gen, and more enterprise features]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008465</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/programming-development/openai-updates-its-new-responses-api-rapidly-with-mcp-support-gpt-4o-native-image-gen-and-more-enterprise-features/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-21T15:30:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Support for remote Model Context Protocol servers, integration of image generation and Code Interpreter tools, and upgrades to file search...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carl Franzen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How JavaScript Lint Rules Work (and Why Abstract Syntax Trees Matter)]]></title>
        <id>682def7ddd9c9fdc3dae95cf</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-javascript-lint-rules-work-and-why-abstract-syntax-trees-matter/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-21T15:21:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Before I started to contribute to eslint-plugin-react, I didn’t think too deeply about the linters I used every day while writing code. Like many developers, I installed them at the start of a project, appreciated the red underlines or auto-fixes, an...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tilda Udufo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mistral AI launches Devstral, powerful new open source SWE agent model that runs on laptops]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008458</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/mistral-ai-launches-devstral-powerful-new-open-source-swe-agent-model-that-runs-on-laptops/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-21T14:57:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Beyond performance and portability, its Apache 2.0 license offers a compelling proposition for commercial applications.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carl Franzen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Download: Google’s AI mission, and America’s reliance on natural gas]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1117249</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/05/21/1117249/the-download-googles-ai-mission-and-americas-reliance-on-natural-gas/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-21T12:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is today’s edition of The Download, our weekday newsletter that provides a daily dose of what’s going on in the world of technology. By putting AI into everything, Google wants to make it invisible If you want to know where AI is headed, this year’s Google I/O has you covered. The company’s annual showcase of next-gen…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rhiannon Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[By putting AI into everything, Google wants to make it invisible]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1117251</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/05/21/1117251/by-putting-ai-into-everything-google-wants-to-make-it-invisible/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-21T11:49:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you want to know where AI is headed, this year’s Google I/O has you covered. The company’s annual showcase of next-gen products, which kicked off yesterday, has all of the pomp and pizzazz, the sizzle reels and celebrity walk-ons, that you’d expect from a multimillion-dollar marketing event. But it also shows us just how…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Will Douglas Heaven</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A South Korean grand master on the art of the perfect soy sauce]]></title>
        <id>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2025/may/21/without-time-there-is-no-flavour-a-south-korean-grand-master-on-the-art-of-the-perfect-soy-sauce</id>
        <link href="https://www.theguardian.com/world/2025/may/21/without-time-there-is-no-flavour-a-south-korean-grand-master-on-the-art-of-the-perfect-soy-sauce"/>
        <updated>2025-05-21T11:19:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AMD unveils new Threadripper CPUs and Radeon GPUs for gamers at Computex 2025]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008206</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/games/amd-unveils-new-threadripper-cpus-and-radeon-gpus-for-gamers-at-computex-2025/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-21T03:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AMD held a Computex press event to introduce its Radeon RX 9060 XT graphics cards and Threadripper CPUs for next-gen gaming and workstations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dean Takahashi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google finally launches NotebookLM mobile app at I/O: hands-on, first impressions]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008400</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/google-finally-launches-notebooklm-mobile-app-at-i-o-hands-on-first-impressions/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T19:29:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As NotebookLM matures, its emerging business-tier capabilities suggest growing alignment with the productivity and compliance...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carl Franzen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google just leapfrogged every competitor with mind-blowing AI that can think deeper, shop smarter, and create videos with dialogue]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008346</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/google-just-leapfrogged-every-competitor-with-mind-blowing-ai-that-can-think-deeper-shop-smarter-and-create-videos-with-dialogue/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T17:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google unveiled major AI advancements at I/O 2025, including Gemini 2.5 with Deep Think, AI Mode in Search, Veo 3 for video with audio, and a $249 Ultra plan aimed at power users and enterprises.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Nuñez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google’s Jules aims to out-code Codex in battle for the AI developer stack]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008361</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/googles-jules-aims-to-out-code-codex-in-battle-for-the-ai-developer-stack/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T17:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google released Jules, its coding agent, into beta as autonomous coding agents are quickly gaining market share.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Emilia David</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Inside Google’s AI leap: Gemini 2.5 thinks deeper, speaks smarter and codes faster]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008366</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/inside-google-ai-leap-gemini-2-5-thinks-deeper-speaks-smarter-codes-faster/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T17:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google is moving closer to its goal of autonomous agentic AI with a series of enhancements to Gemini 2.5 Pro and Flash.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Taryn Plumb</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blazing-fast Solana data via gRPC: access the freshest Solana data from Shredstream leaders]]></title>
        <id>68273f14bf73460001094b35</id>
        <link href="https://blog.quicknode.com/yellowstone-grpc/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T15:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Access the fastest Solana data with the Yellowstone Geyser gRPC self-serve add-on or with the premium hybrid dedicated gRPC node.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>QuickNode</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn LangGraph and Build Conversational AI with Python]]></title>
        <id>682ca2c574938e5428551845</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-langgraph-and-build-conversational-ai-with-python/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T15:41:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you're building conversational AI and tired of messy logic or hard-to-scale workflows, LangGraph makes it easier. It uses graphs to manage dialogue flow, so your bots stay organized even as they get more complex. Great for anything from support ag...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Download: introducing the AI energy package]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1117051</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/05/20/1117051/the-download-introducing-the-ai-energy-package/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T12:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is today’s edition of The Download, our weekday newsletter that provides a daily dose of what’s going on in the world of technology. We did the math on AI’s energy footprint. Here’s the story you haven’t heard. It’s well documented that AI is a power-hungry technology. But there has been far less reporting on the extent…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rhiannon Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AI could keep us dependent on natural gas for decades to come]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1116272</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/05/20/1116272/ai-natural-gas-data-centers-energy-power-plants/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The thousands of sprawling acres in rural northeast Louisiana had gone unwanted for nearly two decades. Louisiana authorities bought the land in Richland Parish in 2006 to promote economic development in one of the poorest regions in the state. For years, they marketed the former agricultural fields as the Franklin Farm mega site, first to…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Rotman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AI’s energy impact is still small—but how we handle it is huge]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1116274</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/05/20/1116274/opinion-ai-energy-use-data-centers-electricity/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With seemingly no limit to the demand for artificial intelligence, everyone in the energy, AI, and climate fields is justifiably worried. Will there be enough clean electricity to power AI and enough water to cool the data centers that support this technology? These are important questions with serious implications for communities, the economy, and the…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Costa Samaras, Emma Strubell, Ramayya Krishnan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft just launched an AI that discovered a new chemical in 200 hours instead of years]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008310</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/microsoft-just-launched-an-ai-that-discovered-a-new-chemical-in-200-hours-instead-of-years/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T18:34:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft launches Discovery platform that uses agentic AI to compress years of scientific research into days, transforming R&D across pharmaceuticals, materials science, and semiconductor industries.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Nuñez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Is your AI app pissing off users or going off-script? Raindrop emerges with AI-native observability platform to monitor performance]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008299</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/is-your-ai-app-pissing-off-users-or-going-off-script-raindrop-emerges-with-ai-native-observability-platform-to-monitor-performance/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T18:09:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With its rebrand and product expansion, Raindrop is betting that the next generation of software observability will be AI-first by design.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carl Franzen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft just taught its AI agents to talk to each other—and it could transform how we work]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008254</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/microsoft-just-taught-its-ai-agents-to-talk-to-each-other-and-it-could-transform-how-we-work/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T16:01:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft unveils multi-agent systems, WhatsApp integration, and Python-powered analytics for Copilot Studio at Build 2025, transforming how enterprises build and deploy AI solutions.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Nuñez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Microsoft Fabric has already been adopted by 70% of the Fortune 500 — and what’s next]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3007980</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/70-of-the-fortune-500-already-use-microsoft-fabric-and-its-now-getting-even-more-features-including-cosmosdb-support/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft integrates CosmosDB into Fabric, open sources DiskANN vector search, and unifies its data platforms to eliminate integration complexity that has slowed enterprise AI adoption.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sean Michael Kerner</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub Copilot evolves into autonomous agent with asynchronous code testing]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008231</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/github-copilot-evolves-into-autonomous-agent-with-asynchronous-code-testing/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub adds agentic capabilities to its Copilot coding assistant, competing with other more asynchronous coding platforms.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Emilia David</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft announces over 50 AI tools to build the ‘agentic web’ at Build 2025]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008229</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/microsoft-announces-over-50-ai-tools-to-build-the-agentic-web-at-build-2025/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T15:59:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft reveals its ambitious AI agent strategy, showcasing how multi-agent systems with persistent memory will transform enterprise workflows and accelerate development timelines.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Nuñez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Reddit, Webflow, and Superhuman are already customers—now GrowthX has $12M to grow]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008276</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/reddit-webflow-and-superhuman-are-already-customers-now-growthx-has-12m-to-grow/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[GrowthX secures $12M in funding for its "service-as-software" platform that combines AI with human expertise to boost content marketing results by up to 300%.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Nuñez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Cybercriminals Crack Your Passwords (And How to Stay One Step Ahead)]]></title>
        <id>682b3930e99a22ce9f9199c8</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-cybercriminals-crack-your-passwords-and-how-to-stay-one-step-ahead/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T13:59:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Passwords are the keys to your digital life  –  email, bank accounts, social media, and even your workplace systems. Unfortunately, they’re also one of the weakest links in cybersecurity.  Every year, billions of credentials are stolen and sold on th...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Manish Shivanandhan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Quantum Machines launches Qualibrate open source framework to speed quantum computer calibration]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008032</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/games/quantum-machines-launches-qualibrate-open-source-framework-to-speed-quantum-computer-calibration/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Quantum Machines, a provider of advanced hybrid quantum-classical control solutions, announced today the release of Qualibrate.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dean Takahashi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Samsung boosts OLED TV gaming with Nvidia G-Sync compatibility]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008019</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/games/samsung-boosts-oled-tv-gaming-with-nvidia-g-sync-compatibility/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Samsung said its 2025 OLED TV lineup will feature Nvidia G-Sync compatibility, delivering smooth gameplay, low latency, and more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dean Takahashi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Salesforce just unveiled AI ‘digital teammates’ in Slack — and they’re coming for Microsoft Copilot]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008273</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/salesforce-just-unveiled-ai-digital-teammates-in-slack-and-theyre-coming-for-microsoft-copilot/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Salesforce launches Agentforce in Slack, transforming workplace productivity with specialized AI agents that operate as digital teammates, replacing one-size-fits-all AI assistants with purpose-built solutions.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Nuñez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Traditional and Neural Order-Independent Transparency]]></title>
        <id>https://www.tobias-franke.eu/publications/tsopouridis25tnoit/index.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.tobias-franke.eu/publications/tsopouridis25tnoit/index.html"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T08:41:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Foxconn builds AI factory in partnership with Taiwan and Nvidia]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008261</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/games/foxconn-builds-ai-factory-in-partnership-with-taiwan-and-nvidia/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T07:14:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nvidia and Foxconn announced they are working with the Taiwan government to build an AI factory supercomputer.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dean Takahashi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nvidia launches AI-first DGX Personal Computing Systems]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008256</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/games/nvidia-launches-ai-first-dgx-personal-computing-systems/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T07:06:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nvidia announced that Taiwan’s leading system manufacturers are set to build Nvidia DGX Spark and DGX Station systems.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dean Takahashi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nvidia-powered supercomputer to enable quantum leap for Taiwan’s research]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008257</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/games/nvidia-powered-supercomputer-to-enable-quantum-leap-for-taiwans-research/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T06:58:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nvidia is powering a supercomputer at Taiwan’s National Center for High-Performance Computing that’s set to deliver over eight times more AI performance than before.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dean Takahashi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nvidia powers world’s largest quantum research supercomputer]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008248</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/games/nvidia-powers-worlds-largest-quantum-research-supercomputer/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T06:48:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nvidia announced the opening of the Global Research and Development Center for Business by Quantum-AI Technology.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dean Takahashi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nvidia provides Omniverse Blueprint for AI factory digital twins]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008243</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/games/nvidia-provides-omniverse-blueprint-for-ai-factory-digital-twins/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T06:34:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nvidia today announced a significant expansion of the Nvidia Omniverse Blueprint for AI factory digital twins, now available as a preview.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dean Takahashi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nvidia charges ahead with humanoid robotics aided by the cloud]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008144</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/games/nvidia-charges-ahead-with-humanoid-robotics-aided-by-the-cloud/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T06:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nvidia said it is racing ahead with humanoid robotics technology, providing more Blackwell systems to accelerate humanoid robot development.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dean Takahashi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Everything’s a bug (or an issue)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bozemanpass.com/everythings-a-bug-or-an-issue/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bozemanpass.com/everythings-a-bug-or-an-issue/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T03:46:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Four years of sight reading practice]]></title>
        <id>https://sandrock.co.za/carl/2025/05/four-years-of-sight-reading-pracice/</id>
        <link href="https://sandrock.co.za/carl/2025/05/four-years-of-sight-reading-pracice/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T03:44:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Benchmarking Crimes Meet Formal Verification]]></title>
        <id>https://microkerneldude.org/2025/04/27/benchmarking-crimes-meet-formal-verification/</id>
        <link href="https://microkerneldude.org/2025/04/27/benchmarking-crimes-meet-formal-verification/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T00:04:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[From dot-com to dot-AI: How we can learn from the last tech transformation (and avoid making the same mistakes)]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3007969</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/from-dot-com-to-dot-ai-how-we-can-learn-from-the-last-tech-transformation-and-avoid-making-the-same-mistakes/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-18T19:05:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The AI winners won’t be the ones slapping “AI” on a landing page — they’ll be creating products enterprises can't live without.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kailiang Fu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Inigo Quilez: computer graphics, mathematics, shaders, fractals, demoscene]]></title>
        <id>https://iquilezles.org/articles/</id>
        <link href="https://iquilezles.org/articles/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-18T09:32:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Extend Power Apps with Reusable Components]]></title>
        <id>682779afad5694b25984f6b1</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/powerapps-component-crash-course/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-16T17:45:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you have experience in traditional software development, low-code tools may feel a bit sparse at first. But to many people’s surprise, traditional techniques often translate quite well to low-code development. Not always one-for-one – but usually ...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brandon Wozniewicz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Write Math Equations in Google Docs]]></title>
        <id>68275cf15ed8a1db0cf8769b</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/write-math-equations-in-google-docs/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-16T15:42:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Math equations are a critical part of academic papers, research reports, and technical documentation. While LaTeX is widely used for professional typesetting, Google Docs offers a robust set of features for inserting and formatting math equations and...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Vikram Aruchamy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to make Developer Friends When You Don't Live in Silicon Valley, with Iraqi Engineer Code;Life [Podcast #172]]]></title>
        <id>68271ae2c90fa4a071c44a2b</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-make-developer-friends-when-you-dont-live-in-silicon-valley-with-iraqi-engineer-codelife-podcast-172/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-16T11:00:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On this week's episode of the podcast, freeCodeCamp founder Quincy Larson interviews software engineer and live coding streamer Code;Life.   For those of you watching the video version of this interview, she lives in Iraq and she uses a 3D avatar to ...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn A1 Level Spanish]]></title>
        <id>68269a8eb0cc91a6c87a682d</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-a1-level-spanish/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-16T01:53:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learning a new language can open doors to new cultures, connections, and opportunities, and Spanish is one of the most widely spoken languages in the world. Whether you're dreaming of traveling to Spanish-speaking countries, connecting with Spanish-s...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is Sui: A Comprehensive Guide to Web3 Scalability]]></title>
        <id>6823533984101f00013a5ca4</id>
        <link href="https://blog.quicknode.com/what-is-sui-a-comprehensive-guide-to-web3-scalability/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-15T23:34:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Explore how Sui Network achieves 300,000 TPS through parallel processing, and its applications in gaming, DeFi, and supply chain management.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>QuickNode</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AI Meets Blockchain: Transforming Technology for the Next Era]]></title>
        <id>682354c584101f00013a5cb9</id>
        <link href="https://blog.quicknode.com/ai-and-blockchain-transforming-technology-together/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-15T23:34:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discover how AI and blockchain integration enhances security, efficiency, and innovation in healthcare, supply chains, and financial services.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>QuickNode</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Adventure Layer: AI Native Onchain Games, Unleashed]]></title>
        <id>6824c55abf73460001094973</id>
        <link href="https://blog.quicknode.com/adventure-layer-launches-on-quicknode-raas/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-15T12:04:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Adventure Layer launches layer-2 chain leveraging QuickNode's Rollup-as-a-Service (RaaS) product.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>QuickNode</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[QuickLee V2: An Improved Transparent Look into RPC Provider Latency]]></title>
        <id>680fc8e1f8ae810001969b47</id>
        <link href="https://blog.quicknode.com/quicklee-v2/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-14T13:57:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[View public and real-time dashboards to better understand latency and speed when evaluating RPC providers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>QuickNode</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>