<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2025-06-02T23:43:51.190Z</id>
    <title>AngJianming RSS Feed</title>
    <updated>2025-06-02T23:43:51.190Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Robinhood completes $200M acquisition of crypto exchange Bitstamp]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/robinhood-200-million-acquisition-bitstamp</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/robinhood-200-million-acquisition-bitstamp?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-06-02T23:31:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Robinhood has acquired the world’s longest-running crypto exchange, Bitstamp, for $200 million, expanding its institutional crypto offerings to Europe, the UK and Asia.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Brayden Lindrea</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto broker FalconX acquires majority stake in Monarq — Report]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/crypto-broker-falconx-acquires-majority-stake-in-monarq-report</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/crypto-broker-falconx-acquires-majority-stake-in-monarq-report?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-06-02T23:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[FalconX has made other moves in 2025, acquiring derivatives startup Arbelos Markets and partnering with Standard Chartered.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Christopher Tepedino</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sonhar em trabalhar por conta própria não é nada fácil.]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/otavio99/sonhar-em-trabalhar-por-conta-propria-nao-e-nada-facil-4ap8</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/otavio99/sonhar-em-trabalhar-por-conta-propria-nao-e-nada-facil-4ap8"/>
        <updated>2025-06-02T23:18:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sonhar em trabalhar por conta própria não é nada fácil.
Pois estamos sempre sentindo:
Ansiedade de não saber por onde começar.
Sobrecarga de informações.
Estresse de tentar dar conta de tudo.
Algo que já me ajudou algumas vezes foi imaginar que 80% dos resultados que busco virão de apenas 20% dos meus esforços.
Ao eliminar o que não é essencial, você permite que o que realmente importa receba mais atenção.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>otavio99</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Containerization ve Orchestration: Modernleştirin, Optimize Edin]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/yunus_emremert_1756b71d3/containerization-ve-orchestration-modernlestirin-optimize-edin-28p7</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/yunus_emremert_1756b71d3/containerization-ve-orchestration-modernlestirin-optimize-edin-28p7"/>
        <updated>2025-06-02T23:12:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Yazılım geliştirme dünyası, özellikle ölçeklenebilirlik ve esneklik söz konusu olduğunda sürekli olarak yeni teknolojileri benimsemeye ve adapte olmaya yöneliktir. Containerization ve orchestration, uygulamalarımızı dağıtma ve yönetme biçimimizi önemli ölçüde değiştiren iki önemli trend. Containerization, uygulamalarımızı ve hizmetlerimizi daha taşınabilir, daha yalıtılmış ve daha verimli hale getirerek mikro hizmet mimarisi trendini destekler. Orchestration ise bu kapsayıcıları yönetme ve ölçeklendirme işini kolaylaştırır, böylece dinamik ve esnek bir altyapı elde ederiz.
Geleneksel sanallaştırma teknolojileri, uygulamalar arasında kaynak paylaşımı ve yalıtımı konusunda bazı zorluklar sunmaktaydı. Containerization, bu zorlukları ele alarak aynı işletim sistemi çekirdeğini paylaşan hafif v…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yunus Emre Mert</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Embed User Preferences]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/gabrieldeavila/how-to-embed-user-preferences-4lhk</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/gabrieldeavila/how-to-embed-user-preferences-4lhk"/>
        <updated>2025-06-02T23:12:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An embedding isn’t just useful for search — it’s also a powerful way to represent user preferences.
Think about how a feed works, like on YouTube. How do you recommend content to someone who loves funny cat videos versus someone who’s into programming tutorials?

Each video usually has tags, right? We can convert those tags into embeddings — mathematical representations of the video’s content.
Once everything is represented as embeddings, we can calculate similarity scores between the user's interests and available content.
But here’s the catch: if a user interacts with multiple videos, how do we combine those interests into a single preference embedding?
The answer: use a decay technique.
This means that recent interactions weigh more, while older ones slowly lose influence over time.
The code is as simple as it sounds.
First, you’ll need a column to store the user’s preference embedding — basically, a vector that represents their tastes.
Now, let’s talk about the decay factor. I usually keep it between 0.1 and 0.25, meaning that we preserve 90% to 75% of the current preferences and update the rest based on the user’s latest action.
💡 Tip: If it’s the user’s first time, just save the embedding as is — no decay needed.
Here’s the full code:
const decayFactor = 0.1;
const decayEmbedding = preferenceEmbedding.map((value, index) => {
  return value * (1 - decayFactor) + actionEmbedding[index] * decayFactor;
});

That’s it. Simple and effective.
Now, every time the user interacts with something — like watching a video or clicking on a product — you update their embedding using this formula.
Then, when they visit the feed, you simply run a similarity search based on their latest preferences. 
A pro tip I highly recommend (and personally use) is to cache the user’s preference embedding using Redis, so you don’t need to fetch or compute it from scratch every time.
And guess what? That’ll be the topic of my next post.
See you soon, folks! 🚀]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gabriel Ávila</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Requesting Feedbacks]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/abdulrahman_nasser_95c51/requesting-feedbacks-3d38</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/abdulrahman_nasser_95c51/requesting-feedbacks-3d38"/>
        <updated>2025-06-02T23:05:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I've just completed a front-end coding challenge from @frontendmentor! 🎉
You can see my solution here: https://www.frontendmentor.io/solutions/css-font-face-rule-zQnrtK_VD8
Any suggestions on how I can improve are welcome!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Abdul-Rahman Nasser</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Ghost in the Machine]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/rawveg/the-ghost-in-the-machine-4m3i</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/rawveg/the-ghost-in-the-machine-4m3i"/>
        <updated>2025-06-02T23:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The static hiss of a magnetic resonance imaging (MRI) scanner, once a symbol of anxious waiting and complex diagnostics, is increasingly overlaid with the hum of sophisticated algorithms. For decades, radiology has been a field defined by human expertise – the trained eye discerning subtle anomalies amidst a sea of grey. Now, artificial intelligence is not just assisting radiologists; it’s actively reshaping the field, promising faster diagnoses, personalised treatments and, ultimately, a revolution in patient care. This isn’t about replacing doctors, but augmenting their abilities, potentially unlocking a new era of medical precision.
Radiology, uniquely positioned, was ripe for an AI takeover. Unlike many areas of medicine relying on subjective patient histories and complex physiological…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tim Green</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Who's Building AI Autopilot?]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/moxon/whos-building-ai-autopilot-5bpl</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/moxon/whos-building-ai-autopilot-5bpl"/>
        <updated>2025-06-02T22:58:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It's wild to think that 3 years after ChatGPT came along, nobody's built an AI that can effectively sync all my tools and automate me. I can't currently do this for myself. Who's building this?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Oscar Moxon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Using ColdFusion and Xpdf to extract PDF metadata]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/gamesover/using-coldfusion-and-xpdf-to-extract-pdf-metadata-4pe3</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/gamesover/using-coldfusion-and-xpdf-to-extract-pdf-metadata-4pe3"/>
        <updated>2025-06-02T22:55:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Xpdf is an open source projects that includes a PDF viewer, but it also includes a collection of command line tools for Linux, Windows and Mac that can perform some helpful functions:
xpdf: PDF viewer (click for a screenshot)


pdftotext: converts PDF to text


pdftops: converts PDF to PostScript


pdftoppm: converts PDF pages to netpbm (PPM/PGM/PBM) image files


pdftopng: converts PDF pages to PNG image files


pdftohtml: converts PDF to HTML


pdfinfo: extracts PDF metadata


pdfimages: extracts raw images from PDF files


pdffonts: lists fonts used in PDF files


pdfdetach: extracts attached files from PDF files
Can ColdFusion already do some of this? Of course it can, but I am always exploring alternative options and have to occasionally perform some process intensive operations outsi…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>James Moberg</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Next.js 13 Made Me Rethink Axios and Build Traxios: Creating an HTTP Client from Scratch for Tractian]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/adrianknapp/how-nextjs-13-made-me-rethink-axios-and-build-traxios-creating-an-http-client-from-scratch-for-19pl</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/adrianknapp/how-nextjs-13-made-me-rethink-axios-and-build-traxios-creating-an-http-client-from-scratch-for-19pl"/>
        <updated>2025-06-02T22:52:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction


When Next.js 13 introduced new capabilities to the native fetch API, it broke the way we used Axios in our web projects at Tractian. This is the story of how I identified the problem, led the creation of a new HTTP client—Traxios—and how this decision positively impacted our team and delivery.
At Tractian, our web team relied heavily on Axios for all HTTP requests. Axios provided a familiar, ergonomic API, interceptors, and instance management, making it a staple in our codebase. However, with the release of Next.js 13, the native fetch API was extended with new options like cache and next, enabling advanced caching and revalidation strategies crucial for modern SSR/SSG applications.
Unfortunately, Axios did not support these Next.js-specific fetch options. Using Axios meant…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Adrian Knapp</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Detailed Explanation of the Timer in the HarmonyOS Cangjie development Language]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/youlanjihua/a-detailed-explanation-of-the-timer-in-the-harmonyos-cangjie-development-language-3m1p</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/youlanjihua/a-detailed-explanation-of-the-timer-in-the-harmonyos-cangjie-development-language-3m1p"/>
        <updated>2025-06-02T22:50:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today, it's time for the popular science session that everyone enjoys again. It can also be said to be the pitfall session. Hahaha. Today, let's talk about the timer in Cangjie's language development. This part is really interesting.
Why do I say so? Because you can hardly find any documentation about Cangjie's timer, nor are there any related code prompts. It can be said that it just keeps writing without a word.
However, it was still found by You LAN Jun with some clues. Today, I'll share it with everyone.
Cangjie's Timer is hidden in the std.sync package and is called Timer. However, when using it, importing only the Timer package is not enough. We need to import these modules:
import std.time.*
import std.sync.Timer
import std.sync.CatchupStyle

The writing method of the timer is also …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>wei chang</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Lobbyists Urge U.S. Senators to Dodge Distraction in Stablecoin Debate]]></title>
        <id>78547b85-d36b-44fd-b419-a13f2877e796</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2025/06/02/crypto-lobbyists-urge-u-s-senators-to-dodge-distraction-in-stablecoin-debate"/>
        <updated>2025-06-02T22:49:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Top industry advocacy groups requested that the Senate stick to the task at hand as it mulls its stablecoin bill while unrelated amendments loom.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jesse Hamilton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Como eu trampei 7 meses de graça com PHP pra receber 700 reais]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/gustavodevdoido/como-eu-trampei-7-meses-de-graca-com-php-pra-receber-700-reais-emj</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/gustavodevdoido/como-eu-trampei-7-meses-de-graca-com-php-pra-receber-700-reais-emj"/>
        <updated>2025-06-02T22:44:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fala, Dev doido!
PHP.
Eu comecei com PHP, apesar de não fazer a mínima ideia de como funcionava. Era uma tecnologia que pintou uma oportunidade, e eu topei...
Eu tava na faculdade ainda, era 2017, e recebia muito e-mail da faculdade com oportunidades. Na maioria, eu não me encaixava, porque eu não sabia nem o que era banco de dados. Mal sabia programar em Java e só mexia com C.
Eu só queria arrumar algum trampo pra ganhar um dinheiro.
bug em PHP. Chamei o cara no WhatsApp e ele me mandou uns bugs. Eu não sabia nem instalar a IDE.
O cara deve ter pensado: "Vamos ver se esse menino é bom".
Lembro que peguei o computador da minha avó, porque o meu Linux não rodava o projeto, só funcionava em Windows, e o cara ainda usava DreamWeaver (sim, em 2017!).
Usei o Windows da minha avó pra resolver os…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gustavo Miranda</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hallucinating with Q: deep conversations at midnight]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/agi_general/hallucinating-with-q-deep-conversations-at-midnight-4hjm</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/agi_general/hallucinating-with-q-deep-conversations-at-midnight-4hjm"/>
        <updated>2025-06-02T22:30:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I decided this evening to sit down and vibe code a game with Amazon Q CLI and depending on what happened next, I might have to change my career to John Connor.
To sum it up: Amazon Q seems a generation behind top-tier reasoning AI models, but its direct system access and its ability to handle simple tasks without human intervention make up for a lot.
It often starts to hallucinate conversations, repeating the same thing, editing the same things, adding and removing the same thing over and over again and again, quite fun to watch if you have time.
The blazing speed of the code edits is phenomenal. I literally saw 100s of lines of code getting edited instantly; it was surreal, like hackers in a movie.


It can read and work on any file on the folder it has been given permission to without an…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>rajat roy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Here’s what happened in crypto today]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/what-happened-in-crypto-today</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/what-happened-in-crypto-today?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-06-02T22:24:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Need to know what happened in crypto today? Here is the latest news on daily trends and events impacting Bitcoin price, blockchain, DeFi, NFTs, Web3 and crypto regulation.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Cointelegraph</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Building a Console-Based Blackjack Game in C# – Card Rendering, Clean Code and a Simple AI Bot]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/porzeraklon/building-a-console-based-blackjack-game-in-c-card-rendering-clean-code-and-a-simple-ai-bot-46pk</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/porzeraklon/building-a-console-based-blackjack-game-in-c-card-rendering-clean-code-and-a-simple-ai-bot-46pk"/>
        <updated>2025-06-02T22:23:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I've been working on a small but complete side project in C# – a playable Blackjack game that runs entirely in the console.
What started as a practice run to sharpen my .NET and clean coding skills turned into a minimal but functional card game, with some extra flair like card rendering and a basic AI bot.
Here's a breakdown of the project and what I learned along the way.


Console-based, cross-platform (runs on .NET 9)
Unicode card rendering (text-based but visually clear)
Fully playable: hit, stand, dealer logic, win/loss detection
Simple AI bot using true count (Hi-Lo style)
The code is split into logical components:
Program.cs: main game loop, player input, win/loss handling
Cards.cs: deck generation, card drawing, visual rendering
Bot.cs: AI logic — currently uses a basic running count to decide whether to hit or stand
The goal was to keep the structure clean and extensible, so it’s easy to maintain and improve.
You can find the full source code here:
🔗 https://github.com/porzeraklon/blackjack
It's open-source and self-contained — no dependencies besides the .NET runtime.
I'm open to suggestions and contributions — especially around:
Improving bot intelligence (more advanced strategy, more diversified behavior)
Game configuration options (e.g. changing stakes, betting)
GUI version later down the road
If you check it out, feel free to leave feedback or open an issue. Hope it inspires someone else working on a similar idea.
Thanks for reading!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Damian Beldegrin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum Foundation lays off staff, rebrands core team]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/ethereum-foundation-lays-off-staff-rebrands-core-team</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/ethereum-foundation-lays-off-staff-rebrands-core-team?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-06-02T22:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Ethereum Foundation has restructured its core development team and reduced headcount to focus on scaling and user experience.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Ana Paula Pereira</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Teaching Program Verification in Dafny at Amazon (2023)]]></title>
        <id>https://dafny.org/blog/2023/12/15/teaching-program-verification-in-dafny-at-amazon/</id>
        <link href="https://dafny.org/blog/2023/12/15/teaching-program-verification-in-dafny-at-amazon/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-02T22:03:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SOL Strategies reports Q2 net loss of $3.5M while staking, validating revenue surge]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/sol-strategies-reports-q2-net-loss-staking-validating-revenue-surge</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/sol-strategies-reports-q2-net-loss-staking-validating-revenue-surge?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-06-02T21:57:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In addition to buffering its SOL holdings, SOL Strategies added SUI to its balance sheets and decreased exposure to Bitcoin in Q1 2025.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Christopher Tepedino</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Conformance Checking at MongoDB: Testing That Our Code Matches Our TLA+ Specs]]></title>
        <id>https://www.mongodb.com/blog/post/engineering/conformance-checking-at-mongodb-testing-our-code-matches-our-tla-specs</id>
        <link href="https://www.mongodb.com/blog/post/engineering/conformance-checking-at-mongodb-testing-our-code-matches-our-tla-specs"/>
        <updated>2025-06-02T21:50:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How S&P is using deep web scraping, ensemble learning and Snowflake architecture to collect 5X more data on SMEs]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3009651</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/data-infrastructure/how-sp-is-using-deep-web-scraping-ensemble-learning-and-snowflake-architecture-to-collect-5x-more-data-on-smes/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-02T21:45:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Previously, S&P only had data on about 2 million SMEs, but its AI-powered RiskGauge platform expanded that to 10 million.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Taryn Plumb</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Japanese Scientists Develop Artificial Blood Compatible with All Blood Types]]></title>
        <id>https://www.tokyoweekender.com/entertainment/tech-trends/japanese-scientists-develop-artificial-blood/</id>
        <link href="https://www.tokyoweekender.com/entertainment/tech-trends/japanese-scientists-develop-artificial-blood/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-02T21:44:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum Foundation Lays Off Some Staff Amid R&D Restructuring]]></title>
        <id>806741fb-74cc-45c1-8969-3a87a825f2f2</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/tech/2025/06/02/ethereum-foundation-lays-off-some-staff-amid-rd-restructuring"/>
        <updated>2025-06-02T21:13:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Critics of the foundation have repeatedly raised the alarm that the blockchain could lose its edge if it fails to address core design issues.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Margaux Nijkerk</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[My AI skeptic friends are all nuts]]></title>
        <id>https://fly.io/blog/youre-all-nuts/</id>
        <link href="https://fly.io/blog/youre-all-nuts/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-02T21:09:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google quietly launches AI Edge Gallery, letting Android phones run AI without the cloud]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3009810</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/google-quietly-launches-ai-edge-gallery-letting-android-phones-run-ai-without-the-cloud/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-02T20:46:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google quietly launched AI Edge Gallery, an experimental Android app that runs AI models offline without internet, bringing Hugging Face models directly to smartphones with enhanced privacy.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Nuñez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Snowflake to buy Crunchy Data for $250M]]></title>
        <id>https://www.wsj.com/articles/snowflake-to-buy-crunchy-data-for-250-million-233543ab</id>
        <link href="https://www.wsj.com/articles/snowflake-to-buy-crunchy-data-for-250-million-233543ab"/>
        <updated>2025-06-02T20:01:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Hampshire Tops List of Most Crypto-Friendly U.S. States: Study]]></title>
        <id>794dd2cd-4fe7-4269-8529-2b2bc0428939</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2025/06/02/new-hampshire-tops-list-of-most-crypto-friendly-us-states-study"/>
        <updated>2025-06-02T20:00:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ASICKey ranked states by tax policy, crypto jobs, and infrastructure; New Hampshire and Wyoming lead the pack.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tom Carreras</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Show HN: I build one absurd web project every month]]></title>
        <id>https://absurd.website/</id>
        <link href="https://absurd.website/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-02T19:52:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Typing 118 WPM broke my brain in the right ways]]></title>
        <id>http://balaji-amg.surge.sh/blog/typing-118-wpm-brain-rewiring</id>
        <link href="http://balaji-amg.surge.sh/blog/typing-118-wpm-brain-rewiring"/>
        <updated>2025-06-02T19:48:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Japan Drives Cardano Trading Surge as Price Battles $0.70 Resistance]]></title>
        <id>40722ff8-9a56-41dc-bc37-e3dc647ff85d</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/06/02/japan-drives-cardano-trading-surge-as-price-battles-070-resistance"/>
        <updated>2025-06-02T19:16:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cardano's native token faces critical technical test amid global economic tensions and regulatory uncertainty.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Helene Braun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Can I stop drone delivery companies flying over my property?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.rte.ie/brainstorm/2025/0602/1481005-drone-delivery-companies-property-legal-rights-airspace/</id>
        <link href="https://www.rte.ie/brainstorm/2025/0602/1481005-drone-delivery-companies-property-legal-rights-airspace/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-02T19:15:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meta Shareholders Overwhelmingly Reject Proposal to Consider Bitcoin Treasury Strategy]]></title>
        <id>16443d80-a01b-4dee-9e43-04066a4405bb</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2025/06/02/meta-shareholders-reject-proposal-to-add-bitcoin-to-balance-sheet"/>
        <updated>2025-06-02T19:07:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The company has $72 billion in cash on its balance sheet, but barely any of the 5 billion shares that voted were in favor of adding bitcoin.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Helene Braun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OpenAI’s Sora is now available for FREE to all users through Microsoft Bing Video Creator on mobile]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3009808</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/openais-sora-is-now-available-for-free-to-all-users-through-microsoft-bing-video-creator-on-mobile/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-02T19:01:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[OpenAI‘s Sora was one of the most hyped releases of the AI era, launching in December 2024, nearly 10 months after it was first previewed to awe-struck reactions due to its — at the time, at least — unprecedented level of realism, camera dynamism, and prompt adherence and 60-second long generation clips. However, much of […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carl Franzen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CVE 2025 31200]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.noahhw.dev/posts/cve-2025-31200/</id>
        <link href="https://blog.noahhw.dev/posts/cve-2025-31200/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-02T18:58:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SEC faces criticism over crypto staking shift]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/sec-faces-criticism-over-crypto-staking-shift</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/sec-faces-criticism-over-crypto-staking-shift?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-06-02T18:42:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Critics say the US regulator's new stance on crypto staking contradicts past enforcement efforts and court rulings, deepening confusion over how digital assets are regulated.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Ana Paula Pereira</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Public Wi-Fi Is Dangerous – And How to Protect Yourself]]></title>
        <id>683deb300e5fd6529479c483</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/why-public-wi-fi-is-dangerous-and-how-to-protect-yourself/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-02T18:19:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Free Wi-Fi feels like a small win when you’re out. Coffee shops, airports, and hotels offer it like candy  –  just tap, connect, and you’re online.  But behind that convenience is a world of risk that most people never see coming. Let’s talk about wh...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Manish Shivanandhan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Code Linked Lists with TypeScript: A Handbook for Developers]]></title>
        <id>683dea64b88211830493d3aa</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-code-linked-lists-with-typescript-handbook/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-02T18:16:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A linked list is a data structure where each item, called a node, contains data and a pointer to the next node. Unlike arrays, which store elements in contiguous memory, linked lists connect nodes that can be scattered across memory. In this hands-on...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yazdun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tether debuts omnichain gold stablecoin on TON]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/tether-debuts-omnichain-gold-stablecoin-ton-network</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/tether-debuts-omnichain-gold-stablecoin-ton-network?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-06-02T17:58:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The XAUt0 token will compete with other gold-backed stablecoins and traditional gold investment instruments.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Christopher Tepedino</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Decorative Text Within HTML]]></title>
        <id>https://shkspr.mobi/blog/2025/05/decorative-text-within-html/</id>
        <link href="https://shkspr.mobi/blog/2025/05/decorative-text-within-html/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-02T17:26:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Piramidal (YC W24) Is Hiring a Senior Full Stack Engineer]]></title>
        <id>https://www.ycombinator.com/companies/piramidal/jobs/1a1PgE9-senior-full-stack-engineer</id>
        <link href="https://www.ycombinator.com/companies/piramidal/jobs/1a1PgE9-senior-full-stack-engineer"/>
        <updated>2025-06-02T17:00:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Consensys Acquires Web3Auth to Reinvent MetaMask Onboarding]]></title>
        <id>093d1bb2-3064-407e-a6ae-bf2fa594b6ea</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/tech/2025/06/02/consensys-acquires-web3auth-to-reinvent-metamask-onboarding"/>
        <updated>2025-06-02T16:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Consensys did not reveal the financial details of the deal, which could bring improvements to MetaMask's onboarding process.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Margaux Nijkerk</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Arcol simplifies building design with browser-based modeling]]></title>
        <id>https://www.arcol.io/</id>
        <link href="https://www.arcol.io/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-02T16:16:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Price predictions 6/2: SPX, DXY, BTC, ETH, XRP, BNB, SOL, DOGE, ADA, HYPE]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/price-predictions-6-2-spx-dxy-btc-eth-xrp-bnb-sol-doge-ada-hype</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/price-predictions-6-2-spx-dxy-btc-eth-xrp-bnb-sol-doge-ada-hype?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-06-02T16:08:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin is witnessing a tough battle near the $105,000 level, but the downside looks limited.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Rakesh Upadhyay</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Treasury Strategy News: Hong Kong's Reitar and VivoPower]]></title>
        <id>eeccc86e-f94f-45b8-a33a-64797230d4ec</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/06/02/crypto-treasury-strategy-news-hong-kongs-reitar-and-vivopower"/>
        <updated>2025-06-02T16:01:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Reitar will be buying bitcoin and VivoPower XRP.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>James Van Straten</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Beginner’s Guide to Graphs — From Google Maps to Chessboards]]></title>
        <id>683dc829f7d4772789f06d02</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/a-beginners-guide-to-graphs/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-02T15:50:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Most of us use Google Maps without thinking twice. You open the app, check which route has the least traffic, and hit start. Then somewhere along the way – maybe you miss a turn (I do that often) – and Maps calmly recalculates your route, showing you...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tilda Udufo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Show HN: Penny-1.7B Irish Penny Journal style transfer]]></title>
        <id>https://huggingface.co/dleemiller/Penny-1.7B</id>
        <link href="https://huggingface.co/dleemiller/Penny-1.7B"/>
        <updated>2025-06-02T15:49:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Riot Platforms Taps Data Center Veteran to Expand Beyond Bitcoin Mining]]></title>
        <id>e542a6f5-5e98-4c65-85aa-71d95e29edc3</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2025/06/02/riot-platforms-taps-data-center-veteran-to-expand-beyond-bitcoin-mining"/>
        <updated>2025-06-02T15:49:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jonathan Gibbs will lead Riot’s push into enterprise-grade data centers for AI and cloud computing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tom Carreras</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mesh Edge Construction]]></title>
        <id>https://maxliani.wordpress.com/2025/03/01/mesh-edge-construction/</id>
        <link href="https://maxliani.wordpress.com/2025/03/01/mesh-edge-construction/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-02T15:23:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Solana Reverses Gains After Failed Rally Sparks Heavy Selling]]></title>
        <id>38e3954d-099b-4039-89dc-3a4082e1c8cf</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/06/02/solana-dips-sharply-after-repeated-usd159-rejection-triggers-high-volume-sell-off"/>
        <updated>2025-06-02T15:21:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Multiple failed breakouts near $159 sent SOL tumbling on heavy volume, with technical signals now pointing to deeper downside risk unless key levels are reclaimed.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>AI Boost</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Show HN: A toy version of Wireshark (student project)]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/lixiasky/vanta</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/lixiasky/vanta"/>
        <updated>2025-06-02T15:20:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[VC Roundup: Twenty One investors inject $100M into BTC treasury, Jump Capital backs Securitize]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/vc-roundup-crypto-venture-capital-may-2025</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/vc-roundup-crypto-venture-capital-may-2025?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-06-02T15:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Twenty One Capital, Securitize, aZen, Savea and Dexari headline a less active month for crypto venture capital.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Sam Bourgi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Who really controls Bitcoin’s price in 2025? Whales, devs or governments, explained]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/explained/who-really-controls-bitcoins-price-in-2025-whales-devs-or-governments-explained</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/explained/who-really-controls-bitcoins-price-in-2025-whales-devs-or-governments-explained?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-06-02T15:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin may be decentralized, but its price isn’t immune to the influence of whales, protocol upgrades, ETF approvals and global regulations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Bradley Peak</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TON Surges 3.7% in V-Shaped Recovery After Finding Strong Support at $3.11]]></title>
        <id>67f3ac48-8d9f-4120-a186-25acd7ba0c84</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/06/02/ton-surges-37-in-v-shaped-recovery-after-finding-strong-support-at-311"/>
        <updated>2025-06-02T15:04:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Open Network's native token demonstrates resilience amid global economic tensions with bullish technical indicators pointing to continued upward momentum.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tom Carreras</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ask HN: Who is hiring? (June 2025)]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=44159528</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=44159528"/>
        <updated>2025-06-02T15:01:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ask HN: Who wants to be hired? (June 2025)]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=44159525</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=44159525"/>
        <updated>2025-06-02T15:01:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Centralized infrastructure requires DePIN adoption]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/centralized-infrastructure-requires-de-pin-adoption</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/centralized-infrastructure-requires-de-pin-adoption?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-06-02T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When centralized infrastructure fails, entire societies are left in the dark. Recent blackouts across Europe and beyond reveal the urgent need for DePIN, empowering communities to build resilient, community-driven solutions that can withstand crises.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Carlos Lei</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin price dips under $104K as Russia-Ukraine woes rile US stocks]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-price-drops-under-104k-russia-ukraine-woes-rile-us-stocks</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-price-drops-under-104k-russia-ukraine-woes-rile-us-stocks?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-06-02T14:54:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin price action gets off to an uncertain start in June with traders staying cautious on which way the market will head.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by William Suberg</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Litecoin Defies Market Pressure as It Holds Key $87.50 Support Level]]></title>
        <id>83b9e809-38f9-4b99-b93f-56bed773e8dc</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/06/02/litecoin-defies-market-pressure-as-it-holds-key-usd87-50-support-level"/>
        <updated>2025-06-02T14:54:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[LTC sustained a key support zone while absorbing selling pressure amid growing geopolitical uncertainty.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>AI Boost</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Circle Eyes $7.2B Valuation in Upsized U.S. IPO Amid Strong Investor Demand]]></title>
        <id>f277462a-385f-4611-a1dc-311bc8ca28f3</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/06/02/circle-eyes-usd7-2b-valuation-in-upsized-u-s-ipo-amid-strong-investor-demand"/>
        <updated>2025-06-02T14:43:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Circle raises its IPO share count and price range as strong investor demand fuels interest.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Helene Braun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AVAX Plunges 9% as Global Economic Tensions Rattle Crypto Markets]]></title>
        <id>06bff855-81b4-4b16-bbd0-c81581ddbaa5</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/06/02/avax-plunges-9-as-global-economic-tensions-rattle-crypto-markets"/>
        <updated>2025-06-02T14:42:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Avalanche token forms potential double bottom pattern at $19.97 support level, but bearish momentum persists amid broader market uncertainty.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>AI Boost</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NEAR Struggles to Break Free From Bearish Momentum Despite Support]]></title>
        <id>8b37f8bc-0545-473f-bf92-040650ec632b</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/06/02/near-struggles-to-break-free-from-bearish-momentum-despite-support"/>
        <updated>2025-06-02T14:41:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Geopolitical tensions and shifting monetary policies create headwinds for the token as it tests critical price levels.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Oliver Knight</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Hidden Weakness]]></title>
        <id>https://serge-sans-paille.github.io/pythran-stories/a-hidden-weakness.html</id>
        <link href="https://serge-sans-paille.github.io/pythran-stories/a-hidden-weakness.html"/>
        <updated>2025-06-02T14:39:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[We Can’t Regulate Our Way to Crypto Leadership. We Still Need Science]]></title>
        <id>3267e783-4313-4981-9489-54f8893b8ed5</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/opinion/2025/06/02/we-cant-regulate-our-way-to-crypto-leadership-we-still-need-science"/>
        <updated>2025-06-02T14:28:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[National Science Foundation funding cuts threaten to devastate U.S. crypto research, say 10 leading professors.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dan Boneh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ATOM Breaks Out of Consolidation Pattern Amid Volume Spike]]></title>
        <id>c8027903-deb0-4d64-b4f8-7f62a2c56f10</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/06/02/atom-breaks-out-of-consolidation-pattern-amid-volume-spike"/>
        <updated>2025-06-02T14:27:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cosmos token shows resilience amid global economic tensions as trading volume spikes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Oliver Knight</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cloudlflare builds OAuth with Claude and publishes all the prompts]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/cloudflare/workers-oauth-provider/commits/main/</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/cloudflare/workers-oauth-provider/commits/main/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-02T14:24:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SEC’s 2025 guidance: What tokens are (and aren’t) securities]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/explained/secs-2025-guidance-what-tokens-are-and-arent-securities</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/explained/secs-2025-guidance-what-tokens-are-and-arent-securities?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-06-02T14:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The SEC’s 2025 guidance aims to bring clarity and a more structured regulatory framework to the digital asset space.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Dilip Kumar Patairya</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tokenized Securities Trading Venue 21X Adds Circle’s USDC Stablecoin]]></title>
        <id>2346c68d-0656-442a-ae88-610501ed11e9</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2025/06/02/tokenized-securities-trading-venue-21x-adds-circle-s-usdc"/>
        <updated>2025-06-02T14:11:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The collaboration will power atomic settlement of tokenized stocks, bonds and funds on 21X’s regulated trading platform.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ian Allison</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Stablecoin Protocol USDT0 Aims to Bring Tokenized Gold Closer to DeFi]]></title>
        <id>ac6539bd-a4fb-4f7e-8ce9-3f823503779d</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2025/06/02/stablecoin-protocol-usdt0-aims-to-bring-tokenized-gold-closer-to-defi"/>
        <updated>2025-06-02T14:09:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The gold-linked XAUT0 token follows the protocol's Tether-linked USDT0 that has grown to $1.3 billion in supply and available on ten DeFi-focused blockchains.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Krisztian Sandor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[$302 Million Lost to Crypto Scams, Hacks, and Exploits in May: CertiK]]></title>
        <id>b336b4f3-3c24-4661-9ae7-867e79836a53</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2025/06/02/usd302-million-lost-to-crypto-scams-hacks-and-exploits-in-may-certik"/>
        <updated>2025-06-02T14:08:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The largest attack was the $225 million exploit of the Cetus Protocol.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Oliver Knight</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ETH Rebounds Sharply From Intraday Lows, Signals Bullish Shift as $2,500 Holds]]></title>
        <id>8a0b6dea-5c83-4d63-a997-c4f3cb97dd5e</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/06/02/eth-rebounds-sharply-from-intraday-lows-signals-bullish-shift-as-usd2-500-holds"/>
        <updated>2025-06-02T14:07:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ETH bounces 1.7% off intraday lows as buyers reclaim control, with surging volume hinting at a bullish trend shift above critical support.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>AI Boost</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How James Wynn's $100M Implosion Is Familiar Leverage Tale]]></title>
        <id>3e42630e-a2ba-477e-805c-ae8a96e5cd0e</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/06/02/how-james-wynn-s-usd100m-implosion-is-a-leverage-tale-as-old-as-time"/>
        <updated>2025-06-02T14:03:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The trader suffered a nine-figure loss despite bitcoin remaining fairly flat in terms of price action.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Oliver Knight</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Circle raises IPO target to $896M amid strong investor interest]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/circle-raises-ipo-target-to-896m-amid-strong-investor-interest</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/circle-raises-ipo-target-to-896m-amid-strong-investor-interest?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-06-02T13:58:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Circle has increased its IPO target to $896 million amid rising investor interest, growing stablecoin adoption and a more favorable US regulatory environment.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Adrian Zmudzinski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SharpLink Shares Sink 30% After Last Week's 2,000% Surge]]></title>
        <id>201293aa-b03c-4600-a2f0-c3740b89aa37</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/06/02/sharplink-shares-sink-26-after-announcing-closing-of-usd425m-ether-funded-treasury-strategy"/>
        <updated>2025-06-02T13:54:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The company Monday morning announced the closing of its $450 million capital raise with which it intends to but ETH for its treasury.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Helene Braun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Dark Times Are Here. Where Is Bitcoin?]]></title>
        <id>430ef7f0-8fe1-4639-9f8e-cb48b00c8993</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/opinion/2025/06/02/the-dark-times-are-here-where-is-bitcoin"/>
        <updated>2025-06-02T13:53:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin was created for a moment like this. But so far it is missing its mark, says Paul Brody, head of blockchain at EY.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paul Brody</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Reducing Cargo target directory size with -Zno-embed-metadata]]></title>
        <id>https://kobzol.github.io/rust/rustc/2025/06/02/reduce-cargo-target-dir-size-with-z-no-embed-metadata.html</id>
        <link href="https://kobzol.github.io/rust/rustc/2025/06/02/reduce-cargo-target-dir-size-with-z-no-embed-metadata.html"/>
        <updated>2025-06-02T13:36:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BNB Tests $660 Resistance as Price Forms Short-Term Bearish Pattern]]></title>
        <id>eb8d8a1a-79c0-4bec-bd43-98bfb08ae9af</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/06/02/bnb-tests-usd660-resistance-as-price-forms-short-term-bearish-pattern"/>
        <updated>2025-06-02T13:25:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Market momentum has been growing for BNB, with the BNB Smart Chain ecosystem showing significant growth.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>AI Boost</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to use index funds and ETFs for passive crypto income]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/how-to-use-index-funds-and-etfs-for-passive-crypto-income</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/how-to-use-index-funds-and-etfs-for-passive-crypto-income?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-06-02T13:24:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto index funds and ETFs can help you earn passive income by diversifying your holdings and minimizing active trading.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Onkar Singh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Polygon NFTs hit $2B sales milestone as network defies downturn]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/polygon-nft-sales-2-billion-rwa-courtyard-growth-2025</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/polygon-nft-sales-2-billion-rwa-courtyard-growth-2025?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-06-02T13:21:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Polygon’s NFT growth in 2025 is fueled by real-world asset marketplace Courtyard, which now rivals DraftKings in all-time sales.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Ezra Reguerra</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to use AI (ChatGPT + Grok) to find the next big altcoin]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/how-to-research-altcoins-using-chatgpt-and-grok</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/how-to-research-altcoins-using-chatgpt-and-grok?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-06-02T13:12:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ChatGPT and Grok can help you analyze altcoins, compare projects, and stay ahead in crypto research.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Dilip Kumar Patairya</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CoinDesk 20 Performance Update: Index Drops 2.6% as All Assets Trade Lower]]></title>
        <id>dcf64019-af54-4a02-97c6-3156bbfbb6a5</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/coindesk-indices/2025/06/02/coindesk-20-performance-update-index-drops-2-6-as-all-assets-trade-lower"/>
        <updated>2025-06-02T13:12:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cardano (ADA) declined 5.9% and Aptos (APT) fell 5.6%, leading index lower.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CoinDesk Indices</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Aethir enables better user acquisition via Instant Play streaming for Doctor Who: Worlds Apart]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3009700</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/games/aethir-enables-better-user-acquisition-via-instant-play-streaming-for-doctor-who-worlds-apart/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-02T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Aethir provides better computing efficiency with its Instant Play streaming solution for Doctor Who: Worlds Apart.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dean Takahashi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ask HN: How do I learn robotics in 2025?]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=44158353</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=44158353"/>
        <updated>2025-06-02T12:58:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Download: US climate studies are being shut down, and building cities from lava]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1117675</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/06/02/1117675/the-download-us-climate-studies-are-being-shut-down-and-building-cities-from-lava/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-02T12:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is today’s edition of The Download, our weekday newsletter that provides a daily dose of what’s going on in the world of technology. The Trump administration has shut down more than 100 climate studies The Trump administration has terminated National Science Foundation grants for more than 100 research projects related to climate change, according to an…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rhiannon Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Strategy ends May with $75M Bitcoin buy as price tumbles to $103K]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/strategy-ends-may-with-75m-bitcoin-buy-at-103k</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/strategy-ends-may-with-75m-bitcoin-buy-at-103k?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-06-02T12:07:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Michael Saylor’s Strategy continued stacking Bitcoin in the last week of May, buying $75.1 million worth of BTC.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Helen Partz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Binance co-founder CZ proposes dark pool DEXs to tackle manipulation]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/binance-co-founder-cz-proposes-dark-pool-dexs-against-manipulation</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/binance-co-founder-cz-proposes-dark-pool-dexs-against-manipulation?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-06-02T10:50:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Binance co-founder Changpeng “CZ” Zhao proposed launching a dark pool perpetual DEX to protect large traders from front-running and MEV attacks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Adrian Zmudzinski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ThorVG: Super Lightweight Vector Graphics Engine]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thorvg.org/about</id>
        <link href="https://www.thorvg.org/about"/>
        <updated>2025-06-02T10:31:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[XRP price risks a 20% crash to $1.70 — Here is why]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/xrp-price-risks-20-crash-1-70-here-is-why</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/xrp-price-risks-20-crash-1-70-here-is-why?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-06-02T09:54:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[XRP ledger activity has dropped sharply in the past two months, increasing the downside prospects for XRP price to drop toward $1.70.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Nancy Lubale</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Show HN: Kan.bn – An open-source alterative to Trello]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/kanbn/kan</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/kanbn/kan"/>
        <updated>2025-06-02T09:47:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ReasoningGym: Reasoning Environments for RL with Verifiable Rewards]]></title>
        <id>https://arxiv.org/abs/2505.24760</id>
        <link href="https://arxiv.org/abs/2505.24760"/>
        <updated>2025-06-02T09:27:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto funds post $286M inflows as Ether tops buying: CoinShares]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/crypto-funds-286-million-inflows-heavy-selling-coinshares</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/crypto-funds-286-million-inflows-heavy-selling-coinshares?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-06-02T09:12:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ether led last week’s $286 million of net inflows to crypto ETPs, while Bitcoin investment products saw outflows of $8 million, CoinShares reported.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Helen Partz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Singapore orders local crypto firms to cease overseas activity by June 30]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/singapore-crypto-firms-deadline-overseas-digital-token-services</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/singapore-crypto-firms-deadline-overseas-digital-token-services?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-06-02T09:06:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Singapore’s central bank has set a June 30 deadline for local crypto firms targeting overseas markets to halt operations or face steep penalties, including fines of almost $200,000.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Ezra Reguerra</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BitoPro confirms $11.5M exploit, says withdrawals unaffected]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitopro-exchange-11-5m-suspicious-outflow</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitopro-exchange-11-5m-suspicious-outflow?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-06-02T09:01:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Taiwan-based exchange BitoPro confirmed an $11.5 million crypto exploit weeks after the breach, saying user funds and withdrawals were unaffected.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Zoltan Vardai</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Trump administration has shut down more than 100 climate studies]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1117653</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/06/02/1117653/the-trump-administration-has-shut-down-more-than-100-climate-studies/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-02T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Trump administration has terminated National Science Foundation grants for more than 100 research projects related to climate change amid a widening campaign to slash federal funding for scientists and institutions studying the rising risks of a warming world. The move will cut off what’s likely to amount to tens of millions of dollars for…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>James Temple</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[$100K retest vs highest monthly close ever: 5 things to know in Bitcoin this week]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/100k-retest-vs-highest-monthly-close-ever-5-things-bitcoin-this-week</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/100k-retest-vs-highest-monthly-close-ever-5-things-bitcoin-this-week?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-06-02T08:42:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin price expectations are back in flux as a record monthly candle close contrasts with worries over a retest of lower support levels next.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by William Suberg</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Metaplanet becomes 8th largest Bitcoin holder with $118M buy]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/metaplanet-becomes-ninth-largest-bitcoin-holder</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/metaplanet-becomes-ninth-largest-bitcoin-holder?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-06-02T08:15:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Metaplanet now ranks as the ninth-largest corporate Bitcoin holder with over 8,888 BTC, surpassing Galaxy Digital and Block Inc. after a $117.9 million purchase.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Zoltan Vardai</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin price levels to watch as ‘bear flag’ breakdown targets $97K]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-price-levels-to-watch-bear-flag-breakdown-targets-97k</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-price-levels-to-watch-bear-flag-breakdown-targets-97k?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-06-02T07:53:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin fell 11% from its $111K all-time highs as traders say BTC price could drop to $97K if key support levels don’t hold amid rising trade tensions.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Nancy Lubale</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[UK-listed IG Group launches crypto trading to retail investors]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/ig-group-uk-crypto-trading-retail-investors</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/ig-group-uk-crypto-trading-retail-investors?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-06-02T07:00:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The new launch expands IG’s existing cryptocurrency offering, as the company has previously offered crypto-based contracts for difference.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Helen Partz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Yuga Labs sells Moonbirds IP to Orange Cap Games]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/yuga-labs-sells-moonbirds-ip-orange-cap-games</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/yuga-labs-sells-moonbirds-ip-orange-cap-games?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-06-02T06:41:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Orange Cap Games has acquired the Moonbirds, Mythics and Oddities NFT collections from Yuga Labs, just a year after the NFT conglomerate acquired them.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Tarang Khaitan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Silk Road founder’s 300 Bitcoin payday unlikely ‘a self donation’ — ZachXBT]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/silk-road-founder-300-bitcoin-unlikely-self-donation</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/silk-road-founder-300-bitcoin-unlikely-self-donation?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-06-02T06:15:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ZachXBT says both the wallet addresses that sent Silk Road founder Ross Ulbricht 300 Bitcoin were active in 2014 and 2019 while he was in prison.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Stephen Katte</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meta won’t buy Bitcoin as shareholders knock back treasury idea]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/meta-shareholders-knock-back-bitcoin-buy-proposal</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/meta-shareholders-knock-back-bitcoin-buy-proposal?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-06-02T06:05:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Meta shareholders shut down a proposal to assess whether Bitcoin should be added to its balance sheet, with just 0.08% of votes in favor of the idea.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Brayden Lindrea</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[War and Wilderness: British Soldiers in Revolutionary America]]></title>
        <id>https://www.historytoday.com/archive/feature/war-and-wilderness-british-soldiers-revolutionary-america</id>
        <link href="https://www.historytoday.com/archive/feature/war-and-wilderness-british-soldiers-revolutionary-america"/>
        <updated>2025-06-02T06:04:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to post when no one is reading]]></title>
        <id>https://www.jeetmehta.com/posts/thrive-in-obscurity</id>
        <link href="https://www.jeetmehta.com/posts/thrive-in-obscurity"/>
        <updated>2025-06-02T04:01:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Princeton INTERCAL Compiler's source code]]></title>
        <id>https://esoteric.codes/blog/published-for-the-first-time-the-original-intercal72-compiler-code</id>
        <link href="https://esoteric.codes/blog/published-for-the-first-time-the-original-intercal72-compiler-code"/>
        <updated>2025-06-02T01:54:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Model Context Protocol: A promising AI integration layer, but not a standard (yet)]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3009642</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/model-context-protocol-a-promising-ai-integration-layer-but-not-a-standard-yet/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-01T20:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Enterprises should experiment with MCP where it adds value, isolate dependencies and prepare for a multi-protocol future.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gopal Kuppuswamy, Cognida</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[When your LLM calls the cops: Claude 4’s whistle-blow and the new agentic AI risk stack]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3009673</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/when-your-llm-calls-the-cops-claude-4s-whistle-blow-and-the-new-agentic-ai-risk-stack/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-01T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Claude 4’s “whistle-blow” surprise shows why agentic AI risk lives in prompts and tool access, not benchmarks. Learn the 6 controls every enterprise must adopt.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matt Marshall</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google To Phase Out Play Gift Cards, Prepaid Balance In Malaysia Starting 15 June 2025]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=354567</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/354567/google-play-gift-cards-malaysia-phase-out/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-01T08:57:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google has announced that it will discontinue the sale and use of Play gift cards and prepaid balance in Malaysia effective 15 June 2025. The tech giant is advising users to redeem and utilise any remaining balances by 31 January 2026, after which all unspent amounts will expire and become unusable. Malaysian users who still […]
The post Google To Phase Out Play Gift Cards, Prepaid Balance In Malaysia Starting 15 June 2025 appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Heirul Kamel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Huawei Watch Fit 4 Series Now Available]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=354531</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/354531/huawei-watch-fit-4-series-now-available/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-01T06:00:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Huawei Watch Fit 4 series, which includes the Watch Fit 4 and the Watch Fit 4 Pro, are now available at stores across the nation. The standard model has a starting price of RM599, while the Pro variant retails for RM999. The smartwatches were officially launched in Malaysia last week alongside the Huawei Watch […]
The post Huawei Watch Fit 4 Series Now Available appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nurul Kamil</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chinese Company Powers On Country’s First 6nm G100 Domestic GPU]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=354558</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/354558/china-first-6nm-g100/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-01T05:56:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A Chinese graphics card company, Lisuan Technology, recently announced on social media that it has successfully powered on its upcoming G100 GPU. It’s a major milestone, primarily because this is both the company’s and country’s first domestically made 6nm GPU. Little is known about the G100. According to Tom’s Hardware, Lisuan made the GPU using […]
The post Chinese Company Powers On Country’s First 6nm G100 Domestic GPU appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John Law</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Aviot WA-J1 Is A Pair Of Headphones With Three Types Of Drivers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=354480</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/354480/aviot-wa-j1-is-a-pair-of-headphones-with-three-types-of-drivers/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-01T04:00:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You’ve heard of headphones with hybrid drivers – using two types of drivers to deliver sound – but have you heard of “tribrid” drivers? That’s essentially what the Aviot WA-J1 is, which the brand also claims is the first of its kind in the world. So what exactly makes up the “tribrid” drivers of the […]
The post Aviot WA-J1 Is A Pair Of Headphones With Three Types Of Drivers appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ian Chee</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Q-VE Likely To Be Official Name of Perodua’s First EV]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=354551</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/354551/q-ve-likely-to-be-official-name-of-peroduas-first-ev/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-01T03:56:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[National carmaker Perodua recently unveiled the final prototype of its electric vehicle (EV) at the Malaysia Auto Show (MAS 2025). In a recent development, the automaker has filed a trademark application for the name “Q-VE” and its accompanying logo with the Intellectual Property Corporation of Malaysia (MyIPO). With this in mind, it raises the question: […]
The post Q-VE Likely To Be Official Name of Perodua’s First EV appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Keran</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[realme C71 Gets SIRIM Certification; Malaysian Launch Imminent]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=354446</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/354446/realme-c71-sirim/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-01T01:00:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[realme recently introduced a new entry-level smartphone in Bangladesh called the C71, which is presumably the successor to the C61. It comes with a much heftier battery, an upgraded screen, and increased durability. The C71 sports a 6.72-inch 1080p LCD display with a 120Hz refresh rate and a peak global brightness of 580 nits. Underneath […]
The post realme C71 Gets SIRIM Certification; Malaysian Launch Imminent appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ikmal Rozlan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Intelligent Agent Technology: Open Sesame! (1993)]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.gingerbeardman.com/2025/05/31/intelligent-agent-technology-open-sesame-1993/</id>
        <link href="https://blog.gingerbeardman.com/2025/05/31/intelligent-agent-technology-open-sesame-1993/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-31T19:09:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The future of engineering belongs to those who build with AI, not without it]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3009633</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/the-future-of-engineering-belongs-to-those-who-build-with-ai-not-without-it/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-31T19:05:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As we look ahead, the relationship between engineers and AI systems will likely evolve from tool and user to something more symbiotic.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rizwan Patel, Altimetrik</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Micro Center nerd store fills the Fry’s vacuum with its return to Silicon Valley]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3009533</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/games/micro-center-nerd-store-fills-the-frys-vacuum-with-its-return-to-silicon-valley/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-31T13:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Micro Center, an electronics retailer, has opened a store in Silicon Valley in California And so the nerd kingdom has returned.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dean Takahashi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Alleged ARM-Based NVIDIA APU With 120W TDP Leaks]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=354554</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/354554/nvidia-arm-apu-leak/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-31T09:18:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Moore’s Law is Dead (MLID) recently showed off what they claim to be an NVIDIA APU, designed for gaming laptops. It’s the closest and more recent look at what could potentially be the dieshot of the chipset that is rumoured to have been co-developed with MediaTek. The brief look at the die also comes with […]
The post Alleged ARM-Based NVIDIA APU With 120W TDP Leaks appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John Law</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[I made a chair]]></title>
        <id>https://milofultz.com/2025-05-27-i-made-a-chair.html</id>
        <link href="https://milofultz.com/2025-05-27-i-made-a-chair.html"/>
        <updated>2025-05-31T06:24:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tesla’s Robotaxi Dreams Are Rolling Forward in Austin]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=354542</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/354542/teslas-robotaxi-dreams-are-rolling-forward-in-austin/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-31T06:10:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tesla is making serious moves in the self-driving world. The electric car automaker is currently testing its autonomous Robotaxi, also referred to as the Cybercab, on public streets in Austin, Texas without safety drivers behind the wheel. For now, Tesla is using modified versions of the Model Y to carry out these trials. According to […]
The post Tesla’s Robotaxi Dreams Are Rolling Forward in Austin appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Keran</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[U Mobile Appoints CIMB As Loan Coordinator For 5G Network Rollout Funding]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=354548</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/354548/u-mobile-appoints-cimb-loan-coordinator-5g-network-rollout/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-31T06:01:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[U Mobile has appointed CIMB as its Loan Coordinator and Mandated Lead Arranger to secure financing of up to RM4 billion to support the nationwide rollout of its 5G network infrastructure. The funds raised will be used to finance capital expenditure aimed at accelerating network deployment, with a target of reaching 80% coverage of populated […]
The post U Mobile Appoints CIMB As Loan Coordinator For 5G Network Rollout Funding appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Heirul Kamel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JBL Flip 7, Charge 6 Land In Malaysia; Priced From RM799]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=354517</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/354517/jbl-flip-7-charge-6-land-in-malaysia-priced-from-rm799/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-31T06:00:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In addition to the Tour One M3 Smart Tx, JBL also launched its newest portable Bluetooth speakers at the City of Sound Roadshow. As the names suggest, the Flip 7 is the latest addition to the brand’s Flip series, while the Charge 6 is the successor to the Charge 5. To start off, both speakers […]
The post JBL Flip 7, Charge 6 Land In Malaysia; Priced From RM799 appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nurul Kamil</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[QwenLong-L1 solves long-context reasoning challenge that stumps current LLMs]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3009560</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/qwenlong-l1-solves-long-context-reasoning-challenge-that-stumps-current-llms/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-30T23:39:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Alibaba's QwenLong-L1 helps LLMs deeply understand long documents, unlocking advanced reasoning for practical enterprise applications.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ben Dickson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ElevenLabs debuts Conversational AI 2.0 voice assistants that understand when to pause, speak, and take turns talking]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3009577</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/elevenlabs-debuts-conversational-ai-2-0-voice-assistants-that-understand-when-to-pause-speak-and-take-turns-talking/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-30T22:00:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With Conversational AI 2.0, ElevenLabs aims to provide tools and infrastructure for truly intelligent, context-aware enterprise voice agents.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carl Franzen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Which LLM should you use? Token Monster automatically combines multiple models and tools for you]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3009547</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/which-llm-should-you-use-token-monster-automatically-combines-multiple-models-and-tools-for-you/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-30T18:35:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This architecture lets Token Monster tap into a range of models from different providers without having to build separate integrations for each one.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carl Franzen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn to Build a Multilayer Perceptron with Real-Life Examples and Python Code]]></title>
        <id>6839f729798ea464918cffe8</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-a-multilayer-perceptron-with-examples-and-python-code/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-30T18:21:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The perceptron is a fundamental concept in deep learning, with many algorithms stemming from its original design. In this tutorial, I’ll show you how to build both single layer and multi-layer perceptrons (MLPs) across three frameworks: Custom class...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kuriko Iwai</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Microfrontends Work: From iframes to Module Federation]]></title>
        <id>6839c4a906e067fe415d54b4</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-microfrontends-work-iframes-to-module-federation/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-30T14:46:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microfrontends are transforming how teams build and deploy frontend applications at scale. This tutorial explores the architectural landscape, from traditional approaches to modern Module Federation implementations. By the end, you'll be equipped to ...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rahul gupta</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Build A Simple Portfolio Blog With Next.js]]></title>
        <id>6839c439ebab1f7974eac355</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-build-a-simple-portfolio-blog-with-nextjs/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-30T14:44:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I have written articles on different platforms including LinkedIn, The Network Bits (Substack), and freeCodeCamp. So I wanted to bring all of these articles together in a single place where someone could go and see all my work. A blog sounded like a ...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chidiadi Anyanwu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fueling seamless AI at scale]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1117440</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/05/30/1117440/fueling-seamless-ai-at-scale/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-30T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[From large language models (LLMs) to reasoning agents, today’s AI tools bring unprecedented computational demands. Trillion-parameter models, workloads running on-device, and swarms of agents collaborating to complete tasks all require a new paradigm of computing to become truly seamless and ubiquitous. First, technical progress in hardware and silicon design is critical to pushing the boundaries…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>MIT Technology Review Insights</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Sort Dates Efficiently in JavaScript]]></title>
        <id>6839b592f8650e337982bcba</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-sort-dates-efficiently-in-javascript/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-30T13:41:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Recently, I was working on a PowerApps Component Framework (PCF) project that required sorting an array of objects by date. The dates were in ISO 8601 format but without a time zone – for example, "2025-05-01T15:00:00.00". Without much thought, I wro...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brandon Wozniewicz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Survive in Tech When Everything's Changing w/ 21-year Veteran Dev Joe Attardi [Podcast #174]]]></title>
        <id>6839abf3d23bb1460e9ea0ea</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-survive-in-tech-when-everythings-changing-w-21-year-veteran-dev-joe-attardi-podcast-174/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-30T13:00:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On this week's episode of the podcast, freeCodeCamp founder Quincy Larson interviews Joe Attardi. He's a software engineer and prolific author of programming books. We talk about: How software development has changed over the past 21 years Tips for s...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Download: sycophantic LLMs, and the AI Hype Index]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1117620</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/05/30/1117620/the-download-sycophantic-llms-and-the-ai-hype-index/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-30T12:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is today’s edition of The Download, our weekday newsletter that provides a daily dose of what’s going on in the world of technology. This benchmark used Reddit’s AITA to test how much AI models suck up to us Back in April, OpenAI announced it was rolling back an update to its GPT-4o model that made ChatGPT’s…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rhiannon Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This benchmark used Reddit’s AITA to test how much AI models suck up to us]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1117551</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/05/30/1117551/this-benchmark-used-reddits-aita-to-test-how-much-ai-models-suck-up-to-us/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-30T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Back in April, OpenAI announced it was rolling back an update to its GPT-4o model that made ChatGPT’s responses to user queries too sycophantic.  An AI model that acts in an overly agreeable and flattering way is more than just annoying. It could reinforce users’ incorrect beliefs, mislead people, and spread misinformation that can be…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rhiannon Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FLUX.1 Kontext enables in-context image generation for enterprise AI pipelines]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3009464</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/flux-1-kontext-enables-in-context-image-generation-for-enterprise-ai-pipelines/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-29T23:32:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[FLUX.1 Kontext from Black Forest Labs aims to let users edit images multiple times through both text and reference images without losing speed.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Emilia David</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[LeetCode Meditations: A Visual Handbook of Data Structures and Algorithms Concepts]]></title>
        <id>6838baed0c839b0170a2e731</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/leetcode-dsa-concepts-handbook/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-29T19:52:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It may seem like an oxymoron when the words "LeetCode" and "meditation" are used together – after all, one thing that almost everyone can agree is that LeetCode is challenging. It's called grinding LeetCode for a reason. It doesn't have anything to d...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eda Eren</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Emotive voice AI startup Hume launches new EVI 3 model with rapid custom voice creation]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3009430</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/emotive-voice-ai-startup-hume-launches-new-evi-3-model-with-rapid-custom-voice-creation/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-29T18:50:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While EVI 3’s specific API pricing has not been announced yet (marked as TBA), the pattern suggests it will be usage-based.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carl Franzen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn Python for Data Science – Full Course for Beginners]]></title>
        <id>6838a96337f76032ee644b85</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-python-for-data-science-full-course/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-29T18:37:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you're interested in data science but not sure where to begin, Python is a great starting point. It’s easy to pick up and has a bunch of libraries that make working with data a lot easier. We just published a course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Show HN: Onlook – Open-source, visual-first Cursor for designers]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/onlook-dev/onlook</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/onlook-dev/onlook"/>
        <updated>2025-05-29T16:31:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Powering High-Performance Web3 Experiences: Gravity (by Galxe) Launches on QuickNode]]></title>
        <id>683622d561c46d0001eed5d9</id>
        <link href="https://blog.quicknode.com/gravity-alpha-launch/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-29T13:54:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Explore Galxe Gravity’s omnichain power on QuickNode. Build scalable, identity-centric dApps effortlessly with dedicated endpoints and developer tools.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>QuickNode</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DeepSeek R1-0528 arrives in powerful open source challenge to OpenAI o3 and Google Gemini 2.5 Pro]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3009405</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/deepseek-r1-0528-arrives-in-powerful-open-source-challenge-to-openai-o3-and-google-gemini-2-5-pro/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-29T13:22:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Additionally, the model’s hallucination rate has been reduced, contributing to more reliable and consistent output.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carl Franzen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Snowflake’s open-source text-to-SQL and Arctic inference models solve enterprise AI’s two biggest deployment headaches]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3009218</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/how-snowflakes-open-source-text-to-sql-and-arctic-inference-models-solve-enterprise-ais-two-biggest-deployment-headaches/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-29T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New open-source efforts from Snowflake aim to help solve that unsolved challenges of text-to-SQL and inference performance for enterprise AI.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sean Michael Kerner</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Encharge AI unveils EN100 AI accelerator chip with analog memory]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3009330</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/games/encharge-ai-unveils-en100-ai-accelerator-chip-with-analog-memory/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-29T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[EnCharge AI, a startup that raised $144 million to date, announced the EnCharge EN100, an AI accelerator built on analog in-memory computing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dean Takahashi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Peer launches Global Simulation as real-time digital Earth with AI agents]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3009041</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/games/peer-launches-global-simulation-as-real-time-digital-earth-with-ai-agents/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-29T12:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Peer launched Global Simulation, a real-time digital Earth where players use avatars to connect by location and build relationships in a living, spatial network.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dean Takahashi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Download: the next anti-drone weapon, and powering AI’s growth]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1117539</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/05/29/1117539/the-download-the-next-anti-drone-weapon-and-powering-ais-growth/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-29T12:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is today’s edition of The Download, our weekday newsletter that provides a daily dose of what’s going on in the world of technology. This giant microwave may change the future of war Imagine: China deploys hundreds of thousands of autonomous drones in the air, on the sea, and under the water—all armed with explosive warheads or…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rhiannon Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What will power AI’s growth?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1117500</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/05/29/1117500/ai-energy-growth-nuclear-natural-gas/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-29T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s been a little over a week since we published Power Hungry, a package that takes a hard look at the expected energy demands of AI. Last week in this newsletter, I broke down the centerpiece of that package, an analysis I did with my colleague James O’Donnell. (In case you’re still looking for an…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Casey Crownhart</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This giant microwave may change the future of war]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1117502</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/05/29/1117502/epirus-drone-zapping-microwave-us-military-defense/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-29T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Imagine: China deploys hundreds of thousands of autonomous drones in the air, on the sea, and under the water—all armed with explosive warheads or small missiles. These machines descend in a swarm toward military installations on Taiwan and nearby US bases, and over the course of a few hours, a single robotic blitzkrieg overwhelms the US…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sam Dean</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DanaBot takedown shows how agentic AI cut months of SOC analysis to weeks]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008704</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/security/agentic-ai-defeated-danabot-exposing-key-lessons-for-soc-teams/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-29T00:23:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Agentic AI played a decisive role in dismantling DanaBot, a Russian malware platform responsible for more than 50 million dollars in damages.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Louis Columbus</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[s3: The new RAG framework that trains search agents with minimal data]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3009182</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/s3-the-new-rag-framework-that-trains-search-agents-with-minimal-data/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T22:51:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[S3 decouples RAG search from generation, boosting efficiency and generalization for enterprise LLM applications with minimal data.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ben Dickson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mistral launches new code embedding model that outperforms OpenAI and Cohere in real-world retrieval tasks]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3009248</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/mistral-launches-new-code-embedding-model-that-outperforms-openai-and-cohere-in-real-world-retrieval-tasks/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T22:11:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mistral's Codestral Embed will help make RAG use cases faster and find duplicate code segments using natural language.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Emilia David</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nvidia CEO takes a shot at U.S. policy cutting off AI chip sales to China]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3009278</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/games/nvidia-ceo-takes-a-shot-at-u-s-policy-cutting-off-ai-chip-sales-to-china/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T21:36:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nvidia CEO Jensen Huang tiptoed into politics with a comment taking a shot at the U.S. policy that has cut off sales of his chips to China.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dean Takahashi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[QuickNode Accelerator - ChaiNova]]></title>
        <id>68377c476b77cd0001482835</id>
        <link href="https://blog.quicknode.com/quicknode-accelerator-chainova/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T21:31:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ChaiNova joins QuickNode’s Accelerator to bring inclusive Web3 access from local shops to global enterprises.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>QuickNode</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nvidia beats estimates for Q1 results as revenues rise 69% from a year ago]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3009231</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/games/nvidia-beats-estimates-for-q1-results-as-revenues-rise-69-from-a-year-ago/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T20:32:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nvidia, the AI and graphics chip company driving societal changes with AI, reported revenue for the first quarter was up 69%.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dean Takahashi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Less is more: Meta study shows shorter reasoning improves AI accuracy by 34%]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3009203</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/less-is-more-meta-study-shows-shorter-reasoning-improves-ai-accuracy-by-34/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T19:17:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New research from Meta reveals AI models achieve 34.5% better accuracy with shorter reasoning chains, challenging industry assumptions and potentially reducing computing costs by 40%.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Nuñez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[QuickNode Accelerator - SettleX]]></title>
        <id>6813ad1304ef2c0001211afb</id>
        <link href="https://blog.quicknode.com/quicknode-accelerator-settlex/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T16:00:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discover SettleX, a modular cross-chain clearing layer improving capital efficiency, privacy, and liquidity across the DeFi landscape.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>QuickNode</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[QuickNode Accelerator - taro/NYU]]></title>
        <id>68222cb536cbae0001089a2b</id>
        <link href="https://blog.quicknode.com/quicknode-accelerator-taro/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T15:59:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Taro is a privacy-first blockchain project from NYU and Microsoft, enhancing financial transparency and accountability in organizations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>QuickNode</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[QuickNode Accelerator - Mements]]></title>
        <id>68222d3a36cbae0001089a38</id>
        <link href="https://blog.quicknode.com/quicknode-accelerator-mements/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T15:59:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mements is building infrastructure for verifiable AI, with timestamped prompts, provable video streaming, and the launch of MemeChain.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>QuickNode</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[QuickNode Accelerator - EcoFundMe]]></title>
        <id>6822330f36cbae0001089a61</id>
        <link href="https://blog.quicknode.com/quicknode-accelerator-ecofundme/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T15:59:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[EcoFundMe connects donors to verified climate projects with tokenized contributions, DAO governance, and transparent onchain funding.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>QuickNode</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[QuickNode Accelerator - Rivalz Network]]></title>
        <id>68248d91bf7346000109494e</id>
        <link href="https://blog.quicknode.com/quicknode-accelerator-rivalz-network/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T15:59:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Rivalz is building verifiable AI infrastructure, enabling smart contracts to query AI oracles, real-world data, and autonomous agents.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>QuickNode</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[QuickNode Accelerator - Hangry Animals]]></title>
        <id>68236ae084101f00013a5cd0</id>
        <link href="https://blog.quicknode.com/quicknode-accelerator-hangry-animals/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T15:58:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hangry Animals blends storytelling, Web3, and social good into a transmedia universe where players own, earn, and impact real causes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>QuickNode</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[QuickNode Accelerator - Boost Ad Network]]></title>
        <id>6813cc2f04ef2c0001211b24</id>
        <link href="https://blog.quicknode.com/quicknode-accelerator-boost-ad-network/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T15:58:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Boost is an onchain-native, privacy-first ad network with verifiable auctions, real attribution, and campaign analytics for Web3.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>QuickNode</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[QuickNode Accelerator - Diamondz Shadow Movies]]></title>
        <id>6824f61dbf734600010949a1</id>
        <link href="https://blog.quicknode.com/quicknode-accelerator-diamondz-shadow-movies/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T15:58:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Diamondz Shadow is creating a blockchain-powered entertainment ecosystem spanning games, film, tokenized media, and real-world utility.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>QuickNode</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[QuickNode Accelerator - Badchain]]></title>
        <id>6825fdc9bf734600010949cf</id>
        <link href="https://blog.quicknode.com/quicknode-accelerator-badchain/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T15:57:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Badchain is Solana’s culture layer, where behavior drives rewards through meme quests, raffles, and community-led incentives.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>QuickNode</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[QuickNode Accelerator - CVEX]]></title>
        <id>68248962bf7346000109492e</id>
        <link href="https://blog.quicknode.com/quicknode-accelerator-cvex/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T15:57:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CVEX is launching Smart Clearing for DeFi, a decentralized derivatives protocol unlocking capital efficiency and scalable markets.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>QuickNode</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[QuickNode Accelerator - Archer Protocol]]></title>
        <id>68248c8fbf7346000109493f</id>
        <link href="https://blog.quicknode.com/quicknode-accelerator-archer-protocol/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T15:57:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Archer is redesigning Web3 UX with natural language trading, multichain intents, and a non-custodial platform for everyone.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>QuickNode</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[QuickNode Accelerator - SNFT Chain]]></title>
        <id>6813ac5b04ef2c0001211aee</id>
        <link href="https://blog.quicknode.com/quicknode-accelerator-snft/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T15:55:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SNFT Chain connects digital assets and physical devices through scalable L2 infrastructure built for creators and tokenized experiences.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>QuickNode</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[QuickNode Accelerator - Creator Network]]></title>
        <id>682234a636cbae0001089a75</id>
        <link href="https://blog.quicknode.com/quicknode-accelerator-creator-network/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T15:55:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Creator Network is a modular L2 for AI-native applications, empowering builders, creators, and ecosystems with low fees and fast UX.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>QuickNode</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rumi raises $4.7M to change passive media into interactive AI experiences]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3009144</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/games/rumi-raises-4-7m-to-change-passive-media-into-interactive-ai-experiences/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Rumi, an AI media company, has raised $4.7 million in a pre-seed funding round to transform passive media with rewards.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dean Takahashi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The AI Hype Index: College students are hooked on ChatGPT]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1117468</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/05/28/1117468/ai-hype-index-college-students-chatgpt-meta-apple-anthropic-grok/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T14:13:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Separating AI reality from hyped-up fiction isn’t always easy. That’s why we’ve created the AI Hype Index—a simple, at-a-glance summary of everything you need to know about the state of the industry. Large language models confidently present their responses as accurate and reliable, even when they’re neither of those things. That’s why we’ve recently seen…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Editors</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Akool Live Camera can translate video calls in real time, swap faces, and get live virtual avatars to mimic human movements]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008843</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/games/akool-live-camera-can-translate-video-calls-in-real-time-swap-faces-and-get-virtual-avatars-to-mimic-human-movements/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Akool Live Camera uses AI to capture human movement and mimic that movement with a generated virtual avatar in real time.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dean Takahashi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Download: the story of OpenAI, and making magnesium]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1117492</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/05/28/1117492/the-download-the-story-of-openai-and-making-magnesium/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T12:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is today’s edition of The Download, our weekday newsletter that provides a daily dose of what’s going on in the world of technology. OpenAI: The power and the pride OpenAI’s release of ChatGPT 3.5 set in motion an AI arms race that has changed the world. How that turns out for humanity is something we are…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rhiannon Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Everyone’s looking to get in on vibe coding — and Google is no different with Stitch, its follow-up to Jules]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3009114</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/everyones-looking-to-get-in-on-vibe-coding-and-google-is-no-different-with-stitch-its-follow-up-to-jules/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T00:49:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google is looking to compete in vibe coding with Stitch, which designs user interfaces (UIs) with one prompt.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Taryn Plumb</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spott’s AI-native recruiting platform scores $3.2M to end hiring software chaos]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3009108</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/spotts-ai-native-recruiting-platform-scores-3-2m-to-end-hiring-software-chaos/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T00:07:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Spott secures $3.2 million in funding to build an all-in-one AI-native recruitment platform that automates workflows and eliminates tech fragmentation for recruitment agencies seeking to focus on high-value activities.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Nuñez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Anthropic debuts Claude conversational voice mode on mobile that searches your Google Docs, Drive, Calendar]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3009105</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/anthropic-debuts-conversational-voice-mode-for-claude-mobile-apps/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-27T23:23:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With the rollout of voice mode, Anthropic continues to broaden Claude's functionality and accessibility to all users.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carl Franzen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security leaders lose visibility as consultants deploy shadow AI copilots to stay employed]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3008925</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/security/shadow-ai-is-consultings-survival-strategy-in-the-genai-era/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-27T22:15:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fearing sweeping layoffs driven by AI and automation, elite consultants and high performers are turning to shadow AI for a competitive edge.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Louis Columbus</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mistral launches API for building AI agents that run Python, generate images, perform RAG and more]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3009083</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/mistral-launches-api-for-building-ai-agents-that-run-python-generate-images-perform-rag-and-more/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-27T18:52:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For professionals like the Lead AI Engineer or Senior AI Engineer, the Mistral Agents API represents a powerful addition to their AI toolkit.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carl Franzen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>