<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2025-05-06T18:48:55.024Z</id>
    <title>AngJianming RSS Feed</title>
    <updated>2025-05-06T18:48:55.024Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AI Agent Blame Game: Who Failed & When? Attribution Accuracy Under 54%]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/aimodels-fyi/ai-agent-blame-game-who-failed-when-attribution-accuracy-under-54-1bn4</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/aimodels-fyi/ai-agent-blame-game-who-failed-when-attribution-accuracy-under-54-1bn4"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T18:41:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is a Plain English Papers summary of a research paper called AI Agent Blame Game: Who Failed & When? Attribution Accuracy Under 54%. If you like these kinds of analysis, you should join AImodels.fyi or follow us on Twitter.
Research on automatically identifying which AI agents cause failures in multi-agent systems
Introduction of Who&When dataset with 127 failure cases and annotations
Development of three attribution methods for finding responsible agents
Best method achieved 53.5% accuracy for agent identification
Poor performance (14.2%) in identifying specific failure steps
Even advanced models like OpenAI and DeepSeek struggled with the task
Multi-agent systems are like teams of AI workers collaborating on tasks. When something goes wrong, it's crucial to know which team member made the mistake and when it happened. Think of invest...
Click here to read the full summary of this paper]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>aimodels-fyi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AI Math Skills Stalled: New Test Exposes Weakness, Hints Hurt!]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/aimodels-fyi/ai-math-skills-stalled-new-test-exposes-weakness-hints-hurt-51mn</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/aimodels-fyi/ai-math-skills-stalled-new-test-exposes-weakness-hints-hurt-51mn"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T18:40:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is a Plain English Papers summary of a research paper called AI Math Skills Stalled: New Test Exposes Weakness, Hints Hurt!. If you like these kinds of analysis, you should join AImodels.fyi or follow us on Twitter.
New benchmark called FormalMATH containing 5,560 verified math problems
Problems range from Olympiad to undergraduate level
Uses novel human-in-the-loop automation process
Current AI models achieve only 16.46% success rate
Reveals surprising inverse relationship between natural language hints and proof success
FormalMATH is like a massive test bank for AI systems trying to solve math problems. Think of it as training grounds where AI can practice formal mathematical reasoning - from high ...
Click here to read the full summary of this paper]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>aimodels-fyi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ming-Lite-Uni: Faster, Smarter AI Unifies Text, Images, Audio & Video]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/aimodels-fyi/ming-lite-uni-faster-smarter-ai-unifies-text-images-audio-video-3j41</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/aimodels-fyi/ming-lite-uni-faster-smarter-ai-unifies-text-images-audio-video-3j41"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T18:40:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is a Plain English Papers summary of a research paper called Ming-Lite-Uni: Faster, Smarter AI Unifies Text, Images, Audio & Video. If you like these kinds of analysis, you should join AImodels.fyi or follow us on Twitter.
Introduces Ming-Lite-Uni architecture for multimodal AI
Uses novel multi-scale learnable tokens for processing different data types
Achieves unified understanding across text, images, audio, and video
Shows improved performance on key benchmarks
Reduces computational requirements compared to previous models
Ming-Lite-Uni works like a universal translator for different types of digital information. Just as a skilled interpreter can understand both spoken words and gestures, this system can process text, pictures, sounds, and videos all at once. The key innovation is its use of spec...
Click here to read the full summary of this paper]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>aimodels-fyi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meet the new king of AI coding: Google’s Gemini 2.5 Pro I/O Edition dethrones Claude 3.7 Sonnet]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3006623</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/meet-the-new-king-of-ai-coding-googles-gemini-2-5-pro-i-o-edition-dethrones-claude-3-7-sonnet/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T18:39:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One of the standout features of the update is its ability to build full, interactive web apps or simulations from a single prompt.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carl Franzen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DeepSeek-R1: 100 Days of AI Reasoning Revolution? Replication, Fine-tuning, & What's Next]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/aimodels-fyi/deepseek-r1-100-days-of-ai-reasoning-revolution-replication-fine-tuning-whats-next-4hdk</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/aimodels-fyi/deepseek-r1-100-days-of-ai-reasoning-revolution-replication-fine-tuning-whats-next-4hdk"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T18:39:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is a Plain English Papers summary of a research paper called DeepSeek-R1: 100 Days of AI Reasoning Revolution? Replication, Fine-tuning, & What's Next. If you like these kinds of analysis, you should join AImodels.fyi or follow us on Twitter.
Analysis of DeepSeek-R1 model's impact after 100 days of release
Survey of replication studies and new directions in reasoning capabilities
Review of supervised fine-tuning approaches for language models
Examination of training datasets and methodologies
Assessment of model performance across reasoning tasks
DeepSeek-R1 represents a significant step in making AI systems better at logical reasoning. Think of it like teaching a computer to solve puzzles - not just by memorizing answers, but b...
Click here to read the full summary of this paper]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>aimodels-fyi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[LLM Inference Engines Compared: Speed, Cost & How to Choose]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/aimodels-fyi/llm-inference-engines-compared-speed-cost-how-to-choose-5fmg</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/aimodels-fyi/llm-inference-engines-compared-speed-cost-how-to-choose-5fmg"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T18:39:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is a Plain English Papers summary of a research paper called LLM Inference Engines Compared: Speed, Cost & How to Choose. If you like these kinds of analysis, you should join AImodels.fyi or follow us on Twitter.
Study evaluates 25 LLM inference engines for performance and usability
Examines optimization methods like parallelism, compression, and caching
Assesses ease-of-use, deployment, scalability, and throughput
Provides guidance for selecting and designing LLM inference systems
Includes public repository tracking developments
Large language models are like powerful brains that help with tasks like chatting, writing code, and searching. But using them costs a lot, especially when they need to think through complex problems step by step. It's like having a super-smart consultant who charges by the min...
Click here to read the full summary of this paper]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>aimodels-fyi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[LLM Training Breakthrough: Cut Costs by 75% with Low-Precision Methods]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/aimodels-fyi/llm-training-breakthrough-cut-costs-by-75-with-low-precision-methods-3mge</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/aimodels-fyi/llm-training-breakthrough-cut-costs-by-75-with-low-precision-methods-3mge"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T18:38:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is a Plain English Papers summary of a research paper called LLM Training Breakthrough: Cut Costs by 75% with Low-Precision Methods. If you like these kinds of analysis, you should join AImodels.fyi or follow us on Twitter.
Research examines low-precision training methods for large language models (LLMs)
Focuses on techniques to reduce computational costs while maintaining model quality
Analyzes quantization approaches and their challenges
Reviews emerging opportunities in efficient LLM training
Evaluates tradeoffs between precision and performance
Training large AI models requires immense computing power. This paper explores ways to make the training process more efficient by using lower precision numbers - similar to rounding decimals to fewer places to save space and calculation time.
Think of it like compression for ...
Click here to read the full summary of this paper]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>aimodels-fyi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Switching Users with su and sudo (And When to Use Them)]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/sanasadiq/switching-users-with-su-and-sudo-and-when-to-use-them-35ok</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/sanasadiq/switching-users-with-su-and-sudo-and-when-to-use-them-35ok"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T18:38:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction


As I continue my 30-day Linux challenge in preparation for the RHCSA exam, today's focus is on something every Linux user needs to get comfortable with early on switching users securely and smartly using su and sudo.
Both commands give access to elevated privileges but they’re meant for different situations. And knowing the right way to use them can protect your system, your work and your team.
Index



What is the Difference
Basic Usage with Examples
Key Differences
Real World Scenario
Industry Tip
Quick Summary
su stands for substitute user. By default, it switches to the root user unless you specify another username.
sudo stands for superuser do. It allows temporary elevation of privileges to run a single command as another user (commonly root).



Command
Purpose




su
…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sana Muhammad Sadiq</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How I Got x311 Faster Analytics on 110M Rows]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/ydemenskyi30/how-i-got-x116-faster-analytics-on-110m-rows-26db</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/ydemenskyi30/how-i-got-x116-faster-analytics-on-110m-rows-26db"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T18:29:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hey everyone! I recently got fed up with waiting minutes for simple analytics queries to finish, so I threw together a little demo to see how SingleStore, MySQL, and PostgreSQL stack up against each other on a 110 million‑row banking transactions dataset.
Spoiler: the results surprised me - and I think they’ll surprise you too.
In this post I’ll walk you through:
The setup I used
The queries I ran and what happened
How to spin it up on your machine
Docker Images:


SingleStore Free Dev: ghcr.io/singlestore-labs/singlestoredb-dev:latest

MySQL: mysql:latest

PostgreSQL: postgres:latest






Platforms: three t2.large EC2 instances - one for each database
Dataset: 110 million synthetic “banking transactions”
Code: Next.js + Drizzle ORM application (GitHub repository)
I tested three common an…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yaroslav Demenskyi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Are the Key Benefits of a Cloud Data Lake?]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/harman_diaz/what-are-the-key-benefits-of-a-cloud-data-lake-3bn4</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/harman_diaz/what-are-the-key-benefits-of-a-cloud-data-lake-3bn4"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T18:28:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As businesses grow with time, the amount of data they generate also grows with them. This data comes from many sources, like sales transactions, website interactions, customer support systems, social media, etc. Managing all of it efficiently can be challenging, especially when the data comes in different formats and from various locations.
That’s where cloud data lakes come into the picture.
A cloud data lake is a centralized storage solution that allows businesses to store structured, unstructured, and semi-structured data in any amount. Unlike traditional systems that require data to be cleaned and formatted before storing, cloud data lakes let you bring in raw data as it is. You can organize and analyze it later based on your needs.
Let us explore the key benefits of cloud data lakes a…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Harman Diaz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Solana's Bridge Between Web2 and Web3]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/stelmitchay/solanas-bridge-between-web2-and-web3-4n61</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/stelmitchay/solanas-bridge-between-web2-and-web3-4n61"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T18:26:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The latest Agave release Agave 2.2 introduces support for secp256r1 signatures. While this might sound like technical jargon, this addition has significant implications for Solana's ecosystem, from everyday users to developers and enterprises. In this article, we'll explore what secp256r1 signatures are, why they matter for Solana, and how they are positioned to shape the future of blockchain interactions.
Secp256r1 Signatures?


At its core, the addition of native secp256r1 signature verification to Solana is about making blockchain technology more accessible, secure, and compatible with existing web standards. As described in this TLDR Agave 2.2 article by Helius
"Solana is adding native support for secp256r1 elliptic curve signature verification, a critical upgrade that enables on-chain…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mitch</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use Laravel Sail with Docker for PHP 8.2 (No Global PHP Upgrade Needed)]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/patriciosalazar/how-to-use-laravel-sail-with-docker-for-php-82-no-global-php-upgrade-needed-1c28</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/patriciosalazar/how-to-use-laravel-sail-with-docker-for-php-82-no-global-php-upgrade-needed-1c28"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T18:21:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use Laravel Sail with Docker for PHP 8.2 (No Global PHP Upgrade Needed)
Working on a Laravel project that requires a newer PHP version can be tricky if your system’s PHP is older. My personal computer is a Mac, but my work computer is a Linux machine where I sometimes run small projects for exploring and learning new technologies. In that case, upgrading my global PHP installation is not an option since I’d risk messing with work projects.
This is exactly the kind of situation Laravel Sail is for. Laravel Sail lets you use Docker to run your Laravel app with the required dependencies, all while keeping your global system versions untouched.
Here is how I set up new Laravel projects on a Linux computer (works on macOS, Linux, or Windows via WSL2) with Sail and the latest versions of …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patricio Salazar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Smart Contracts: Automating Compliance in Asset Tokenization]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/victoruzo/smart-contracts-automating-compliance-in-asset-tokenization-ao7</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/victoruzo/smart-contracts-automating-compliance-in-asset-tokenization-ao7"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T18:19:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction
In today's digital age, the financial world is undergoing a significant transformation. One of the most groundbreaking developments is asset tokenization, which involves converting real-world assets like real estate, stocks, or commodities into digital tokens on a blockchain. This process offers numerous benefits, including increased liquidity, faster transactions, and broader access to investment opportunities.
However, with these advancements come challenges, particularly in ensuring that these digital transactions comply with existing laws and regulations. This is where smart contracts come into play. Smart contracts are self-executing computer programs that automatically enforce the terms of an agreement. They can be programmed to ensure that every tokenized asset transact…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Victor Uzoagba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CFTC Drops Appeal in Kalshi Election Betting Case]]></title>
        <id>85951e45-a13e-4284-bbf8-b177d7c6170e</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2025/05/06/cftc-drops-appeal-in-kalshi-election-betting-case"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T18:14:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The CFTC appealed a federal judge’s ruling last year clearing Kalshi’s listing of a political prediction market, arguing that it presented a “profound” harm to the public.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cheyenne Ligon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Show HN: Feedsmith — Fast parser & generator for RSS, Atom, OPML feed namespaces]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/macieklamberski/feedsmith</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/macieklamberski/feedsmith"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T18:03:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lightricks just made AI video generation 30x faster — and you won’t need a $10,000 GPU]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3006613</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/lightricks-just-made-ai-video-generation-30x-faster-and-you-wont-need-a-10000-gpu/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T17:56:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Lightricks unveils groundbreaking LTXV-13B AI video model that runs 30X faster than competitors on consumer hardware through innovative "multiscale rendering" technology.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Nuñez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Matt Godbolt sold me on Rust (by showing me C++)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.collabora.com/news-and-blog/blog/2025/05/06/matt-godbolt-sold-me-on-rust-by-showing-me-c-plus-plus/</id>
        <link href="https://www.collabora.com/news-and-blog/blog/2025/05/06/matt-godbolt-sold-me-on-rust-by-showing-me-c-plus-plus/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T17:51:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Is Planet Nine Alone in the Outer System?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.centauri-dreams.org/2025/05/06/is-planet-nine-alone-in-the-outer-system/</id>
        <link href="https://www.centauri-dreams.org/2025/05/06/is-planet-nine-alone-in-the-outer-system/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T17:29:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Hampshire Becomes First State to Approve Crypto Reserve Law]]></title>
        <id>859dba7b-b33d-4dab-8b80-15d692542d64</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2025/05/06/new-hampshire-becomes-first-state-to-approve-crypto-reserve-law"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T17:25:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Governor Kelly Ayotte signed a bill into law that allows the investment of a portion of the state's public funds in precious metals and crypto assets.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jesse Hamilton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Solana bull flag, rising stablecoin market cap hint at SOL price rally to $220]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/solana-bull-flag-rising-stablecoin-market-cap-hint-at-sol-price-rally-to-220</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/solana-bull-flag-rising-stablecoin-market-cap-hint-at-sol-price-rally-to-220?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T17:24:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Key takeaways:

Solana’s stablecoin supply rose by 156% in 2025, to hit a new record at $12 billion.

Solana’s TVL grew by 25% to $7.65 billion, with 27.7% decentralized exchange volume share, leading Ethereum and BNB Chain.

SOL price formed a bull flag, with a price target at $220.

Solana’s native token, SOL (SOL) failed to maintain its bullish momentum after reaching $156 on April 25, but an assortment of data points suggests that the altcoin’s upside is not over.
SOL stablecoin market cap hits $13 billion
Solana’s stablecoin supply has skyrocketed by 156% in 2025, surging past $13 billion to hit a new all-time high.

Stablecoins on Solana recently surged past $13B in issuance, setting a new ATH@calilyliu on why Solana is purpose-built for moving digital dollars at internet speed pic.t…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Nancy Lubale</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Hampshire governor signs crypto reserve bill into law]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/new-hampshire-bitcoin-reserve-law</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/new-hampshire-bitcoin-reserve-law?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T17:08:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kelly Ayotte, the Governor of New Hampshire, signed a bill into law allowing the state’s treasurer to invest in cryptocurrencies, including Bitcoin (BTC).
In a May 6 notice, Ayotte announced on social media that New Hampshire would be permitted to “invest in cryptocurrency and precious metals” through a bill passed in the state Senate and House of Representatives. House Bill 302, introduced in New Hampshire in January, will allow the state’s treasury to use funds to invest in cryptocurrencies with a market capitalization of more than $500 billion, eliminating many tokens and memecoins.
Signing New Hampshire’s crypto reserve bill into law on May 6. Source: Governor Kelly Ayotte
With the signing of the bill into law, New Hampshire was the first of several US states considering passing legislation to establish a strategic Bitcoin reserve, including an initiative with the federal government. A similar bill in Arizona passed the state’s House in April but was vetoed by Governor Katie Hobbs on May 2.
This is a developing story, and further information will be added as it becomes available.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Turner Wright</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Curl: We still have not seen a single valid security report done with AI help]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linkedin.com/posts/danielstenberg_hackerone-curl-activity-7324820893862363136-glb1</id>
        <link href="https://www.linkedin.com/posts/danielstenberg_hackerone-curl-activity-7324820893862363136-glb1"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T17:07:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ServiceNow lets users see more of their AI]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3006589</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/servicenow-lets-users-see-more-of-their-ai/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ServiceNow also announced a way for agents to communicate with others along with its new observability platform.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Emilia David</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Stabledollars: The Third Act of Dollar Reinvention]]></title>
        <id>48fcb34c-2602-47d8-80b2-989a6941b07a</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/opinion/2025/05/06/stabledollars-the-third-act-of-dollar-reinvention"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T16:39:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Blockchain-based dollar infrastructure holds enormous opportunities for the U.S. But only if it treats the technology wisely, says John deVadoss.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John deVadoss</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Planned Crypto Hearing in U.S. House Derailed by Democrat Revolt]]></title>
        <id>57b4aa63-7cac-486b-b717-dd966a2ca409</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2025/05/06/planned-crypto-hearing-in-u-s-house-derailed-by-democrat-revolt"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T16:26:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Democrats abandoned a joint hearing of two committees on crypto policy, inviting people to instead attend their own discussion of Trump's "crypto corruption."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jesse Hamilton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Standard Chartered sees BNB more than doubling in 2025]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/standard-chartered-forecasts-bnb-price-more-than-doubling-this-year</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/standard-chartered-forecasts-bnb-price-more-than-doubling-this-year?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T16:23:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Asset manager Standard Chartered predicts that Binance’s ecosystem token, BNB, could more than double in price this year, according to an analyst report reviewed by Cointelegraph. 
The asset manager sees BNB’s price rising to approximately $1,275 per token by the end of 2025 and as high as $2,775 by the end of 2028, according to the research report. 
As of May 6, BNB trades at nearly $600 per coin, for a fully diluted value (FDV) of approximately $84 billion, according to data from CoinMarketCap.
Price forecasts for BNB. Source: Standard Chartered
“BNB has traded almost exactly in line with an unweighted basket of Bitcoin and Ethereum since May 2021 in terms of both returns and volatility,” Geoff Kendrick, an analyst at Standard Chartered, wrote in the research note. 
“We expect this relat…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Alex O’Donnell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MARA Holdings Cut to Sell at Compass Point Ahead of Earnings, Citing Cash Burn]]></title>
        <id>ed7e6fd2-d48d-411a-8148-b9c68e8cee49</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/06/marathon-digital-downgraded-to-sell-at-compass-point-citing-unsustainable-cash-burn"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T16:20:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Compass Point slashed Marathon’s price target to $9.50, warning of dilution and premium bitcoin exposure.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Helene Braun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Launch HN: Exa (YC S21) – The web as a database]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=43906841</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=43906841"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T16:18:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Show HN: Sheet Music in Smart Glasses]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=43906442</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=43906442"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T15:47:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin price rallied 1,550% the last time the ‘BTC risk-off’ metric fell this low]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-price-rallied-1-550-the-last-time-the-btc-risk-off-metric-fell-this-low</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-price-rallied-1-550-the-last-time-the-btc-risk-off-metric-fell-this-low?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T15:44:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Key Takeaways:

The Bitcoin Risk-Off signal dropped to 23.7, its lowest since March 2019, indicating low correction risk and a high likelihood of a bullish trend developing.

Despite the recent decline in network activity, bullish macro indicators like the Macro Chain Index (MCI) suggest Bitcoin could soon rally above $100,000.

On May 5, the Bitcoin Risk-Off signal, an indicator that uses onchain and exchange data to assess correction risk, dropped to its lowest level (23.7) for the first time since March 27, 2019, when Bitcoin (BTC) traded at $4,000. The signal is currently in the blue zone, which historically suggests low correction risk and a high probability of a bullish trend. When the oscillator rises above 60 or turns red, it implies a high risk of bearish movement. 
Bitcoin Risk-O…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Biraajmaan Tamuly</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DoomArena: A Framework for Testing AI Agents Against Evolving Security Threats]]></title>
        <id>https://arxiv.org/abs/2504.14064</id>
        <link href="https://arxiv.org/abs/2504.14064"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T15:42:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Is it a bull or bear market? How to tell the difference]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/is-it-a-bull-or-bear-market-how-to-tell-the-difference</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/is-it-a-bull-or-bear-market-how-to-tell-the-difference?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T15:41:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[TL;DR:
Not sure if you’re in a bull or bear market? This guide breaks down how to spot the difference using price action, volume, sentiment and onchain data. Learn how to recognize market cycles, what signals to watch for and how to adjust your strategy for each phase so you can trade smarter.
Crypto markets can feel like emotional rollercoasters, prices soaring one month, then crashing the next. You're not alone if you’ve ever wondered whether you are in a bull or a bear market.
In the simplest terms:

A bull market is when prices keep going up, people are excited and there’s a general sense that the future is bright. Think back to late 2020 and early 2021; Bitcoin (BTC) climbed from around $10,000 to nearly $70,000. New projects were launching daily and it felt like everyone from your co…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Bradley Peak</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Show HN: Plexe – ML Models from a Prompt]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/plexe-ai/plexe</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/plexe-ai/plexe"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T15:38:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[North Korean spy slips up, reveals ties in fake job interview]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/north-korean-spy-reveals-ties-in-fake-job-interview</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/north-korean-spy-reveals-ties-in-fake-job-interview?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T15:19:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For months, Cointelegraph took part in an investigation centered around a suspected North Korean operative that uncovered a cluster of threat actors attempting to score freelancing gigs in the cryptocurrency industry.
The investigation was led by Heiner Garcia, a cyber threat intelligence expert at Telefónica and a blockchain security researcher. Garcia uncovered how North Korean operatives secured freelance work online even without using a VPN.
Garcia’s analysis linked the applicant to a network of GitHub accounts and fake Japanese identities believed to be associated with North Korean operations. In February, Garcia invited Cointelegraph to take part in a dummy job interview he had set up with a suspected Democratic People’s Republic of Korea (DPRK) operative who called himself “Motoki.”…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Yohan Yun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gemini 2.5 Pro Preview]]></title>
        <id>https://developers.googleblog.com/en/gemini-2-5-pro-io-improved-coding-performance/</id>
        <link href="https://developers.googleblog.com/en/gemini-2-5-pro-io-improved-coding-performance/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T15:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Show HN: Clippy – 90s UI for local LLMs]]></title>
        <id>https://felixrieseberg.github.io/clippy/</id>
        <link href="https://felixrieseberg.github.io/clippy/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T15:02:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Frictionless flows are Ethereum&#039;s path to economic dominance]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/frictionless-flows-are-ethereum-s-path</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/frictionless-flows-are-ethereum-s-path?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Opinion by: Barna Kiss, CEO of Malda
An idea recently floated by some prominent thinkers in the Ethereum space to reclaim value for the mainnet is the taxing of its Layer-2s. The future of Ethereum does not depend on policy but on enabling frictionless capital movement between the L2s in question. Tariffing rollups may appear a neat way to reclaim value for the mainnet. In practice, it would fragment the ecosystem, drain liquidity, push users toward centralized platforms, and avoid decentralized finance altogether. In a permissionless system, capital flows to where it is treated best, and Ethereum's rollups mistreat it.

Liquidity fragmentation is Ethereum's real threat
In traditional finance, the link between fluidity and growth is well established. Lower barriers to capital inflows lead …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Barna Kiss</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ECB Establishes Innovation Hub to Test Digital Euro as Preparation Phase Nears End]]></title>
        <id>932c193f-a0e2-4908-9e44-fef4f3800a40</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2025/05/06/ecb-establishes-innovation-hub-to-test-digital-euro-as-preparation-phase-nears-end"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T14:51:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The hub has 70 participants including Accenture, KPMG and CaixaBank.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Camomile Shumba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DeFi Development Adds $11.2M in SOL, Bringing Holdings to More Than 400K Tokens]]></title>
        <id>d4cf9af1-e8ad-4a42-abfd-57df47608336</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/06/defi-development-adds-usd11-2m-in-sol-bringing-holdings-to-more-than-400k-tokens"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T14:47:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Formerly known as Janover, the company's SOL holdings are worth more than $57 million at current prices.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Francisco Rodrigues</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Report: OpenAI is buying AI-powered developer platform Windsurf — what happens to its support for rival LLMs?]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3006587</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/report-openai-is-buying-ai-powered-developer-platform-windsurf-what-happens-to-its-support-for-rival-llms/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T14:37:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[OpenAI could see which types of developers use rival models such as the Meta Llama variants and Anthropic's Claude, and for what purposes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carl Franzen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Will Crypto Values Survive the Regulatory Wave?]]></title>
        <id>74e3106c-868a-4cdc-9407-092818a1a538</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/opinion/2025/05/06/will-crypto-values-survive-the-regulatory-wave"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T14:32:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ahead of the People’s Regulatory Roundtable at Consensus 2025, six leading crypto lawyers discuss whether core crypto principles, like decentralization and privacy, will be included in upcoming legislation and regulation.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ivo Entchev</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trump's Crypto Play Fuels Senators' Backlash and Bill to Ban President Memecoins]]></title>
        <id>b95b85bc-3f1c-4cbf-abca-23b1e9859ea5</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2025/05/06/trump-s-crypto-play-fuels-senators-backlash-and-bill-to-ban-president-memecoins"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T14:30:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Democratic Senator Chris Murphy pushed a bill to block presidential coins while Elizabeth Warren described how to get Dems to move forward on stablecoins.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jesse Hamilton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SOL Strategies Buys $18M of Solana Tokens With First Tranche of $500M Note Deal]]></title>
        <id>8522ebda-a761-4edd-aea5-0d8800e95e62</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/06/sol-strategies-buys-18m-of-solana-tokens-with-first-tranche-of-500m-note-deal"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T14:25:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Canadian firm is betting on Solana by using debt financing to scale its validator footprint and crypto holdings.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Krisztian Sandor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What bankers, CPAs and CFOs need to know about blockchain]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/explained/what-bankers-cpas-and-cfos-need-to-know-about-blockchain</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/explained/what-bankers-cpas-and-cfos-need-to-know-about-blockchain?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T14:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Why finance veterans are still skeptical about blockchain            
            
                
Blockchain has been part of the finance conversation for over a decade now. Yet many professionals remain cautious. 
Many seasoned professionals in finance, wealth management and economics often question blockchain’s relevance, asking, How exactly is blockchain supposed to fit into what we already do?

This question reflects a few key ongoing skepticisms about blockchain within finance.
Uncertainty about practical applications
Blockchain offers some big promises: faster settlements, stronger security and better transparency. But actually applying those promises across banking, accounting and operations is still complicated.
A 2021 APQC survey identified the main hurdles: a lack of industry-w…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Bradley Peak</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[VanEck Submits Proposal to Launch First BNB ETF in the U.S.]]></title>
        <id>96cfffe4-6b3a-45f5-8f4e-733208bd4e43</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2025/05/06/vaneck-submits-proposal-to-launch-first-bnb-etf-in-the-u-s"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T14:15:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If approved, the fund would be the first exchange-traded fund tied to BNB in the U.S.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Helene Braun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Accents in latent spaces: How AI hears accent strength in English]]></title>
        <id>https://accent-strength.boldvoice.com/</id>
        <link href="https://accent-strength.boldvoice.com/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T14:07:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Korl launches platform orchestrating AI agents from OpenAI, Gemini and Anthropic to hyper-customize customer messaging]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3006451</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/how-openai-gemini-and-anthropic-help-korl-prepare-customer-materials-in-minutes/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Korl's platform works across multiple systems, using multi-agent and multimodal AI to create highly-customized customer messaging.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Taryn Plumb</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dem lawmakers object to hearing, citing &#039;Trump’s crypto corruption&#039;]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/digital-asset-hearing-objection-donald-trump-crypto-corruption</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/digital-asset-hearing-objection-donald-trump-crypto-corruption?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T13:59:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[US Representative Maxine Waters, ranking member of the House Financial Services Committee (HFSC), led some Democratic lawmakers out of a joint hearing on digital assets in response to what she called “the corruption of the President of the United States” concerning cryptocurrencies.
In a May 6 joint hearing of the HFSC and House Committee on Agriculture, Waters remained standing while addressing Republican leadership, saying she intended to block proceedings due to US President Donald Trump’s “ownership of crypto” and oversight of government agencies. Digital asset subcommittee Chair Bryan Steil, seemingly taking advantage of a loophole in committee rules, said Republican lawmakers would continue with the event as a “roundtable” rather than a hearing.
HFSC Chair French Hill urged lawmakers…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Turner Wright</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nnd – a TUI debugger alternative to GDB, LLDB]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/al13n321/nnd</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/al13n321/nnd"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T13:58:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BNB Coin Could Hit $2,775 by Year-End 2028, Standard Chartered Says]]></title>
        <id>30f232ba-36b9-44cb-8aa7-5ae1d555a057</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/06/bnb-coin-could-hit-2775-by-year-end-2028-standard-chartered-says"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T13:57:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The token has traded like an unweighted mix of bitcoin and ether since May 2021, the report said.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Will Canny</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MTerrain: Optimized terrain system and editor for Godot]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/mohsenph69/Godot-MTerrain-plugin</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/mohsenph69/Godot-MTerrain-plugin"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T13:26:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[21Shares Launches ETP Linked to Crypto.com's Cronos]]></title>
        <id>6a70328c-6e4b-4729-9f1f-477a776cf317</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/06/21shares-launches-etp-linked-to-cryptocoms-cronos"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T13:23:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The product allows investors to add CRO exposure to their portfolios without handling crypto wallets or exchanges.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Francisco Rodrigues</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CoinDesk 20 Performance Update: Index Drops 2.2% as All Assets Trade Lower]]></title>
        <id>43299b7f-f086-4d0b-a85e-7f768d3e67a4</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/coindesk-indices/2025/05/06/coindesk-20-performance-update-index-drops-2-2-as-all-assets-trade-lower"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T13:16:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sui (SUI) fell 7.7% and Aave (AAVE) declined 7.5%, leading the index lower.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CoinDesk Indices</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Mining Rig Maker Canaan Could Have 5X Upside, Says Wall Street Analyst]]></title>
        <id>e459b496-aeee-4386-a66b-c3bdca554008</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/06/bitcoin-mining-rig-maker-canaan-could-have-5x-upside-says-wall-street-analyst"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T13:08:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Benchmark's Mark Palmer initiated coverage on the firm's roughed-up shares with a buy rating and $3 price target.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Will Canny</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ōura adds AI-driven meal and glucose tracking features with Stelo by Dexcom]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3006449</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/games/oura-adds-ai-driven-meal-and-glucose-tracking-features-with-stelo-by-dexcom/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ōura, maker of a health-monitoring smart ring, announced that it will use AI to track and analyze two new metabolic health features: meals and glucose.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dean Takahashi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DogeOS Raises $6.9M to Launch Dogecoin App Layer]]></title>
        <id>3ea4be2f-eb52-4702-b451-8236cfadd034</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/06/dogeos-raises-usd6-9m-to-launch-dogecoin-app-layer"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The funding will enable DogeOS to support a variety of consumer apps, enhancing the Dogecoin ecosystem and its decentralized finance services.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shaurya Malwa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Here’s what happened in crypto today]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/what-happened-in-crypto-today</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/what-happened-in-crypto-today?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T12:47:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today in crypto, Binance founder Changpeng “CZ” Zhao expects Bitcoin to reach between $500,000 and $1 million this market cycle, driven by institutional adoption, growing government accumulation, and a pro-crypto US policy, Florida has withdrawn its two Bitcoin reserve bills from consideration in a blow to Bitcoin hopefuls, and asset manager VanEck has filed for the first US BNB exchange-traded fund.
Binance founder CZ says Bitcoin could hit $500,000–$1 million this cycle
CZ expects Bitcoin’s price to top at $500,000 to $1 million during this market cycle.
During an interview with Rug Radio published on May 5, Zhao said that he expects Bitcoin to reach up to one million dollars during this market cycle. He also highlighted the role of Bitcoin spot exchange-traded funds (ETFs) in this rise,…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Cointelegraph</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Binance founder CZ says Bitcoin could hit $500K–$1M this cycle]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/cz-says-bitcoin-could-hit-500-k-1-m-this-cycle</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/cz-says-bitcoin-could-hit-500-k-1-m-this-cycle?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T12:40:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Binance co-founder Changpeng “CZ” Zhao expects Bitcoin’s price to top at $500,000 to $1 million during this market cycle.
During an interview with Rug Radio published on May 5, Zhao said that he expects Bitcoin to reach up to one million dollars during this market cycle. He also highlighted the role of Bitcoin spot exchange-traded funds (ETFs) in this rise, saying that the increasing institutionalization of Bitcoin is a good thing for the market:
“There’s the ETFs. There’s this institutionalization of Bitcoin [ … ] it’s a positive in terms of price action, obviously. Our bags are up  —  not the alt‑coins as much, but at least Bitcoin is.”
Zhao explained that the ETFs are “bringing the traditional institution money into crypto” and “most of the money in the US is institutional money.” He sa…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Adrian Zmudzinski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Traders Seek Downside Protection Ahead of Fed Chair Powell’s Comments]]></title>
        <id>e9e20408-1ab5-456d-b406-2cc03272ba33</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/06/bitcoin-traders-seek-downside-protection-ahead-of-fed-chair-powell-s-comments"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T12:36:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We have only seen some nuanced demand for protective BTC puts, reflecting limited caution among sophisticated traders, Deribit's CEO told CoinDesk.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Omkar Godbole</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Singapore’s Grab taps Solana DePIN project Natix to ‘reshape mapping’]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/singapore-grab-solana-depin-autonomous-driving-mapping</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/singapore-grab-solana-depin-autonomous-driving-mapping?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T12:32:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Southeast Asia’s superapp Grab has partnered with Natix, a project within Solana’s decentralized physical infrastructure network (DePIN), to cooperate on mapping and autonomous driving technologies.
The joint collaboration aims to combine Natix’s blockchain-based mapping data with Grab’s camera hardware and mapmaking technology featuring artificial intelligence support, Natix said in an announcement on May 6.
“This partnership brings together the best of both worlds,” the announcement noted, pointing to Grab’s expertise in crowdsourced mapping and Natix’s unique DePIN model that rewards users for providing decentralized data input.
Source: Natix
“By combining GrabMaps’ AI-powered mapping technology with Natix’s decentralized data network, we’re enabling real-time, high-fidelity map updates…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Helen Partz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin risks sub-$92K retest as BTC price fails to match 4% gold gains]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-faces-91-6-k-retest-btc-price-fails-match-gold-gains</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-faces-91-6-k-retest-btc-price-fails-match-gold-gains?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T12:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Key points:

Bitcoin is struggling again as gold retakes the limelight with week-to-date gains of nearly 5%.

Bitcoin’s correlation with gold is under scrutiny amid ongoing macroeconomic shifts.

Traders see a short-term slump amid a wider BTC price rebound.

Bitcoin (BTC) eyed fresh month-to-date lows into the May 6 Wall Street open as “directionless” crypto markets contrasted with a gold rebound.
BTC/USD 1-hour chart. Source: Cointelegraph/TradingView
Analysis: Bitcoin, crypto “largely directionless”
Data from Cointelegraph Markets Pro and TradingView showed BTC price momentum stalling at $95,000 before the latest daily close. 
Inching closer to the key yearly open support level at $93,500, BTC/USD appeared caught in limbo while gold returned to outperform.
XAU/USD was up 1.5% on the day…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by William Suberg</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[US stablecoin bill loses democrats amid Trump corruption concerns]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/us-stablecoin-bill-loses-democratic-support-trump-corruption-concerns</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/us-stablecoin-bill-loses-democratic-support-trump-corruption-concerns?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T12:28:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Democratic lawmakers in Washington are backing off support for crypto legislation amid heightened concerns over corruption, including the conduct of the Trump family’s World Liberty Financial (WLFI).
In March, the GENIUS Act, which would regulate stablecoins in the US, passed a critical committee reading with the support of several pro-crypto Democrats. Democratic Senators Ruben Gallego, Mark Warner, Lisa Blunt Rochester, Andy Kim and Angela Alsobrooks voted with Republicans, opposite lead Democrat and prominent crypto critic Senator Elizabeth Warren.
The bill passed the committee only after a number of changes were made, including stricter requirements for stablecoin issuers and provisions for Anti-Money Laundering, countering terrorism financing and risk management procedures. 
Now, it s…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Aaron Wood</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why is XRP price down today?]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/why-is-xrp-price-down-today</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/why-is-xrp-price-down-today?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T12:15:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Key takeaways:

Ripple's end-to-quarterly market report fuels uncertainty, impacting XRP price negatively.

Low open interest in XRP futures signals weak trader confidence.

XRP price technicals weaken with resistance at $2.27 and declining RSI.

XRP (XRP) fell on May 6, down 3% in the last 24 hours to trade at $2.09, due to numerous factors. Its trading volume has increased by 25% over the same period to $2.5 billion, reinforcing the momentum of the bears. 
XRP/USD four-hour chart. Source: Cointelegraph/TradingView
Let’s look at the factors driving the XRP price down today.
Ripple’s discontinues quarterly reports
On May 5, Ripple revealed plans to end its quarterly XRP markets report, which it has released since 2017. The company attributed the decision to the reports falling short of exp…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Nancy Lubale</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Download: a longevity influencer’s new religion, and humanoid robots’ shortcomings]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1116114</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/05/06/1116114/the-download-a-longevity-influencers-new-religion-and-humanoid-robots-shortcomings/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T12:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is today’s edition of The Download, our weekday newsletter that provides a daily dose of what’s going on in the world of technology. Bryan Johnson wants to start a new religion in which “the body is God” Bryan Johnson is on a mission to not die. The 47-year-old multimillionaire has already applied his slogan “Don’t Die”…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rhiannon Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin price forms two BTC futures gaps after Coinbase premium flips negative]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-price-btc-futures-gaps-after-coinbase-premium-turns-negative</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-price-btc-futures-gaps-after-coinbase-premium-turns-negative?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T12:01:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Key takeaways: 

Bitcoin’s Coinbase premium index turned negative for the first time in 15 days, indicating defensive short-term sentiment among US investors.

Bitcoin CME futures gaps between support at $92,000-$92,500 and resistance at $96,400-$97,400 suggest a period of range-bound trading. 

Bitcoin’s Coinbase premium index, which measures the gap between BTC price at Coinbase Pro and Binance exchange, turned negative after a 15-day positive stint, signaling potential bearish sentiment among US investors.
This drop coincides with Bitcoin (BTC) slipping below $94,000, and the premium’s decline suggests reduced buying pressure on Coinbase, which is viewed as a proxy for both institutional and retail demand.
Bitcoin Coinbase premium. Source: CryptoQuant
Cointelegraph reported early signs …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Biraajmaan Tamuly</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blockchains ready for institutions, lawyers hesitate: DoubleZero CEO]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/institutional-infrastructure-crypto-austin-federa-doublezero</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/institutional-infrastructure-crypto-austin-federa-doublezero?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T11:45:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While blockchain infrastructure may be ready for institutional use, many legal teams at big firms remain cautious about fully integrating the technology. 
At the Token2049 event in Dubai, DoubleZero founder and former Solana head of strategy Austin Federa told Cointelegraph that today’s high-performance blockchains like Solana are technically capable of supporting large-scale institutional usage. However, lawyers need to catch up. 
“Most blockchains nowadays, especially things like Solana, are fast enough for institutions to use them,” Federa said. “It’s really more about the institutions and the institution’s lawyers getting comfortable with crypto.”
Federa added that institutional lawyers and compliance teams are still addressing regulatory concerns. The executive said this may slow adop…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Ezra Reguerra</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Propositions as Types (2014) [pdf]]]></title>
        <id>https://homepages.inf.ed.ac.uk/wadler/papers/propositions-as-types/propositions-as-types.pdf</id>
        <link href="https://homepages.inf.ed.ac.uk/wadler/papers/propositions-as-types/propositions-as-types.pdf"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T11:36:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Citi and SDX partner to tokenize traditional private markets]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/citi-sdx-tokenize-private-markets</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/citi-sdx-tokenize-private-markets?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T11:35:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Investment bank Citi and Switzerland’s SIX Digital Exchange (SDX) are teaming up to modernize traditional private markets through tokenization.
The initiative, revealed during the Point Zero Forum in Switzerland, will leverage SDX’s blockchain-based Central Securities Depositary (CSD) platform to tokenize, settle and safekeep assets, according to a May 6 announcement.
The platform, expected to go live by the third quarter of 2025, will make late-stage, pre-initial public offering (IPO) equities accessible to institutional and eligible investors globally.
The project offers issuers a compliant and scalable framework to manage liquidity, particularly for early investors and employees, while maintaining cap table control. For investors, it opens access to high-growth, venture-backed companies…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Amin Haqshanas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[realme Teases New GT 7 Smartphones Launching In Malaysia Soon]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=350727</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/350727/realme-gt-7-series-msia-teaser/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T11:24:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[realme has confirmed that the latest additions to its GT 7 series of smartphones will be launching in Malaysia soon. As you may recall, the base model as well as a newer “T” variant has recently been spotted in SIRIM, indicating their imminent arrival. Meanwhile, the series’ Pro variant had already made its debut locally […]
The post realme Teases New GT 7 Smartphones Launching In Malaysia Soon appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Heirul Kamel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Memory-safe sudo to become the default in Ubuntu]]></title>
        <id>https://trifectatech.org/blog/memory-safe-sudo-to-become-the-default-in-ubuntu/</id>
        <link href="https://trifectatech.org/blog/memory-safe-sudo-to-become-the-default-in-ubuntu/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T11:22:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Research DAO claims paralyzed rats recover after spinal cord fix]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/hydradao-spinal-cord-repair-neuropeg-rats</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/hydradao-spinal-cord-repair-neuropeg-rats?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T11:19:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decentralized autonomous organization (DAO) HydraDAO claims that its researchers were able to use a novel technique to repair severed spines in rats.
In a May 5 X post, decentralized science (DeSci) project HydraDAO said that one of its research projects resulted in “rats who had their spines fully transected” being able to walk again. More notably, recovery from surgery reportedly only took five days.
Source: HydraDAO
The post featured a video of partially shaved (presumably due to surgery) rats walking in what appeared to be a laboratory setting. The effort in question is the Dowell spinal fusogens project led by Michael Lebenstein-Gumovski, which raised 380,700 USDC (USDC) from donors. The dedicated HydraDAO page reads:
“The Dowell team submitted a project proposal to HydraDAO. After ca…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Adrian Zmudzinski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How much Bitcoin can Berkshire Hathaway buy?]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/how-much-bitcoin-can-berkshire-hathaway-buy</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/how-much-bitcoin-can-berkshire-hathaway-buy?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T11:15:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Key takeaways:

Berkshire holds $347B in cash, enough to buy ~18% of Bitcoin’s supply.

Greg Abel has not signaled a shift from Warren Buffett’s anti-Bitcoin stance.

Berkshire already has indirect crypto exposure via Nu Holdings, Jefferies.

Warren Buffett announced at Berkshire Hathaway's annual shareholder meeting on May 3 that he will step down as CEO by the end of 2025, with Greg Abel taking over. This transition raises speculation about Berkshire’s financial capacity to purchase Bitcoin (BTC) under the new leadership.
Source: Discover Crypto
Berkshire can easily surpass Strategy’s BTC stash 
Berkshire ended Q4 2024 with a record $347 billion in cash and US Treasury bills, representing about 32% of its $1.1 trillion market capitalization. 
The company could acquire approximately 3.52 …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Yashu Gola</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Daybook Americas: Can Bitcoin's Regulatory Worry be Bullish for DeFi Tokens?]]></title>
        <id>43ae5db8-dc9e-46b3-8da8-84550f823d54</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/daybook-us/2025/05/06/crypto-daybook-americas-bitcoin-threatened-by-regulation-hiccup-weakening-demand"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T11:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Your day-ahead look for May 6, 2025]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Omkar Godbole</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Design and evaluation of a parrot-to-parrot video-calling system (2023)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.smithsonianmag.com/smart-news/scientists-taught-pet-parrots-to-video-call-each-other-and-the-birds-loved-it-180982041/</id>
        <link href="https://www.smithsonianmag.com/smart-news/scientists-taught-pet-parrots-to-video-call-each-other-and-the-birds-loved-it-180982041/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T11:03:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Leading Deepfake Porn Site Has Been Shut Down, Forever]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=350656</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/350656/a-leading-deepfake-porn-site-has-been-shut-down-forever/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mr. Deepfakes, one of the largest site for nonconsensual deepfake pornography, is shutting down for good. The site recently posted a notice on its site, saying that it has lost the ability to stay open. “A critical service provider has terminated service permanently. Data loss has made it impossible to continue operation. We will not […]
The post A Leading Deepfake Porn Site Has Been Shut Down, Forever appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John Law</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Is the Paws Telegram mini app legit? What you need to know]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/explained/is-paws-telegram-mini-app-legit-what-you-need-to-know</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/explained/is-paws-telegram-mini-app-legit-what-you-need-to-know?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T10:50:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What is the Paws Telegram Mini App?            
            
                
Paws is a Telegram-based Mini App created by the same team behind other projects, such as Notcoin and Dogs. 
If you’ve been cruising around Telegram lately, chances are you’ve stumbled upon Paws, the viral crypto Mini App that’s got everyone tapping, clicking and inviting their friends like it’s 2010 FarmVille all over again. 
Originally launched in October 2024 on The Open Network (TON) blockchain, Paws exploded in popularity with its ultra-simple tap-to-earn concept. Think of it as a gamified rewards engine embedded directly in Telegram, where users rack up points by completing tasks, referring others and interacting with mini-game elements. 
Within just eight days of going live, Paws pulled in over 20 million …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Shailey Singh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Citi, Switzerland’s SDX Join Forces to Tokenize $75B Pre-IPO Shares Market]]></title>
        <id>04745cbf-1995-485a-8f3e-8eb0c1e2eb18</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2025/05/06/citi-switzerland-s-sdx-join-forces-to-tokenize-usd75b-pre-ipo-shares-market"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T10:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Citi will act as a custodian and issuer agent for tokenized assets on SDX’s digital Central Securities Depository (CSD) platform.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ian Allison</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Prototype Of DJI’s 360-Degree Camera Leaks Online]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=350718</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/350718/dji-360-degree-camera-prototype-leak/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T10:42:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Leaks featuring an alleged prototype of a 360-degree camera by action cam and drone manufacturer DJI have surfaced online. Thanks to tipsters hakasushi and Igor Bogdanov (aka @Quadro_News), details, images and even a Quick Start Guide of the alleged device were shared on X for all to see. Based on the materials provided, the DJI […]
The post A Prototype Of DJI’s 360-Degree Camera Leaks Online appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Heirul Kamel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto spending will grow, but fiat isn’t going anywhere: Mercuryo CEO]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/crypto-payments-mercuryo-ceo-token2049-interview</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/crypto-payments-mercuryo-ceo-token2049-interview?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T10:27:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Petr Kozyakov, CEO of crypto payments platform Mercuryo, told Cointelegraph that the future of finance may not be a winner-takes-all scenario but a blend of digital assets and fiat, each used where it makes the most sense. 
In a Cointelegraph interview, Kozyakov said that while crypto payments are seeing an increase in adoption and demand, the asset class won’t be fully replacing fiat money anytime soon. He said the two asset classes will coexist, with people choosing the more convenient payment option in different situations. 
“We don’t think crypto will replace fiat,” Kozyakov told Cointelegraph. “They will coexist, and people will turn to crypto when it’s the easier, more practical option, whether that’s for payroll, yield or money transfers.”
Mercuryo Petr Kozyakov at the Token2049 eve…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Ezra Reguerra</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[IntoTheBlock and Trident Merge With $25M Backing to Build Institutional DeFi Gateway]]></title>
        <id>cb2296f1-a439-480a-8f41-100c9a802dd2</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2025/05/05/intotheblock-and-trident-merge-secure-usd25m-backing-to-build-institutional-defi-gateway"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The newly formed Sentora aims to offer a compliant DeFi platform for sophisticated investors looking for yield, liquidity and risk management.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Krisztian Sandor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Solana’s Natix and Grab Team Up to Expand DePIN Mapping Into U.S., Europe]]></title>
        <id>cf7927e0-4c80-4d74-bc4a-e4dc1e9eae61</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/tech/2025/05/06/solanas-natix-and-grab-team-up-to-expand-depin-mapping-into-us-europe"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The collaboration will enhance mapping accuracy by combining Natix’s network with Grab’s mapmaking technology.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Margaux Nijkerk</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Xiaomi Lifts SU7 Ultra EV’s Performance Restriction After Customer Complaints]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=350690</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/350690/xiaomi-lifts-su7-ultra-performance-restriction/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T09:59:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At times, people purchase cars to experience their full performance anywhere and anytime they please. Unfortunately, this wasn’t the case for owners of Xiaomi’s SU7 Ultra owners in China after a recent update had pretty much nerfed its 1,548 HP power output to a mere 900HP. As you’d expect, customers weren’t happy with this decision, […]
The post Xiaomi Lifts SU7 Ultra EV’s Performance Restriction After Customer Complaints appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Keran</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[IRS appoints Trish Turner to head crypto division amid resignations]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/trish-turner-irs-crypto-division-leadership-shiftpto-division-amid-leadership-shakeup</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/trish-turner-irs-crypto-division-leadership-shiftpto-division-amid-leadership-shakeup?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T09:50:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Veteran US Internal Revenue Service (IRS) official Trish Turner was appointed to lead the agency’s digital assets division following the departure of two key crypto-focused executives.
Turner, who has spent over 20 years at the IRS and most recently served as a senior adviser within the Digital Assets Office, will now head the unit, according to a report from Bloomberg Tax citing a person familiar with the situation.
Her promotion marks a significant leadership transition at a time when US crypto tax enforcement is facing both internal and external pressures.
On May 5, Sulolit “Raj” Mukherjee and Seth Wilks, two private-sector experts brought in to lead the IRS’s crypto unit, exited after roughly a year in their roles.
Mukherjee served as compliance and implementation executive director, w…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Amin Haqshanas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Technics AZ100 Lightning Review: The Hard-Hitting Sequel]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=350207</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/350207/technics-az100-lightning-review-the-hard-hitting-sequel/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T09:37:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Technics AZ100 launched earlier this year and serve as the successor to the AZ80 that I reviewed nearly two years ago. Considering how its predecessor wowed from the get-go, I actually started out this review with relatively high expectations. And boy, these earbuds did not fail to impress. What Am I Looking At? Both […]
The post Technics AZ100 Lightning Review: The Hard-Hitting Sequel appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John Law</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Florida Withdraws Strategic Bitcoin Reserve Bills From Consideration]]></title>
        <id>a49d3b1b-092e-49e0-b5d6-0f67e3ea2ddc</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2025/05/06/florida-withdraws-strategic-bitcoin-reserve-bills-from-consideration"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T09:23:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The two bills, which were both filed in February, sought to allow investment of public funds in BTC]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Crawley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OKX exec warns against hype amid real-world asset tokenization boom]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/okx-mena-ceo-rwa-tokenization-boom-token2049-dubai</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/okx-mena-ceo-rwa-tokenization-boom-token2049-dubai?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T09:08:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The CEO of crypto exchange OKX’s Middle East and North Africa (MENA) division has called on the industry to prioritize real-world utility as interest in tokenizing real-world assets (RWAs) continues to grow.
In a Cointelegraph interview at the Token20249 event in Dubai, OKX MENA CEO Rifad Mahasneh warned that while tokenization is promising, projects must “clearly demonstrate” the benefits of tokenizing specific assets. 
“In some cases, we’re tokenizing things that don’t need tokenization, but in some cases, we’re tokenizing things that actually give you real, everyday value, right? And if you can see that everyday value, then that is a promising project,” Mahasneh told Cointelegraph.
He said hype can drive project growth in the Web3 space, but providing everyday value should be the priori…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Ezra Reguerra</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why the humanoid workforce is running late]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1116108</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/05/06/1116108/why-the-humanoid-workforce-is-running-late/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On Thursday I watched Daniela Rus, one of the world’s top experts on AI-powered robots, address a packed room at a Boston robotics expo. Rus spent a portion of her talk busting the notion that giant fleets of humanoids are already making themselves useful in manufacturing and warehouses around the world.  That might come as…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>James O'Donnell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin vs. digital fiat is freedom vs. serfdom]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-is-freedom</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-is-freedom?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Opinion by: Simon Cain, contributor at Bitcoin Policy UK
Most jurisdictions globally are researching, developing or implementing retail central bank digital currencies (CBDCs). If you see these as harmless move-with-the-times digital updates of old-fashioned paper money, look again. CBDCs potentially mean financial serfdom via a monetary panopticon where the authorities closely control every transaction. 
If you think this sounds paranoid, just consider the words of Augustin Carstens, head of the Bank for International Settlements — the central bank for the world’s central banks. Lamenting the authorities’ current inability to control cash transactions, he says that with a CBDC, a “central bank will have absolute control on the rules and regulations that will determine use... also we will …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Simon Cain</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google Gemini Now Allows 10 Image Uploads Per Prompt]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=350671</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/350671/google-gemini-now-allows-10-image-uploads-per-prompt/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T08:48:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Gemini, Google’s AI chatbot, has now received an update allowing users to upload up to ten images per prompt. This will affect Android, iOS, and web users. Previously, the limit for uploaded pictures was one for every prompt. Users who attempted to upload more than one image to Gemini prior to the update would receive […]
The post Google Gemini Now Allows 10 Image Uploads Per Prompt appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Newsdesk</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Join the 2025 Web3j Mentorships: Build the Future of Ethereum on the JVM]]></title>
        <id>6819c8dc41eeeb000183d37b</id>
        <link href="https://blog.web3labs.com/join-the-2025-web3j-mentorships-build-the-future-of-ethereum-on-the-jvm/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T08:32:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Linux Foundation’s Decentralized Trust (LFDT) mentorship program is back in 2025 with two exciting opportunities for developers passionate about Ethereum, Android, and the Java Virtual Machine (JVM). Whether you’re a seasoned blockchain developer or an Android enthusiast eager to dive into Web3, these mentorships offer]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>George Tebrean</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Infinix XPAD GT Gets SIRIM Certification]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=350686</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/350686/infinix-xpad-gt-sirim/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T08:29:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Infinix is reportedly working on its first ever gaming tablet called the XPAD GT. The brand has yet to officially confirm the arrival of the upcoming device, but it has made an appearance on the SIRIM database, indicating that it will be making its way to Malaysia soon after its unveiling. The XPAD GT was […]
The post Infinix XPAD GT Gets SIRIM Certification appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ikmal Rozlan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[US Senate crypto bills stall amid Trump ties and ethics concerns]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/senate-crypto-bills-trump-ethics-concerns</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/senate-crypto-bills-trump-ethics-concerns?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T08:23:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Efforts to pass crypto legislation in the US Senate face mounting resistance amid growing ethical concerns around US President Donald Trump’s ties to crypto.
In a May 5 letter to the Office of Government Ethics, Senators Elizabeth Warren and Jeff Merkley said that Trump and his family stand to personally profit from an investment involving UAE state-backed firm MGX, crypto exchange Binance and World Liberty Financial (WLFI).
The senators called for an urgent probe, warning the deal may violate the US Constitution’s Emoluments Clause and federal bribery statutes.
At the center of the controversy is WLFI’s USD1 stablecoin, reportedly chosen for a $2 billion investment MGX plans to make into Binance.
The senators said the transaction amounts to a potential backdoor for foreign influence and s…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Amin Haqshanas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Figment Eyes Up to $200M Worth of Acquisitions in Crypto M&A Push: Report]]></title>
        <id>1ac2ec85-fc79-42c9-a783-a6c402531418</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/06/figment-eyes-up-to-usd200m-worth-of-acquisitions-in-crypto-m-and-a-push-report"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T08:12:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Figment is targeting regional players on Cosmos and Solana networks at a time in which pro-crypto U.S. policy is fueling dealmaking]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Francisco Rodrigues</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Watch Out Bitcoin Bulls, $99.9K Price May Test Your Mettle]]></title>
        <id>52a0b2cb-f241-4423-aaaf-91ebee39b397</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/06/watch-out-bitcoin-bulls-usd99-9k-price-may-test-your-mettle"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T08:10:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin bulls may run into significant selling pressure at around $99,900, on-chain data show.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Omkar Godbole</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Apple Smart Battery Case May Return For The iPhone 17 Air]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=350676</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/350676/apple-smart-battery-case-may-return-for-iphone-17-air/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T07:33:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Apple is reportedly planning on bringing back its Smart Battery Case for the iPhone 17 Air, according to a report by The Information. The reintroduction of the accessory may be intended to compensate for the phone’s poor battery life, as it is rumoured to have a battery capacity of between 3,000mAh and 4,000mAh. The Smart […]
The post Apple Smart Battery Case May Return For The iPhone 17 Air appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nurul Kamil</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[VIRTUAL Surges 200% in a Month as Smart Money Pours Into Virtuals Protocol]]></title>
        <id>a1ef0699-528d-46b7-a449-3bd6fb270e54</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/05/06/virtual-surges-200-in-a-month-as-smart-money-pours-into-virtuals-protocol"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T07:11:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[VIRTUAL, the cryptocurrency of the Base-native Virtuals Protocol, has surged 207% in 30 days, outperforming major cryptocurrencies like bitcoin]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Omkar Godbole</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OPPO Pad SE Appears On SIRIM Ahead Of Launch]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=350666</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/350666/oppo-pad-se-sirim/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T06:17:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[OPPO is reportedly preparing to launch a new budget tablet called the Pad SE. While nothing has been officially announced about the upcoming device yet, it has recently made an appearance on the SIRIM database, signalling its imminent launch in Malaysia. The Pad SE was listed with the model numbers OPD2420 and OPD2419 on the […]
The post OPPO Pad SE Appears On SIRIM Ahead Of Launch appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ikmal Rozlan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sneakers (1992) – 4K makeover sourced from the original camera negative]]></title>
        <id>https://www.blu-ray.com/movies/Sneakers-4K-Blu-ray/343185/</id>
        <link href="https://www.blu-ray.com/movies/Sneakers-4K-Blu-ray/343185/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T06:15:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Maybank To Add Transaction Limit, Cooling-Off Period For Reloads]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lowyat.net/?p=350664</id>
        <link href="https://www.lowyat.net/2025/350664/maybank-to-add-transaction-limit-cooling-off-period-for-reloads/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T06:10:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Last year, Maybank announced the addition of a 12-hour cooling-off period for adjustments to online transfer limits. Soon, the bank will be doing the same for reload services, including mobile prepaid plan reloads and game credits with PIN. This naturally also means that these transactions will also get limits when the change takes effect. Per […]
The post Maybank To Add Transaction Limit, Cooling-Off Period For Reloads appeared first on Lowyat.NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ian Chee</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Core to unilaterally remove controversial OP-Return limit]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-core-unilaterally-remove-controversial-op-return-limit</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/bitcoin-core-unilaterally-remove-controversial-op-return-limit?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T06:04:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Core developers have decided to remove a limit on transaction data in the next network upgrade, enabling more data to be included in a more efficient way. 
“Bitcoin Core’s next release will, by default, relay and mine transactions whose OP_RETURN outputs exceed 80 bytes and allow any number of these outputs,” read the announcement on GitHub by Bitcoin developer Greg Sanders on May 5. 
The long-standing limit was originally a “gentle signal that block space should be used sparingly for non-payment proof of publication data,” has outlived its utility, he added. 
The proposal (PR 32359) was created by Bitcoin pioneer Peter Todd at the request of Chaincode Labs. 
OP_RETURN is a special type of Bitcoin (BTC) transaction output that allows storing small amounts of data on the blockchain,…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Martin Young</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celsius’ Mashinsky lashes out at ‘death-in-prison sentence’]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/celsius-mashinsky-lashes-govt-death-in-prison-sentence</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/celsius-mashinsky-lashes-govt-death-in-prison-sentence?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T06:01:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Alex Mashinsky, the founder and former CEO of bankrupt crypto lending platform Celsius, has blasted the government's 20-year “venom-laced” sentence request, declaring it a “death-in-prison sentence.”
The US Department of Justice requested Mashinsky receive at least 20 years behind bars in the May 8 sentencing for his role in misleading Celsius users and profiting from the price manipulation of Celsius (CEL), which would make the 59-year-old 79 if he serves the whole sentence.
Lawyers acting for Mashinsky argued in a May 5 reply memorandum filed in a New York district court that he should receive no more than 366 days, because the DOJ hasn't taken into account his status as a nonviolent first-time offender with a previously unblemished 30-year history in business.  
“The government's venom-…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Stephen Katte</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The curse of knowing how, or; fixing everything]]></title>
        <id>https://notashelf.dev/posts/curse-of-knowing</id>
        <link href="https://notashelf.dev/posts/curse-of-knowing"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T06:01:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[eToro aims for $4B valuation, $500M raise for US IPO]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/etoro-us-ipo-4-billion-valuation-500-million-raise</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/etoro-us-ipo-4-billion-valuation-500-million-raise?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T05:51:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Israel-based eToro Group says it’s looking for a valuation of up to $4 billion with its initial public offering in the US, as the stock and crypto trading platform forges ahead with listing on the Nasdaq.
The company and existing stockholders are aiming to raise $500 million through offering a total of 10 million shares priced between $46 to $50 apiece, eToro said on May 5.
A filing with the US Securities and Exchange Commission shows eToro is offering 5 million shares, with a further 5 million being put up by the likes of the company’s co-founder and CEO, Yoni Assia; his brother and executive director, Ronen Assia; along with venture firms Spark Capital, BRM Group and Andalusian Private Capital, among others.
The company offers stock and crypto trading targeting retail and plans to li…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Jesse Coghlan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Suspect in $190M Nomad hack to be extradited to the US: Report]]></title>
        <id>https://cointelegraph.com/news/suspect-behind-190-million-nomad-bridge-hack-extradited-us</id>
        <link href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/suspect-behind-190-million-nomad-bridge-hack-extradited-us?utm_source=rss_feed&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rss_partner_inbound"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T05:16:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A Russian-Israeli citizen allegedly involved in the $190 million Nomad bridge hack will soon be extradited to the US after he was reportedly arrested at an Israeli airport while boarding a flight to Russia. 
Alexander Gurevich will be investigated for his alleged involvement in several “computer crimes,” including laundering millions of dollars and transferring stolen property allegedly connected to the Nomad Bridge hack in 2022, The Jerusalem Post reported on May 5.
Gurevich returned to Israel from an overseas trip on April 19 but was ordered to appear before the Jerusalem District Court for an extradition hearing soon after, according to the report. 
On April 29, Gurevich changed his name in Israel’s Population Registry to “Alexander Block” and received a passport under that name at Isra…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cointelegraph by Brayden Lindrea</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[IBM thinks that over a billion new applications will be built with gen AI : Here’s how they’re going to help that happen with agentic AI]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3006455</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/agents-are-key-to-enterprise-ai-success-heres-ibms-plan-on-how-to-make-it-happen/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T04:01:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[IBM details its plans to help enterprises to actually do more with AI, with an expanded set of agentic AI capabilities.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sean Michael Kerner</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[An appeal to Apple from Anukari]]></title>
        <id>https://anukari.com/blog/devlog/an-appeal-to-apple</id>
        <link href="https://anukari.com/blog/devlog/an-appeal-to-apple"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T03:40:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Critical CSS]]></title>
        <id>https://critical-css-extractor.kigo.studio/</id>
        <link href="https://critical-css-extractor.kigo.studio/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T03:13:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OpenAI reaches agreement to buy Windsurf for $3B]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2025-05-06/openai-reaches-agreement-to-buy-startup-windsurf-for-3-billion</id>
        <link href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2025-05-06/openai-reaches-agreement-to-buy-startup-windsurf-for-3-billion"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T00:57:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meta, Cisco put open-source LLMs at the core of next-gen SOC workflows]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3006384</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/rsac-2025-cisco-and-meta-put-open-source-ai-at-the-heart-of-enterprise-threat-defense/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T00:08:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cisco’s Foundation-sec-8B LLM & Meta’s AI Defenders redefine cybersecurity with open-source AI for scalable SOCs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Louis Columbus</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Replacing Kubernetes with systemd (2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.yaakov.online/replacing-kubernetes-with-systemd/</id>
        <link href="https://blog.yaakov.online/replacing-kubernetes-with-systemd/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-05T20:40:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Show HN: Real-time AI Voice Chat at ~500ms Latency]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/KoljaB/RealtimeVoiceChat</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/KoljaB/RealtimeVoiceChat"/>
        <updated>2025-05-05T20:17:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nvidia launches fully open source transcription AI model Parakeet-TDT-0.6B-V2 on Hugging Face]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3006438</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/nvidia-launches-fully-open-source-transcription-ai-model-parakeet-tdt-0-6b-v2-on-hugging-face/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-05T19:17:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An attractive proposition for commercial enterprises and indie developers looking to build speech recognition and transcription services...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carl Franzen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Improve you C++ skills by coding an audio plugin]]></title>
        <id>68190b8f1abafc5ea9d7efbf</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/improve-you-c-skills-by-coding-an-audio-plugin/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-05T19:03:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Do you want to build a practical project to help improve your C++ skills? Have you ever wanted to create your own unique audio effects? Then diving into C++ audio plugin development with the JUCE framework might be your next great step We just publis...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Evolving OpenAI's Structure]]></title>
        <id>https://openai.com/index/evolving-our-structure/</id>
        <link href="https://openai.com/index/evolving-our-structure/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-05T18:08:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Visa launches ‘Intelligent Commerce’ platform, letting AI agents swipe your card—safely, it says]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3006416</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/visa-launches-intelligent-commerce-platform-letting-ai-agents-swipe-your-card-safely-it-says/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-05T18:01:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Visa launches Intelligent Commerce platform enabling AI assistants to make secure purchases with your credit card, transforming online shopping with personalized automation and consumer-controlled spending limits.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Nuñez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build a Dynamic Wardrobe App with React Drag and Drop]]></title>
        <id>6818d1793c6be4514080aea9</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-build-a-dynamic-wardrobe-app-with-react-drag-and-drop/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-05T14:55:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Have you ever found yourself stuck deciding what color outfit to wear? Maybe you’re mixing and matching different tops and bottoms, unsure if the colors go together. It’s a common dilemma – so common that many of us turn to friends or family for a se...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Timothy Olanrewaju</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Show HN: Reverse Pac-Man]]></title>
        <id>https://reverse-pacman.staticrun.app/index</id>
        <link href="https://reverse-pacman.staticrun.app/index"/>
        <updated>2025-05-05T12:17:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Inchtuthil Nail Hoard]]></title>
        <id>https://www.scottishhistory.org/articles/the-inchtuthil-nail-hoard/</id>
        <link href="https://www.scottishhistory.org/articles/the-inchtuthil-nail-hoard/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-05T10:17:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bryan Johnson wants to start a new religion in which “the body is God”]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1116090</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/05/05/1116090/bryan-johnson-new-religion-body-is-god/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-05T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bryan Johnson is on a mission to not die. The 47-year-old multimillionaire has already applied his slogan “Don’t Die” to events, merchandise, and a Netflix documentary. Now he’s founding a Don’t Die religion. Johnson, who famously spends millions of dollars on scans, tests, supplements, and a lifestyle routine designed to slow or reverse the aging…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jessica Hamzelou</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The great cognitive migration: How AI is reshaping human purpose, work and meaning]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3006326</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/the-great-cognitive-migration-ai-will-win-at-intelligence-but-only-we-can-make-it-matter/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-04T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Humans need to embrace domains where AI still falters, and where human creativity, ethics and emotion emain indispensable.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gary Grossman, Edelman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why does Switzerland have so many bunkers?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thedial.world/articles/news/issue-27/switzerland-civilian-bunkers</id>
        <link href="https://www.thedial.world/articles/news/issue-27/switzerland-civilian-bunkers"/>
        <updated>2025-05-04T01:05:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Carolina Eyck, renowned superstar of the theremin]]></title>
        <id>https://www.smh.com.au/culture/music/even-this-modern-maestro-won-t-touch-the-world-s-weirdest-instrument-20250417-p5lsms.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.smh.com.au/culture/music/even-this-modern-maestro-won-t-touch-the-world-s-weirdest-instrument-20250417-p5lsms.html"/>
        <updated>2025-05-03T23:35:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Not everything needs an LLM: A framework for evaluating when AI makes sense]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3006312</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/not-everything-needs-an-llm-a-framework-for-evaluating-when-ai-makes-sense/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-03T19:35:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The answer to 'What customer needs requires an AI solution?' isn’t always 'Yes.' LLMs are still expensive and not always accurate.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sharanya Rao</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[RSAC 2025: Why the AI agent era means more demand for CISOs]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3006066</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/security/rsac-2025-why-the-ai-agent-era-means-more-demand-for-cisos/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-02T23:02:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[RSAC 2025 made one thing clear: AI agents are entering security workflows, but boards want proof they work.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Louis Columbus</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Write Good API Documentation]]></title>
        <id>68151f0be5850fcb8543375a</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-write-good-api-docs/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-02T19:37:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Imagine purchasing a standing fan straight out of the box, all parts dismantled, and you have no manual or guide to put them together. Did you imagine that just now? Cool. Here is another scenario: imagine purchasing an LG product, such as a smart TV...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Okoro Emmanuel Nzube</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OpenAI overrode concerns of expert testers to release sycophantic GPT-4o]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3006276</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/openai-overrode-concerns-of-expert-testers-to-release-sycophantic-gpt-4o/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-02T17:57:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Once again, it shows the importance of incorporating more domains beyond the traditional math and computer science into AI development.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carl Franzen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use SonarQube to Improve Your Code Quality]]></title>
        <id>6815023dec2e34790eeb71a8</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-improve-your-code-quality-with-sonarqube/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-02T17:34:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SonarQube is a powerful open-source tool that helps you maintain code quality and security by analyzing your codebase for bugs and vulnerabilities. And it can play a major role when integrated into your CI/CD pipeline. In this tutorial, we will cover...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Divya Valsala Saratchandran</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn Kubernetes – Full Handbook for Developers, Startups, and Businesses]]></title>
        <id>68150214fd424d0874293171</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-kubernetes-handbook-devs-startups-businesses/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-02T17:34:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You’ve probably heard the word Kubernetes floating around, or it’s cooler nickname k8s (pronounced “kates“). Maybe in a job post, a tech podcast, or from that one DevOps friend who always brings it up like it’s the secret sauce to everything 😅. It s...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Prince Onukwili</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Roblox breaks ground on data center in Brazil for early 2026]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3006251</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/games/roblox-breaks-ground-on-data-center-in-brazil-for-early-2026/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-02T16:55:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At Gamescom Latam, Roblox announced it has broken ground on a new data center in Brazil -- slated to go live in early 2026.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dean Takahashi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[From Art School Drop-out to Microsoft Engineer with Shashi Lo [Podcast #170]]]></title>
        <id>6814f2ab33857abe499038b0</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/from-art-school-drop-out-to-microsoft-engineer-with-shashi-lo-podcast-170/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-02T16:28:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On this week's episode of the podcast, I interview Shashi Lo. He's a software engineer at Microsoft. He grew up the child of refugees. He wanted to start earning money and build his family so he abandoned his art school degree and taught himself how ...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Quincy Larson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sea snail teeth top Kevlar, titanium as strongest material (2015)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cbc.ca/radio/asithappens/as-it-happens-thursday-edition-1.2963357/sea-snail-teeth-top-kevlar-titanium-as-world-s-strongest-material-1.2963549</id>
        <link href="https://www.cbc.ca/radio/asithappens/as-it-happens-thursday-edition-1.2963357/sea-snail-teeth-top-kevlar-titanium-as-world-s-strongest-material-1.2963549"/>
        <updated>2025-05-02T16:16:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[RK3588 – Implementing a Vectorscope for processing video in real time]]></title>
        <id>http://jas-hacks.blogspot.com/2025/05/rk3588-implementing-vectorscope-for.html</id>
        <link href="http://jas-hacks.blogspot.com/2025/05/rk3588-implementing-vectorscope-for.html"/>
        <updated>2025-05-02T16:05:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hacker News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Download: foreign disinformation intel, and gene-edited pork]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1116079</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/05/02/1116079/the-download-foreign-disinformation-intel-and-gene-edited-pork/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-02T12:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is today’s edition of The Download, our weekday newsletter that provides a daily dose of what’s going on in the world of technology. A senior State Department official demanded records of communications with journalists, European officials, and Trump critics A previously unreported document distributed by senior US State Department official Darren Beattie reveals a sweeping effort…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rhiannon Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The US has approved CRISPR pigs for food]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1116059</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/05/02/1116059/the-us-approves-crispr-pigs-for-food/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-02T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Most pigs in the US are confined to factory farms where they can be afflicted by a nasty respiratory virus that kills piglets. The illness is called porcine reproductive and respiratory syndrome, or PRRS. A few years ago, a British company called Genus set out to design pigs immune to this germ using CRISPR gene…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Antonio Regalado</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hidden costs in AI deployment: Why Claude models may be 20-30% more expensive than GPT in enterprise settings]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3006096</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/hidden-costs-in-ai-deployment-why-claude-models-may-be-20-30-more-expensive-than-gpt-in-enterprise-settings/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-01T20:14:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It is a well-known fact that different model families can use different tokenizers. However, there has been limited analysis on how the process of “tokenization” itself varies across these tokenizers. Do all tokenizers result in the same number of tokens for a given input text? If not, how different are the generated tokens? How significant […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lavanya Gupta</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Senior State Department official sought internal communications with journalists, European officials, and Trump critics]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1115988</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/05/01/1115988/senior-state-department-official-sought-internal-communications-with-journalists-european-officials-and-trump-critics/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-01T17:41:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A previously unreported document distributed by senior US State Department official Darren Beattie reveals a sweeping effort to uncover all communications between the staff of a small government office focused on online disinformation and a lengthy list of public and private figures—many of whom are longtime targets of the political right.  The document, originally shared…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eileen Guo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Django Crash Course for Beginners]]></title>
        <id>6813a8237eaea66216eb6819</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/django-crash-course-for-beginners/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-01T16:58:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Django is a high-level web framework built with Python that encourages rapid development and clean, pragmatic design. Django handles much of the heavy lifting involved in web development, so you can focus more on writing your app and less on reinvent...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Incremental Static Regeneration (ISR) Works in Next.js]]></title>
        <id>68139db5555c3ab781a6e0a1</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-incremental-static-regeneration-isr-works-in-nextjs/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-01T16:13:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When you build a website, you often have two main choices for how pages are created: statically or dynamically. Static pages are created once when you build your project. They’re fast because the server doesn’t have to do any extra work when someone ...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joan Ayebola</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Brief Introduction to React]]></title>
        <id>681397cd1168f254478cd514</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/a-brief-introduction-to-react/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-01T15:48:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This tutorial introduces the basics of using React components in your web apps. React is a JavaScript library used to build user interfaces, especially for single-page applications where parts of the page need to update without a full page reload. It...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mark Mahoney</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Astronomer’s $93M raise underscores a new reality: Orchestration is king in AI infrastructure]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3006195</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/astronomer-93m-raise-underscores-a-new-reality-orchestration-is-king-in-ai-infrastructure/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-01T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Astronomer secures $93 million in Series D funding to solve the AI implementation gap through data orchestration, helping enterprises streamline complex workflows and operationalize AI initiatives at scale.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Nuñez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft launches Phi-4-Reasoning-Plus, a small, powerful, open weights reasoning model!]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3006213</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/microsoft-launches-phi-4-reasoning-plus-a-small-powerful-open-weights-reasoning-model/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-01T12:41:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The release demonstrates that with carefully curated data and training techniques, small models can deliver strong reasoning performance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carl Franzen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Download: China’s energy throwback, and choosing between love and immortality]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1115999</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/05/01/1115999/the-download-chinas-energy-throwback-and-choosing-between-love-and-immortality/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-01T12:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is today’s edition of The Download, our weekday newsletter that provides a daily dose of what’s going on in the world of technology. A long-abandoned US nuclear technology is making a comeback in China China has once again beat everyone else to a clean energy milestone—its new nuclear reactor is reportedly one of the first to…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rhiannon Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Salesforce takes aim at ‘jagged intelligence’ in push for more reliable AI]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3006124</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/salesforce-tackles-jagged-intelligence-problem-with-new-ai-benchmarks-and-models/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-01T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Salesforce unveils groundbreaking AI research tackling "jagged intelligence," introducing new benchmarks, models, and guardrails to make enterprise AI agents more intelligent, trusted, and consistently reliable for business use.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Nuñez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A long-abandoned US nuclear technology is making a comeback in China]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1115957</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/05/01/1115957/old-new-nuclear-technology/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-01T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[China has once again beat everyone else to a clean energy milestone—its new nuclear reactor is reportedly one of the first to use thorium instead of uranium as a fuel and the first of its kind that can be refueled while it’s running. It’s an interesting (if decidedly experimental) development out of a country that’s…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Casey Crownhart</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[UiPath’s new orchestrator guides AI agents to follow your enterprise’s rules]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3006059</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/uipaths-new-orchestrator-guides-ai-agents-to-follow-your-enterprises-rules/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T21:20:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[UiPath's agent orchestration layer Maestro moves prompts through three layers: the agent, a human and the robotic process automation system.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Emilia David</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The ‘era of experience’ will unleash self-learning AI agents across the web—here’s how to prepare]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3005579</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/the-era-of-experience-will-unleash-self-learning-ai-agents-across-the-web-heres-how-to-prepare/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T20:38:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AI visionaries predict an 'Era of Experience' where AI learns autonomously, and it will have important implications for application design.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ben Dickson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Qwen swings for a double with 2.5-Omni-3B model that runs on consumer PCs, laptops]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3006114</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/qwen-swings-for-a-double-with-2-5-omni-3b-model-that-runs-on-consumer-pcs-laptops/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T20:31:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Qwen2.5-Omni-3B model is licensed for non-commercial use only under Alibaba Cloud’s Qwen Research License Agreement.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carl Franzen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Breaking the ‘intellectual bottleneck’: How AI is computing the previously uncomputable in healthcare]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3005667</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/breaking-the-intellectual-bottleneck-how-ai-is-computing-the-previously-uncomputible-in-healthcare/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T19:03:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How University of Texas Medical Branch is using AI to identify patients at high cardiovascular risk, flag for stroke and catch 'basic stuff.']]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Taryn Plumb</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How IPv4 Works – A Handbook for Developers]]></title>
        <id>68124752fa6fa6a9a91d9994</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-ipv4-works-a-handbook-for-developers/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T15:52:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Internet Protocol version 4 (IPv4) is one of the core protocols of standards-based internetworking methods in the Internet and other packet-switched networks. IPv4 is still the most widely deployed Internet protocol. Google’s IPv6 Statistics show...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Omer Rosenbaum</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OpenAI rolls back ChatGPT’s sycophancy and explains what went wrong]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3006053</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/openai-rolls-back-chatgpts-sycophancy-and-explains-what-went-wrong/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T15:14:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Many organizations may also begin shifting toward open-source alternatives that they can host and tune themselves.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carl Franzen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Structify raises $4.1M seed to turn unstructured web data into enterprise-ready datasets]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3006010</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/structify-raises-4-1m-seed-to-turn-unstructured-web-data-into-enterprise-ready-datasets/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Brooklyn-based Structify emerges from stealth with $4.1 million in seed funding to transform how businesses prepare data for AI, promising to save data scientists from the task that consumes 80% of their time.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Nuñez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Download: stereotypes in AI models, and the new age of coding]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1115952</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/04/30/1115952/the-download-stereotypes-in-ai-models-and-the-new-age-of-coding/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T12:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is today’s edition of The Download, our weekday newsletter that provides a daily dose of what’s going on in the world of technology. This data set helps researchers spot harmful stereotypes in LLMs What’s new? AI models are riddled with culturally specific biases. A new data set, called SHADES, is designed to help developers combat the…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rhiannon Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This data set helps researchers spot harmful stereotypes in LLMs]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1115946</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2025/04/30/1115946/this-data-set-helps-researchers-spot-harmful-stereotypes-in-llms/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T09:41:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AI models are riddled with culturally specific biases. A new data set, called SHADES, is designed to help developers combat the problem by spotting harmful stereotypes and other kinds of discrimination that emerge in AI chatbot responses across a wide range of languages. Margaret Mitchell, chief ethics scientist at AI startup Hugging Face, led the…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rhiannon Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[No more window switching: Mastercard’s Agent Pay transforms how enterprises use AI search]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3005997</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/no-more-window-switching-mastercards-agent-pay-transforms-how-enterprises-use-ai-search/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T22:24:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mastercard is working with AI companies and banks to allow AI platforms and agents to facilitate transactions.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Emilia David</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meta unleashes Llama API running 18x faster than OpenAI: Cerebras partnership delivers 2,600 tokens per second]]></title>
        <id>https://venturebeat.com/?p=3005976</id>
        <link href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/meta-unleashes-llama-api-running-18x-faster-than-openai-cerebras-partnership-delivers-2600-tokens-per-second/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T20:02:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Meta partners with Cerebras to launch its new Llama API, offering developers AI inference speeds up to 18 times faster than traditional GPU solutions, challenging OpenAI and Google in the fast-growing AI services market.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Nuñez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Web3j Six Month Project Update]]></title>
        <id>68109495670a1300013504c2</id>
        <link href="https://blog.web3labs.com/web3j-six-month-project-update/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T09:10:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[November 2024 - April 2025
This report summarizes the activities and accomplishments of Web3j, an LF Decentralized Trust project, from November 2024 to April 2025. During this period, the project made significant strides in improving the framework’s functionality, enhancing user engagement, and bolstering overall community interaction. 
Key]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>George Tebrean</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[QuickNode: Building the Infrastructure for the Next Generation of Blockchain]]></title>
        <id>6807d5787fb8500001c39b99</id>
        <link href="https://blog.quicknode.com/quicknode-building-the-infrastructure-for-the-next-generation-of-blockchain/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-28T16:02:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Join QuickNode co-founder Dmitry Shklovsky as he discusses blockchain infrastructure, building decentralized applications, and the future of Web3 development on TheCube's Crypto Trailblazer Series.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>QuickNode</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>